Lucky Shop
Guidance Zone
MEMBER
Peerless!
Kombucha
100 pills
¥50,000
Everyone should recruit more members to sign up for Peerless Kombucha Z!
100 pills
¥50,000
Network business
inviting new participants
Once you do...
100 pills
¥50,000
Incredible!
The members you recruit will recruit more members,
and you'll rake in the cash!
Sawashiro
Kobayashi
Goto Y.
Yajima
Inoue
Goto S.
Matsuki
Sanada
Tanii
Will we really make a profit?
「Make a profit?」
Absolutely!
I have never once in my life spoken a lie!
Kombucha Z
Will this stuff really sell?
It will!
There will be more and more members,
...and you'll all become filthy rich!
Filthy Rich
Forget about that.
Hey there, big guy.
You've got a cute face.
What are you doing?!
P–Please stop that!
Oh my. Such an innocent little thing.
I said, please stop that!
His name is Itoshiki Nozomu
An elite salaryman at a multi-level health food company
Doesn't like women or lotus roots
Burst of Flowers
The Surprising Blunders of Baron Munchhausen
From Volume 1's bookjacket
Originally published 16th September, Showa 80
Beauty of Nature
Fried Meat Set
Lotus Roots
While extremely innocent with intense likes and dislikes
Nozomu Itoshiki would more or less be considered a serious, ordinary young man
Until that day
Nishi-Bakurocho 8-chome
Teetotaler's Cafe BON
Teetotaler's Caf '
Me?
Yes.
You.
Comrade Nozomu Itoshiki.
Comrade?
You haven't been to any meetings recently.
And you haven't kept in touch.
What's been going on?
Meetings?
What do you mean?
Isn't it obvious?
The HAMASHO meetings.
The revolutionary religious order...
HAMASHO.
Teetotaler's Cafe BON
Teetotaler's Caf '
Religious order HAMASHO.
HAMASHO
Yes.
You should know of it.
After all, you were one of the leaders.
One of the leaders?
Me?
I know nothing about it!
Nothing at all!
What does HAMASHO mean, anyway?
HAMASHO
Is it short for Hamada Shoko?
Or perhaps Hamada Shogo?
Neither.
A religious order which worships in the Bahama s while receiving golden sho wers.
Abbreviated...
HAMASHO.
How could such a bizarre religion exist?!
Wh–What did you say?!
You just called us a bizarre religion, didn't you?!
A–An apostate!
Matsumura
Kawane
Takeda
Sugita
Eri
Kouda
Mitsuko
Yamamori
An apostate!
「Wh–What's that」
Wh–What's that?!
Murasame
Gioh
Luca
Sakurai
An apostate!
An apostate.
Infidels cannot be forgiven!
Punish the sinner!
SHOCK
The followers of the revolutionary religious order @HAMASHO were hidden all around the city
Nozomu was pursued as an apostate by an order he had never actually joined
What an ordeal...
Gérard
This should be far enough...
Palm Reading
No way!
Nideal
Umbrellas
I was never a believer!
So I can't be an apostate!
You've got it wrong!
You have the wrong man!
This defies logic!
How can people be so unreasonable?!
I'm in despair!
This irrational world has left me in despair!
What?
Itoshiki Nozomu escaped?
Use any means necessary!
Capture him!
Sieg HAMASHO!
Nozomu, still being chased, found a boat and set to sea
If I use this...
But the boat was actually a trap placed by their leader, who bore a resemblance to De**in Zabi
The island Nozomu arrived at was HAMASHO's base
What is this place?!
I know your weaknesses!
Women and lotus roots!
Aware of Nozomu's weaknesses, the leader sent a swarm of women with one-meter busts
Nozomu is in grave danger
Moral
Wh–What is this?!
We finally meet, Nozomu.
We will be modifying your traitorous body
into a loyal soldier of HAMASHO.
Modifying humans?
What are you talking about?!
That's just unrealistic—
They're real!
Moral
Come.
Let's begin!
I beg you.
If you're going to modify me,
at least turn me into a grasshopper man!
Or a beetle man!
Give me a nice clean public image!
Moral
Understood.
I'll turn you into a bizarre mole cricket man!
After being turned into a mole cricket man, Nozomu escapes the base before he can be brainwashed
I'm in despair!
Being turned into a mole cricket man has left me in despair!
I'm already paid next to nothing!
Now, I'm a mole cricket!
Damn it!
I'll go die!
No, wait.
If I'm going to live such a worthless life,
I might be happier if I let them brainwash me.
Nozomu decided to return to the base to be brainwashed, but it was already too late
HAMASHO's mutant brigade had already come in pursuit
Wh–What do I do?!
Cornered by the mutant brigade, Nozomu decided to jump
His body plunged into the night sea
Nozomu's ordeal continued
He was captured by pirates and tortured
Save me!
Fought with sea monsters
Wracked by hunger and thirst
Barely alive, he finally reached the Ashi**** Cape School for Girls
Ashi**** Cape is famous for *******
Nurse's Office
I was so surprised to find him sleeping there.
You came from Tokyo, right?
Y–Yes.
Thought so.
I was worried.
You were taking so long to take over.
Take over?
What do you mean?
This is your new teacher.
Teacher?
Before he knew what was going on, Nozomu Itoshiki had become a teacher at a school for girls
The first class
It's a pleasure to meet you.
I will be your new teacher, Itoshiki Nozomu.
Yes!
May I call you Left-wing Guerilla from now on?
Left-wing Guerilla
Left-wing Guerilla?
What's that?
I just felt that you looked left-wing and guerilla-like.
I see.
He does have a left-wing guerilla vibe.
Mr. Left-wing Guerilla!
Nice to meet you!
I'm in despair!
Being given a meaningless nickname has left me in despair!
I'll die this time.
Teacher.
If you're going to die, you might as well do someone a favor.
A favor?
A fake wedding.
Fake wedding
We need you to marry a girl from the Holy Nosebleed Empire.
Fake wedding?
Nosebleed?
She's the one.
Nozomu Itoshiki, pressured into a fake wedding with a girl from a country he's never heard of
What will be his fate
From the bookjacket of 「Sayonara, Zetsubou-sensei」 Volume 1
Original Work
Kumeta Koji
「Sayonara, Zetsubou-sensei」
(Serialized in Kodansha's
「Weekly Shonen Magazine」)
【Zoku】 Sayonara, Zetsubou-sensei
runba runba runba runba runba
ルンバ ルンバ ルンバ ルンバ ルンバ
Rumba, rumba, rumba, rumba, rumba
Series Organization
& Dramatization
Oguro Yuichiro
Character Design / Overall
Key Animation Supervisor
Morioka Hideyuki
runba runba runba runba runba
ルンバ ルンバ ルンバ ルンバ ルンバ
Rumba, rumba, rumba, rumba, rumba
Art Director
Kakoi Hirotsugu
Color Key
Takizawa Izumi
Visual Effects
Sakai Motoki
runba runba runba runba runba
ルンバ ルンバ ルンバ ルンバ ルンバ
Rumba, rumba, rumba, rumba, rumba
Director of
Photography
Egami Satoru
Editor
Seki Kazuhiko
runba runba runba runba runba
ルンバ ルンバ ルンバ ルンバ ルンバ
Rumba, rumba, rumba, rumba, rumba
samayoru sugata ha sanagara runba
さまよう姿はさながらルンバ
Wandering around looks just like the rumba
Cast
Itoshiki Nozumu
yoromeku sugata mo mecha kucha runba
よろめく姿も目茶苦茶ルンバ
Staggering around in a mess, like the rumba
Fuura Kafuka
Kitsu Chiri
Tsunetsuki Matoi
fura tsuki naga ramo ikitei runba
ふらつきながらも生きていルンバ
It may be shaky but I'm still living the rumba
Fujiyoshi Harumi
Kobushi Abiru
Hito Nami
Otonashi Meru
Komori Kiri
Kimura Kaere
hata kara mirya dansu ni mie runba
はたからみりゃダンスに見えルンバ
From the side it looks like a dance, rumba
Kaga Ai
Mitama Mayo
Ookusa Manami
Sekiutsu · Maria · Taro
Kudo Jun
Kino Kuniya
yokereba isshou ni odori masen ka?
よければ一緖に踊りませんか？
If it's all right would you like to dance with me?
Emperor Penguin
iie iie anata ja odore masen wa
いえいえアナタじゃ踊れませんわ
No way, you can't dance
Oriental Stork
hitori ja munashii odoro yo runba
一人じゃ空しい踊ろよルンバ
But it's lonely by myself, let's dance the rumba
Ms. Sakurai
ototoi koya gare hitori de runba
おととい來やがれ一人でルンバ
Get away from me, do a one-man rumba
Other
Staff
ore no nedan wo dare ga kime ta?
俺の値段を誰が決めた？
Who decided my worth?
Assistant Director
Tatsuwa Naoyuki
Chief Direction
Miyamoto Yukihiro
Key Animation Supervisor
Yamamura Hiroki
tora ya hyou ga bokura no kokoro nimo
虎や豹が僕らの心にも
Tigers and leopards lurk in our minds
Sound Director
Kameyama Toshiki
Music
Hasegawa Tomoki
Music Production
StarChild Records
Opening Theme
「Fantasy Rumba」
Lyrics
Ohtsuki Kenji
Composition
Arrangement
NARASAKI
Vocals
Ohtsuki Kenji
and the
Zetsubou Girls
Fuura Kafuka
Kitsu Chiri
Kimura Kaere
Tarou·Maria
Hito Nami
kemono tachi ga hiso mukoto shiranai kara yatsura
獣たちがひそむこと知らないからやつら
They don't know that the beasts are lurking
yasui ne wotsuke yagatte
安い値をつけやがって
So they undervalue us
toki hanatsu ze!
解き放つぜ！
Release!
saa, nige madoe sono suki ni
さぁ、逃げまどえその隙に
Now, when they run about
Opening Directors
Oishi Tatsuya
Miyamoto Yukihiro
odoro yo boku tachi ha runba
踊ろよ僕たちはルンバ
We are going to dance the rumba
Producer
Moriyama Atsushi
Animation
Producer
Kubota Mitsutoshi
hohoemi karoya kani kimi to
微笑み軽やかに君と
Smiling lightly along with you
Director
Shinbo Akiyuki
Animation Production
SHAFT
sono hi wa kuru noka?
その日は来るのか?
Will that day ever come?
wakara nakute
わからなくて
I don't know
Production
Sayonara, Zetsubou-sensei
Production Committee
Thank you for
buying the DVDS
You are the reason
we are able
to produce more
Zetsubou-sensei
Thank you
so very much
This is a Class of Many Problems, so Please Keep That in Mind
From Chapter 10
Originally published 29th June, Showa 80
It is better to be hated for what you are than to be loved for what you are not.
– Gide (1869-1951 French)
My
name is
Hito Nami
I am a poor little truant.
I am a poor little truant
However,
I'm willingly going to school today.
Of course, I have a reason.
I have a reason
Nobody feels sorry for me.
Poor thing
2-VI
Why didn't anyone get worried and come to my house?
Question
Who are you?
A student in this class!
Question
I'm a truant!
Body Care
But you're here today.
I just happened to show up!
Really, now.
I'm sorry.
I'm not this class's teacher.
Then what is our teacher doing?
Um, well...
He's been truant since last week.
The teacher's truant?
It's not so unusual these days.
A truant teacher is worse than a truant student.
I wonder if he's okay.
Doesn't it make you worry?
Are you okay?
Worried
They're worrying about him instead of me!
Heh...
Oh, well...
They'll have no choice but to worry about me once they see this.
Ah.
How did you get that injury?
Are you okay?
Yes
Yes!
Oolong
Filming
Those are some serious injuries.
I'm fine.
I just fell down.
That doesn't happen from falling down,.
There's a rumor about her father committing DV.
DV?
Blend different
kinds of grapes
for 100% juice
Doesn't it make you worry?
Worry
Worry?
They're worrying about someone else again!
Abiru Kobushi
Alleged Victim of DV
Ha
You hear about DV all the time these days.
It's not that unusual.
Beware of skin damage when going outside
Skin
Whitening
A far more serious problem...
...kept me from coming to school.
My father's business failed...
Our house was repossessed...
We've been moving between run-down apartments, on the run from debt collectors.
Never knowing if we'll have food to eat...
I had no time for school...
It must have been hard.
Yes
Yes!
Let the clerk know if you don't need a bag.
Take the bags home
instead of throwing them away.
Please help keep our
city a clean place.
No Littering
Japan's full of stuff!
Food lying everywhere!
You can't starve!
You shouldn't eat out of the trash.
But I was hungry.
growl
These mushrooms grew in my country.
Can you tell which one is edible?
Beware of skin damage when going outside
Skin
Darkening
N–No idea...
They're both poisonous!
You can't eat either!
But we still ate them...
We still ate them...
...or else we would have starved to death.
Two of my friends who ate them, tragically...
That's enough!
Sekiutsu ・ Maria ・ Taro
(Japanese Name)
Refugee Girl
(Illegal Alien)
It makes me so worried.
They're worrying about someone else again!
Fine.
If nobody cares about me, I'll play my last card!
I guess I'll just die.
No!
Don't do it!
Yes!
Yes
Wh–What is this?!
So Teacher was here.
What is this person doing?!
As you can see...
A suicide attempt.
Suicide?!
Suicide
Attempt
It happens all the time.
Don't worry about it.
I made eye contact!
Super Negative Teacher
Nozomu Itoshiki
2-VI's Teacher
This person is our teacher.
Our teacher?!
You're probably surprised.
This class is full of troublemakers.
With a teacher like that...
But I'm relived.
You're normal.
Normal?!
Tears are the
smallest ocean
humans can
create
Normal
Normal...
Normal is never meant in a good way!
My my.
Isn't that nice, An?
You've already made friends.
Mika
An
How are you getting along with Mika?
Great!
Kenta
An
How about with Kenta?
Great!
Nami
An
What about with Nami?
Normal.
SHOCKERS
"Normal"... "Normal" is never meant in a good way!
Normal...
Normal is never meant in a good way!
Young
Gamgam
Is that manga any good?
It's normal.
Young
Gamgam
Is his girlfriend cute?
She's normal.
This is a normal job.
Donations
A normal speed train always falls behind
•
Extra-inconvenient normal paper fax
Normal classes at a magnet school
•
I'm not normal!
I'm a poor little truant!
A
Fuzzy logic is derived from fuzzy set theory
dealing with reasoning that is approximate
rather than precisely deduced from classical
predicate logic. It can be thought of as the
application side of fuzzy set theory
dealing with well thought out real world expert
values for a complex problem (Klir 1997).
Degrees of truth are often confused with
probabilities. However, they are distinct
conceptually; fuzzy truth represents membership
in vaguely defined sets, not likelihood of some
event or condition. For example, if a 100-ml glass
contains 30 ml of water, then, for two fuzzy sets,
Empty and Full, one might define the glass as
being 0.7 empty and 0.3 full. Note that the concept
of emptiness would be subjective and thus would
depend on the observer or designer. Another
designer might equally well design a set
membership function where the glass would be
considered full for all values down to 50 ml. A
probabilistic setting would first define a scalar
variable for the fullness of the glass, and second,
conditional distributions describing the probability
that someone would call the glass full given a
specific fullness level. Note that the conditioning
can be achieved by having a specific observer
that randomly selects the label for the glass,
a distribution over deterministic observers, or both.
While fuzzy logic avoids talking about randomness
in this context, this simplification at the same time
obscures what is exactly meant by the statement
the 'glass is 0.3 full'.
"A poor little truant?"
But even our teacher's truant.
Chiri 「A poor, little truant? But even our teacher's truant.」
Forget high school, I'm even truant from driver's ed!
Nozomu 「Forget high school, I'm even truant from driver's ed!」
Driver's ed?!
The one even dangerous people can still manage to pass?!
Actually, those have the least chance of failing.
Nami 「The one even dangerous people can still manage to pass?!」
Nozomu 「Actually, those have the least chance of failing.」
And Fujiyoshi's older brother...
Backroom
I can make it in the business without going to school
...is a truant at Momogi Animation Academy.
I'll get my money back
Old men with cameras come during cultural festivals (voice acting program)
Essay tests
Revenue from voice acting program is used to support other schools
180k a month
Comedy Course
Fukuoka campus is extremely poor
B*nd
Fukuoka campus festivals feature a large, self-made Gundam
Not recognized as a vocational school
Revenue from voice acting program is used to support other schools
Half the people at Tokyo campus leave by summer
Don't say that out loud!
It's pretty sad.
Chiri 「And Fujiyoshi's older brother is a truant at Momogi Animation Academy.」
Harumi 「Don't say that out loud!」
Chiri 「It's pretty sad.」
A
The relationship of symmetry to aesthetics is
complex. Certain simple symmetries, and in
particular bilateral symmetry, seem to be
deeply ingrained in the inherent perception
by humans of the likely health or fitness of
other living creatures, as can be seen by the
simple experiment of distorting one side of
the image of an attractive face and asking
viewer to rate the attractiveness of the
resulting image. Consequently, such
symmetries that mimic biology tend to have
an innate appeal that in turn drives a powerful
tendency to create artifacts with similar
symmetry. One only needs to imagine the
difficulty in trying to market a highly
asymmetrical car or truck to general
automotive buyers to understand the power
of biologically inspired symmetries
such as bilateral symmetry.
An ordinary truant lacks impact.
Besides, if you're a truant, why are you here?
You can't be a truant!
Either stop calling yourself a truant or stop coming to school!
That really irritates me!
Make up your mind properly!
Kitsu Chiri
Methodical
Busybody
Super cool
Are you a student in this class?
PAT
Finger-stop bottle
I'm relieved that you're normal.
After all, this class has 31...
No, 32 despair-inducing students.
You could call this a classroom of despair!
Harumph
Incidentally, the parts that are hidden
aren't covered up because they haven't been thought of yet.
Didn't someone just spill coffee over it?
That's right...
I see a lot of dangerous-looking people...
Kimura Kaere
Girl with Bilingual Personalities
Otonashi Meru
Abusive E-mail Girl
MAIL MAIL
Kaga Ai
Guilt Complex Girl
Mitama Mayo
Exactly the
way she looks
Kotonon
Net Idol
Fujiyoshi Harumi
Slash
Addiction
Snatch
I'd rather a truant than any of those!
Come with me!
That girl...
...refuses to leave!
Refuses to leave?!
Someone who refuses to leave is far more trouble than someone who refuses to come!
Shut-in Girl
who refuses
to leave
school
Komori Kiri
She's been cooped up in this school for a long time,
and still refuses to leave.
A girl
who
refuses
to go
to school
A girl
who
refuses
to leave
school
Thou must
not open
– Kiri
Genshiken 2
A meeting that was never meant to happen
Well, if you think about it, they would never normally meet.
You ended up meeting
because you came to school!
「Going through Tsuji Jinsei books won't help!!」
Going through Tsuji Jinsei books won't help!
That was hard
What's so special about refusing to leave?!
She just stays at school.
Someone who doesn't go to school is a bigger threat to society!
She just stays at school?
Komori.
Teach this girl how difficult it is to stay at school.
If you say so...
Fine.
Well then...
Will you be able to stay at school?
You win if you can stay inside the school building.
That's easy.
The melody of Träumerei begins to play when it's time to go home.
I already want to go home!
Don't you feel uneasy?
Don't you feel discouraged?
Th–This is nothing!
Soup made by a lady wearing a catskin.
Did Träumerei have lyrics?
I head to a neighborhood where all the old ladies have disappeared.
Tarts made by a lady wearing a dogskin.
Two shovels were sold at the hardware store.
What's with these disturbing lyrics?!
They're driving me insane!
Driving me insane!
A hole as deep as a young man's height...
Don't make up lyrics to Träumerei!
Super
Positive
Girl
Kafuka Fuura
(Pen name)
Komori.
You're friends with this school shut-in?
Komori isn't a shut-in.
She's a zashiki-warashi.
Certified JZU Member (Japan Zashiki-warashi Union)
By cooping herself up in the school, she's protecting the school from evil spirits.
If she were to leave, the school would be destroyed in a flash.
In fact, the house she used to be in was tragically destroyed.
Eh
Komori is a certified member of the Japan Zashiki-warashi Union.
She's a proper warashi, so you don't need to worry.
What's she talking about?!
Uh...
The situation always gets complicated when you show up.
Then I'll see you later!
Wh–What was that?
Poooon
Turmeric
Salad oil
Beef
Onions
Honey
to taste
1 tablespoon
Garam marsala
Chili
Salt
Potatoes
Carrots
Cumin
Ginger
Garlic
Coriander
Apples
A mother's love
Th–This is...
The smell of curry wafts in from town as the sun sets.
Mommy!
Mom
my
The growing shadows of metal poles in the schoolyard.
The sorrowful crying of animals.
The reflection of your weary face in the windows of a dark hallway.
HUFF
PUFF
You should go home instead of pushing yourself.
It's only going to get worse.
Fear and paranoia will drive you to see illusions in the dark school building.
No way!
I couldn't possibly see any illusions.
Right, Teacher?
Yeah.
Somebody's behind you!
Nobody's there!
Don't say weird stuff like that!
I just saw...
Something's there...
Tsunetsuki Matoi
Super Loving
Stalker Girl
There's nothing there!
Why can't you see it?!
Could it be a ghost?!
Faint
I–I'm gonna go get some fresh air.
It's dark!
This is scary!
I wanna go home!
This is scarier than I expected!
YANK
Don't worry!
It isn't scary!
We're not the only ones in the darkness!
Look.
A baby.
The bottom half of a baby is hanging from the ceiling!
I'm not your mommy!
Mom
Mommy!
my
No!
Normal Girl
Hito Nami
2-VI
That was my experience as a truant.
Discussing truancy from HR
That's right...
I'd completely forgotten...
...that Hito was a truant.
Uh-huh
That's right
I vaguely remember that being how it went
I saw this setting somewhere
How could you forget such a dramatic event?!
Next season confirmed if DVD sales pass 30k
Uh...
Because it was relatively normal?
Don't say normal!
Seat #28
Hito Nami
Normal Girl
If we didn’t meet back then
ano toki deawanakeray yume de
あの時出逢わなけりゃ夢で
I wouldn’t be having nightmares in my dreams
unasarenaide irareta
うなされないでいられた
If you weren’t born in this world
anata ga kono yo ni umarenakereba
あなたがこの世に生まれなければ
Then I would’ve died without knowing jealousy or pain
netami nante, itami nante, shirazu ni sunda
ネタミなんて痛みなんて知らずに済んだ
The one who you wanted
anata ga hoshigatta no wa
あなたが欲しがったのは
Was a person completely opposite of me
watashi to mattaku gyaku no hito
わたしとまったく逆のひと
I can see that we’re connected by a crimson thread…
makka na ito de tsunagiau no ga mieru
真っ赤な糸でつなぎ合うのが見える
I’m a blue thread
watashi wa aoi ito
わたしは蒼い糸
Try touching me; my heart now
sawatte mite yo kono kokoro wa ima
触ってみてよこの心はいま
Falls in love on its own,
katte ni koi o shite
勝手に恋をして
gets hurt on its own
katte ni kizutsuiteru
勝手に傷ついてる
Don’t touch me; if my thoughts can’t be fulfilled
sawaranaide yo kono omoi kanawanai no nara
触らないでよこの想い叶わないのなら
Then only an indigo bruise remains inside of my chest
massao na aza mune no naka nokoru dake de
真っ青なあざ胸の中残るだけで
This show is a work of fiction.
Similarity to any actual people, organizations,
or HAMASHO is purely coincidental.
Death Country
Once we left the tunnel, there was another tunnel.
After that tunnel, there was another tunnel.
After that tunnel, there was yet another tunnel.
The tunnels went on and on.
Tunnels.
Tunnels the entire way.
That was my life.
I left the tunnel to find myself in another tunnel.
Despair cured my cold.
Illustration:
Terada Katsuya