January
February
March
April
May
June
July
10th
11th
12th
13th
School Opening Anniversary
Everybody, July 13th is the day our school was founded.
July 13th
STARE
Teacher....
「What is it..?」
What is it?
Perry is coming for the School Opening Anniversary!
Perry is coming
Yes?
July 13th
For the School Opening Anniversary
Perry is
He really came!
Original Work
Kumeta Koji
「Sayonara, Zetsubou-sensei」
(Serialized in Kodansha’s
「Weekly Shonen Magazine」)
【Zoku】 Sayonara Zetsubou-sensei
Series Organization
& Dramatization
Oguro Yuichiro
Rumba, rumba, rumba, rumba, rumba
runba runba runba runba runba
Character Design/Overall
Key Animation Supervisor
Morioka Hideyuki
Rumba, rumba, rumba, rumba, rumba
runba runba runba runba runba
Art Director
Kakoi Hirotsugu
Color Key
Takizawa Izumi
Visual Effects
Sakai Motoki
Rumba, rumba, rumba, rumba, rumba
runba runba runba runba runba
Director of
Photography
Egami Satoru
Editor
Seki Kazuhiko
Rumba, rumba, rumba, rumba, rumba
runba runba runba runba runba
Wandering around looks just like the rumba
samayoru sugata ha sanagara runba
Cast
Itoshiki Nozumu
Staggering around in a mess, like the rumba
yoromeku sugata mo mecha kucha runba
Fuura Kafuka
Kitsu Chiri
Tsunetsuki Matoi
It may be shaky but I’m still living the rumba
fura tsuki naga ramo ikitei runba
Fujiyoshi Harumi
Kobushi Abiru
Hito Nami
Otonashi Meru
Komori Kiri
Kimura Kaere
From the side it looks like a dance, rumba
hata kara mirya dansu ni mie runba
Kaga Ai
Mitama Mayo
Ookusa Manami
Sekiutsu·Maria·Taro
Kudo Jun
Kino Kuniya
If it’s all right would you like to dance with me?
yokereba isshou ni odori masen ka?
Emperor Penguin
No way, you can’t dance
iie iie anata ja odore masen wa
Oriental Stork
But it’s lonely by myself, let’s dance the rumba
hitori ja munashii odoro yo runba
Ms. Sakurai
Get away from me, do a one-man rumba
ototoi koya gare hitori de runba
Other
Staff
Who decided my worth?
ore no nedan wo dare ga kime ta?
Assistant Director
Tatsuwa Naoyuki
Chief Direction
Miyamoto Yukihiro
Key Animation Supervisor
Yamamura Hiroki
Tigers and leopards lurk in our minds
tora ya hyou ga bokura no kokoro nimo
Sound Director
Kameyama Toshiki
Music
Hasegawa Tomoki
Music Production
StarChild Records
Opening Theme
「Fantasy Rumba」
Lyrics
Ohtsuki Kenji
Composition
Arrangement
NARASAKI
Vocals
Ohtsuki Kenji
and the
Zetsubou Girls
Fuura Kafuka
Kitsu Chiri
Kimura Kaere
Tarou·Maria
Hito Nami
They don’t know that the beasts are lurking
kemono tachi ga hiso mukoto shiranai kara yatsura
So they undervalue us
yasui ne wotsuke yagatte
Release!
toki hanatsu ze!
Now, when they run about
saa, nige madoe sono suki ni
Opening Directors
Oishi Tatsuya
Miyamoto Yukihiro
We are going to dance the rumba
odoro yo boku tachi ha runba
Producer
Moriyama Atsushi
Animation
Producer
Kubota Mitsutoshi
Smiling lightly along with you
hohoemi karoya kani kimi to
Director
Shinbo Akiyuki
Animation Production
SHAFT
Will that day ever come?
sono hi wa kuru noka?
I don’t know
wakara nakute
Production
Sayonara, Zetsubou-sensei
Production Committee
Born in 1794
in northern
Rhode Island
as the third son
in a
naval family
Forelocks Yet to Be Opened
Originally published 13th July, Showa 80
From Chapter 12
Perry has come for the School Opening Anniversary!
What's that supposed to mean?!
Ah.
Open the ports
Because Perry opened Japan's ports?
That has nothing to do with the school's anniversary!
Perry!
Hey, I'm here, Kafuka.
Is he a friend of yours?
You shouldn't simply be friends with anybody and everybody.
Now that the Commodore is here, many things will be opened.
The book opens
Huh?
Perry is a troubled foreigner who lives nearby, who isn't satisfied by just opening ports.
He needs to open everything.
Horse mackerel
Horse mackerel?
Horse mackerel cut open?!
Perry opens everything.
That's right! I'll open everything!
Hmm?
Starting with that!
Teacher!
If we don't catch Perry, he'll open everything in the school!
Let's just leave him be.
Wait!
Library
Book
Nozomu
Jun
Th-This is...!
A guy who looked kind of like a Perry came in and opened every single book the library.
So this is Perry's doing?
Sure is.
Come, let's keep chasing.
No way!
It's obvious that Perry passed through here.
All of the doors and lockers have been opened.
The unopened Eva cans I collected!
RAGE
But I haven't even opened up yet!
You shouldn't really be bringing that kind of thing to school!
Home Economics
HISS
Th-This smell is...
Don't open all of the gas valves!
HISS
Even if you're Perry, there are things you shouldn't open!
Lonely Death travel guide
Besides, I've already had my eyes on this spot for a while.
What if they beef up the security measures?!
Where are you going now?!
Ah, this is lame. I'm going home.
Open your ****, high school girl!
Commodore Perry, that's a bit...
Commodore Perry, that's also a bit...!
I happen to swing that way.
Blush...
Which way are you talking about?!
I'm Perry.
I'm Perry
I'll open everything in this world!
Komori
Do not open
Kiri
What's this?
An unopened room that's actually a hikikomori's room.
It doesn't look like Teacher intends to stop him.
Do not open
Kiri
Ah! He opened Komori-san's room!
Eek!
GRIN
Pluck
Ah! He opened something else!
SOB
I opened it!
I'd only been opened by Teacher before...
Don't say things that will create misunderstandings!
Why isn't that open?!
Hallway
Hito
Itoshiki
Tsunetsuki
Teacher, this is terrible!
Commodore Perry threatened the principal...
A view of the pool
and forced him to open the pool!
Yay, the pool!
I'm Perry. I even open the pool.
Open the pool?
Lonely Death travel guide
That's my spot to drown myself! I had it first!
What if they tighten the security measures?!
Kimura
Entrance
Kobushi
Otonashi
Kitsu
Tsunetsuki
Itoshiki
Pool
You there. How dare you assault me earlier?
I'll sue you!
I'll have this thoroughly investigated in a court of law!
Poke
Stop bitching, buttface!
It's your fault for wearing such a short skirt!
H-He's opening up a can on me!
GRIN
I'm Perry. I open up a can on you.
I'm Perry
I open up
a can
on you
I open up
a can
on you
I open up
a can
on you
I open up
a can
on you
I open up
a can
on you
I open up
a can
on you
I open up
a can
on you
I open up
a can
on you
Was that supposed to be funny?!
Commodore Perry.
If you want to open things,
try to open Teacher's heart.
That's no help!
Vexille
Teacher's heart follows a policy of isolation.
He doesn't open his heart to anyone.
Dejima
Isolation?
We can't have that! Open up!
Open your heart.
No way.
This is good. Let's watch it together.
No way!
Commodore Perry is trying all kinds of methods to open Teacher's heart.
Isolate
But he's refusing to open his heart.
To open his heart, I must draw closer to it.
But how?
Wait, where am I? This isn't a school anymore!
This is Teacher's inner space, that is, within his heart!
While trying to open his heart, you made it in here!
Within his heart...
So I should be able to open his heart from here somehow!
How naïve.
He's in his own heart!
People cant force others' hearts to change!
Especially not my rotten heart!
Run away now!
Such a person's thoughts are filled with despair.
A hanging rope dangles from the branch of a withered tree in this wasteland.
Even in town.
There is no hope left here.
Even those who appear kind secretly disdain and loathe me!
What pain it is to be constantly scorned and cursed!
And the worst is my own realization that I'm a worthless, good-for-nothing excuse for a human being!
I'm in despair!
The despair in my heart has left me in despair!
And this is only the beginning!
My heart goes deeper and deeper!
Help me!
Nooooooo!
Despair: 「Waaaaah!」             As Despair screams, the background shatters like a mirror shattering.
Despair: 「I'm in despair! The despair in my heart has left me in despair!!」
Perry: 「Eek!」
The world falls.
Despair and Perry
also fall.
Despair: 「(To Perry) This is only the beginning. My real nose is far more impressive.」
Perry: 「(With a pale face) Help me!」                     The world continues to fall.
Chiri
Harumi
Abiru
It looks like I'm back in reality.
That was a terrible experience.
Xcholar
Flip
beautiful girls sealed inside
secret
The forbidden
centerfold!!
But here comes a direct assault on your crotch!
You may
have made
it this far...
Extra!
This is a pinup mag with a sealed centerfold!
Flop
Still unopened?!
Are you disappointed, Perry?
The sealed centerfolds in a pinup mag are usually disappointing after you open them.
Yes, some things in this world are never meant to be opened!
・Pandora's Box
・E-mail with a virus
・The sticker on the back of a PSX (They won't fix it for you)
・School gate (Intruders will get in)
・Can of Surstromming (Smelliest food in the world)
・Parents' bedroom ・Trunk of a black car
・Trepanation            ・Electric thermos
・Large wicker hamper ・Door to weaving room
・Open education
Th-That's true...
Perry may have been mistaken.
To be honest, I'm not actually Perry.
We already knew that.
Recollection...
When I first came to Japan and had no friends...
Shimoigusa Station
She talked to me, a complete stranger.
You look like Perry.
You look like Perry
Perry! Perry! Mr. Perry!
I was very happy.
Afterwards, I decided to become Perry.
Seriously...
You're too good at worming into people's hearts.
But I'm going to stop opening everything by force.
So...
I'm opening a new chapter.
I'm opening a
new chapter.
Commodore Perry, that's a bit...
Perry hasn't learned his lesson at all.
Even if you're Perry, I won't let it end this way!
Teacher, you're talking funny.
Forelocks Yet to Be Opened
Originally published 13th July, Showa 80
From Chapter 12
Wait!
Are you Perry or Peril?!
Make up your mind!
Um, well... When you put it that way...
Perry's Store for
Perry
Closed
for
Business
It closed even though it was Perry.
What was he selling?
When you want to
get all the toppings
they don't all fit
so either the
sauce or the toppings
go on another plate
Dressup at Tiffany's
Originally published 28th February, Showa 82
From Chapter 85
Emperor
Empress
Paper Lamp
Three Court Ladies
Raised dishes
Five
Musicians
Vocalist
Minister of the Left
(old man)
Serving tray
Minister of the Right
(young man)
Tachibana orange
Imperial Guards
Cherry Blossoms
Late
The Doll Festival is obviously overembellishment, isn't it?
Huh?
The Master says "to go beyond is as wrong as to fall short".
Before people realize it, they've overembellished everything.
For example
RATTLE
Like this.
For example
And this!
And this
Draft Inside
And this!
YANK
I'm
gonna
make you
melt.
HEH
Why!!
Both the hair and the skin
use screentone
all over the place
For example
LATE
And this makeup, as well!
Who did that?
Maria did it to herself.
She doesn't like shoes and underwear, but she's fine with this stuff, huh?
Shoes and under--
What was that?
Maria feels sick whenever she wears shoes or underwear.
I'm not wearing any right now!
Okay.
We'll ignore that.
Setting that aside
Both old and young people overembellish!
Are you trying to be Madame de Pompadour?!
When nobody says anything, things become more overembellished!
Like the decorations on a sashimi plate at a Japanese diner!
Edible part
Basilica
of Bargains
Or the amusement park on top of a discount store!
Or the pile of crane game stuffed animals in a car!
I
II
III
V
There are people who put all seven dwarves in the back of their car.
Anyone who has dwarves on their car usually has all seven.
Since they're the seven dwarves.
You can't just put one.
Nozomu 「What's with this conversation」
Well, it's true that some people don't know how to coordinate.
Like wearing a checkered tie with a checkered shirt.
Or wearing chrome heart rings on all ten fingers.
Or furnishing a room with high class items that have no common theme.
Doesn't that apply to a lot of manga artists who suddenly become rich after making a hit?
Don't say that out loud.
That isn't overembellishing.
Eh?
A checkered tie with a checkered shirt...
would be the act of a master of chic.
Huh?
Commoners are incapable of such coordination.
Émile Gallé's pottery...
Gaudi's architechture...
The Kabuki style...
The beauty of addition.
A local form of Art Nouveau based on Japanism!
Art Nouveau
Whenever you start using fancy terms, people who have no clue are turned off,
and people who are experts shoot off objections!
The worst possible turn of events!
Come.
Let's go look for masters of chic in the neighborhood.
There's one.
Overembell--
ugh
A master of chic!
Recognized as
Master of Chic
Today only
Everything 25%
off!!
It looks like we're being complimented.
Thank you.
Even more overembellishment!
Beer
COCCO Reibanya
Curry
Spring is
the season
for curry
Hamburger patty
Sausage
Boiled egg
Cheese
Spinach
Pork Cutlet
Natto
Large Serving of Rice
Mushrooms
LATE
Recognized as
Master of Chic
A master of chic!
He just added too many toppings!
You can also find masters of chic at Baskin Robbins and Starbucks.
Coffee
Milk
Frothed Milk
Whipped Cream
Chopped almond
Cherry
You can, but those are pretty expensive.
Oh my
Oh my.
A master of chic wearing a hat over a hat.
Recognized as
Master of Chic
That's terrible even for an overembellishment!
You can expect good things from a house like this.
There's always a cover on the doorknob.
Homemade
And they make potpourri by hand.
And have pieces of felt lying around.
And lots of types of tea!
You're very well-versed.
A master of chic!
Recognized as
Master of Chic
Ma'am.
Let's talk about Sylvanian some other time.
Muscle Age! DS
Higurashi DS
Pro Baseball DS
Onee-chan DS
A
Precure DS
Boobs Boy DS
Signs peppered around a game store!
On sale now!
Beyond just
selling
On sale now!
More and more
new systems coming out!
A
Muscle Age! DS
Plenty
of PS3s
in stock
A
No ETA
on next
shipment
Muscle Age! DS
A
Beware fakes
and bootlegs
A
Notice
See our
demo display
A
There's more coming
in the -z series!
Pro Baseball DS
A
Almost sold out!
Undercover security
on duty
Master of chic!
A person living in the park who's gathered too many belongings.
Limited Edition
DVD Box
Itoshiki
Nozomu
A
Game
Novels
Layout Illustrations
Storyboards
A DVD that comes with so many extras that you can't tell which one's the main item...
This one
That would be meant for masters of chic, right?
Those splendid masters of chic!
•
A grilled meat restaurant featuring harp music
The screens on newer pachinko and pachislot machines
•
Fancy acceptance certificates
for prep schools
•
Human skirt on Kohaku
Swarov*ki cell phone
•
Maga**ne's home page
Fashion leader of table tennis world
•
The Flyers' rainbow-colored uniform
Dior's Japanesey dress during Paris Fashion Week
•
Gu*dam Astray Gold Frame Amatsu
Yuna's outfit
•
Uniforms in SoreChiru
Prehistoric Fish Beast **ran
•
Hino**** Driving School
**yama Manufacturing School
•
Elementary school pencil cases
that come with magnifying glasses and tape measures
•
Sour face on Dr. Kawa*****
70% of Japanese men are overwrapped
•
Manga volume that comes with a picro**
Isn't that overembellishment?
Overembellishment isn't limited to the real world.
What do you mean?
Like this.
Contributed by the JZU
What is that?
An avatar.
You can choose hairstyles, clothes, and accessories, and make another you on the Internet.
Create avatar
A lot of people overembellish.
GRIN
What are you grinning about?
I made an avatar for you.
Create avatar
Teacher's a master of chic!
Stop doing things to make people look down on me!
I made one for everybody.
Create avatar
Please make an overembellished avatar for me.
Sure.
Uh...
Isn't there a part that could be a little more overembellished?
There's an extremely simple-looking part there...
It's already overembellished enough.
I found one!
Drop the makeup already.
I found somebody overembellished.
Here!
Wrong person.
Over here!
It's Mr. Jinroku.
He's dressed rather plainly...
And why do we have to watch from here?
Is he overembellished?
That isn't overembellishment!
Mr. Jinroku!
What the heck did you do when you were younger?!
Elder Brother Kei Itoshiki
Big brother...
How could you do that to a sacred idol?
You'll be...
Cursed!
There's only one way to save you.
No!
Is Teacher a master of chic?
Any parts that aren't drawn on will be taken by evil spirits.
I'm in despair!
This curse that applies to anyone who isn't a master of chic has left me in despair!
Next Day
I like eating warm anpan.
On break.
-Tatsuwa
I'm overembellished!
You're not overembellished.
What are you talking about?
I put some on her.
Shoes.
She put shoes on me.
Ew! Ew!
The world is spinning!
Overembellished...
Foremost among flowers are
those of cherry trees,
of men the warrior,
of pillars cypress,
fish bream,
sleeves scarlet as autumn leaves,
and of flowers the plum-blossom
Rouse Up, O Old Men of the Old Age
Originally published 24th May, Showa 81
From Chapter 50
Everybody.
It's a new semester.
What? It's already May...
What are you talking about?
I mean the old new semester.
Old New Semester
Old new semester?
I don't know what you mean.
The new semester according to the old calendar.
If there can be an Old New Year, why can't there be an old new semester?
That's not all
That's not all...
Old
There should also be Old Christmas!
And Old Valentine's Day!
Old
Old New Year's Eve
And Old New Year's Eve, too?
New
Tokyo
Tower
That goes without saying!
moji
I secretly anticipate receiving chocolate on Old Valentine's Day,
giri
and glare jealously at couples on Old Christmas.
When exactly are Old Christmas and Old Valentine's Day?
Incidentally, Old Golden Week is coming up.
I can't wait.
So you're not going to come on a school day.
Applause?
Marvelous.
Who are you?
One who loves the old.
You're...
My old friend...
Yes.
Your old friend...
Uhh
Uh...
U
Uh
Uhh
Old
So old, and such a sudden reunion, that I can't recall your name.
Sudden
Same here.
Old friends, but it's too sudden
Shouldn't old friends be really close?
Doesn't it just mean that they used to be friends?
My old friend does an even better job of living in the old calender.
Yes.
As one who loves the old...
I drive an old car.
I love thee.
I love thy skin.
I love thee so much
I could die
I write love letters in Old Japanese.
I walk across the Old Tokaido!
I'm still in love with the old Zaku.
Rejoice!
This is the old school building!
I went to the old school building to meet an old friend
I went to the old school building to meet an old friend.
What's with this conversation?
In any case, I'm a fan of the old.
It's a big wave.
Other people would say that I have taken my love of the old to the extreme.
That's right.
It'll be Old Mother's Day after Old Golden Week.
You should at least observe Mother's Day normally...
What are you saying?
My old mother would be my real mother.
I don't get along very well with my new mother.
Old Mother's
Old
Day
Mother's Day
That's what you meant?
Anyway, Japanese people have a harsh view of the old.
I concur, old friend.
Old items have to become vintage before they're considered valuable.
Shiiou University
This is...
A college campus.
College clubs pamper new members,
so the old new members who joined last year are ignored and about to snap.
Sophomores = Old new students
Poor things...
I want to cheer them up!
Hang in there, old students!
Don't call us old students!
Why?
•
Old new employee
Old artist award
•
Old manga offensive
Old livedoor
•
Bats and Terry
Old Burma
•
Old Soviet Union
Born in
village ruled by
the Khmer Rouge
In any case, I desire a restoration of the old.
Kyusengumi
Old
Kyujyo
Script
Furuta Kyuta
My love for the old is no ordinary love.
But no matter how much you say you love the old,
you don't have an old name.
SHOCKERS
If you don't have an old name, wouldn't you be an amateur fan of the old?
An old name, huh...
Old name...
Sounds nice!
Happy New Year
Tokyo-to Koishikawa-ku Otowa-cho Daiu
Itoda Yumi
(old name Adachi)
I'd love to write "old name **" on New Year's cards and stuff.
There is only one way for a man to acquire an old name.
Marry into another family!
Let me marry into your family!
CRUNCH
What are you doing all of a sudden?!
Every girl in this class belongs to Teacher, so you have no chance.
Don't make me sound like a bad person!
Really...
My old-fashioned way of thinking would never let me do such a thing.
What are you doing?
She showed up out of nowhere.
Rin was kidnapped.
Now... Let us become man and wife.
And I shall have my old name.
No!
Back
Then
Shrine
They've come!
Back
Then
Shrine
The Tigers!
Back
Then
Shrine
Do you think you're going to get away with this?!
I'm the one who wants to marry into another family and get rid of the Itoshiki name!
Give it up, Rin.
Father is the kind of person who appreciates such entertaining escapades.
Tokita!
Do something about this insolent fool!
Understood
Understood.
Young man.
It's true that you'll have an old name once you marry into this family.
However, at the same time
However, at the same time...
You will no longer be old friends with young master Nozomu!
Old Friend
You'll no longer be old friends...
Brother-in-law
You'll be brothers-in-law.
Win one
Lose one
Win one! Lose one!
What a quandary.
Old friend?
Old name?!
A rare quandary indeed.
That's right, Teacher's family is an old family.
Old Name
Old Friend
Old Family
Two to one.
Furthermore, the Itoshiki family was an old zaibatsu (plutocrat).
Old Name
Old Friend
Old Family
Old
Zaibatsu
Three to one.
That didn't help, Tokita!
I've made up my mind.
I'm marrying you.
Don't!
If you do that
If you do that, that wouldn't be fair to Rin.
Hey, you.
I can introduce you to someone to marry.
They all want to marry a Japanese person.
Choose whoever you want!
They don't mind if it's only on paper.
That fits perfectly with my intentions.
Hey!
But if you marry into one of their families, you'll become a citizen of their country, right?
I'm not really sure though.
New Citizenship
You can have an old name without marrying into a different family.
Actually, you already have an old name!
Your old name was...
Belovzerov VI!
A penniless poet in 17th century Saint Petersburg!
What did you say?!
I'm sorry!
I couldn't hear you because of all the noise in the background!
A penniless poet in 17th century Saint Petersburg!
Wouldn't that be my past life's name, instead of my old name?!
Your current name becomes your old name in your next life.
How about it?
Want to join me?
Uh, well...
Let's journey together!
Aren't we old friends?!
Secret
My secret messenger has delivered his report.
The two of you aren't old friends.
2 - VI
You were only friendly on the first day of grade school.
In other words...
One-day Friend
One-day friends.
Don't split them apart!
One-day Friend
You were only friends for one day.
So that's why they couldn't remember each other's names.
They were only friends on the first day.
Afterwards, they made different friends and grew apart.
That happens...
So old friends are one-day friends.
Then everything else is one-day...
The Old Testament would be the One-day Testament.
One-day Testament
One-day Japanese Soldier
One-day Japanese soldier.
One-day Hashimoto Faction
One-day Hashimoto faction.
One-day Zaku
One-day Zaku.
One-day Lupin
One-day Lupin!
One-day name!
That's called a Narita divorce.
If we didn’t meet back then
ano toki deawanakeray yume de
I wouldn’t be having nightmares in my dreams
unasarenaide irareta
If you weren’t born in this world
anata ga kono yo ni umarenakereba
Then I would’ve died without knowing jealousy or pain
netami nante, itami nante, shirazu ni sunda
The one who you wanted
anata ga hoshigatta no wa
Was a person completely opposite of me
watashi to mattaku gyaku no hito
I can see that we’re connected by a crimson thread…
makka na ito de tsunagiau no ga mieru
I’m a blue thread
watashi wa aoi ito
Try touching me; my heart now
sawatte mite yo kono kokoro wa ima
Falls in love on its own,
katte ni koi o shite
gets hurt on its own
katte ni kizutsuiteru
Don’t touch me; if my thoughts can’t be fulfilled
sawaranaide yo kono omoi kanawanai no nara
Then only an indigo bruise remains inside of my chest
massao na aza mune no naka nokoru dake de
This show is a work of fiction.
Similarity to any actual people, organizations,
or HAMASHO is purely coincidental.
Run, Eros......
Literature
of Despair
From
Volume 2
Run, Eros.
Melos was enraged.
Whaddya mean, ¥70,000 for a couple beers?!
Ya said there wasn't any extra charge!
No, that's our regular price.
Then I'll go grab some money!
Leave a friend then.
I'll bury him if you don't come back.
Melos ran.
Sorry.
I might not be coming back.
Let's despair over the next episode too!
Illustration:
Asakura Maru