You're listening to King Records.
It's 9 PM on the hour.
Hot-blooded Freak Club.
So long...
Mr. Despair!
Episode 7.
The "Seventeen years old.
Don't you want to grab your wrinkles?"
Chapter.
Whoosh. Whoosh. Whoosh.
A cold wind blows.
The location is in front of a station.
A shopping district at the end of the year.
Outside the bar...
...are a number of patrons gathered for a year-end party.
The students of 2-H...
...arrive on their way home from school.
They're holding year-end parties everywhere.
Said the methodical busybody girl, Chiri Kitsu-chan.
Wait...
How did Napple's hair go on this side?
It's the season for relaxing and forgetting your age.
Replied the normal girl, Nami Hitou-chan.
Don't say normal!
What was that about forgetting your age?
You should never forget your age!
The one who appeared babbling nonsense as always...
Nozomu Itoshiki.
Um...
Our Mr. Despair.
Chiri-chan and everyone else reacts to Mr. Despair's words.
Oh...
There isn't a shot from behind.
What are you talking about?
Said the tail-loving, alleged victim of DV...
Man, I'm out of time!
...Abiru Kobushi-chan.
You should never forget your age!
Take a look!
Shuffle. Shuffle. Shuffle.
Mr. Jinroku walked into sight.
But Pine and Napple barely ever shop up.
Thump. Thump. Thump. Thump.
Sounds of a rhythmic song come from his headphones.
Nightmare rules!
Eh?
Harumi!
Mr. Jinroku's listening to music for young people...
Go take a bath!
I'm busy right now!
This would be forgetting your age.
Then your brothers are going to take theirs first!
Everybody's forgotten their own age!
Eh!
For example...
Does that work?
A mother leaving her kids to go see a sentai show.
A father getting a full tan at a tanning parlor.
Fine!
They can go first!
Or a 38-year-old shoujo manga artist wearing a gothic lolita outfit.
There's this phrase, "age appropriate."
Does it really matter?
Even underage idols...
...forget their age.
There was a fuss about that...
There are examples of forgetting your age in the household.
For example...
No!
A thirty-year-old NEET...
So violent!
...and the mother taking care of him!
Ken-chan.
Here's ice cream and cola.
And I bought the manga you wanted.
What about the limited edition figure?
No!
Stupid!
Hurry up!
It's limited edition!
Okay, okay.
Both parent and child are forgetting their age!
In the eyes of parents, their child will always be a child.
Nothing, huh?
Ours wouldn't be considered forgetting our age, right?
What is it?
I still take baths with my dad occasionally.
That's bad!
Very bad!
Oh?
You were here?
That doesn't matter!
You shouldn't take baths together!
Guess I don't have a shot from behind...
But we're family.
That's true...
Dash. Dash. Dash.
This is the bath in Abiru-chan's home.
Splash.
H-Hey!
Who are you?
Why'd you jump in my bath all of a sudden?
This is an indirect bath.
So exciting.
Back to the original location.
Mr. Despair and company walk through town in search of people who have forgotten their age.
In any case...
Both old and your people forget their age!
I'm in despair!
A Japan that's forgotten its age has left me in despair!
Huh?
It's Ookusa-san.
The one who was out shopping...
...was Manami Ookusa-chan from Mr. Despair's class.
It's super minor.
Everyone goes to Napple X Pine.
Ookusa-san.
How commendable.
Are you on an errand for your mother?
No way!
That's not it.
I'm shopping for my husband's dinner.
What?
I'm a housewife.
I'm very busy.
Bye.
And with that, Ookusa-san departed.
I'm not lying.
Go do a search.
Don't casually reveal such important matters!
And this would also be forgetting your age...
You shouldn't say that.
A married high school girl...
...wouldn't be considered forgetting your age.
It isn't that unusual in America.
And didn't Japan have Yuki Okazaki-san?
Besides...
...she's doing a fine job on the academic work.
Th-That's true...
I misspoke.
However...
...the fact remains that many people forget their age!
For example...
...that voice actress who says she's seventeen years old.
Hello!
Kikuko Inoue-san, seventeen years old!
Kikuko Inoue's the guest on today's Mr. Despair.
She actually showed up!
I happened to be passing by.
Kikuko Inoue.
Seventeen years and 9,619 days old.
U-Uh...
Hey now.
Oh?
You're too soft.
Hey now!
T-Two hits...
Thank you!
I believe that your age depends on how you feel.
Then I'll be leaving now.
And with that, Kikuko Inoue-san departed.
See.
Even Inoue-san says so.
Your age doesn't matter!
And it's possible to forget your age in a good way.
Irritated.
I've been standing here listening to you...
What is it?
It doesn't matter what anyone says...
...people are not allowed to forget their age!
You must live properly according to your age!
I am a woman who doesn't allow people to forget their age!
But there are different kinds of ages, Chiri-chan.
Here.
How old are you, Teacher?
What is this?
It's a mobile game that tells you your mental age.
Mental age?
Such a thing exists now...
Rattle, rattle, rattle as Mr. Despair plays the game.
Beep. Beep. Beep.
Beep!
We have a result!
Your mental age is fifty-seven.
F-Fifty-seven!?
No way!
You've forgotten your age, Teacher.
Live properly according to your age.
Mr. Despair begins living according to his age after being threatened by Chiri-chan.
He wears a padded kimono and putters with his bonsai in the yard.
It'll look better if I cut this spot.
Snip. Snip.
Oh, looking good!
Gosh, my back hurts.
Isn't that a really stereotypical portrayal of a 57-year-old man?
57-years-olds act younger these days.
Teacher's being fifty-seven in his own way so it's okay.
I wonder how old Chiri-chan is.
What is that?
A program that determines your skin's age.
Beep. Beep. Beep.
I'll sue!
Beep.
We have a result!
Your skin age is twenty-eight.
Twenty-eight?
My skin is...
You've forgotten your age.
I am a woman who doesn't allow people to forget their age!
I'll live properly like a 28-year-old!
The location is the apartment, Heights Cape of Thirty Years.
Ring. Ring. Ring.
The phone rings.
Hello?
Oh, it's you, Mom.
Another arranged marriage?
There's no need to worry.
I've got my own plans.
Another stupid story.
Got it.
I'll call again.
Click.
She hangs up the phone.
I don't actually have any plans though...
Chiri-chan sits back and relaxes.
That's it!
I'll go with Pine X Napple.
She sets up the Jyoba exercise machine she ordered online and turns it on.
There's no point in tailoring my work to other people.
Whir. Whir. Whir.
Looks like my metabolism's lower.
Wonder if my circulation's also improved.
Mr. Despair and Kafuka-chan watch from outside the window.
Chiri-chan's really into it.
Is that her interpretation of a 28-year-old woman?
It's sad...
That's all for today's Hot-blooded Freak Club.
Listen again next time!
This is what I call a real Japanese meal.
You're surfing the Internet this early, Majiru?
It's my duty as a fan to check for updates on the blog.
Your duty as a fan?
I see.
Everybody...
I will be holding a duty lesson today.
We're in high school.
We've already completed our educational duties.
Duties...
Your number of duties increases every year.
There are all kinds of duties!
No!
Your number of duties increases...
...without you realizing it.
Like updates on Kawori ******'s blog!
Or Takamisakari's Robocop!
Or message cards from Co-op Shiraishi-san!
Before you know it, they become duties!
However...
If you try to stop...
...people wonder why...
...so you have no choice but to continue!
Strikeout!
Handkerchief.
Not yet?
Where's the handkerchief?
No handkerchief yet?
If you shirk your duty...
...you'll be criticized by society.
Don't shop up in casual clothes, **** Hata!
Why aren't your legs spread!?
Fulfill your duty!
See?
Why am I the example?
In any case...
...many things have become duties!
Everybody!
We meet again!
Kokuko Inoue, seventeen years old!
Hey now!
I'm in despair!
This world of ever-increasing duties has left me in despair!
Was that also a duty?
Rest assured.
That wasn't a duty.
I have to say it or else people will talk.
Nobody will say anything.
Many people with a strong sense of responsibility...
...believe something's a duty...
...when it really isn't!
Wouldn't that be a self-conscious duty?
Self-conscious?
No.
Let's go observe the spread of self-conscious duty around town.
Like that.
Today's message from Hair Salon Takawo...
It's gotten remarkably cold.
Last night, the manager...
And employees held a hot pot party...
And had a blast.
Oh, that.
Some people look forward to reading those.
I couldn't stop if I wanted to.
Nobody's looking forward to it...
...but he assumes it's his duty and works hard.
It's the same over there.
What's on your mind?
What's on my mind?
Isn't that obvious?
I'm coming up with a new menu.
Everybody's looking forward to it.
I couldn't stop if I wanted to.
It's true that some places feel that it's their duty to come up with unusual menus.
Like that.
The comic Harumi draws for the local paper.
Nobody reads it...
yet she feels it's her duty.
She's kept it going for seven years.
Another ridiculous display of athletic ability!
It's true that...
...some people arbitrarily decide that something's their duty.
Like you. You!
Those are merely self-conscious duties!
They may believe that they're doing a good thing...
...but in most cases, they're making other people feel a sense of duty.
What are those?
DVDs people recommended to me.
It's really hilarious!
"It's hilarious! I'll lend you them so watch!"
Did you watch it?
Well...
Wasn't it hilarious?
I'm letting him down...
I'm sorry!
I didn't watch it yet!
I feel guilt every time we meet when he asks!
Did you watch it?
Mr. Jinroku...
Hello.
Mr. Itoshiki...
Fancy meeting you here...
By the way...
Have you gone to that ramen place?
That's right...
You like ramen, right?
I found a great ramen place.
I'll give you directions so go try it out.
Ah, yes...
I'll give it a try...
I'm sorry!
I didn't go yet!
That's right!
I'm putting on a handbell concert with some friends.
Please come if you'd like.
Other people...
...are giving me more and more duties!
You're the one giving other people a sense of duty, Teacher.
Sorry to always bother you, big sis Komori.
Teacher's unreliable...
...so I have to support him from the side.
Komori-san.
Ever since we started living here...
...she's been doing this all the time.
Now that you mention it...
...it did seem like meals just magically appeared.
Didn't you think something was weird!?
I have lots of free time since I just coop myself in school...
I also folded your laundry.
You're...
...too sloppy.
To think I was giving other people a sense of duty...
It's fine.
I like being indoors.
Then...
...I might as well let you spoil me a bit longer.
Here.
That's boring.
Give me money. I'm gonna hit the slots.
Here.
If you spoil him he's never gonna stop.
He's helpless when I'm not around.
You're turning into a Damens, Komori-chan!
Who knows what Teacher will do if I leave him alone...
The way you chase Teacher around...
...would be a self-conscious duty, right?
This isn't the real me.
One day, I'll do great things.
Like make an IT company.
It's the duty of NEETs and hikikomoris...
...to watch new anime.
There are no notable items to mention.
We will be cleaning tomorrow...
...so please bring your PE uniforms.
That's about it.
Oh, also...
It's April...
...but everyone flunked...
...and will remain second-years.
That's all.
Don't say it so casually!
Please don't tell us so casually!
When it's that important!
What are you talking about?
That's what people do in this world.
Inform people about getting married through a fax.
Inform people of retirement through a homepage.
Breakup through a text message.
Demotion through a single sheet of paper.
This society uses casual methods to convey important messages.
You people are the same!
You sneak astonishing remarks into casual conversation!
I have a husband.
I'm not wearing underwear.
Shocking revelations in utterly mundane chitchat!
It's like the "The Hidden Blade" of conversation!
That reminds me...
I've experienced that.
My mother was always busy with work...
...so she often wasn't home.
During a conversation as we ate dinner and watched TV...
According to a recent study...
There were around 270,815 divorces...
...during the year Showa 82...
...meaning that a couple divorces every 90 seconds.
A couple divorces every 90 seconds...
We also got divorced last month.
I didn't tell you?
Don't say it so casually.
They'd gotten divorced at some point.
You also tend to make casual revelations.
That reminds me...
A while back...
Good morning.
You should hurry or you'll be late.
I'm off.
Dad.
Are you taking the day off?
I quit yesterday.
Don't say it so casually!
He managed to find another job...
...and is working now though.
R-Really...
Once, when I went to a friend's house...
Kudou-kun...
Could you help me move the washing machine?
Sure.
Is this okay?
Thanks.
My husband's in prison right now...
...so I don't have enough brawn around the house.
She said it so casually.
Then here you go.
Thanks.
Who was that woman?
Your father's girlfriend.
She told you so casually, huh?
That also reminds me...
I'm so impressed, Fujiyoshi-san.
You're raising four children.
We weren't planning on having the youngest, Harumi, though.
I was already four months pregnant when we found out.
Don't say it so casually!
It's gotten really gloomy in here.
Now, now...
Everybody...
Let's just casually move on.
Weren't you the one who brought it up?
Oh, I almost forgot.
There will be a student assembly next month.
Didn't you just casually ignore something?
What do you mean?
Something definitely doesn't feel right.
Why is Rin-chan here?
It's a new semester...
...so she probably transferred here?
Well, it's not a big deal.
Don't just casually ignore it!
Wait!
What is this?
Isn't it the name of our school?
The name of our school was never mentioned before...
What's with this Suzuki Shoten High School!?
Naming rights.
In other words, the right to name a high school.
We're named after our sponsor.
This is the first time I've heard about it!
The name has been constantly changing...
It's not a big deal.
Don't be so casual about it!
That's right...
I don't see some of the students that were in this class...
Like him.
Or him.
They passed.
Don't be so casual about it!
You're going to use this opportunity to casually ignore randomly inconvenient plot settings!
It's pretty hard.
Like Inoue-san's a bit earlier...
We'll have to change the number of days between TV and DVD version.
Didn't you just casually reveal something?
In any case...
You will find that people casually reveal embarrassing information everywhere.
Please look at this.
In this world, a single piece of paper is used...
...for an important message that...
...my personal information has been leaked!
Everyone talks casually!
Are you in despair!?
Are you in despair, dear brother!?
That was a rude interruption, Rin!
If casual talk has left you in despair...
...why don't you do the opposite?
The opposite?
I see...
I'll say something utterly pointless...
...in a grandiose and overdramatic manner.
That reminds me...
I...
...haven't eaten lunch today!
He hasn't...
Eaten...
Lunch...!?
Hey!
Don't overdramatize something that doesn't matter!
I've decided to oppose society...
...and make worthless statements in a grandiose manner!
That sounds fun.
May I try it?
Go ahead.
Something terrible happened yesterday.
Amazingly...
...my filling fell out!
This feels good.
I wanna try it, too.
Me, too!
So do I!
I'm...
...going home early today!
Chinese cabbage cost...
...over 400 yen!
A big announcement from Kotonon.
I changed my hair color!
While we're at it...
...we should go for an overdramatic reaction as well.
I thought the elevator was going up...
...but it was going down!
Down, you say!?
I bought a can of coffee.
But...
...it was warm!
What was that!?
So sorry! So sorry!
How could I make such a dramatic statement!?
Give it a try, Chiri.
It's fun.
How stupid.
But it looks kind of fun.
Yes...
That reminds me...
I injected juice into my sister once!
I overdramatized such a trifle of a matter.
That's a really big deal!
What are you saying?
A really big deal would be compressed gas...
Don't say it!
Wait!
She was a little sister!?
That's the real shocker!
Young death master.
I inherited my desire to die from my parents...
...and spent most of my childhood plotting my death.
In grade school...
...I jumped from the second floor, but I didn't die.
The next year...
...I tried slitting my wrists with a paper knife...
...but I still didn't die.
The year after that...
...I tried hanging myself my twisting paper into a rope...
I tried gassing myself to death with chimichangas but I didn't die.
Such was my life.