Original Work
Kumeta Koji
「Sayonara, Zetsubou-sensei」 (Serialized in Kodansha’s 「Weekly Shonen Magazine」)
【Zoku】 Sayonara Zetsubou-sensei
Itoshiki Majiru
Fuura Kafuka
Kitsu Chiri
•
Tsunetsuki Matoi
Komori Kiri
Kobushi Abiru
Itoshiki Rin
Otonashi Meru
Kimura Kaere
•
Sekiutsu·Maria·Taro
Fujiyoshi Harumi
Ookusa Manami
•
Mitama Mayo
Kaga Ai
Hito Nami
Series Organization
& Dramatization
Oguro Yuichiro
Rumba, rumba, rumba, rumba, rumba
runba runba runba runba runba
Character Design/Overall
Key Animation Supervisor
Morioka Hideyuki
Rumba, rumba, rumba, rumba, rumba
runba runba runba runba runba
Art Director
Kakoi Hirotsugu
Rumba, rumba, rumba, rumba, rumba
runba runba runba runba runba
Color Key
Takizawa Izumi
Rumba, rumba, rumba, rumba, rumba
runba runba runba runba runba
Visual Effects
Sakai Motoki
Wandering around looks just like the rumba
samayoru sugata ha sanagara runba
Director of Photography
Egami Satoru
Staggering around in a mess, like the rumba
yoromeku sugata mo mecha kucha runba
Editor
Seki Kazuhiko
It may be shaky but I’m still living the rumba
fura tsuki naga ramo ikitei runba
Key Animation Supervisor
Yamamura Hiroki
From the side it looks like a dance, rumba
hata kara mirya dansu ni mie runba
If it’s all right would you like to dance with me?
yokereba isshou ni odori masen ka?
Assistant Director
Tatsuwa Naoyuki
Chief Direction
Miyamoto Yukihiro
Sound Director
Kameyama Toshiki
No way, you can’t dance
iie iie anata ja odore masen wa
Music
Hasegawa Tomoki
Music Production
StarChild Records
But it’s lonely by myself, let’s dance the rumba
hitori ja munashii odoro yo runba
Opening Theme
「Fantasy Rumba」
Lyrics
Ohtsuki Kenji
Composition
Arrangement
NARASAKI
Vocals
Ohtsuki Kenji
and the
Zetsubou Girls
Fuura Kafuka
Kitsu Chiri
Kimura Kaere
Tarou·Maria
Hito Nami
Get away from me, do a one-man rumba
ototoi koya gare hitori de runba
Who decided my worth?
ore no nedan wo dare ga kime ta?
Opening Directors
Oishi Tatsuya
Miyamoto Yukihiro
Tigers and leopards lurk in our minds
tora ya hyou ga bokura no kokoro nimo
They don’t know that the beasts are lurking
kemono tachi ga hiso mukoto shiranai kara yatsura
So they undervalue us
yasui ne wotsuke yagatte
Release!
toki hanatsu ze!
Now, when they run about
saa, nige madoe sono suki ni
We are going to dance the rumba
odoro yo boku tachi ha runba
Director
Shinbo Akiyuki
Smiling lightly along with you
hohoemi karoya kani kimi to
Producer
Moriyama Atsushi
Animation Producer
Kubota Mitsutoshi
Will that day ever come?
sono hi wa kuru noka?
Animation Production
SHAFT
Production
Sayonara, Zetsubou-sensei
Production Committee
I don’t know
wakara nakute
If we didn’t meet back then
ano toki deawanakeray yume de
I wouldn’t be having nightmares in my dreams
unasarenaide irareta
If you weren’t born in this world
anata ga kono yo ni umarenakereba
Then I would’ve died without knowing jealousy or pain
netami nante, itami nante, shirazu ni sunda
The one who you wanted
anata ga hoshigatta no wa
Was a person completely opposite of me
watashi to mattaku gyaku no hito
I can see that we’re connected by a crimson thread…
makka na ito de tsunagiau no ga mieru
I’m a blue thread
watashi wa aoi ito
Try touching me; my heart now
sawatte mite yo kono kokoro wa ima
Falls in love on its own,
katte ni koi o shite
gets hurt on its own
katte ni kizutsuiteru
Don’t touch me; if my thoughts can’t be fulfilled
sawaranaide yo kono omoi kanawanai no nara
Then only an indigo bruise remains inside of my chest
massao na aza mune no naka nokoru dake de