You’re listening to King Records.
It’s 9 PM on the hour.
Hey there.
What, you perv?
Heat Man
Bamboo Bowl
Hot-blooded Freak Club.
So long…
Mr. Despair!
Original Work
Kumeta Koji
「Sayonara, Zetsubou-sensei」 (Serialized in Kodansha’s 「Weekly Shonen Magazine」)
【Zoku】 Sayonara Zetsubou-sensei
Itoshiki Majiru
Fuura Kafuka
Kitsu Chiri
•
Tsunetsuki Matoi
Komori Kiri
Kobushi Abiru
Itoshiki Rin
Otonashi Meru
Kimura Kaere
•
Sekiutsu·Maria·Taro
Fujiyoshi Harumi
Ookusa Manami
•
Mitama Mayo
Kaga Ai
Hito Nami
Series Organization
& Dramatization
Oguro Yuichiro
runba runba runba runba runba
Rumba, rumba, rumba, rumba, rumba
Character Design/Overall
Key Animation Supervisor
Morioka Hideyuki
runba runba runba runba runba
Rumba, rumba, rumba, rumba, rumba
Art Director
Kakoi Hirotsugu
runba runba runba runba runba
Rumba, rumba, rumba, rumba, rumba
Color Key
Takizawa Izumi
runba runba runba runba runba
Rumba, rumba, rumba, rumba, rumba
Visual Effects
Sakai Motoki
samayoru sugata ha sanagara runba
Wandering around looks just like the rumba
Director of Photography
Egami Satoru
yoromeku sugata mo mecha kucha runba
Staggering around in a mess, like the rumba
Editor
Seki Kazuhiko
fura tsuki naga ramo ikitei runba
It may be shaky but I’m still living the rumba
Key Animation Supervisor
Yamamura Hiroki
hata kara mirya dansu ni mie runba
From the side it looks like a dance, rumba
yokereba isshou ni odori masen ka?
If it’s all right would you like to dance with me?
Assistant Director
Tatsuwa Naoyuki
Chief Direction
Miyamoto Yukihiro
Sound Director
Kameyama Toshiki
iie iie anata ja odore masen wa
No way, you can’t dance
Music
Hasegawa Tomoki
Music Production
StarChild Records
hitori ja munashii odoro yo runba
But it’s lonely by myself, let’s dance the rumba
Opening Theme
「Fantasy Rumba」
Lyrics
Ohtsuki Kenji
Composition
Arrangement
NARASAKI
Vocals
Ohtsuki Kenji
and the
Zetsubou Girls
Fuura Kafuka
Kitsu Chiri
Kimura Kaere
Tarou·Maria
Hito Nami
ototoi koya gare hitori de runba
Get away from me, do a one-man rumba
ore no nedan wo dare ga kime ta?
Who decided my worth?
Opening Directors
Oishi Tatsuya
Miyamoto Yukihiro
tora ya hyou ga bokura no kokoro nimo
Tigers and leopards lurk in our minds
kemono tachi ga hiso mukoto shiranai kara yatsura
They don’t know that the beasts are lurking
yasui ne wotsuke yagatte
So they undervalue us
toki hanatsu ze!
Release!
saa, nige madoe sono suki ni
Now, when they run about
odoro yo boku tachi ha runba
We are going to dance the rumba
Director
Shinbo Akiyuki
hohoemi karoya kani kimi to
Smiling lightly along with you
Producer
Moriyama Atsushi
Animation Producer
Kubota Mitsutoshi
sono hi wa kuru noka?
Will that day ever come?
Animation Production
SHAFT
Production
Sayonara, Zetsubou-sensei
Production Committee
wakara nakute
I don’t know
So
Episode 7.
what was
goat versus cow girl
all about
anyway
?
The “Seventeen years old. Don’t you want to grab your wrinkles?” chapter.
Seventeen Years Old
Don’t You Want To Grab Your Wrinkles?
From Chapter 12
Originally published 29th November, Showa 81
Whoosh. Whoosh. Whoosh.
A cold wind blows.
The scene, in front of a station.
A shopping district at the end of the year.
Outside the bar are a number of patrons gathered for a year-end party.
The students of 2-VI arrive on their way home from school.
Wear and you won’t be in despair.
Fashion Master
Find those magic boots that make your
legs 5 cm thinner and 5 cm longer!
I want to wear my favorite dress every day…
But it’s boring to wear the same thing all the time!!
End-of-year tips to make you
look the coolest!Look two years
more grown up with out rules of
fashion and makeup!
“They’re holding year-end parties everywhere,”
Fashionable samples of
popular products
Racing jackets, leopardskin, fur,
ponchos, booties - 100 ways to show off
while you’re covered up!
said the methodical busybody girl, Chiri Kitsu-chan.
Wait…
How did Napple’s hair go on this side?
“It’s the season for relaxing and forgetting your age,”
replied the normal girl, Hito Nami.
Don’t say normal!
Tekkaishi
Mononokai
Dive Girls
Piercing Koishikawa
Rocket
Use the silver power!!
Roujin Work
Mobile Suit Gundam ***
Colored Pencil Shin-chan
Big Fuckup!
Familiar with Ero /
Bonnou Coil
Must-see for girls
(Appendix)
Butler Book
[Alluring Tokita]
Zetsubo-Sensei
Lululululuch of the Self-deprecation
Viewers’ passionate responses
to stages 24 & 25!!
What was that about forgetting your age?
You should never forget your age!
The one who appeared babbling nonsense as always…
30th Heights
Congratulations
Nozomu Itoshiki.
Um…
Congratulations
30th Heights
Our Mr. Despair.
Chiri and the others react to Mr. Despair’s words.
Deadline is 8/5!!
Oh…
There isn’t a shot from behind.
What are you talking about?
Man, I’m out of time!
Said the tail-loving alleged DV victim, Kobushi Abiru.
You should never forget your age!
Take a look!
Shuffle. Shuffle. Shuffle.
Mr. Jinroku walked into sight.
But Pine and Napple barely ever show up.
Thump. Thump. Thump. Thump.
Sounds of a rhythmic song come from his headphones.
Nightmare rules!
Eh?
Harumi
Mother
Harumi,
go take
a bath.
Harumi, go take a bath!
Mr. Jinroku’s listening to music for young people…
I’m busy right now!
I’m busy
right
now!
This would be forgetting your age.
Then your brothers
are going to
take theirs first!!
Then your brothers are going to take theirs first!
Everybody’s forgotten their own age!
Eh~.
For example…
Okay?
A mother leaving her kids to go see a sentai show.
Mm~.
A father getting a full tan at a tanning parlor.
Fine! They can go first!
Fine!
They
can go
first!
Or a 38-year-old shoujo manga artist wearing a gothic lolita outfit.
There’s this phrase, “age appropriate.”
Does it really matter?
Even underage idols forget their age.
There was a fuss about that…
There are examples of forgetting your age at home, too.
For example…
Oh no!
A thirty-year-old NEET and the mother taking care of him!
So violent!
Kenny.
Here’s some ice cream and a cola.
And I bought the manga you wanted.
What about the limited edition figure?
Oh no!
Stupid!
Hurry up!
It’s limited edition!
Okay, okay.
Both parent and child are forgetting their age!
In the eyes of parents, their child will always be a child.
Nothing, huh?
Mine isn’t really forgetting my age.
Pine X Napple
What is it?
I just still take baths with my dad from time to time.
Pine X Napple
Deadline is 8/5!!
That’s bad!
Very bad!
Oh?
You were here?
That doesn’t matter!
Shota
BL Search
Slash Search
Boys Love Links
Fallen Angels’ Sundays
ZBoy’s Love Rumble
white rose garden
Pine x Napple
I’m the Sexiest
Yaoblog
Falling for You
Ohraigeki
Boy’s Game Site
You shouldn’t take baths together!
Pine X Napple
Guess I don’t have a shot from behind…
But we’re family.
That’s true…
Dash. Dash. Dash.
This is the bath in Abiru’s house.
Pine X Napple
Splash.
H-Hey!
Who are you?
Why’d you jump in my bath all of a sudden?
This is an indirect bath.
So exciting.
Back to the original location.
Mr. Despair and company walk through town in search of people who have forgotten their age.
In any case…
Enter message
Wait,      ＜＞__＜＞
is Pine X Napple
minor? ＼(-o-)／
Wait,      ＜＞__＜＞
is Pine X Napple
minor? ＼(-o-)／
Wait,      ＜＞__＜＞
is Pine X Napple
minor? ＼(-o-)／
Wait,      ＜＞__＜＞
is Pine X Napple
minor? ＼(-o-)／
Both old and your people forget their age!
Wait,      ＜＞__＜＞
is Pine X Napple
minor? ＼(-o-)／
Wait,      ＜＞__＜＞
is Pine X Napple
minor? ＼(-o-)／
Wait,      ＜＞__＜＞
is Pine X Napple
minor? ＼(-o-)／
Wait,      ＜＞__＜＞
is Pine X Napple
minor? ＼(-o-)／
Wait,      ＜＞__＜＞
is Pine X Napple
minor? ＼(-o-)／
Wait,      ＜＞__＜＞
is Pine X Napple
minor? ＼(-o-)／
Wait,      ＜＞__＜＞
is Pine X Napple
minor? ＼(-o-)／
Wait,      ＜＞__＜＞
is Pine X Napple
minor? ＼(-o-)／
Wait,      ＜＞__＜＞
is Pine X Napple
minor? ＼(-o-)／
Wait,      ＜＞__＜＞
is Pine X Napple
minor? ＼(-o-)／
Wait,      ＜＞__＜＞
is Pine X Napple
minor? ＼(-o-)／
Wait,      ＜＞__＜＞
is Pine X Napple
minor? ＼(-o-)／
Wait,      ＜＞__＜＞
is Pine X Napple
minor? ＼(-o-)／
Wait,      ＜＞__＜＞
is Pine X Napple
minor? ＼(-o-)／
Wait,      ＜＞__＜＞
is Pine X Napple
minor? ＼(-o-)／
Wait,      ＜＞__＜＞
is Pine X Napple
minor? ＼(-o-)／
Wait,      ＜＞__＜＞
is Pine X Napple
minor? ＼(-o-)／
Wait,      ＜＞__＜＞
is Pine X Napple
minor? ＼(-o-)／
Wait,      ＜＞__＜＞
is Pine X Napple
minor? ＼(-o-)／
I’m in despair!
Wait,      ＜＞__＜＞
is Pine X Napple
minor? ＼(-o-)／
Wait,      ＜＞__＜＞
is Pine X Napple
minor?       ＼(-o-)／
Wait,      ＜＞__＜＞
is Pine X Napple
minor?       ＼(-o-)／
Wait,      ＜＞__＜＞
is Pine X Napple
minor?       ＼(-o-)／
Wait,      ＜＞__＜＞
is Pine X Napple
minor?       ＼(-o-)／
Wait,      ＜＞__＜＞
is Pine X Napple
minor?       ＼(-o-)／
Wait,      ＜＞__＜＞
is Pine X Napple
minor?       ＼(-o-)／
Wait,      ＜＞__＜＞
is Pine X Napple
minor?       ＼(-o-)／
A Japan that’s forgotten its age has left me in despair!
Send
Huh?
It’s Ohkusa!
The one who was out shopping…
Receive
…was Ohkusa Manami-chan from Mr. Despair’s class.
It’s super minor.
Everyone goes to Napple X Pine.
Ms. Ohkusa.
How commendable.
Are you on an errand for your mother?
No way!
That’s not it.
I’m shopping for my husband’s dinner.
Send
Receive
What?
Seat #16
Ohkusa Manami
High School Housewife • Multiple Responsibilities
I’m a housewife.
I’m very busy.
Bye.
Received
message
I’m not lying.
Go look it up or something.
And with that, Mrs. Ohkusa departed.
I’m not lying.
Go do a search.
Don’t casually reveal such important matters!
And this would also be forgetting your age…
You shouldn’t say that.
A married high school girl wouldn’t be considered forgetting your age.
It isn’t that unusual in America.
And didn’t Japan have Okazaki Yuki?
Anyway, she’s doing fine with her schoolwork.
Pine X Napple
Th-That’s true…
I misspoke.
However, the fact remains that many people forget their age!
For example, that voice actress who says she’s seventeen years old.
Hello!
Inoue Kikuko, seventeen years old!
Inoue Kikuko’s the guest on today’s Mr. Despair.
She actually showed up!
I happened to be passing by.
Deadline is 8/5!!
Slash Search Engine
Inoue Kikuko.
Seventeen years and 9,619 days old.
U-Uh…
Come on.
Deadline is 8/5!!
Slash Search Engine
Oh?
Your voices are too soft.
Come on!
T-Two hits…
Thank you!
I believe that your age depends on how you feel.
Anyway, I’ll be leaving now.
And with that, Inoue Kikuko departed.
Enter message
I checked. (pДq)∴It’s super minor
(;_;)     What am I gonna do for
Summer Comiket? I’m drawing
Pine X Napple ＼(’A’)／
See.
Even Inoue says so.
Your age doesn’t matter!
And it’s possible to forget your age in a good way.
Irritated.
I’ve been standing here listening to you…
What is it?
It doesn’t matter what anyone says, people are not allowed to forget their age!
Sending
Sent
I checked. (pДq)∴It’s super minor
(;_;)     What am I gonna do for
Summer Comiket? I’m drawing
Pine X Napple ＼(‘A’)／
Receiving
You must live properly according to your age!
Received
message
Now you’ve done it.
That won’t sell -＜__＞-
What are you going to do?
I’m a woman who doesn’t allow people to forget their age!
Enter message
I‘ll think about it...
I’ll think about it....
I’ll think about it.....
But there are different kinds of ages, Chiri.
I’ll think about it....
Sending
Sent
Here.
How old are you, Teacher?
What is this?
It’s an app that tells you your brain age.
Brain age?
Such a thing exists now…
Rattle, rattle, rattle as Mr. Despair plays the game.
Beep. Beep. Beep.
Hey there.
What, you perv?
Heat Man
Bamboo Bowl
Beep!
We have a result!
Your mental age is fifty-seven.
F-Fifty-seven?!
No way!
You’ve forgotten your age, Teacher.
Live properly according to your age.
Mr. Despair begins living according to his age after being threatened by Chiri.
He wears a padded kimono and putters with his bonsai in the garden
It’ll look better if I cut this spot.
Snip. Snip.
Oh, looking good!
Gosh, my back hurts.
Isn’t that a really stereotypical portrayal of a 57-year-old man?
57-years-olds act younger these days.
Teacher’s being 57 in his own way so it’s okay.
I wonder how old Chiri is.
What is that?
An app that determines your skin’s age.
Beep. Beep. Beep.
I’ll sue!
Beep.
We have a result!
Your skin age is twenty-eight.
Twenty-eight?
My skin is…
Napple × Pine
Pine × Napple
You’ve forgotten your age.
I am a woman who can’t accept the forgetting of ages!
I’ll live like a proper 28-year-old!
The location is the apartment, 30th Heights.
Ring. Ring. Ring.
The phone rings.
Hello?
Oh, it’s you, Mom.
A
No make-up again today
Perfect Girl
Having a photo published is the
best chance to let people see you.
But if you aren’t used to it,
you’ll feel that everyone else
is on a higher level. You
end up with low esteem.
It’s a sad thing. Every
time you eat, you
feel yourself getting
fat. You get
depressed and
break down into
tears.
Another guy you want me to meet?
There’s no need to worry.
I’ve got my own plans.
Another stupid story.
Got it.
I’ll call again.
Click.
She hangs up the phone.
I don’t actually have any plans though…
That’s it!
Chiri sits back and relaxes.
Enter message
I’ll go with Pine X Napple.
(-A-)／  There’s no point
in tailoring my work to
other people. ＼(^A^)／
She sets up the Jyoba exercise machine she ordered online and turns it on.
There’s no point in tailoring my work to other people.
Whir. Whir. Whir.
Sending
Sent
Looks like my metabolism’s lower.
Wonder if my circulation’s also improved.
Mr. Despair and Kafuka watch from outside the window.
Chiri’s really getting into it.
Is that her interpretation of a 28-year-old woman?
It’s sad…
That’s all for today’s Hot-blooded Freak Club.
Listen again next time!
Night Watch Office
This is what I call a real Japanese meal.
You’re surfing the Internet this early, Majiru?
Just Between You and Me
It’s my duty as a fan to check for updates on the blog.
Duty
Just Between You and Me
Your duty as a fan?
Duty
I see.
Everybody looks
forward to the
blackboard jokes
so we couldn’t
stop if
we wanted to
Duty and Soldiers
Originally published 1st November, Showa 81
From Chapter 71
-
VI
Itoshiki
Everybody…
I will be holding a duty lesson today.
Duty Lesson
We’re in high school.
We’ve already completed our educational duties.
Duties…
I love you, Ai
I have no energy
without Wide.
I love you, Tomo
Your number of duties increases every year.
There are all kinds of duties!
Duty
No!
Your number of duties increases without you realizing it.
Kawori’s Between You and Me
Like updates on ****** Kawori’s blog!
Or Takamisakari’s Robocop!
Or message cards from Shiraishi at the co-op!
Before you know it, they become duties!
However, if you try to stop,
people wonder why and you have no choice but to continue!
Koshien
Strikeout!
Handkerchief.
Handkerchief
Where’s the
handkerchief
No handkerchief yet?
Handkerchief.
Whisper
Not yet?
Where’s the handkerchief?
No handkerchief yet?
Handkerchief
Wipe
If you shirk your duty, you’ll be criticized by society.
Don’t show up in your street clothes, **** Hata!
Why aren’t your legs spread?!
Fulfill your duty!
See?
Why am I the example?
Hoshino Aki’s cleavage
Katsura Sanshi’s flip-flopping
Ishida Jun’ichi going barefoot
Nakao Akira’s neckerchief
Uchiyama’s big appetite
The Kano sisters’ extravagant lifestyle
The Ventures’ chromatic runs
Yukorin’s interview interruptions
Hard Gay being hard gay
t.A.T.u canceling at the last second
HAMASHO’s G-Jumper
mixi responses
Rakuten’s 39 wins
Shogakukan’s study magazines
Swimsuit covers
Run, think, ho
Asia Cup
Inoue Kiku
In any case, many things have become duties!
Everyone!
We meet again!
Kokuko Inoue, seventeen years old!
Come on!
I’m in despair!
This world of ever-increasing duties has left me in despair!
Was that also a duty?
Rest assured.
That wasn’t a duty.
President V Putin
I have to say it or else people will talk.
Nobody will say anything.
Many people with a strong sense of responsibility believe something’s a duty when it really isn’t!
Wouldn’t that be a self-conscious duty?
Self-conscious?
Self-conscious
Duty
No.
Let’s go observe the spread of self-conscious duty around town.
Like that.
Today’s message
from Hair Salon Takawo
It’s gotten
remarkably cold.
Last night, the
manager and employees
held a hot pot party
and had a blast.
The frigid temperature
has the tress
preparing for autumn
Want to try
turning your hair
and autumn color?
Today’s message from Hair Salon Takawo…
It’s gotten remarkably cold.
Last night, the manager
and employees held a hot pot party
and had a blast.
Oh, that.
Some people look forward to reading those.
I couldn’t stop if I wanted to.
Nobody’s looking forward to it, but he assumes it’s his duty and works hard.
Stab
Miracle 355 Crepe
It’s the same over there.
What’s on your mind?
What’s on my mind?
Isn’t that obvious?
Natto Potato Crêpe
A
Apricot Seed Soy Sauce Crêpe
Seaweed Banana Crêpe
A
Apple Vinegar Mayo Crêpe
Millet Rice Crêpe
A
Brown Sugar Syrup Onion Crêpe
I’m coming up with a new menu.
Sense of duty
Miracle 355 Crepe
Everybody’s looking forward to it.
I couldn’t stop if I wanted to.
It’s true that some places feel that it’s their duty to come up with unusual menus.
Like that.
The comic Harumi draws for the local paper.
Nobody reads it…
Yet she feels it’s her duty.
She’s kept it going for seven years.
Another ridiculous display of athletic ability!
Duty
It’s true that some people arbitrarily decide that something’s their duty.
Like you. You!
Hide’s fashion upon return to Japan
Wig Boxer
”1, 2, 3, Unbelievable!”
The stuff after chapter 3 of RO*D
Kobayashi Sachiko’s costume for Kohaku
Kimura Taro’s puns
Hiroshima’s Saito’s handkerchief (red)
Battle caps on PET bottles
Extra cover on magazine
Japa**t’s extras
MOS’s production label
Reducing cell phone size
The “world’s police” Ame
Koizumi surprise
They may believe that they’re doing a good thing,
but in most cases, they’re making other people feel a sense of duty.
What are those?
DVDs people recommended to me.
It’s hilarious!
A
“It’s hilarious! I’ll lend you them so watch!”
It’s hilarious!
A
Ah yeah…
It’s really hilarious!
A
Ah yeah…
It’s hilarious!
Did you watch it?
Well…
Wasn’t it hilarious?
I’m letting him down…
I’m sorry!
I didn’t watch it yet!
I feel guilt every time we meet when he asks!
Did you watch it?
Crash
Ah…
Mr. Jinroku.
Hello.
Mr. Itoshiki.
Fancy meeting you here.
By the way
By the way…
Have you gone to that ramen place?
That’s right…
You like ramen, right?
I found a great ramen place.
I’ll give you directions so go try it out.
Ah, yes. I’ll give it a try…
I’m sorry!
I didn’t go yet!
Gasp!!
That’s right!
Handbell Recital
The sound of handbells
during Christmas
Time: 12/17 (Sun)
Starting 7 PM
Place: Yotsuya, Hanazono,
SD Hall
Director
(Arai)
I’m putting on a handbell concert with some friends.
Please come if you’d like.
Other people are giving me more and more duties!
Duty
You’re the one giving other people a sense of duty, Teacher.
Night Watch Office
Thanks for always helping out, big sis Komori.
Teacher’s unreliable, so I always have to stay by his side.
Komori.
Ever since we started living here she’s been doing this all the time.
Now that you mention it…
It did seem like meals just magically appeared.
Didn’t you think something was weird?!
I have lots of free time since I just coop myself in school…
I also folded your laundry.
You’re too sloppy.
To think that I was giving other people a sense of duty…
It’s fine.
I like being indoors.
Then I might as well let you spoil me a bit longer.
Half a day later
Hard
Mellow
Yellow
Realtime
Night Watch Office
Dream time
Here.
That’s boring.
Give me money. I’m gonna hit the slots.
Here.
If you spoil him he’s never gonna stop.
He’s helpless when I’m not around.
Sense of Duty
You’re turning into a doormat, Komori!
Night Watch Office
Who knows what Teacher will do if I leave him alone…
The way you chase Teacher around would be a self-conscious duty, right?
This isn’t the real me.
One day, I’ll do great things.
Like start an IT company.
It’s the duty of NEETs and shut-ins to watch late-night anime.
There are no notable items to mention.
-
VI
We will be cleaning tomorrow, so please bring your gym uniforms.
That’s about it.
Oh, also…
It’s April, but you’re all being held back a year, and will continue to be juniors.
That’s all.
Hmm.
Don’t say it so casually!
Please don’t tell us so casually when it’s something that important!
What are you talking about?
That’s what people do in this world.
Marriage
Inform people about getting married through a fax.
Just married
Retirement
Inform people of your retirement through your homepage.
Breakup
Breakup through a text message.
Goodbye,
Sato
Ebizou
Demote
Directive
As of today,
you have been assigned
to Hinamizawa.
Demotion through a single sheet of paper.
This society uses casual methods to convey important messages.
You people are the same!
You sneak astonishing remarks into casual conversation!
I have
a husband
I have a husband.
I have
a husband
I’m not
wearing
any panties
I have
a husband
I’m not
wearing
any panties
I have
a husband
I’m not
wearing
any panties
I have
a husband
I’m not
wearing
any panties
I have
a husband
I’m not
wearing
any panties
I have
a husband
I’m not
wearing
any panties
I have
a husband
I’m not
wearing
any panties
I have
a husband
I’m not
wearing
any panties
I have
a husband
I’m not
wearing
any panties
I’m not
wearing
any panties
I’m not
wearing
any panties
I’m not
wearing
any panties
I’m not
wearing
any panties
I’m not
wearing
any panties
I’m not
wearing
any panties
I’m not
wearing
any panties
I’m not
wearing
any panties
I’m not
wearing
any panties
I’m not
wearing
any panties
I’m not
wearing
any panties
I’m not wearing underwear.
I’m not
wearing
any panties
I’m not
wearing
any panties
I’m not
wearing
any panties
I’m not
wearing
any panties
I’m not
wearing
any panties
I’m not
wearing
any panties
I’m not
wearing
any panties
I’m not
wearing
any panties
I’m not
wearing
any panties
I’m not
wearing
any panties
Shocking revelations in utterly mundane chitchat!
It’s like the “The Hidden Blade” of conversation!
That reminds me.
I’ve experienced that.
My mother was always busy with work, so she often wasn’t home.
During a conversation as we ate dinner and watched TV…
According to a recent study, there were around 270,815 divorces
during the year Showa 82, meaning that a couple divorces every 90 seconds.
A couple divorces every 90 seconds…
We also got divorced last month.
I didn’t tell you?
Don’t say it so casually.
They’d gotten divorced at some point.
You also tend to make casual revelations.
That reminds me. A while back…
Good morning.
You should hurry or you’ll be late.
I’m off.
Dad.
Are you taking the day off?
I quit yesterday.
Don’t say it so casually!
Actress >>> artist
He managed to find another job, so he’s working now.
R-Really…
Once, when I went to a friend’s house…
Kudo, could you help me move the washing machine?
Sure.
Is this okay?
Thanks.
My husband’s in prison right now, so I don’t have enough brawn around the house.
Oshirihojiri bug
She said it so casually.
Enter message
Then here you go.
Thanks.
Enter message
Who was that?
Who was that woman?
Your father’s girlfriend.
Enter message
She told you so casually, huh?
That also reminds me…
I’m so impressed, Fujiyoshi-san.
You’re raising four children.
We weren’t planning on having the youngest, Harumi, though.
I was already four months pregnant when we found out.
Don’t say it so casually!
Gloom
It’s gotten really gloomy in here.
Now, now
Now, now…
Everybody…
Everybody
Now, now
Let’s just casually move on.
Weren’t you the one who brought it up?
Oh, I almost forgot.
There will be a student assembly next month.
Didn’t you just casually ignore something?
What do you mean?
Something definitely doesn’t feel right.
Why is Rin here?
It’s a new semester,
so she probably transferred here?
Well, it’s not a big deal.
Go be Mr Aso’s kid
Don’t just casually ignore it!
Student Assembly
Suzuki Shoten High School
Wait!
What is this?
Isn’t it the name of our school?
Suzuki Shoten High School
The name of our school was never mentioned before…
What’s with this Suzuki Shoten High School?!
Naming rights.
In other words, the right to name a high school.
We’re named after our sponsor.
This is the first time I’ve heard about it!
Bellybutton lint
The name has been constantly changing.
It’s not a big deal.
Don’t be so casual about it!
Don’t…
That’s right…
I don’t see some of the students that were in this class.
Like him.
Or him.
They passed.
Don’t be so casual about it!
You’re going to use this opportunity to casually ignore random inconvenient plot points!
Sorry m(__)m,
Grownup stuff happened and
we weren’t able to replace them
~AD Kamada
Sorry m(__)m,
Grownup stuff happened and
we weren’t able to replace them
~AD Kamada
It’s pretty hard.
Like Inoue’s a bit earlier…
We’ll have to change the number of days between TV and DVD version.
Didn’t you just casually reveal something?
In any case…
You will find that people casually reveal embarrassing information everywhere.
Notice that your information has been leaked
This message confirms that your personal data
Please look at this.
Notice that your information has been leaked
This message confirms that your personal data
In this world, a single piece of paper is used
Notice that your information has been leaked
for an important message that my
personal information has been leaked!
Notice that your information has been leaked
We hope to find you in good health.
This message confirms that your personal data
has been leaked.
Everyone talks casually!
All characters in this game are over 18 years of age
Inquire at theaters for showtimes.
Image for illustrative purposes only
Effects vary from person to person
Inquire at theaters for showtimes.
All characters in this game are over 18 years of age
Effects vary from person to person
Inquire at theaters for showtimes.
All characters in this game are over 18 years of age
Irreplacable Object
Effects vary from person to person
All characters in this game are over 18 years of age
Image for illustrative purposes only
Effects vary from person to person
Irreplacable Object
Image for illustrative purposes only
Effects vary from person to person
All characters in this game are over 18 years of age
Irreplacable Object
Effects vary from person to person
SURGEON GENERAL’S WARNING: Quitting Smoking Now Greatly Reduces Serious Risks to Your Health.
All characters in this game are over 18 years of age
Irreplacable Object
SURGEON GENERAL’S WARNING: Quitting Smoking Now Greatly Reduces Serious Risks to Your Health.
All characters in this game are over 18 years of age
118% refers to a single person receiving multiple job offers
SURGEON GENERAL’S WARNING: Quitting Smoking Now Greatly Reduces Serious Risks to Your Health.
All characters in this game are over 18 years of age
Other charges may apply
“School” Girl
My actual age is 2
The
Are you in despair?!
Are you in despair, dear brother?!
That was a rude interruption, Rin!
If casual talk has left you in despair, why don’t you do the opposite?
The opposite?
I see…
I’ll say something utterly pointless,
but in a grandiose and overdramatic manner.
-
VI
That reminds me…
I…
I haven’t eaten lunch today!
Bajeebus
He hasn’t…
Eaten…
Lunch…?!
Lunch?!
Hey!
Don’t overdramatize something that doesn’t matter!
I’ve decided to oppose society, and
make worthless statements in a grandiose manner!
That sounds fun.
Flatscreen
Station
master
May I try it?
Go ahead.
A victory that wasn’t broadcast
Something terrible happened yesterday.
Amazingly
Amazingly…
My filling fell out!
Bajeebus
This feels good.
I wanna try it, too.
Me, too!
So do I!
I’m…
Going home early today!
Shock
That chinese cabbage cost…
Over 400 yen!
Shock
Big Announcement from Kotonon
A big announcement from Kotonon.
I changed my hair color!
Shock
Enter message
Good
morning!
Shock
While we’re at it, we should go for an overdramatic reaction as well.
I thought the elevator was going up, but it was going down!
Shock
Down, you say?!
I bought a can of coffee.
But…
It was warm!
What was that?!
I’m so sorry! I’m so sorry!
How could I make such a dramatic statement?!
Give it a try, Chiri.
It’s fun.
How stupid.
But it looks kind of fun.
Sorry
Abe
Yes…
That reminds me…
I injected juice into my sister once!
I overdramatized such a trifle of a matter.
That’s a really big deal!
A
Garlic injections provide vitamin
such as B1 and B2 as well as glucose.
Vitamin B improves the recovery of energy,
removes the lactic acid that causes fatigue,
and produces energy which leads to high stamina.
The injected Vitamin B1 contains sulfuric acid which emits a garlic-like odor, thus the name.
Garlic injections are good.
They just happen to be illegal.
What are you saying?
A really big deal would be compressed gas…
Don’t say it!
A
Unneeded cans of compressed gas,
abandoned, used cans of compressed gas,
or cans of compressed gas that someone has used
are frequently left lying around.
Under the Compressed Gas Security Act,
leaving cans of compressed gas
lying around is a criminal act.
A government department is assigned to
control any matters in this area.
R
oa
Wait! Chiri is a little sister?!
r
That’s the real shocker!
Casually Ignore
The girl
I love
already
had
a
boyfriend
Don’t say it so Casually!
Melos Stood and Retorted Furiously
From Chapter 90
Originally published 11th April, Showa 82
If we didn’t meet back then
ano toki deawanakeray yume de
I wouldn’t be having nightmares in my dreams
unasarenaide irareta
If you weren’t born in this world
anata ga kono yo ni umarenakereba
Then I would’ve died without knowing jealousy or pain
netami nante, itami nante, shirazu ni sunda
The one who you wanted
anata ga hoshigatta no wa
Was a person completely opposite of me
watashi to mattaku gyaku no hito
I can see that we’re connected by a crimson thread…
makka na ito de tsunagiau no ga mieru
I’m a blue thread
watashi wa aoi ito
Try touching me; my heart now
sawatte mite yo kono kokoro wa ima
Falls in love on its own,
katte ni koi o shite
gets hurt on its own
katte ni kizutsuiteru
Don’t touch me; if my thoughts can’t be fulfilled
sawaranaide yo kono omoi kanawanai no nara
Then only an indigo bruise remains inside of my chest
massao na aza mune no naka nokoru dake de
This show is a work of fiction.
Similarity to any actual Hot-blooded Freak Club, Manabe Kawori, or Gay*dam is purely coincidental.
Little Mord Fauntleroy
Literature
of Despair
From
Volume 3
Young death master.
I inherited my desire to die from my parents, and spent most of my childhood plotting my death.
In grade school, I jumped from the second floor, but I didn’t die.
The next year, I tried slitting my wrists with a paper knife, but I still didn’t die.
The year after that, I tried hanging myself my twisting paper into a rope.
I tried to choke myself on an artichoke but I didn’t die.
Such was my life.
Illustration:
Hikawa Hekiru