TOP: So
TOP: what was
TOP: goat versus cow girl
TOP: all about
TOP: anyway
TOP: ?
TEXT: Seventeen Years Old
Don't You Want To Grab Your Wrinkles?
Original Chapter Seventy-Four
Published November 29th, Showa 81
BIG MIDDLE TEXT: [Wear and you won't be in despair.]
[Fashion Master 100]
SMALL TEXT (from bottom and up): [Find those magic boots!!]
[Legs 5 cm thinner and 5 cm longer]
[But it's boring to wear the same thing every day!!]
[I wont to wear my favorite dress every day...]
[Laws of fashion and make-up]
[Look like a 2-year-old adult]
[Look better than everyone else]
(to the right)[Fashionable Samples]
[Popular Item]
[Show off 100 items on your body!!]
[Booties, ect...]
[Riders, Leopard skin, Fur, Poncho]
LEFT TEXT (from top to bottom): Tekkaishi
Mononoge
Fly Girls
Piercing Koishikawa Rocket
Use the silver power!! Roujin Work
Mobile Suit Gundam ()()()
Colored Pencil Shin-chan
Ookiku Buremakutte
Ero no Tsukaima / Bonnou Coil
Must-see for girls (Appendix)
Butler Book [Alluring Tokita]
Magical Virgin Feature
According to legend,
if you're still a virgin at 30, you can use magic.
RIGHT TEXT (from top to bottom): Mr. Despair
Lululululusu of the Self-depreciation
Passionate viewer's response to stages 24 & 25!!
TEXT: Cape of Thirty Years
Congratulations
NOTE: Draft due 8/5!!
LEFT SIGNS: Harumi
RIGHT SIGNS: Mother
TEXT: Harumi, go take a bath.
I'm busy right now!
TEXT: Then your brothers are going to take theirs first!!
TEXT: Eh~~~~.
TEXT: Does that work?
TEXT: Mmm~~~~.
TEXT: Fine!
They can go first!
TEXT: Pine X Napple
NOTE: Draft due 8/5!!
TEXT: Is Pine X Napple minor?
SIGNS: Send
TEXT: Receive
SIGNS: Receive
TOP TEXT: Seat #16
MIDDLE TEXT: Manami Ookusa
BOTTOM TEXT: High School Housewife • Multiple Responsibilities
TEXT: I'm not lying. Go do a search.
TEXT: Pine X Napple
NOTE: Draft due 8/5!!
TEXT: Coupling Search Engine
TEXT: I checked
It's super minor.
What am I gonna
do for Summer Comiket
I'm drawing a
Pine X Napple
TEXT: Sending
TEXT: Sent
TEXT: I checked
It's super minor.
What am I gonna
do for Summer Comiket
I'm drawing a
Pine X Napple
TEXT: Receiving
TEXT: Received
TEXT: Now you've done it.
That won't sell.
What are you gonna do?
TEXT: I'll think about it
TEXT: Sending
TEXT: Sent
TOP TEXT: Napple X Pine
BOTTOM TEXT: Pine X Napple
TOP TEXT: No make-up again today
Perfect Girl
BOTTOM TEXT: Having a photo published is the best
chance to let people see you. But if
you aren't used to it, you'll feel that
everyone else is on a higher level.
You end up with low esteem.
It's a sad thing. Every time you eat,
you feel yourself getting fat. You get
depressed and break down into tears.
TEXT (from top to bottom): Dead Line Dance
Unparralelled Beauty (Color Fix Mode)
ABIRU fetish HARUMI
KAERE MISS UNIVERSE(S) MARIA
NAMI Main Character HITOU
KIRI Kagerou (Double Busybody) MATOI
CHIRI Casket of Rosos KITSU
KAFUKA ~Promise with God~
KICA981 Character Song Album "Zetsubou Song Collection"
BL ~Drown in a whirlpool of romance....
♂X♂ The days I spent with you
ZBSS74 Love Elegy for You
CGHR Romeo for Pretty Boys
00 Fangirl Meister
TEXT: I'll go with Pine X Napple. There's no point in tailoring my work to other people.
TEXT: Sending
TEXT: Sent
SIGN: Night Watch Office
TEXT: Just Between You and Me
SIGNS: Duty
SIGN: Everybody looks
SIGN: forward to the
SIGN: blackboard jokes
SIGN: so we couldn't
SIGN: stop if
SIGN: we wanted to
SIGNS: Duty and Soldiers
Published November 1st, Showa 81
Original Chapter Seventy-one
SIGN: 2 - H
Duty Lesson
LEFT TEXT: I love you, Ai-chan
MIDDLE TEXT: I have no energy without Wide
RIGHT TEXT: I love you, Tomo-chan
SIGN: Duty
TEXT: Kawori's Between You and Me
SIGN: Koshien
TEXT: Handkerchief
LEFT TEXT: Where's the handkerchief
RIGHT TEXT: No handkerchief yet?
TEXT: Whisper
TEXT: Handkerchief
TEXT: WIPE
TEXT (from top to bottom): Aki Hoshino's cleavage
Sanshi Katsura's flip-flopping
Junichi Ishida going barefoot
Akira Nakao's neckerchief
Uchiyama-kun's big appetite
Kanou sister' extravagant lifestyle
The Ventures' chromatic runs
Yuko-rin's interview interruptions
Hard Gay being hard gay
t.A.T.u canceling at the last second
HAMASHO's G-Jumper
mixi's responses
Rakuten's 39 wins
Shogakukan's study magazines
Swimsuit front pages
Run, think, polyvalent, win Asia Cup
Kikuko Inoue's "Seventeen Years Old" "Hey now"
President Le Putin
RIGHT TEXT: Self-conscious
LEFT TEXT: Duty
TEXT (from top to bottom): Today's message from Hair Salon Takawo
It's gotten remarkably cold.
Last night, the manager
and employees held a hot pot party
and had a blast.
The frigid temperature has the tress
preparing for autumn
Want to try turning your hair
and autumn color?
TEXT: Stab
SIGN: Miracle 355 Crêpe
TEXT (from top to bottom): Natto Potato Crêpe
Apricot Seed Soy Sauce Crêpe
Seaweed Banana Crêpe
Apple Vinegar Mayo Crêpe
Millet Rice Crêpe
Brown Sugar Syrup Onion Crêpe
SIGN: Miracle 355 Crêpe
SIGN: Duty
TEXT (from top to bottom): Hide's fashion upon return to Japan
Wig Boxer
"1, 2, 3, Unbelievable!"
The stuff after chapter 3 of RO()D
Sachiko Kobayashi's costume for Red and White
Taro Kimura's puns
Hiroshima's Saito's handkerchief (red)
Battle caps on PET bottles
Extra cover on magazine
Japa()()t's extras
MOS's production label
Reducing cell phone size
Koizumi surprise
LEFT TEXT: It's hilarious!
LEFT TEXT: Ah, yeah...
TEXT: CRASH
TEXT: Ah...
TEXT: By the way
TEXT: Gasp!!
TOP TEXT: Handbell Recital
MIDDLE TEXT: The sound of handbells during Christmas
LOWER TEXT: When
12/17 (Sun) Starting 7 PM
Where
Yotsuya, Hanazono, SD Hall
RIGHT TEXT: Director
(Arai)
SIGN: Duty
SIGN: Night Watch Office
TEXT: Half a day later
LEFT TEXT: Realtime
RIGHT TEXT: Night Watch Office
BOTTOM TEXT: Dream time
SIGN: Night Watch Office
TEXT: Sense of Duty
SIGN: 2 - H
TEXT: Hmm.
TEXT: Marriage
TEXT: Retirement
TEXT: Breakup
TEXT: Satou-san,
Goodbye
Ebizou
TEXT: Demote
TEXT: Directive
As of today,
you have been assigned to Hinamizawa.
TEXT: Voice actress >> >> Teacher
TEXT: Oshirihojiri bug
TEXT: Who was that?
TEXT: DOYONDO
TEXT: Now, now
TEXT: Everybody
LEFT TEXT: Now, now
RIGHT TEXT: Everybody
TEXT: Go be aso-san's kid
TEXT: Suzuki Shoten High School Student Assembly
TEXT: Suzuki Shoten High School
TEXT: Bellybutton lint
TEXT: Don't...
TEXT: Notice that your information has been leaked // We hope to find you in good health.
TEXT: Notice that your information has been leaked
TEXT (from top to bottom): Notice that your information has been leaked
We hope to find you in good health.
This message confirms that your personal data has been leaked.
TEXT (from top to bottom): A photo is just an image
Effects vary from person to person
Special charges may apply
Too much smoking may harm your health
Inquire at theaters for showing times.
118% means you passed multiple times
The 0.1% alcohol on non-alcoholic beer
All characters in this game are over 18 years of age
Reconstruction Impossible Article
High "School" Girl
My actual age is 26
SIGN: 2 - H
TEXT: BAJEEBUS
TEXT: He hasn't...
TEXT: Eaten...
TEXT: Lunch...!?
TEXT: Dilute station master
TEXT: A victory that wasn't broadcast
TEXT: Amazingly
TEXT: BAJEEBUS
TEXT: SHOCK
TEXT: Big Announcement from Kotonon
TEXT: I changed my hair color!
TEXT: SHOCK
top of phone
TEXT: Good morning!
TEXT: SHOCK
TEXT: Sorry
-Abe-san
TOP TEXT: Garlic injections provide vitamins such as B1 and B2 as well as glucose.
Vitamin B improves the recovery of energy, removes the lactic acid that causes fatigue, and produces energy which leads to high stamina.
BOTTOM TEXT: The injected Vitamin B1 contains sulfuric acid which emits a garlic-like odor, thus the name.
Garlic injections are good. They just happen to be illegal.
TOP TEXT: Unneeded cans of compressed gas, abandoned, used cans of compressed gas, or cans of compressed gas that someone has used
are frequently left lying around. Under the High Voltage Gas Security Act, leaving cans of compressed gas lying around is a criminal act.
BOTTOM TEXT: A government department is assigned control any matters in this area.
TEXT: ROAR
TEXT: Casually Ignore
SIGN: The person
SIGN: I love
SIGN: fell
SIGN: in love
SIGN: with
SIGN: someone else
TEXT: Don't say it so Casually!
Melos Stood and Retorted Furiously
Published April 11th, Showa 82
Original Chapter Ninety
TEXT: This show is a work of fiction.
There is no relation to the real Hot-blooded Freak Club, Kawori Manabe, or Gay()dam.
TOP LEFT TEXT: Despair Literature
BOTTOM LEFT TEXT: From Volume Three
RIGHT TEXT: Young Death Master
TEXT: Illustration: Hekiru Hikawa