Sign: Incredible Turn of Events!!!
The end.
Your yukata's a cute pink, Chiri-chan.
Your light blue one's also beautiful.
That's right...
Today is Tanabata...
Teacher.
Your cell phone strap is quite cute, Kisu-san.
Your hair ornament is also pretty.
Shouldn't you comment on  my yukata...
...instead of a call phone strap in this situation?
I understand what you mean.
However...
It can't be helped!
For some reason...
...humans are creatures who are drawn away from the main point!
They focus on the sponsor name on his chest instead of the actual match!
Binbo...?
The position of Takuya Ki****'s 'stache...
...instead of the actual movie!
It's high...
Places really high...
The suspect's unusual name...
...instead of the crime committed!
Sorata...?
Once your attention's been drawn...
...that's all you can think about...
...and you completely forget about the main point!
Consequently...
..."Takuya Ki****'s 'stache was high."
...was all I got out of the movie.
What's with that?
I'm currently reporting live from the scene of the crime.
It looks like something happened in our area.
The suspect is believed to have used this escape route.
Currently available information indicates...
What's!?
With?
That weird...
Shirt?
You focus on...
...the weird shirt in the gallery instead of the actual crime!
What was all the fuss about?
There was a sighting of a young man wearing a weird shirt.
Well...
I'm ashamed to say that it's also happened to me.
You, Kitsu-san?
These are English exercises...
Translate into English.
What is this?
It's bread.
You don't know what that is!?
Shouldn't it be obvious!?
It's bread!
The fact that he doesn't know what bread is...
...is a bigger problem than the problem itself.
Yeah, one of those, huh...
Yes!
People tend to be drawn away from the main point!
I'm in despair!
Our people's tendency to be drawn away from the main point has left me in despair!
Hello.
It's true that I also once founf myself drawn away from the main point.
Kobushi-san.
There was a tragedy in the neighborhood recently.
At the funeral...
...the mourner's anime voice was all I could think about...
All I could think about...
Even when I knew it was rude...
...it was all I could think about...
I suppose that could happen.
People are prone to letting...
...their attention be drawn away from the main point!
That always happens.
Where your attention's drawn away from the main point.
It's also happened to you?
I can remember it happening.
I was in line at a crępe shop a while back.
That's normal.
Greetings, Earthlings.
We are the backbone of this universe...
The El Ninonians.
We will now commence out invasion of Earth.
Aliens!?
Invade Earth!?
N-No way!
Isn't this a rather sudden turn of events!?
Who are you complaining to?
It's hopeless.
I'm in despair.
Humanity going down without a fight has left me in despair.
A reason to be in despair that other people can agree with for once.
Shouldn't we run away?
There's nowhere to run.
Humanity will be annihilated!
U-Uh...
You're my old friend...
Yes!
Your old friend...
Actually, a few days ago...
...I found this ancient document in a super ancient Jomon ruin.
Wh-What's wrong with you!?
We're busy right now!
I-I see...
This ancient document...
...contains the location of an ultimate weapon from a super ancient civilization.
If we find this ultimate weapon...
...won't we be able to drive the aliens away?
So?
Where is this ultimate weapon?
According to the ancient text...
El Ninonians!
A-ha!
It's right underneath us!
Terribly convenient!
In any case, let's dig!
Adjutant.
Perhaps using the giant robot for the invasion of this planet was overkill?
There is a saying on this planet...
...that even lions use all their strength when trying to catch rabbits.
Shall we observe the terrified rabbits?
As you wish.
You're pretty impressive...
Wanna join out team?
No.
I just came to collect data for a baseball manga.
Stop! Stop!
It's awfully noisy.
I wonder if there's a fire.
It appears that terror has struck many people.
What a carefree bunch!
Sorry.
Did I hurt your feelings?
Hey, Majiru-kun.
Wanna see my swimsuit?
Though I can't replace Manabe.
General!
This isn't the time to be watching!
You're right. I can't.
How could I make such a mistake?
Launch all combat units!
Let's finish them off in one fell swoop!
It's hopeless...
We can't find the ultimate weapon...
...and the enemy's sending more robots...
We have no chance...
We have no chance!
You're so annoying!
You could stop whining...
...and give us a hand.
I found it!
A stone mask?
Is this really the ultimate weapon?
Why don't you try putting it on?
You're right.
Evaporate!
Th-This is it...
This seems pretty crazy...
Either way, I'll just wipe out the enemies!
Erster!
Zweiter!
Proper Sword!
Dritter!
Sh-She's strong!
But why German?
Fart?
Underwear in a Japanese outfit.
How crass.
Bell peppers!?
Why bell peppers?
You wanted to see my swimsuit?
What are you talking about?
Of course not!
Really.
General!
Our robot army...
What!?
Erupting Gold Finger!
How about it?
I'm the true Dynasty Warrior!
I shouldn't have let my attention be drawn away from the main point!
Man...
This episode had an excellent story.
It ruled, Teacher!
A battle that will leave its mark on the history of Earth!
B-By the way...
What is it?
I was so bothered by the "fart" written on the alient robot...
...that I don't remember the main point.
And all I can remember are the peppers on her underwear.
I'm in despair.
You're such a bookworm, Kudou-kun.
I want to read all kinds of books all over the world.
Read all kinds of things?
Do you only read books?
What are you talking about, Teacher?
Read all kinds of things...
You intend to read my heart, don't you!?
To read the pitch-black darkness in my heart...
...and criticize me for my slightly evil thoughts!
I won't let that happen!
You won't read my heart!
For I've sealed off my heart!
I'm not thinking that...
...anime DVDs are really expensive!
So that's what you think...
No way.
Even I...
...can't read other people's hearts.
R-Really?
You should try reading a book, Teacher.
I-Is that so...
In that case...
This looks interesting.
It's been read.
The book I want to read has been read.
This one, too.
And this one!
Every single book I want to read...
...had already been read!
I'm being read...
You've read so many books that...
...it's no wonder you can read other people's hearts.
That's not all...
He can probably read every single thing out there!
Read pitches like Manager Nomura.
Read the green at the Masters.
Read an election...
Read the table...
To be able to read a course Sakura Yokomine's father couldn't...
I'm impressed.
What are you talking about?
To be able to read an election former party leader Okada couldn't...
I'm impressed!
But that doesn't mean...
...you'll have an easy time reading my heart!
That's right...
If I don't think unnecessary thoughts...
...he won't be able to read them.
Don't think about anything...
Clear my mind...
Isn't it early for OOOO Adachi to say she's pregnant after two months?
She only missed it once then.
Did she say two months so nobody would suspect AOOOOO?
Shoot!
Did you just read what I was thinking!?
You did, didn't you!?
I can no longer live!
Teacher.
If you don't want him to read your heart...
...I have a good idea.
And what would that be?
He can't read your heart if you don't have one.
You just have to become a heartless person.
What would qualify as a heartless person?
Someone who litters around town...
Or wrecks sand castles made by little kids...
Or tricks elderly people and installs lost of ventilation fans under the floor...
Or breaks flood gates.
Or raises disaster relief money in frong of the station and embezzles it...
Please don't arbitrarily use me as an example!
Aren't there any better heartless activities?
But they're supposed to be heartless.
Heartless...
"The Heartless King."
Yes?
Long ago, there was a kingdom...
...with a king who wanted everything.
He would buy...
...everything he wanted around the world with money.
The king would say...
"There is nothing I do not possess."
One day...
...a travelling merchant appeared and said...
"Forgive me...
...but there is something Your Majesty does not possess.
That would be a human heart."
The king used his body to protect the child from the demon kidnapper.
"Thank you!
Thank you, Your Majesty!"
That was when...
...the king finally attained a human heart.
In exchange for his life...
It was only for a bried moment in his long life...
...but the king attained a heart...
...and was happy.
What was that!?
What just happened!?
Kudou-kun is a natural-born storyteller...
...who can tell a fairy tale about any subject.
A cell phone...
"Disposable Celly."
Hiroshi-kun bought a cell phone shaped like a person.
Hiroshi-kun abused the cell phone.
But the cell phone had a limited number of charges.
In no time...
...there was only one charge left on the phone.
That was when a murder happened.
"Hurry and call the police!"
"But if I call, then you'll..."
"Don't worry about me!
Make the call!"
"The Raccoon's Tail Rental Store."
"The Mouse's Lawsuit."
Mousey!
"The Proper Amoeba."
Hello.
"The Transparent Wig."
A jellyfish was being bullied.
The gentleman negotiated with the children...
...and saved the jellyfish.
"Thank you so much!
I want to show my gratitude.
Is there anything you want?"
The jellyfish asked.
"Let's see...
I suppose I want a wig right now."
"Then I'll become your wig."
Wig!?
"I appreciate the sentiment...
...but my scalp is visible through your transparent body.
It's the thought that counts."
And with that, the gentleman left.
But the jellyfish wouldn't accept that.
Jelly the Jellyfish...
...wanted to become his wig...
...so it drowned itself in a giant squid's ink!
How gallant!
I want to meet a girl like Jelly!
To be able to touch so many hearts...
Kudou-kun must be able to read hearts.
Read all kinds of things!
I won't let you read my heart!
I'll flit from thought to thought...
...and achieve an empty mind!
You just read the ending of this story, didn't you!?
I won't let that happen!
I'll make it an ending you'll never read!
And ending you'll never read!
I'm sick of all the penguins!
So...
He did this so the ending couldn't be read?
Didn't see it coming, right?
What kind of ending is this?
It's not an ending.
I happened to run into Abiru-san today.
A wind blew...
...and flipped Abiru-san's skirt.
I gently told her that I didn't see anything.
Her embarassed reaction was quite cute.
Then we took a walk together.
That's what I'll put in my diary.
For when you're feeling down...
Despair Herbal Medicine.
Big sis Komori.
Big sis Komori...
Oh, Majiru-kun.
I didn't see anything.
I fell asleep this early?
I yelled really loudly before I came in.
I see.
But what brings you to my place?
This just came.
Yay.
It came.
What did you order?
Hold on for a bit.
Ta-da!
It's a swimsuit.
See.
Isn't it cute?
You never go outside.
You won't be going to the pool or beach.
I still wanna wear a swimsuit.
I'm gunna change so don't peek.
Like I would.
Majiru-kun.
What is it?
You just peeked, didn't you?
L-Like I'd wanna look at your childish body.
That's right.
You're not interested in me.
Majiru-kun prefers women like Manabe.
Twitch.
Stupid Manabe...
I don't care about her.
Besides, what's with the Kirin guy!?
You never mentioned him on your blog!
Majiru-kun...
Sorry.
Did I hurt your feelings?
Hey, Majiru-kun.
Wanna see my swimsuit?
Though I can't replace Manabe.
Just kidding.
What are you doing?
Confiscated!
Look, Majiru-kun.
It's Kiri in a swimsuit.
Look, look!
Look, look.
This one might be a little old.
Did I put on some weight?
You can't see?
I can't see.
Really.
Too bad.
Cheeky boy.
These are actually prescription glasses.
Give them back!
No.
If I give them back now...
...you'll be able to see everything.
Are you mad?
Not really.
Hey, Majiru-kun.
I'll tell you something good.
Well...
Red bean bread...
...comes in whole bean and bean paste varieties.
There's a big difference.
Who cares about that?
There's a tokusatsu on at this hour?
This actress looks like Chiri-chan.
Hey, Majiru-kun.
I have a question.
Do you like your melon bread with a hard shell or soft shell?
Seriously, stop asking pointless questions!
You're purposely talking about stuff nobody cares about, aren't you?
Like how to eat a chocolate coronet!
Nobody gives a damn!
Just maybe...
You wanted to see my swimsuit?
Wh-What are you talking about?
Of course not!
Really.
Which way am I facing?
This way?
No, maybe not.
This way!
You're facing this way!
Wrong.
I'm facing the other way.
That was cheap.
Wanna go again?
Forget it.
I can't put up with this.
Really.
What a pointless story.
It's not the main story...
...so I guess it can't be helped.
But if this story were to be more popular than usual...
...it would invalidate everything we've been doing.
Man...
This episode had an excellent story.
It ruled, Teacher!
So everybody prefers a pointless story!
So they liked it.
The Restaurant with Many Condolence Calls.
Restaurant Puffer Fish House.
"This restaurant has many condolence calls so please keep that in mind."
So the decease chef had many friends while he was alive?
No, we're selling puffer fish without a license...
...so it's not that we reveive many condolence calls...
...rather, we have to make condolence calls to all the customers who've died.
"Wah!"
Tremble. Tremble. Tremble.
The two began to cry.
"Bury yourself in the sand to counter the poison.
We can't wait 15 minutes for the ambulance."