Sign-middle-right: Tanabata
Sign-right: Tanabata
Sign-top-left: Here
Sign-right: Ginza Shopping District
Sign-top: Suspect
Sign-bottom: Sorata Ooki (36)
Sign-top-right: Tanabata
Sign-middle: For DTTV
Sign-middle-lower: Cybernetic TV
Sign: Delicious!!
Sign: Gloom
Sign-top-left: Absolutely Positive Concert
Sign-top-right: Tanabata
Sign: Hello
--FULLSCREEN-MULTILINE SIGN START--
The suspect's wig instead of the crime itself
The female astronaut's mustached husband instead of the female astronaut
Eoozo's Kabuki escapades in real life instead of his Kabuki acting skills
Anime opening song's Oricon ranking instead of the anime itself
The handkerchief instead of baseball
Shy instead of golf
Mascot character instead of the disaster it represents
Beooham's oddly hight-pitched voice instead of his face
The price of gasoline at the station ooya Yagioo worked at instead instead of movie's actual story
The newspaper wrapping around the box lunch she made for you instead of the lunch itself...
The country that cares more about beating Japan instead of the global image
Johony's instead of volleyball
The woman in the audience glaring at the froom instead of the actual wedding ceremony
--FULLSCREEN-MULTILINE SIGN END--
--SCROLLING SIGN START--
Original Work Kohji Kumeta "Sayonara Zetsubou Sensei" (Serialized in Kodansha "Weekly Shounen Magazine") Series Organization
· Dramatization Yuichiro Ogura Overall Key Animation Supervisor Character Design Hideyuki Morioka Art Directory Hirotsugu Kakoi
Color Key Izumi Takizawa Visual Effects Motoki Sakai Director of Photography Satoru Egami Editor Kazuhiko Seki Overall Key
Animation Supervisor Hiroki Yamamura Assistant Director Naoyuki Tatsuwa Chief Direction Yukihiro Miyamoto Sound Director Toshiki
Kameyama Music Tomoki Hasegawa Music Production Starchild Records Producer Atsushi Moriyama Animation Producer Mitsutoshi Kubota
Director Akiyuki Shinbo
--SCROLLING SIGN END--
Sign: [Zoku·] Sayonara Zetsubou Sensei
Sign: So Long Mr. Despair Extreme
Sign: Break
Sign: down
Sign: the wall
Sign: with
Sign: good
Sign: posture.
Sign: An Artist by the Roadside
Sign: Ancient Japanese Legends
Sign: Omitted
Sign: Fart
Sign: Over 1000 Kills
Sign: In the year 1976
Sign: we moved to Sannomiya Center City.
Sign: I suggested a number of store names to my father
Sign: but he didn't like any of them.
Sign: When I tried flipping my father's name around
Sign: and he decided to go with that.
Sign: I Have Mostly Read Shameful Books
--FULLSCREEN-MULTILINE SIGN START--
From Elbow to Knee
Evening Primrose on Fuji is a Mistake
Fly Past That Country
Leap Before You Look
What an Incredible Bother
An Arist by the Roadside
The Faux Pas of Baron Munchausen
Adornment at Tiffany's
Duty and Soldiers
I Have Mostly Read Shameful Books
Rouse Up, O Old Men of the Old Age
Forelocks Yet to Be Opened
Seventeen Year Old Don't You Want to Grab Your Wrinkles?
Raw Yatsuhashi Dough must be Baked
I am Fated to be an Outcast
Removing Toxins and Stains
White at the End of the Tunnel
Confessions of a Mask
--FULLSCREEN-MULTILINE SIGN END--
Sign: Rainy Days
Sign-left: Biographies
Sign-top: Topographies
Sign: How-to Books
Sign: Books
Sign-left: Hobbies
Sign-middle: How-to Books
Sign-middle-left: How-to Books
Sign-middle-right: Lifestyle
Sign-right: Arts
Sign-top-left: Mataro gets away?
Sign-left: Hobbies
Sign-middle-left: How-to Books
Sign-middle-right: Lifestyle
Sign-right: Performing Arts
Sign-far-right: Medic
Sign: I-Is that so?
Sign: In that case...
Sign-top: Ruu of the Lizard Forest by Aio Hiiragi
Sign-middle: Jun Kudou
Sign-left: Law
Sign-middle-left: Economics
Sign-middle: Finance
Sign-top: Adventures of the Rabbit Two by Jin Hoshizora
Sign-middle: Jun Mudou
Sign-top: Blazing Battle by Ashura K
Sign-middle: Jun Kudou
Sign-top: Hamburg Red by Aoi Hiirahi
Sign-middle: Seiji Amasawa
Sign-left: Society
Sign-middle: Statistics
Sign-middle-right: Economics
Sign: Baseless Statement
Sign-left: Horie Unconfirmed
Sign-middle-left: Supermarket Manager
Sign-right: Junichiro Ooizumi
Sign-left: Love Story Black
Sign-top: Clear mind
Sign-left: Sorry about using an ancient story
Sign: You did, didn't you
Sign: Alchemy
Sign: "Teacher"
Sign-middle: Holy Texts
Sign-middle-right: Philosophy
Sign-right: Education
Sign-left: Black Magic
Sign-middle: Spiritual World
Sign-right: Philosophy
Sign-far-left: kawa
Sign-middle-left: ShoOOOOkan
Sign-middle: OOdansha
Sign-top-left: 10,000
Sign-left: 10,000
Sign-middle: Donations
Sign-right: 1,000
Sign-top-right: 1,000
Sign-left: Art
Sign-middle-left: Language
Sign-middle: Literature
Sign-middle-right: Philosophy
Sign-right: Gerography
Sign-left: Fairy Tale
Sign-middle: Mystery
Sign-middle-bottom: One Sunny Day
Sign-top: The Heartless King
Sign-bottom: Jun Kudou
Sign: Omitted
Sign-top: It's on the top bookshelf - Tenma
Sign: In Tears
Sign-left: Reference
Sign-middle: Miscellaneous
Sign-right: Essays
Sign-top: Disposable Celly
Sign-bottom: Jun Kudou
Sign: I don't need this!
Sign: It's 5:20
Sign: In Tears
Sign: Phone Telegram
Sign-cellphone: (;_;)(;_;)(;_;)(;_;) Now you've made my eyes sting!! Jerkwad!!
Sign-top: Electronic Magazines
Sign: Omitted
Sign: In Tears
Sign-left: Statues
Sign-right: International Law
Sign: Omitted
Sign: In Tears
Sign-far-left: ational
Sign-middle-left: Economics
Sign-middle-right: Medicine
Sign-right: Finance
Sign: Omit
Sign: ted
Sign: In Tears
Sign-middle: LGAT
Sign-right: Self-
Sign: In Tears
Sign-top-left: Bawl
Sign-left: SOB
Sign-middle-left: BAWL
Sign-middle: TEAR
Sign-middle-right: SNIFF
Sign-right: WAIL
Sign-top: WAIL
Sign-middle: BAWL
Sign-bottom-left: TEAR
Sign-bottom: SNIFF
Sign-bottom-right: SOB
Sign-left: Lengends
Sign-middle: Magic
Sign: Blizzardy You
Sign: Genius Storyteller Jun Kudou Seat #6
Sign: Kageriou Usui's Diary First Storm of Spring
Sign-top: For when you're feeling down
Sign-bottom-left: Despair Pharaceuticals
Sign-bottom-right: Despair Herbal Medicine
Sign: We will not broadcast the uncut version of the "part that wasn't the main story" from episode four, "An Artist by the Roadside"
Sign: Ehime Prefecture
Sign: Type A
Sign: T165
Sign: B84
Sign: W55
Sign: H85
Sign: The Inconspicuous Summer
Sign-top: Goodwill
Sign-top-left: Effort
Sign-middle: Courage
Sign-top-right: Except I did...
Sign-top-left: Spirit
Sign-middle: Guts
Sign-top-right: Did I yell...?
Sign: Tea King
Sign-top-left: Main story occurring elsewhere.
Sign-top-left: Panties...
Sign-left: Main story occurring elsewhere
Sign: GRR
Sign-bottom: Kawori
Sign-top-right: Main story occurring elsewhere
Sign-top-left: Main story occurring elsewhere
Sign-bottom-left: Main story occurring elsewhere
Sign-top: This is the main story
Sign-left: National Zeshiki-warashi Union Meeting
Sign-middle: Pico
Sign-right: Put the cart before the horse
Sign-left: National Zeshiki-warashi Union Meeting
Sign-middle: Pico
Sign-right: Ups and downs
Sign-left: National Zeshiki-warashi Union Meeting
Sign-middle: Pico
Sign-right: Clear Mirror Still Water
Sign-bottom-left: Main story occurring elsewhere
Sign-left: Whole bean
Sign-right: Bean paste
Sign-book-title-1: The Progression of the National Zashiki-warashi Union
Sign-book-title-2: Future Detective Conan 1
Sign-book-title-3: Future Detective Conan 2
Sign-book-title-4: Onion Encyclopedia
Sign-book-title-5: Pat-kun's Secret I
Sign-book-title-6: Pat-kun's Secret II
Sign-book-title-7: How to go SEED
Sign-book-title-8: Labyrinth
Sign-top: Blue Luck
Sign-middle: Really White People
Sign-left: National Zeshiki-warashi Union Meeting
Sign-middle: Pico
Sign-right: Cut and Dried
Sign-bottom-left: Main story occurring elsewhere
Sign-left: National Zeshiki-warashi Union Meeting
Sign-middle: Chico
Sign-right: Fortune weal and woe
Sign-left: National Zeshiki-warashi Union Meeting
Sign-middle: Chico
Sign-right: Shocked and amazed
Sign-book-title-1: The Progression of the National Zashiki-warashi Union
Sign-book-title-2: Future Detective Conan 1
Sign-book-title-3: Future Detective Conan 2
Sign-book-title-4: Onion Encyclopedia
Sign-left: National Zeshiki-warashi Union Meeting
Sign-middle: Chico
Sign-right: Perseverance moves mountains
Sign: Spin
Sign-left: National Zeshiki-warashi Union Meeting
Sign-middle: CoCo
Sign-right: Avici hell
Sign-left: National Zeshiki-warashi Union Meeting
Sign-middle: CoCo
Sign-right: Avici hell
Sign-left: National Zeshiki-warashi Union Meeting
Sign-middle: CoCo
Sign-right: Avici hell
Sign-bottom-left: Main story occurring elsewhere
Sign-top-left: Main Story < Paointless Story
Sign-left: Magazine Survey Results
Sign-top-right: SNIFF
Sign-right: Increase
--ENDING--
Sign: This show is a work of fiction.
Sign: There is no relation to the real invaders, Junkudo, or Kawori Manabe.
Sign-top-left: Despair Literature
Sign-bottom-left: From Volume Four
Sign-rop-right: The Restaurant with Many Condolence Calls
Sign-being-written-top-right: Restaurant
Sign-top: NEXT EPISODE WILL BRING DESPAIR DESTINY APOCALYPSE
Sign-bottom-left: Illustration: Kunihiko Ikuhara