Your yukata's a cute pink, Chiri-chan.
Your light blue one's also beautiful.
That's right...
Today is Tanabata...
Teacher.
Sign-middle-right: Tanabata
Sign-right: Tanabata
Your cell phone strap is quite cute, Kisu-san.
Sign-top-left: Here
Sign-right: Tanabata
Your hair ornament is also pretty.
Shouldn't you comment on  my yukata...
...instead of a call phone strap in this situation?
Sign-right: Ginza Shopping District
I understand what you mean.
However...
It can't be helped!
For some reason...
...humans are creatures who are drawn away from the main point!
They focus on the sponsor name on his chest instead of the actual match!
TV Announcer: The defenders can't catch up!
TV Announcer: Here comes the shot!
Binbo...?
The position of Takuya Ki****'s 'stache...
...instead of the actual movie!
It's high...
Places really high...
Sign-top: Suspect
Sign-bottom: Sorata Ooki (36)
The suspect's unusual name...
...instead of the crime committed!
Sorata...?
Sign-top-right: Tanabata
Once your attention's been drawn...
...that's all you can think about...
...and you completely forget about the main point!
Consequently...
..."Takuya Ki****'s 'stache was high."
...was all I got out of the movie.
What's with that?
Sign-middle: For DTTV
Sign-middle-lower: Cybernetic TV
I'm currently reporting live from the scene of the crime.
It looks like something happened in our area.
The suspect is believed to have used this escape route.
Currently available information indicates...
What's!?
Sign: Delicious!!
Sign: Gloom
With?
Sign-top-left: Absolutely Positive Concert
That weird...
Shirt?
You focus on...
...the weird shirt in the gallery instead of the actual crime!
Sign-top-right: Tanabata
What was all the fuss about?
There was a sighting of a young man wearing a weird shirt.
Well...
I'm ashamed to say that it's also happened to me.
You, Kitsu-san?
These are English exercises...
Translate into English.
What is this?
It's bread.
You don't know what that is!?
Shouldn't it be obvious!?
It's bread!
The fact that he doesn't know what bread is...
...is a bigger problem than the problem itself.
Yeah, one of those, huh...
Yes!
People tend to be drawn away from the main point!
I'm in despair!
Our people's tendency to be drawn away from the main point has left me in despair!
Sign: Hello
Hello.
It's true that I also once founf myself drawn away from the main point.
Kobushi-san.
There was a tragedy in the neighborhood recently.
At the funeral...
...the mourner's anime voice was all I could think about...
All I could think about...
Even when I knew it was rude...
...it was all I could think about...
I suppose that could happen.
People are prone to letting...
...their attention be drawn away from the main point!
--FULLSCREEN-MULTILINE SIGN START--
The suspect's wig instead of the crime itself
The female astronaut's mustached husband instead of the female astronaut
Eoozo's Kabuki escapades in real life instead of his Kabuki acting skills
Anime opening song's Oricon ranking instead of the anime itself
The handkerchief instead of baseball
Shy instead of golf
Mascot character instead of the disaster it represents
Beooham's oddly hight-pitched voice instead of his face
The price of gasoline at the station ooya Yagioo worked at instead instead of movie's actual story
The newspaper wrapping around the box lunch she made for you instead of the lunch itself...
The country that cares more about beating Japan instead of the global image
Johony's instead of volleyball
The woman in the audience glaring at the froom instead of the actual wedding ceremony
--FULLSCREEN-MULTILINE SIGN END--
That always happens.
Where your attention's drawn away from the main point.
--SCROLLING SIGN START--
Original Work Kohji Kumeta "Sayonara Zetsubou Sensei" (Serialized in Kodansha "Weekly Shounen Magazine") Series Organization
· Dramatization Yuichiro Ogura Overall Key Animation Supervisor Character Design Hideyuki Morioka Art Directory Hirotsugu Kakoi
Color Key Izumi Takizawa Visual Effects Motoki Sakai Director of Photography Satoru Egami Editor Kazuhiko Seki Overall Key
Animation Supervisor Hiroki Yamamura Assistant Director Naoyuki Tatsuwa Chief Direction Yukihiro Miyamoto Sound Director Toshiki
Kameyama Music Tomoki Hasegawa Music Production Starchild Records Producer Atsushi Moriyama Animation Producer Mitsutoshi Kubota
Director Akiyuki Shinbo
--SCROLLING SIGN END--
It's also happened to you?
I can remember it happening.
I was in line at a crępe shop a while back.
That's normal.
Sign: [Zoku·] Sayonara Zetsubou Sensei
Sign: So Long Mr. Despair Extreme
Sign: Break
Sign: down
Sign: the wall
Sign: with
Sign: good
Sign: posture.
Sign: An Artist by the Roadside
Greetings, Earthlings.
We are the backbone of this universe...
The El Ninonians.
We will now commence out invasion of Earth.
Aliens!?
Invade Earth!?
N-No way!
Sign: Incredible Turn of Events!!!
Isn't this a rather sudden turn of events!?
Who are you complaining to?
It's hopeless.
I'm in despair.
Humanity going down without a fight has left me in despair.
A reason to be in despair that other people can agree with for once.
Shouldn't we run away?
There's nowhere to run.
Humanity will be annihilated!
U-Uh...
You're my old friend...
Yes!
Your old friend...
Sign: Ancient Japanese Legends
Actually, a few days ago...
...I found this ancient document in a super ancient Jomon ruin.
Wh-What's wrong with you!?
We're busy right now!
Sign: Omitted
I-I see...
This ancient document...
...contains the location of an ultimate weapon from a super ancient civilization.
If we find this ultimate weapon...
...won't we be able to drive the aliens away?
So?
Where is this ultimate weapon?
According to the ancient text...
El Ninonians!
A-ha!
It's right underneath us!
Terribly convenient!
In any case, let's dig!
Adjutant.
Perhaps using the giant robot for the invasion of this planet was overkill?
There is a saying on this planet...
...that even lions use all their strength when trying to catch rabbits.
Shall we observe the terrified rabbits?
As you wish.
You're pretty impressive...
Wanna join out team?
No.
I just came to collect data for a baseball manga.
Stop! Stop!
It's awfully noisy.
I wonder if there's a fire.
It appears that terror has struck many people.
What a carefree bunch!
Sorry.
Did I hurt your feelings?
Hey, Majiru-kun.
Wanna see my swimsuit?
Though I can't replace Manabe.
General!
This isn't the time to be watching!
You're right. I can't.
How could I make such a mistake?
Launch all combat units!
Let's finish them off in one fell swoop!
It's hopeless...
We can't find the ultimate weapon...
...and the enemy's sending more robots...
We have no chance...
We have no chance!
You're so annoying!
You could stop whining...
...and give us a hand.
I found it!
A stone mask?
Is this really the ultimate weapon?
Why don't you try putting it on?
You're right.
Evaporate!
Th-This is it...
This seems pretty crazy...
Either way, I'll just wipe out the enemies!
Erster!
Zweiter!
Proper Sword!
Dritter!
Sh-She's strong!
But why German?
Sign: Fart
Fart?
Underwear in a Japanese outfit.
How crass.
Bell peppers!?
Why bell peppers?
You wanted to see my swimsuit?
What are you talking about?
Of course not!
Really.
General!
Our robot army...
What!?
Erupting Gold Finger!
Sign: Over 1000 Kills
How about it?
I'm the true Dynasty Warrior!
I shouldn't have let my attention be drawn away from the main point!
Man...
This episode had an excellent story.
It ruled, Teacher!
A battle that will leave its mark on the history of Earth!
B-By the way...
What is it?
I was so bothered by the "fart" written on the alient robot...
...that I don't remember the main point.
And all I can remember are the peppers on her underwear.
I'm in despair.
Sign: In the year 1976
Sign: we moved to Sannomiya Center City.
Sign: I suggested a number of store names to my father
Sign: but he didn't like any of them.
Sign: When I tried flipping my father's name around
Sign: and he decided to go with that.
Sign: I Have Mostly Read Shameful Books
--FULLSCREEN-MULTILINE SIGN START--
From Elbow to Knee
Evening Primrose on Fuji is a Mistake
Fly Past That Country
Leap Before You Look
What an Incredible Bother
An Arist by the Roadside
The Faux Pas of Baron Munchausen
Adornment at Tiffany's
Duty and Soldiers
I Have Mostly Read Shameful Books
Rouse Up, O Old Men of the Old Age
Forelocks Yet to Be Opened
Seventeen Year Old Don't You Want to Grab Your Wrinkles?
Raw Yatsuhashi Dough must be Baked
I am Fated to be an Outcast
Removing Toxins and Stains
White at the End of the Tunnel
Confessions of a Mask
--FULLSCREEN-MULTILINE SIGN END--
Sign: Rainy Days
Sign-left: Biographies
Sign-top: Topographies
You're such a bookworm, Kudou-kun.
I want to read all kinds of books all over the world.
Sign: How-to Books
Read all kinds of things?
Do you only read books?
Sign: Books
Sign-left: Hobbies
Sign-middle: How-to Books
What are you talking about, Teacher?
Read all kinds of things...
You intend to read my heart, don't you!?
To read the pitch-black darkness in my heart...
...and criticize me for my slightly evil thoughts!
Sign-left: Hobbies
Sign-middle-left: How-to Books
Sign-middle-right: Lifestyle
Sign-right: Arts
I won't let that happen!
You won't read my heart!
For I've sealed off my heart!
Sign-top-left: Mataro gets away?
I'm not thinking that...
...anime DVDs are really expensive!
Sign-left: Hobbies
Sign-middle-left: How-to Books
Sign-middle-right: Lifestyle
Sign-right: Performing Arts
Sign-far-right: Medic
So that's what you think...
No way.
Even I...
...can't read other people's hearts.
R-Really?
You should try reading a book, Teacher.
Sign: I-Is that so?
Sign: In that case...
I-Is that so...
In that case...
This looks interesting.
Sign-top: Ruu of the Lizard Forest by Aio Hiiragi
Sign-middle: Jun Kudou
It's been read.
Sign-left: Law
Sign-middle-left: Economics
Sign-middle: Finance
The book I want to read has been read.
Sign-top: Adventures of the Rabbit Two by Jin Hoshizora
Sign-middle: Jun Mudou
This one, too.
Sign-top: Blazing Battle by Ashura K
Sign-middle: Jun Kudou
And this one!
Sign-top: Hamburg Red by Aoi Hiirahi
Sign-middle: Jun Kudou
Sign-middle: Seiji Amasawa
And this one!
Every single book I want to read...
...had already been read!
Sign-left: Society
Sign-middle: Statistics
Sign-middle-right: Economics
I'm being read...
You've read so many books that...
...it's no wonder you can read other people's hearts.
Sign: Baseless Statement
That's not all...
He can probably read every single thing out there!
Read pitches like Manager Nomura.
Read the green at the Masters.
Sign-left: Horie Unconfirmed
Sign-middle-left: Supermarket Manager
Sign-right: Junichiro Ooizumi
Read an election...
Read the table...
To be able to read a course Sakura Yokomine's father couldn't...
I'm impressed.
What are you talking about?
To be able to read an election former party leader Okada couldn't...
I'm impressed!
Sign-left: Love Story Black
But that doesn't mean...
...you'll have an easy time reading my heart!
That's right...
If I don't think unnecessary thoughts...
...he won't be able to read them.
Don't think about anything...
Clear my mind...
Sign-top: Clear mind
Sign-left: Sorry about using an ancient story
Isn't it early for OOOO Adachi to say she's pregnant after two months?
She only missed it once then.
Did she say two months so nobody would suspect AOOOOO?
Shoot!
Did you just read what I was thinking!?
Sign: You did, didn't you
You did, didn't you!?
I can no longer live!
Sign: Alchemy
Sign: "Teacher"
Teacher.
Sign-middle: Holy Texts
Sign-middle-right: Philosophy
Sign-right: Education
If you don't want him to read your heart...
...I have a good idea.
Sign-left: Black Magic
Sign-middle: Spiritual World
Sign-right: Philosophy
And what would that be?
He can't read your heart if you don't have one.
You just have to become a heartless person.
Sign-far-left: kawa
Sign-middle-left: ShoOOOOkan
Sign-middle: OOdansha
What would qualify as a heartless person?
Someone who litters around town...
Or wrecks sand castles made by little kids...
Or tricks elderly people and installs lost of ventilation fans under the floor...
Or breaks flood gates.
Sign-top-left: 10,000
Sign-left: 10,000
Sign-middle: Donations
Sign-right: 1,000
Sign-top-right: 1,000
Or raises disaster relief money in frong of the station and embezzles it...
Please don't arbitrarily use me as an example!
Sign-left: Art
Sign-middle-left: Language
Sign-middle: Literature
Sign-middle-right: Philosophy
Sign-right: Gerography
Aren't there any better heartless activities?
But they're supposed to be heartless.
Sign-left: Fairy Tale
Sign-middle: Mystery
Sign-middle-bottom: One Sunny Day
Heartless...
"The Heartless King."
Yes?
Sign-top: The Heartless King
Sign-bottom: Jun Kudou
Long ago, there was a kingdom...
...with a king who wanted everything.
He would buy...
...everything he wanted around the world with money.
The king would say...
"There is nothing I do not possess."
One day...
...a travelling merchant appeared and said...
"Forgive me...
...but there is something Your Majesty does not possess.
That would be a human heart."
Sign: Omitted
The king used his body to protect the child from the demon kidnapper.
"Thank you!
Thank you, Your Majesty!"
That was when...
...the king finally attained a human heart.
In exchange for his life...
It was only for a bried moment in his long life...
...but the king attained a heart...
...and was happy.
Sign-top: It's on the top bookshelf - Tenma
The end.
Sign: In Tears
Sign-left: Reference
Sign-middle: Miscellaneous
Sign-right: Essays
What was that!?
What just happened!?
Kudou-kun is a natural-born storyteller...
...who can tell a fairy tale about any subject.
A cell phone...
"Disposable Celly."
Sign-top: Disposable Celly
Sign-bottom: Jun Kudou
Sign: I don't need this!
Hiroshi-kun bought a cell phone shaped like a person.
Sign: It's 5:20
Hiroshi-kun abused the cell phone.
But the cell phone had a limited number of charges.
In no time...
...there was only one charge left on the phone.
That was when a murder happened.
"Hurry and call the police!"
"But if I call, then you'll..."
"Don't worry about me!
Make the call!"
Sign: In Tears
Sign: Phone Telegram
Sign-cellphone: (;_;)(;_;)(;_;)(;_;) Now you've made my eyes sting!! Jerkwad!!
Sign-top: Electronic Magazines
"The Raccoon's Tail Rental Store."
Sign: Omitted
Sign: In Tears
Sign-left: Statues
Sign-right: International Law
"The Mouse's Lawsuit."
Sign: Omitted
Sign: In Tears
Sign-far-left: ational
Sign-middle-left: Economics
Sign-middle-right: Medicine
Sign-right: Finance
Mousey!
"The Proper Amoeba."
Sign: Omit
Sign: ted
Sign: In Tears
Sign-middle: LGAT
Sign-right: Self-
Hello.
"The Transparent Wig."
A jellyfish was being bullied.
The gentleman negotiated with the children...
...and saved the jellyfish.
"Thank you so much!
I want to show my gratitude.
Is there anything you want?"
The jellyfish asked.
"Let's see...
I suppose I want a wig right now."
"Then I'll become your wig."
Wig!?
"I appreciate the sentiment...
...but my scalp is visible through your transparent body.
It's the thought that counts."
And with that, the gentleman left.
But the jellyfish wouldn't accept that.
Sign: In Tears
Sign-top-left: Bawl
Jelly the Jellyfish...
...wanted to become his wig...
...so it drowned itself in a giant squid's ink!
How gallant!
I want to meet a girl like Jelly!
Sign-left: SOB
Sign-middle-left: BAWL
Sign-middle: TEAR
Sign-middle-right: SNIFF
Sign-right: WAIL
Sign-top: WAIL
Sign-middle: BAWL
Sign-bottom-left: TEAR
Sign-bottom: SNIFF
Sign-bottom-right: SOB
Sign-left: Lengends
Sign-middle: Magic
To be able to touch so many hearts...
Kudou-kun must be able to read hearts.
Read all kinds of things!
I won't let you read my heart!
I'll flit from thought to thought...
...and achieve an empty mind!
Sign: Blizzardy You
You just read the ending of this story, didn't you!?
I won't let that happen!
I'll make it an ending you'll never read!
And ending you'll never read!
I'm sick of all the penguins!
So...
He did this so the ending couldn't be read?
Didn't see it coming, right?
What kind of ending is this?
It's not an ending.
Sign: Genius Storyteller Jun Kudou Seat #6
Sign: Kageriou Usui's Diary First Storm of Spring
I happened to run into Abiru-san today.
A wind blew...
...and flipped Abiru-san's skirt.
I gently told her that I didn't see anything.
Her embarassed reaction was quite cute.
Then we took a walk together.
That's what I'll put in my diary.
Sign-top: For when you're feeling down
Sign-bottom-left: Despair Pharaceuticals
Sign-bottom-right: Despair Herbal Medicine
For when you're feeling down...
Despair Herbal Medicine.
Sign: We will not broadcast the uncut version of the "part that wasn't the main story" from episode four, "An Artist by the Roadside"
Big sis Komori.
Big sis Komori...
Sign: Ehime Prefecture
Sign: Type A
Sign: T165
Sign: B84
Sign: W55
Sign: H85
Sign: The Inconspicuous Summer
Sign-top: Goodwill
Oh, Majiru-kun.
Sign-top-left: Effort
Sign-middle: Courage
Sign-top-right: Except I did...
I didn't see anything.
Sign-top-left: Spirit
Sign-middle: Guts
Sign-top-right: Did I yell...?
I fell asleep this early?
I yelled really loudly before I came in.
I see.
But what brings you to my place?
Sign: Tea King
This just came.
Yay.
It came.
What did you order?
Hold on for a bit.
Ta-da!
It's a swimsuit.
See.
Isn't it cute?
Sign-top-left: Main story occurring elsewhere.
You never go outside.
You won't be going to the pool or beach.
I still wanna wear a swimsuit.
I'm gunna change so don't peek.
Sign-top-left: Panties...
Like I would.
Sign-left: Main story occurring elsewhere
Majiru-kun.
What is it?
Sign-left: Main story occurring elsewhere
You just peeked, didn't you?
L-Like I'd wanna look at your childish body.
Sign: GRR
That's right.
You're not interested in me.
Majiru-kun prefers women like Manabe.
Twitch.
Stupid Manabe...
Sign-bottom: Kawori
I don't care about her.
Besides, what's with the Kirin guy!?
You never mentioned him on your blog!
Majiru-kun...
Sign-top-right: Main story occurring elsewhere
Sorry.
Did I hurt your feelings?
Hey, Majiru-kun.
Wanna see my swimsuit?
Though I can't replace Manabe.
Just kidding.
What are you doing?
Confiscated!
Look, Majiru-kun.
It's Kiri in a swimsuit.
Look, look!
Look, look.
This one might be a little old.
Did I put on some weight?
Sign-top-left: Main story occurring elsewhere
You can't see?
I can't see.
Really.
Too bad.
Cheeky boy.
Sign-bottom-left: Main story occurring elsewhere
These are actually prescription glasses.
Give them back!
No.
If I give them back now...
...you'll be able to see everything.
Sign-top: This is the main story
Sign-left: National Zeshiki-warashi Union Meeting
Sign-middle: Pico
Sign-right: Put the cart before the horse
Are you mad?
Not really.
Sign-left: National Zeshiki-warashi Union Meeting
Sign-middle: Pico
Sign-right: Ups and downs
Hey, Majiru-kun.
I'll tell you something good.
Sign-left: National Zeshiki-warashi Union Meeting
Sign-middle: Pico
Sign-right: Clear Mirror Still Water
Well...
Red bean bread...
Sign-bottom-left: Main story occurring elsewhere
...comes in whole bean and bean paste varieties.
Sign-left: Whole bean
Sign-right: Bean paste
There's a big difference.
Who cares about that?
Sign-book-title-1: The Progression of the National Zashiki-warashi Union
Sign-book-title-2: Future Detective Conan 1
Sign-book-title-3: Future Detective Conan 2
Sign-book-title-4: Onion Encyclopedia
Sign-book-title-5: Pat-kun's Secret I
Sign-book-title-6: Pat-kun's Secret II
Sign-book-title-7: How to go SEED
Sign-book-title-8: Labyrinth
There's a tokusatsu on at this hour?
TV: Erster!
Sign-top: Blue Luck
Sign-middle: Really White People
This actress looks like Chiri-chan.
Sign-left: National Zeshiki-warashi Union Meeting
Sign-middle: Pico
Sign-right: Cut and Dried
Hey, Majiru-kun.
I have a question.
Do you like your melon bread with a hard shell or soft shell?
Seriously, stop asking pointless questions!
You're purposely talking about stuff nobody cares about, aren't you?
Sign-bottom-left: Main story occurring elsewhere
Like how to eat a chocolate coronet!
Nobody gives a damn!
Sign-left: National Zeshiki-warashi Union Meeting
Sign-middle: Chico
Sign-right: Fortune weal and woe
Just maybe...
You wanted to see my swimsuit?
Sign-left: National Zeshiki-warashi Union Meeting
Sign-middle: Chico
Sign-right: Shocked and amazed
Wh-What are you talking about?
Of course not!
Sign-book-title-1: The Progression of the National Zashiki-warashi Union
Sign-book-title-2: Future Detective Conan 1
Sign-book-title-3: Future Detective Conan 2
Sign-book-title-4: Onion Encyclopedia
Really.
Sign-left: National Zeshiki-warashi Union Meeting
Sign-middle: Chico
Sign-right: Perseverance moves mountains
Sign: Spin
Which way am I facing?
Sign-left: National Zeshiki-warashi Union Meeting
Sign-middle: CoCo
Sign-right: Avici hell
This way?
Sign-left: National Zeshiki-warashi Union Meeting
Sign-middle: CoCo
Sign-right: Avici hell
No, maybe not.
Sign-left: National Zeshiki-warashi Union Meeting
Sign-middle: CoCo
Sign-right: Avici hell
This way!
You're facing this way!
Wrong.
I'm facing the other way.
That was cheap.
Wanna go again?
Forget it.
I can't put up with this.
Really.
What a pointless story.
It's not the main story...
...so I guess it can't be helped.
But if this story were to be more popular than usual...
...it would invalidate everything we've been doing.
Sign-bottom-left: Main story occurring elsewhere
Man...
This episode had an excellent story.
It ruled, Teacher!
Sign-top-left: Main Story < Paointless Story
Sign-left: Magazine Survey Results
Sign-top-right: SNIFF
Sign-right: Increase
So everybody prefers a pointless story!
So they liked it.
--ENDING--
Sign: This show is a work of fiction.
Sign: There is no relation to the real invaders, Junkudo, or Kawori Manabe.
Sign-top-left: Despair Literature
Sign-bottom-left: From Volume Four
Sign-rop-right: The Restaurant with Many Condolence Calls
The Restaurant with Many Condolence Calls.
Restaurant Puffer Fish House.
Sign-being-written-top-right: Restaurant
"This restaurant has many condolence calls so please keep that in mind."
So the decease chef had many friends while he was alive?
No, we're selling puffer fish without a license...
...so it's not that we reveive many condolence calls...
...rather, we have to make condolence calls to all the customers who've died.
"Wah!"
Tremble. Tremble. Tremble.
The two began to cry.
"Bury yourself in the sand to counter the poison.
We can't wait 15 minutes for the ambulance."
Sign-top: NEXT EPISODE WILL BRING DESPAIR DESTINY APOCALYPSE
Sign-bottom-left: Illustration: Kunihiko Ikuhara