My child,
listen carefully.
The story I'm about to tell is very important.
It is the story of a long, long journey,
a story that will be passed down from parent to child forever, starting now.
I'm hungry.
Argh, I'm hungry!
That's all you've been saying.
You're so slow. Walk faster.
Hey, you guys!
Do you know of the menu item, "Ramen Set"?
I'm absolutely starving right now.
There's nothing I want more than to eat a Ramen Set.
But...
But, unfortunately, I'm broke. So...
Come! It's time for a fun puppet show.
You can pay me afterwards.
What do you think?
Isn't it great?
Isn't it interesting?
Isn't it fun?
What the hell is this?!
What a filthy doll!
Uncool.
Can't it do anything else?
Hey! Hey!
Kids are best when they're honest.
You can pay me as much as you want, okay?
That's why we're telling you honestly it's not cool.
Why should we pay for something like this?
Are you stupid?
Listen, you guys!
Take that!
Run!
Wait, you guys!
It's so hot...
Surely
R-R-Ramen set!
Episode 1
Hello!
Who is this girl?
Are you alone?
It's hot, isn't it?
What?!
What does she want?
Money?
I have no money.
Aren't you thirsty?
I'll buy you a drink.
Here!
You fell.
g-gao~
TL NOTE ABOUT GAO
Gooey Concentrated Peach Nectar
Why did you do that?
You're teasing me, aren't you?
That's not true.
This drink is delicious.
Do you want to go to the beach?
Why?
Because I want to play.
Huh?
Yesterday, the little kids were playing on the beach.
Whilst I sat next to you as you slept, I kept thinking it looked fun, and I wanted to play too.
You were watching me?
You've been sleeping there since yesterday, right?
I poked you to try and wake you up, but you didn't wake up.
I was so hungry, I couldn't move.
Where are you going?
To work.
Work?
What kind of work?
A puppet show.
Huh?
It's gone!
Is it that important?
I need it for work.
It's hot, isn't it?
It's alright. Just go on home.
There it is!
Crow! Crow!
No! It's the other thing!
Aren't you glad?
Yeah, I am. It's all thanks to you.
Now you can play with me, right?
What do you want?
Huh?
Why have you been following me all this time?
Like I said, we're going to play on the beach.
We're going to race and splash water at each other
And when we're finished, we'll say "See you tomorrow!" and go our separate ways.
That sounds almost like we're friends.
Yes, friends.
We're friends.
So you see,
I want to play.
We don't even know each other's names yet.
I'm Misuzu Kamio.
What's yours?
Yukito Kunisaki...
But listen! I have work to do.
Since I'm hungry, I have to earn some money.
Oh! If that's the case...
I followed her blindly home, lured by the thought of food.
It's nice to eat with someone else, isn't it?
Do you usually eat alone?
Mommy comes home late, and I don't have a daddy.
After you finish eating, let's play, okay?
No way. If it gets late, I'll have trouble finding a place to stay.
You haven't found a place to stay yet?
No. I'll probably end up sleeping outside.
Stay at my house!
Now listen. We just met today.
Mmhm, mmhm.
And you have no idea who on earth I am.
Mmhm.
Who in their right mind would let someone like that stay?
In any case, your mom wouldn't allow it.
Mommy's really lax, so I don't think it'll be a problem.
Though, I guess one shouldn't talk of one's parents like that.
But really, it's okay for you to stay.
I'm tired. I don't have the energy to play.
Then we can play tomorrow.
It's summer vacation, so I have plenty of time.
No way.
g-gao~
Hey, what do you think math is useful for?
Will quadratic functions be useful for me in the future?
How should I know?
Anyway, why am I helping you with your homework?
Hey, your eyes are too close.
Yukito-san, you sound just like Mommy.
Do I?
Mommy's home.
Hey!
She crashed her motorcycle into the shed.
Don't worry. It happens all the time.
Are you really sure it's okay for me to be here?
Yup! I'll persuade her.
Absolutely not!
This is not how you said it would be.
Enough! No discussion!
There's no way we can let a young guy like him stay.
g-gao~
How many times do I have to tell you to stop saying that?
How do you know Misuzu?
CLASSMATE
Uh... I'm her classmate.
Huh? You look a bit old for that.
DON'T FALL FOR ME.
Don't fall for me.
As if I would!
Well, you seem to have guts. I like that about you.
That's right. Yukito-san is a very good person.
I understand.
I'll let him stay.
Seriously?
Seriously? Of course! I'm deadly serious.
But there are two conditions.
You'll sleep in the shed.
And...
You will have a drink with me.
Eh?
And then, in the end, this is what he said...
"Perhaps the one who fell in love was me."
See!
How's that?
I win, right?
So I told him,
"The fish you let escape was a mermaid,"
How's that?
That struck home, right?
How did it end up like this?
Mommy's at her best.
Hey, freeloader. Why are you looking so glum?
Why don't you join in?
My eeeeeyes!
Yukito-san!
Join in?
What do you want me to say?
Anything, like a story of an erotic confession of love or a hidden talent.
I see.
In that case,
Oh, that's the doll from earlier.
Oh!
Wow! That's impressive!
This trick is how I earn a living.
My mother also used to travel with this as her profession.
Does this have a punch line?
No good. You're not funny at all.
But isn't it amazing he's not using any tricks?
Who cares?
Even if it had obvious strings showing, it would be better if it were funny.
Good night.
Ah! He's leaving on his own!
It doesn't really matter that you don't have any talents.
Just down the sorrow with some drinks.
My name's Haruko. Haruko Kamio.
Give me one more glass, missus.
Didn't I tell you my name so that you wouldn't call me that?
Geez! You're such an insensitive guy.
So...
Are you a runaway?
I'm on a journey.
Are you chasing a goal or a dream?
I guess.
You're so young.
Well, compared to you.
You're quite a funny guy.
I am?
I may not look like it, but I have a pretty good eye for judging men.
I can let you stay for a while, but I have a favor to ask.
Can you look after her?
Huh?
You've seen her reckless side, right?
She's impulsive, and once something catches her eye, she'll be attracted to it like a bee to honey.
So I'm a babysitter?
Also, can you stop her saying that phrase?
"Gao!"
It's what she says when she's frustrated or about to cry, right?
Yeah.
It's supposed to sound like a dinosaur.
She loves dinosaurs. She's been saying that since she was little.
She's still just a child.
What are you doing?
Well, I have to take remedial classes.
Has Haruko already left?
Yeah. She leaves early every day.
It's the first time in a while that I've eaten breakfast with someone.
Yukito-san, what are you going to do today?
For now, I'll walk you to school.
Haruko asked me to watch you so that you don't do anything stupid.
She still doesn't trust me at all.
Gao!
I'm done!
It's a map of this town.
That was fast.
It will show you where you people gather together.
It'll be useful for your work, right?
Yeah, it'll help.
Oh, I'm going to be late.
Misuzu-chin is in a pinch!
TL NOTE
I'll come to pick you up after school.
We'll meet here.
Okay!
Waah!
Japanese use
these, right?
Here
I'm
studying.
Munch
Its the ocean! Munch Delicious!
What... is this?
W-what in the world is this?
Is this how she sees the world?
Piko!
What do you want?
Pikopiko!
Are you this town's local legendary creature?
Pikopikopiko!
If he really is, if I do it a favor, then it'll give me something in return
just like in those fairytales.
Pikopikopiko!
Okay, come here.
I'll show you something good.
Piko!
Pikopiko!
Piko! Piko!
What do you think?
Isn't it such a great trick that it makes you feel like giving me something in return?
Piko! Piko! Piko! Piko!
Piko!
Hey!
Pikooo!
Wait!
Piko!
Piko! Piko! Piko!
Pi-P-Pi-Piko!
Piko!
Pikopiko! Pikopiko!
Piko! Piko!
Give me a break, you evil extraterrestial creature.
Piko... Piko.
Piko!
You won't get away!
What are you doing?
A strange extraterrestrial creature stole my doll and ran away.
Piko!
You mean him?
Potato isn't an extraterrestrial creature.
He's a stray dog from my neighborhood.
That's actually a dog?
Piko! Pikopiko!
Huh?
Pikopiko! Pikopikopiko! Piko!
I see...
I'm sorry he caused you so much trouble.
Why are you apologizing?
Well, Potato said that he took your doll and ran here.
Apparently, he wanted to play with you.
Pikopiko!
You can understand what he's saying?
Yes! We're best friends.
Right, Potato?
Pikopiko!
It seems there are worlds here on Earth I know nothing about.
Thanks.
Are you hurt?
Oh, this?
Um, well...
No, I have to keep it a secret.
I'm Kano Kirishima.
You are?
I'm Yukito Kunisaki.
Are you free, by any chance?
I guess.
All right!
I'm naming you Freefreeplanetling Number 2!
Who's Number 1?
Me!
And Potato is Number 3.
Piko!
And what does a Freefreeplanetling do?
They just have time on their hands.
That's the fate of a Freefreeplanetling.
Right? We have nothing to do, do we, Potato?
Pikopiko!
I have to go to school now.
So I'll say good-bye for now.
I thought you were a Freefreeplanetling?
You actually believed that?
You're such a kid!
See you!
Are all the girls who wear that uniform weird?
Hey!
What is it?
Have you ever wondered what you would do if you had magical powers?
Huh?
You look surprised!
See you!
Magic?
Oh, Yukito-san!
How did your work go?
A great success!
Wow, really?
I'm sorry; I lied.
There won't be any business until there are more people.
Why is this place so quiet when people should be returning from work?
Well, this station has been shut down.
You should have told me that earlier.
g-gao~
Ouch!
Why did you hit me?
Haruko told me to scold you when you say that.
Oh, how cute!
Tohno-san?
You know her?
Yeah.
What are you worried about?
H-Hello!
Hello!
What a coincidence.
Y-Yes, quite a coincidence.
I was surprised.
What were you doing?
Basking in the sun.
Huh?
Just kidding.
It's evening right now.
Hey, who is this girl?
Minagi Tohno. She's my classmate.
She's smart.
She's at the top of our class, and she's president of the Astronomy Club.
Please just call me Tohno.
Hey! Minagi!
Oh, Yukito-san is flying like a leaf!
Hey! Let's hurry up and go back to blowing bubbles!
You know, I'm doing really good now!
Come on!
Is this your younger sister?
No, I'm not.
I'm Michiru, Minagi's best friend.
Who are you?
I'm Tohno-san's classmate.
That hurt!
What?!
Are you one of Minagi's classmates too?
I'm an innocent passer-by who just got bowled over by you.
I've got it!
Minagi, this is a perverted kidnapper who's come to take us.
I'm on this side too?
Who are you calling a kidnapper?!
Yikes! He's mad.
Us young girls are in trouble!
Wow, it had a great sound.
Kamio-san, who is this?
Yukito Kunisaki-san.
A traveler?
He's a traveler who is staying with us now.
There's no hope left if you're a perverted homeless kidnapper.
Kamio-san, I think we'd best be going.
What? But I was finally able to make nice bubbles.
Let's do it some more.
Kami-Kami too.
Kami-Kami... Me?
It's getting dark, so let's do it tomorrow.
I'll pack a lunch for us.
See you!
Kamiya!
Byebye!
Yukito Kunisaki!
Yeah?
Geez, you should get lost!
What was that?!
Hey, for tomorrow's lunch, can you make hamburgers?
All right.
Really?
Yay!
Did I do something wrong to that brat?
Hmm, I don't know.
I haven't made a single yen today.
You were standing there like that when we met yesterday, too.
Ever since I was little, I've had this longing for the sky.
Why?
I don't know.
It's just...
I have this feeling that my other self is out there...
That's a romantic thought, isn't it?
That the real me is in the sky.
It sounds so wonderful.
Being able to see far into the distance,
everything on earth would seem so insignificant,
and one would find a kind feeling towards others, don't you think?
Misuzu...
you are...
For me, that was the start of a summer as short as a star's twinkle, and as long as eternity.
Next Episode Preview
It might be the other you that I've been looking for.
I'm not cut out to be a parent.
I should have stayed alone.
I had a dream.
A mysterious dream.
A dream about the sky.
I was in the sky.
It was a world I'd never seen before.
Everything extends endlessly into infinity.
Hey,
did you have wings in your dream?
Episode 2