The day before summer break
My name is Misuzu,
Misuzu Kamio.
We need to give you a name too.
Hm...
Isn't that the guy we met on the bank on our way home from school?
Nobody's interested in a puppet show like that these days.
Argh, I'm hungry!
I know.
Sora.
Note: Sora means sky.
Let's name you Sora.
Oh.
That's where I always stand to gaze at the sky...
We watched the fading vapor trails
kieru hikoukigumo bokutachi wa miokutta
消える飛行機雲僕たちは見送った
They were so dazzling, I ran away
mabushikute nigeta
眩しくて逃げた
I was so frustrated, I released your hand
kuyashikute yubi wo hanasu
悔しくて指を離す
The place she can't reach is still there in the distance
todokanai basho ga mada tooku ni aru
届かない場所がまだ遠くにある
She gazes at  it, keeping her wish to herself
negai hi dake himete mitsumeteru
願いだけ秘めて見つめてる
Children walk along the summer railway tracks
kodomotachi wa natsu no senro aruku
子供たちは夏の線路歩く
Holding in both hands their wishes to take flight
ryoute ni wa tobidatsu kibou wo
両手には飛び立つ希望を
Chasing, chasing the fading vapor trails
kieru hikoukigumo oikakete oikakete
消える飛行機雲追いかけて追いかけて
It hasn't changed since the day we crossed that hill
kono oka wo koeta ano hi kara kawarazu
この丘を越えたあの日から変わらず
And never will
itsumademo
いつまでも
And just as we are now, standing tall
massugu ni bokutachi wa aru youni
真っ直ぐに僕たちはあるように
We'll guard the strength of a sea god
watatsumi no youna tsuyosa wo mamoreru yo
わたつみのような強さを守れるよ
Surely
kitto
きっと
Hello.
He doesn't look like he's sick.
It feels like we're friends since we're sitting like this.
It's a beautiful sunset, isn't it?
I wish I could play like that with someone too.
Oh.
Bye-bye!
Episode 10
What's that black thing?!
He followed me.
It seems like he's too small to fly yet.
I'm amazed he's so friendly.
I named him Sora.
We're going to live together.
No way!
Wah, that was quick.
If you want a pet, get a cat or dog.
Having something like this wandering around the house would be depressing.
That's not true.
He's cute. See?
Say hello to Mommy.
My eye!
Uh...
Mommy was really mad, wasn't she?
I'll sneak you into my room tonight.
Let's both apologize to Mommy tomorrow, okay?
Summer break starts tomorrow.
I think I'm going to try to invite some of my classmates over this year.
But will they play with me?
Let's try practicing it a bit.
Um...
I want you to play with me this summer.
Oh, I have remedial classes,
so it'll have to be in the afternoon.
We'll swim in the ocean,
play cards, play with fireworks,
and also do homework together, okay?
I'll just copy yours, so it'll be easy for me...
Just kidding.
I'll do my best too.
Yes.
I feel more confident now.
I'll be back at noon, so just play by yourself till then, okay?
Don't go too far though.
Piko?
Pika pika piko piko.
Piko piko piko piko piko piko.
Pikori.
Piko?
Piko!
Piko piko!
Oh!
Look, a crow!
Oh, you're right.
He's all black!
Ew, how disgusting!
Eh? He's cute.
Ah! He's coming this way!
Run!
Go away!
Wait!
Huh?
It's a crow.
Where did you come from?
Oh, don't worry.
I won't be mean to you.
Oh, no, don't do that.
I can't take that off yet.
That's because if I take it off when I'm grown up, I'll be able to use magic.
There are cars on the roads, so be careful.
See you!
Hey, hey, wanna go to the beach?
Sure, sure!
My swimsuit this year is really revealing.
Eh?!
I mustn't cry.
Hold it back. Hold it back.
Sora,
it seems like I'm going to be all alone this summer too.
I couldn't get anyone to play with me
since everyone knows that I'm not a normal girl.
But I'll do something really fun by myself.
For my summer assignment, I'll make a picture diary and write about all the fun things I do.
So... So I'll be fine.
It's that person from yesterday.
Hey, I don't really want to be all alone after all.
For the long summer break, I don't want to be the only one all alone!
So I'm going to try talking to that guy.
If he seems like a nice person, I'll try asking him to play with me.
Smile. Smile. Act natural.
R-R-Ramen set!
Hello.
Are you alone?
What do you mean?!
Why is there yet another?!
Yet another?!
You made me say it three times.
That just shows how shocking it is.
But Mommy...
Absolutely not!
This is not how you said it would be.
Well, you seem to have guts. I like that part of you.
That's right. Yukito-san is a very good person.
I understand.
I'll let him stay.
Wah!
Seriously?
Seriously? Of course! I'm dead serious.
So his name's Yukito Kunisaki, huh?
He seems to get along well with Misuzu, but she hasn't had another one of those attacks yet.
He just might be able to become Misuzu's friend.
She hasn't had a single friend all this time because of her illness.
Besides, he doesn't seem to be a bad guy, so I want to take a chance on him.
Don't you have a different one?
The rest are all too small.
Mm, it smells nice.
Sora,
Yukito-san and Mommy have work, and I have remedial classes.
Watch the house, okay?
Oh!
Are they out?
I bought this for them; now what should I do?
What on earth are you doing out here?
You should be at home!
It's me.
Perfect timing. Hop on.
There's going to be a festival here soon.
It's the tenth summer festival since that summer.
I still remember it well even after all this time.
She sat in front of where they were selling chicks and talked to them for a long time,
saying, "Gao! Gao!"
That girl thought that if she brought a chick up, it'd grow up to be a dinosaur.
Even if she did raise a chick from a fair,
there's no way it would survive to grow up.
I took her hand and tried to drag her home.
And then...
That child, who always believed that she mustn't cause anyone any trouble,
stared at me and said really longingly, "I want this," just that once.
Misuzu wasn't a wanted child.
She was born to an unmarried couple who were always fighting.
Then my older sister died, leaving the father and the child.
The father pushed his own daughter onto me.
It was really troublesome.
I somehow lived on believing that one day that man would come back for his daughter.
But you know, after spending so much time with that child,
she'd easily get flustered and so clumsy,
but she'd forget that and laugh,
so I can't help but laugh along with her.
Despite all that, I'm not her mother.
That man might come any day to take her away.
Then, I'll have no choice but to return to living alone.
I maintained my own way of life so that I won't be too miserable when that eventually happens.
That's why I've never given her a present, not even on her birthday.
Every year, I pretend I forgot.
I debated what to do this year too, but...
I won't after all!
It's too late for us to become a real family now.
That person...
And this view...
I'm sure I've seen them somewhere before.
But...
When?
Where?
I just can't remember.
Wah, a cicada flew in through the vent again!
Wah, the soy sauce bottle fell over!
Wah, the salad oil spilled!
Wah, Yukito-san's bacon and eggs got messed up!
Yukito-san, is it good?
Yeah.
Really?
It doesn't taste like cicadas?
What do you mean by that?!
Nothing, nothing at all.
Wah!
G-Gao!
Hey.
Where are you going?
What a weird crow.
I pray that Saika-onee-chan gets better.
Mommy,
are there really gods?
Of course there are.
The gods are watching over you and Saika right now.
They will definitely grant your wish.
Oh!
Mommy!
This is a god.
It was walking all by itself.
It looks like it's brand new.
Let's leave it here
since this is the house of the gods.
Okay.
Oh my...
Are you all by yourself?
You aren't flying away, are you?
How smart.
If you don't have a home, will you come to the station with me?
I think you can definitely become good friends with Michiru.
You can also eat as much food as you want.
Ultra-happy...
I see... So you have a home to return to.
I hope you'll keep trying
so that, one day, you'll be able to fly with those wings.
Just think about how I feel, being called out to school each time you have an attack.
I'm sorry.
You're fine when you're with that freeloader, right?
I thought you'd gotten better.
Mm.
Well, I'm going back to work, okay?
I'm sorry for causing you trouble.
Mommy was angry, wasn't she?
But, you know, she came to school so quickly.
She always does.
Yukito-san is probably waiting.
I wonder if he's worried.
I have to act as natural as possible.
I'll make it seem like I was just careless and forgot to meet him
because I want Yukito-san to think I'm a normal girl.
Misuzu,
I'm home.
I'm home!
Oh!
Misuzu suddenly—
I know.
Sora,
apparently Yukito-san left.
I wanted to spend more time with him.
But he said he'll still walk me to and from school like before,
so I'll just have to accept that, right?
I'll still be able to see him every day, right?
Ow!
I wonder what's wrong.
Lately, I've been getting a pain in my back every now and then.
Why did you take Misuzu in?
That's why she isn't getting the love she needs.
Think about it!
You're the only parent she has!
He didn't have to be so harsh.
I've always known that, even without being told.
How much longer do I have to live like this?
Never giving her a present, even for her birthday...
Always scared that she might suddenly disappear one day...
I've decided.
I'll make her my child.
I'll march into Tachibana's house and negotiate with him.
That's right. I'll travel around by myself, visiting hot springs.
What are you thinking?!
What about Misuzu?
Misuzu, I'll be back.
If I stay with you any longer, neither of us will live,
so I've decided to run away from you.
Well, I guess it can't be helped.
It can't be helped, right?
It was fun spending the summer break with you, Yukito-san.
I feel the same.
Really?
Yeah.
Well, I'm going now.
Bye-bye, Yukito-san.
Oh.
He's gone.
I'm going to be all alone,
really alone.
If I'm all alone, I won't be able to stay strong.
What should I do?
I have a good idea.
I should go on a trip too.
If I do that, Yukito-san and I won't have to be separated.
That's a good idea...
It's not that I want to leave this house.
I just have to stay away from you.
Oh.
Hang in there.
Even if you're alone, stay strong.
Yes.
I'll hang in there even if I'm alone.
I'm a strong girl.
Good.
See you.
I'm all alone now,
really all alone.
Yukito-san.
Mommy.
It hurts.
It hurts!
I was all alone until today.
It'll be the same tomorrow.
In the end, even if I try my best, I just cause other people trouble.
Nothing good ever happens.
I should've just continued giving up, like I've always done,
without loving anyone.
I'll go to sleep.
I don't have to wake up again.
Why didn't I realize it sooner?
I was happy just being here with you and watching you smile.
Why is it?
I thought I couldn't get up anymore...
Yukito-san?
Where did you go?
You came back, didn't you?
That's right.
I remember now.
I was once a human,
a human named Yukito Kunisaki,
and I was with Misuzu.
Hey, I'm better again.
I think I can try my hardest again.
Hey, Yukito-san?
Misuzu...
Oh.
I'm here.
Right here.
Yukito-san!
Misuzu.
Yukito-san.
Yukito-san!
Misuzu.
I'm going to do my best.
I'm going to do my best, okay?
So... So don't go anywhere anymore. Stay by my side forever.
Yukito-san.
It's all right.
You're a strong girl,
so you'll definitely be able to reach a goal that no one else has ever been able to reach.
I'm sure you'll reach it.
I don't want you to go anywhere.
Don't go!
I'll always be near you.
I'll never forget you.
I'll be with you.
Yukito-san?
Yukito-san!
Oh.
My mind is becoming hazy again.
But Misuzu, I'm with you.
I'll be with you forever.
Yukito-san, wait!
Don't go!
Hang in there, Misuzu.
Until you reach your goal, hang in there, okay, Misuzu?
Yes.
I'll hang in there.
I'lll hang in there, Yukito-san.
Oh.
Grasping the white fragments of an interrupted dream
shiroku togireta yume no kirehashi wo tsukamaete
白く途切れた夢の切れ端をつかまえて
A boy runs
shounen wa hashiru
少年は走る
When he lets go, they disappear into the distant sound of the wind
te wo hanashitara dokomademo tooku kaze no ne ni kieteyuku
手を放したらどこまでも遠く風の音に消えてゆく
The kindness I could once see is now gone
itsuka mieta yasashisa wa mou nai
いつか見えた優しさはもうない
I just look at my feet, stepping forward alone
hitori fumidasu ashidake miteru
ひとり踏み出す足だけ見てる
I listened to the singing until it disappeared when morning came
asa ni wa kieta ano utagoe wo itsumademo kiiteta
朝には消えたあの歌声をいつまでも聞いてた
I followed the footprints we'd left behind into the distance
bokura ga nokoshita ano ashiato wo itsumademo otteta
僕らが残したあの足跡をいつまでも追ってた
Next Episode Preview
How short should I cut it?
I'll leave it up to you, Mommy.
Mommy?
Yes, that's me.
Mommy went far away.
Misuzu!
I'm your father.
No!
If at that time, she still says she doesn't want to stay with me... If she says that, I'll accept it...
Mm?
Gao...
Episode 11