Sora,
I had a dream about someone I love.
Yukito-san really did come back after all, right?
He gave me something important, right?
That's why...
I can't just give up on something like this, right?
It's all right.
Even if I'm alone, I'll do my best.
We watched the fading vapor trails
kieru hikoukigumo bokutachi wa miokutta
消える飛行機雲僕たちは見送った
They were so dazzling, I ran away
mabushikute nigeta
眩しくて逃げた
I was so frustrated, I released your hand
kuyashikute yubi wo hanasu
悔しくて指を離す
The place she can't reach is still there in the distance
todokanai basho ga mada tooku ni aru
届かない場所がまだ遠くにある
She gazes at  it, keeping her wish to herself
negai hi dake himete mitsumeteru
願いだけ秘めて見つめてる
Children walk along the summer railway tracks
kodomotachi wa natsu no senro aruku
子供たちは夏の線路歩く
Holding in both hands their wishes to take flight
ryoute ni wa tobidatsu kibou wo
両手には飛び立つ希望を
Chasing, chasing the fading vapor trails
kieru hikoukigumo oikakete oikakete
消える飛行機雲追いかけて追いかけて
It hasn't changed since the day we crossed that hill
kono oka wo koeta ano hi kara kawarazu
この丘を越えたあの日から変わらず
And never will
itsumademo
いつまでも
And just as we are now, standing tall
massugu ni bokutachi wa aru youni
真っ直ぐに僕たちはあるように
We'll guard the strength of a sea god
watatsumi no youna tsuyosa wo mamoreru yo
わたつみのような強さを守れるよ
Surely
kitto
きっと
Today, I'll try going outside
even though it hurts to walk.
I'll try my best.
TAKEDA
SHOP
Let's rest for a bit.
I guess I'll get my usual,
the weird juice.
Hm.
Huh?
It's that person,
the one who was living with us until the other day.
Who is she?
She seems vaguely familiar.
Episode 11
So the freeloader left?
Well, he'll eventually come back if he has nowhere to go.
I had a tough time too.
I was trying my best so that you could stay here forever.
Eh?
You aren't my child.
You'll be taken to Tachibana's house someday.
That's why I ignored you even though we lived together.
If I started to love you, it would be hard for us to separate, right?
I always pushed away my feelings so that I would be fine no matter when you leave.
But there was no point. I love you.
I can't lie to myself anymore, so I've decided;
I'll make you my own child.
I was on my knees in front of
Tachibana's house the whole time.
In the end, they finally gave in.
You didn't have to do that.
Eh?
I decided that I'll do my best on my own and not cause trouble anymore.
Misuzu!
What's wrong, Misuzu?!
Were you really that sick?
I thought you just had a cold.
Your legs won't move?
Let's go see the doctor.
I'm sure you'll get better.
You know, that female doctor at the clinic.
I'm sure she can help you.
No hospital can cure me.
Eh?
Yukito-san and I discovered the reason for my illness.
My other self is in the sky, and she's carrying a burden by herself.
That's the reason why my body won't move.
You always spout these fantasies.
Hey, Mommy...
Let's keep on living like before, without worrying about each other.
Eh?
Let's live our separate lives.
I'll do my best on my own.
W-Why would you say something like that?
Are you angry because I left you alone all this time?
All right.
If you don't want to see a doctor, I don't mind.
I'll take good care of you.
But two are better than one.
Let's do our best together!
Okay, Misuzu?
How is it? Is it good?
I see.
Sorry.
I'll make it tasty next time, okay?
I don't want any.
Your cooking never tastes good.
Even if it doesn't taste good, children grow up eating their parents' cooking.
I'm sorry.
Was it that bad?
That's not it.
It's just that if we become close,
you'll get sick too.
Was that in your dream too?
Listen, Misuzu.
I'm not afraid of getting sick at all.
If I get sick, I'll be happy.
It'd be proof that we've become close, right?
Here, eat up.
It's delicious.
Mommy...
What is it?
How short should I cut it?
I'll leave it up to you, Mommy.
Hm.
Then I'll cut it to where you look the cutest, okay?
Okay.
Mommy, you have more wrinkles now.
Do you want me to shave your head?
Just kidding.
You look young, Mommy.
When you came to an open house at school, everyone else's moms were older,
so I was really happy.
You answered a question wrong and started crying.
Yeah.
I felt like I had to show off for you,
so I raised my hand even though I didn't know the answer.
Then you hit me in front of everyone.
That's because you said your favorite phrase, "Gao".
Discipline, discipline.
Thanks to you, Misuzu has grown up into a good girl.
That's true.
You've grown up quite a lot.
You hardly ever say that phrase anymore either.
Misuzu?
Oh well, it's easier this way.
O-Oh!
Uh...
I'll just have to even it all out.
Oh, no!
Now the other side is too short!
I managed to even out the left and the right, but...
Huh?
It's really short!
I'm sorry!
I feel like a little girl again,
Mommy's girl.
That's right.
Let's start over again from here.
The two of us together, okay?
Yeah.
We'll start from here, right?
V!
Hey, the summer festival is soon, right?
Oh, yeah... That's right. I forgot all about it.
I want to go with you, Mommy.
Of course! I'll take you.
And then, I want to go to the beach too
because I've never gone with you before.
You have a lot of places you want to go to, don't you, Misuzu-chin?
Yeah.
I want to do a lot of fun things with you, Mommy.
Yes! Let's do all sorts of fun things together.
Picture Diary
We'll fill your picture diary up with fun things.
You know, Mommy...
Hm?
I'll remember your smile, Mommy.
I'll always remember it...
Mommy's...
I don't know what you're talking about.
What do you mean, Misuzu?
Misuzu, you're up?
What's wrong?
Are you still sleepy?
Who are you?
Hm?
Lady, who are you?
You forgot?!
You said you'd be strong with your mother.
Mommy?
Yes, that's me.
Mommy went far away.
You don't have to remember that.
I'm your substitute mother.
Oh.
Hm...
It's okay.
From today, I'll try to restore your memory.
It's all right if I'm Aunt Haruko until the day you see me as your mother again.
Misuzu!
I borrowed this for you.
Look! Now you can go outside with this.
It hurts to walk!
That's what this wheelchair is for.
Come here.
I'll push you.
It's more fun playing cards by myself.
Hey, let's play together.
It'll feel good to be outside in the sun where there are lots of fun things to do.
Oh.
Huh?
The wind is blowing.
Yes, it is.
The sun is sizzling.
The cicadas are chirping.
Yes. Noisy, aren't they?
It feels nice.
Does it?
I'm glad.
TAKEDA
SHOP
What is the meaning of this?!
Keisuke...
Who is that?
Misuzu, I'm your father.
Huh?
As you know, this child cannot be surrounded by too many people.
That's why I left her with you in this quiet town.
But it was a mistake.
Haven't you heard?
She's my child now.
I already got your parents' approval.
She's my child,
mine and Ikuko's.
You give her to me when she gets in the way
and then come to get her when you remember her.
Do you think this home exists for your convenience?!
How can I leave her here with you where she gets sicker?!
Stop using such formal language!
Just hearing it creeps me out.
Aunty, you're scary...
Ah, I'm sorry for yelling.
Aunty?
T-That's not how it is...
Until just a little while ago, she called me Mommy all the time.
Come. Let's go, Misuzu.
Say "thank you" to your aunty.
Come on. Where's your "thank you"?
Huh?
Thank you.
No!
No! No!
Don't take Misuzu away!
Misuzu has been alone all this time.
Whose fault is that?
Wasn't it ours?!
That's why I've decided to stay with her forever.
Are you still going to push her around because of the trouble between us?!
Haruko...
I'm not too smart, so I don't know how to put it nicely...
But I do know this – I want to be with her so much more than you do!
That's the absolute truth!
Then let's ask her.
Misuzu, do you want to stay with Aunty Haruko from now on?
Aunty?
Yes.
Do you want to keep living with her from now on?
Hm...
Keisuke.
Keisuke, wait!
Three days.
Wait just three days.
If at that time, she still says she doesn't want to stay with me... If she says that, I'll accept it...
Then you can take Misuzu away.
Please, Keisuke!
Three days...
Can I regain the time we've lost in just that?
Misuzu-chan, you really like dinosaurs, don't you?
This is a Maiasaura.
It means good mother dinosaur.
Heh. It sounds like me.
This is a Velociraptor.
It means swift thief.
Hah! That sounds like Keisuke!
I wonder which one of us is the thief...
It's hot.
It is, isn't it?
But it's only a short walk, so hang on.
It should be cooler at the beach.
Let's eat our lunch box there,
the lunch box that I made.
I want to go home.
Don't say that.
Our lunch will go to waste.
Go home.
There are sweet egg rolls too.
I made them because you asked for them.
Let's make this a fun day, okay?
No.
You really want to go home?
Go home...
Then what's going to happen to the lunch box that I made?
I don't know.
I see.
Then do whatever you want!
If you want to play by yourself that much, then find your own way home!
Idiot!
It's hot.
I feel dizzy.
W-W-Wah!
Gao...
Let's go...
Let's go home, Misuzu.
I've known it all along;
I'm really not cut out to be a mother.
That's all there is to it.
What I've been doing isn't...
Wah!
Misuzu, what happened?!
Catch it!
Eh?
Huh?
Catch it.
Cicada.
All right. I'll catch it for you!
I'm the cicada-catcher-aunt!
Cicada-catcher-aunt?
That's right.
A scaredy-cat like you needs one, right?
Yeah.
Eh?
There!
Got it!
Now you can play without worrying, right?
Yes.
I see.
Then I guess I'll be going.
Is it all right for Aunty to stay here?
Yes.
I'm not going to ask for much anymore.
I'll be happy if I can just stay with you all day long.
That's all that I wish for.
This is the day I promised Keisuke.
That fool. He'll come to ask you again.
Then you'll say you want to go with him, right?
You'll say you don't want to stay with me anymore, right?
Summer break is a long way from ending,
but our time together ends today.
Is it all right?
TAKEDA
SHOP
Yeah.
It's all right.
I see.
Hey, Keisuke.
There's one last place I want to take her.
Can I have a bit more time?
Misuzu, it's the ocean.
It's the ocean.
It's beautiful, isn't it?
We've come so far.
I wonder how many years it took for the two of us to come here together.
We could have enjoyed this beautiful view any time we wanted.
What exactly were we doing?
Is it all right now?
She's heavy. It's been a long time since you carried her.
It's all thanks to you that she's grown this big.
Thank you.
Oh, yeah...
Give this to her.
She loves this stuffed animal.
She'll calm down and sleep if she's holding this.
If she's still whining, give her this to drink.
It's her favorite juice.
I understand.
See you.
Shouldn't you go too?
Your princess is leaving.
Idiot!
What are you doing?!
Misuzu...
Mommy!
Misuzu!
That's right.
I'm your mother.
Mommy...
After that, the two of them talked for a long time in the sunset.
I'll bring a doctor I can trust, so will you let her be examined?
I finally realized that
the person who'd been with Misuzu all this time was...
Misuzu's mother.
Grasping the white fragments of an interrupted dream
shiroku togireta yume no kirehashi wo tsukamaete
白く途切れた夢の切れ端をつかまえて
A boy runs
shounen wa hashiru
少年は走る
When he lets go, they disappear into the distant sound of the wind
te wo hanashitara dokomademo tooku kaze no ne ni kieteyuku
手を放したらどこまでも遠く風の音に消えてゆく
The kindness I could once see is now gone
itsuka mieta yasashisa wa mou nai
いつか見えた優しさはもうない
I just look at my feet, stepping forward alone
hitori fumidasu ashidake miteru
ひとり踏み出す足だけ見てる
I listened to the singing until it disappeared when morning came
asa ni wa kieta ano utagoe wo itsumademo kiiteta
朝には消えたあの歌声をいつまでも聞いてた
I followed the footprints we'd left behind into the distance
bokura ga nokoshita ano ashiato wo itsumademo otteta
僕らが残したあの足跡をいつまでも追ってた
Next Episode Preview
I had wings.
They were pure white wings, and I was flying through the sky.
I see.
What a nice dream.
No. It was a sad dream,
the saddest dream in the world.
But you know, that was my last dream.
From now on I will stay with you,
forever and always.
Final Episode