When I think about it,
I feel like everything that's happened so far has been a trial for me to become your real mother.
The paralysis in your legs and your memory loss...
They prepared me to start everything over again from the beginning.
Mommy...
Oh!
Misuzu!
Misuzu, hang on!
Where does it hurt?
I'll rub it for you.
It hurts. It hurts, Mommy.
Here?
Does it hurt here?
No.
Your legs? Your arms?
W-Wings...
My wings... hurt.
After a while, Misuzu will begin to forget: about me and about you, too.
Then, after having her last dream, she'll probably die.
That can't be true.
If she falls asleep...
If she has a dream, she'll...
Misuzu, you're going to the summer festival, right?
You're going to the summer festival with Mommy, right?
I want to go to the festival.
I want a baby dinosaur.
You mean a chick, right?
I'm sure there'll be a stand selling them.
Can I buy a dinosaur?
Sure! We'll eat some delicious things too.
Let's make tomorrow a really fun day!
So please get better,
Misuzu!
We watched the fading vapor trails
kieru hikoukigumo bokutachi wa miokutta
消える飛行機雲僕たちは見送った
They were so dazzling, I ran away
mabushikute nigeta
眩しくて逃げた
I was so frustrated, I released your hand
kuyashikute yubi wo hanasu
悔しくて指を離す
The place she can't reach is still there in the distance
todokanai basho ga mada tooku ni aru
届かない場所がまだ遠くにある
She gazes at  it, keeping her wish to herself
negai hi dake himete mitsumeteru
願いだけ秘めて見つめてる
Children walk along the summer railway tracks
kodomotachi wa natsu no senro aruku
子供たちは夏の線路歩く
Holding in both hands their wishes to take flight
ryoute ni wa tobidatsu kibou wo
両手には飛び立つ希望を
Chasing, chasing the fading vapor trails
kieru hikoukigumo oikakete oikakete
消える飛行機雲追いかけて追いかけて
It hasn't changed since the day we crossed that hill
kono oka wo koeta ano hi kara kawarazu
この丘を越えたあの日から変わらず
And never will
itsumademo
いつまでも
And just as we are now, standing tall
massugu ni bokutachi wa aru youni
真っ直ぐに僕たちはあるように
We'll guard the strength of a sea god
watatsumi no youna tsuyosa wo mamoreru yo
わたつみのような強さを守れるよ
Surely
kitto
きっと
Misuzu, it's morning.
The summer festival is today.
Mm...
The festival.
Final Episode
Please, gods,
do something.
Onee-chan!
I'm such an idiot.
There's no way they'd hold the festival.
Miracles never happen.
There's no way that gods exist.
What did this girl do wrong?!
She waited like a good girl!
She was so looking forward to the summer festival!
Why can't she be rewarded?!
It's just like that time.
In the end, I'm never able to give you anything, am I?
Mommy.
Where's the baby dinosaur?
Why?
Why is it here?
I threw it away.
So you've been waiting all this time.
Misuzu.
Misuzu, wake up.
What is it, Mommy?
There's the dinosaur, right there.
Oh!
Let's go get it together, okay?
Here, try your best.
Yes.
Mommy will help you too.
This will be a happy memory for both of us.
Let's take good care of it and raise it together.
I'm tired already.
I'm sleepy.
No!
Do your best with me.
Your friend is here too.
We're all here.
Let's be happy together.
Mm.
Just a little further...
We can reach our happiness.
See? You got it!
I did it!
It's my birthday present to you.
I haven't been able to give you one all this time we've been together,
but will you accept one now?
Yes. I'm happy.
You are?
Aren't you glad, Misuzu?
It's cute.
It goes, "Gao!"
Gao!
Thank you, gods.
Mommy...
She hasn't slept for a long time, has she?
Because of me...
Oh, no.
I was asleep just now, wasn't I?
Sorry.
No. Let's sleep.
I want to sleep with you, Mommy.
What should I do?
If you go to sleep and dream, your pain will worsen, won't it?
No, it doesn't hurt anymore.
Huh?
It hasn't hurt for a while now.
I wonder why.
Really?
It really doesn't hurt?
Really.
That's why I want to sleep.
I'll sleep a lot and get better.
I see.
I'm so glad!
It's really great, isn't it, Misuzu?
Since you were doing your best,
you were rewarded, right, Misuzu?
Misuzu...
No...
That isn't a cracker.
You can't eat it.
I'm sorry, Mommy, for lying.
But you wouldn't have rested unless I had.
Yukito-san...
Picture Diary
I think I'll write in my diary.
Oh!
Misuzu?
I fell asleep.
Does your body hurt?
Do you remember who I am?
Mommy,
good morning!
The sky is bright.
That means it'll be a good day.
Mommy, I had another dream last night.
A dream?
You start hurting whenever you have a dream, right?
It's all right.
I don't hurt anywhere.
Besides, my dreams will end today.
Really?
There's really nothing wrong, right?
You don't hurt anywhere, right?
I'm fine.
V!
I see.
That freeloader said something about after your last dream...
But I guess he was wrong, right?
I was so worried.
It was like living a long nightmare.
But it's finally over, right?
Mommy.
I can't tell you not to cry anymore; I'm a crybaby too.
Don't cry.
That's right.
I mustn't cry when there's nothing to be sad about, right?
My dream last night was about a dinosaur with wings.
He was saying, "Gao," and flying like he really enjoyed it.
Is that so?
And I was flying even higher than him.
I looked back over my shoulder;
I had wings.
They were pure white wings,
and I was flying through the sky.
I see.
What a nice dream.
No. It was a sad dream,
the saddest dream in the world.
But anyway, that was my last dream.
From now on I will stay with you,
forever and always.
Ah. It's a really nice day, isn't it?
Yeah, it feels really nice.
It smells like summer.
Yeah, it does.
What kind of smell does it have?
The smell of the sea.
Yeah, that's right.
The smell of the sun.
Yeah, that's also true.
Mommy's smell.
Yeah, that too.
Hey! I don't want it to reek of my smell!
It smells a lot like you, Mommy.
Are you sure?
Yes. This summer smelled a lot like you, Mommy.
The smell of my precious mommy.
If it reeked of that, it would suck.
That would suck.
But it was a good smell...
Is that so?
I'm glad.
Yes, I'm glad.
It's hot, isn't it?
Yeah, it sure is hot.
Hey, Misuzu, do you want me to guess what you're you're thinking now?
Sure.
I want to drink juice.
Wow, you're good.
Anybody could've guessed that.
Concentrated
gooey
Milk
Flavor
Peach
Gerurun
Melon
Flavor
I want this.
This again?
You really like this one, don't you?
Which one should I get?
I recommend the Gerurun juice.
Really?
Concentrated
gooey
Gerurun
Gooey?! It's hard!
Who would want juice like this?!
Don't throw it away!
You're supposed to squeeze it while you drink.
Like this?
Well, it isn't that bad...
It's summer break, isn't it?
It's a summer break of just the two of us.
But that's okay; we can play together.
Hey, Mommy.
I want you to go on ahead by yourself.
Why?
Is there a reason?
Yes.
Take Sora with you too.
Is this far enough?
Yeah. Wait there.
Don't push yourself too much!
Mommy, keep standing there.
Huh?
No matter what happens, don't move.
I'm going to do my best.
I'll do my best to walk over there
because, Mommy, you're my goal.
I see.
I'm the goal?
Yes. You and Sora are the goal.
Take your time.
I'll wait as long as you need.
Okay.
Are you all right?
Yeah!
V!
V...
Misuzu, over here.
I'm over here.
That's right, slow and steady.
If you keep working hard like that, you'll definitely get better.
Let's do our best together, okay?
Okay, Misuzu?
It's enough, right?
Huh?
What is?
I did my best, right?
It's all right for me to go to my goal now, right?
Are you tired already?
All right, after you reach me, we'll go home and play cards or something.
No...
My goal...
The goal I've been trying to reach all this time...
Eh?
I... did my best, so it's enough now, right?
I can rest now, right?
You mean it hurts?
You've been hurting all this time?
Don't move!
It's not true.
Tell me it's not true!
You're going to get better, right?
The bad dreams are supposed to be over, right?!
I'm sorry, Mommy.
But I was able to do all that I needed to.
That's why I'll go to my goal, okay?
No, Misuzu.
Don't move.
You can't leave!
It's just started!
Didn't we start our lives over again yesterday?!
We're going to take it back,
the happy life that we should have started ten years ago.
We're going to take it back together, starting now!
Our happiness has just started!
No, we did everything.
It's enough already.
This summer was filled with enough happiness for a lifetime.
No!
You're wrong!
There are still lots of things I want to do,
lots of things I want to do with my beloved Misuzu!
All of that starts now!
I decided I would try my best one more time this summer break,
the summer break that started on the day I met Yukito-san.
Even though all sorts of things happened,
even though it was hard and painful sometimes,
I'm glad I tried my hardest!
Because my goal was to be happy...
Because I wasn't all alone...
That's why...
I'll go to my goal now, okay?
No! It's just started!
It's just started, I tell you!
Goal!
ano umi doko made mo aokatta tooku made
The eternally blue sea stretched into the distance
あの海どこまでも青かった遠くまで
ano michi doko made mo tsuzuiteta massugu ni
The path continued endlessly straight ahead
あの道どこまでも続いてた真っ直ぐに
I've finally reached it,
the place I've always looked for.
A place of happiness.
A place of... eternal happiness.
ichiban hayaku sunao ni waratta mono gachi
The first one to show a genuine smile wins
一番早く素直に笑った者勝ち
No!
I don't want that!
Mommy,
thank you.
ichiban suki na ano hito waratteru
The one I love most is smiling
一番好きなあのひと笑ってる
Misuzu!
You taught me so much!
How to escape from living alone...
dare yori mo tooku ni itte mo koko kara mata waratte kureru
Even if I go farther away than anyone else, would you still smile for me from here?
誰よりも遠くに云ってもここからまた笑ってくれる
Don't leave me!
Don't leave me alone!
I don't need anything else.
I don't need friends, new clothes, luxuries, or anything!
Just being with you is enough for me.
hitomi wo tojireba futto natsu no hi no nioi
When I close my eyes, I catch the scent of a summer day
瞳を閉じればふっと夏の日の匂い
Let's live together happily at the Kamio house.
Okay, Misuzu?
Misuzu!
ano kawa asonderu futarikiri dorodarake
We're playing in the river, just us two, covered in mud
あの川遊んでるふたりきり泥だらけ
I've spent the days since then crying and crying.
I've run out of tears to shed.
Yeah.
ano kumo otteiru todoitara shiawase to
We're chasing the clouds; we'll find happiness once we reach them
あの雲追っている届いたら幸せと
Family is amazing, isn't it?
Happiness beyond compare and pain beyond compare, rolled into one.
That's truly what it means for people to live.
That's why I lived...
ichiban hayaku kono saka nobotta mono gachi
The first one who gets to the top of this hill wins
一番早くこの坂登った者勝ち
Why I lived together with her.
We were reckless and tattered,
strong yet weak.
I'm starting to make no sense.
No, I understand,
ichiban suki na ano basho mezashite
Head for the place that we love the most
一番好きなあの場所目指して
so much that it hurts.
Yeah...
You would understand, right?
We're adults, after all.
You know, I'm confident now that I'm her mother.
Even though I might not have
been great, I'm still her mother.
takusan no omoide ga aru hoka ni wa nani mo iranai gurai
I have so many memories that I almost need nothing else
たくさんの思い出がある他にはなにも要らないぐらい
I've decided to quit my job and work at the local daycare center.
From now on, I want to live surrounded by all sorts of families.
That's what I feel.
hitomi wo tojireba sugu ano umi no nioi
When I close my eyes, I catch the scent of the sea
瞳を閉じればすぐあの海の匂い
I'll come and visit you sometime.
That'll be good.
I'll be waiting.
The end of summer...
My break is ending too.
So many fun things
happened this summer break.
Mommy even got me
a baby dinosaur.
It was great.
mata natsu ga kuru giniro ni hikaru
Summer will come again; glimmering silver,
また夏がくる 銀色に光る
minamo ni utsusu futaribun no kage
Our two shadows reflect on the water's surface
水面に写す ふたりぶんの影
Is that you, Sora?
You've grown quite big.
Or are you a different crow?
I can't tell.
But if you're Sora, I'll have to scold you, saying,
"What are you still doing here? She's not here anymore."
You know, you have to go
since you have wings.
The sky is an eternally unreachable place for us humans, who have no wings.
So you must fly!
For us humans who have no wings,
take all of our hopes and dreams, and return them to the sky!
Please!
Then we'll be able to live peaceful lives.
That's how I feel.
I hope someday we can meet again.
Well, best of luck to you!
Before I knew it, I was looking at the sky,
the sky that had always been filled with a sad color,
an endless blue that continues into infinity.
The girl returned to that eternity.
The girl is still all alone.
That's why I shall continue on a journey to find her.
And someday, I shall bring her back
to welcome a new beginning.
My child,
listen carefully.
The story I'm about to tell is very important.
It is the story of a long, long journey,
a story that will be passed down forever from parent to child, starting now.
We continue to inherit the memories of the stars.
We see and hear everything that happens on this planet,
and pass them on from parent to child.
The memories of the stars must be eternally happy ones.
When the sky is clouded over by hatred and war,
this planet will be overwhelmed by grief and all will be lost.
Someday, the day of destruction will come.
It is a fate that cannot be avoided.
But, in the end,
may the last child, who bears the memories of the stars, have only happy memories.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
I was just remembering something from the past.
The sun will be setting soon, won't it?
Yeah.
Before it does, let's check it out.
Check what out?
The thing you've always wanted to check out:
what's beyond this shoreline.
Did I say something like that?
Maybe you didn't...
But I had a feeling you were thinking it.
That's true. I want to check it out.
If we go now, we can find out what lies beyond it... you and I.
Let's go, shall we?
Yup.
For them, cruel days await.
For us, it's the beginning.
Goodbye...
The End
Grasping the white fragments of an interrupted dream
shiroku togireta yume no kirehashi wo tsukamaete
白く途切れた夢の切れ端をつかまえて
A boy runs
shounen wa hashiru
少年は走る
When he lets go, they disappear into the distant sound of the wind
te wo hanashitara dokomademo tooku kaze no ne ni kieteyuku
手を放したらどこまでも遠く風の音に消えてゆく
The kindness I could once see is now gone
itsuka mieta yasashisa wa mou nai
いつか見えた優しさはもうない
I just look at my feet, stepping forward alone
hitori fumidasu ashidake miteru
ひとり踏み出す足だけ見てる
I listened to the singing until it disappeared when morning came
asa ni wa kieta ano utagoe wo itsumademo kiiteta
朝には消えたあの歌声をいつまでも聞いてた
I followed the footprints we'd left behind into the distance
bokura ga nokoshita ano ashiato wo itsumademo otteta
僕らが残したあの足跡をいつまでも追ってた
Preview
Intruding while your master is changing is the epitome of disloyalty!
Poke.
"I will not allow you to kill anyone" – was that it?
Do you really think I'll keep my word?
Ryuya-dono...
Uh, well...
Summer – Special Episode