When did you alter the wall?
I made preparations a while back, so that we could escape at any time.
You were supposed to be my guardian.
Aren't you quite devoted to your job?
This is no time to be sarcastic!
I know...
Until I meet Mother I am prepared to endure any hardship.
There aren't any roads from now on.
Watch your step.
This is no big deal, I—
As I said...
Kanna-sama, are you all right?
Do I look all right to you?
I cannot tell.
It is too dark.
I hope your clothes did not get dirtied...
You worry more about the
clothes than your master?!
Both of you, lift the bottom of your kimonos up.
Oh!
Both of us at the same time.
Ryuya-sama, you're so lewd.
Yeah, you're no different from an animal.
Do you even understand what you're saying?
I'm only telling you to lift up your kimonos so it's easier to walk.
I think our pursuers are close by.
Ryuya-sama...
Huh?
We watched the fading vapor trails
kieru hikoukigumo bokutachi wa miokutta
消える飛行機雲僕たちは見送った
They were so dazzling, I ran away
mabushikute nigeta
眩しくて逃げた
I was so frustrated, I released your hand
kuyashikute yubi wo hanasu
悔しくて指を離す
The place she can't reach is still there in the distance
todokanai basho ga mada tooku ni aru
届かない場所がまだ遠くにある
She gazes at  it, keeping her wish to herself
negai hi dake himete mitsumeteru
願いだけ秘めて見つめてる
Children walk along the summer railway tracks
kodomotachi wa natsu no senro aruku
子供たちは夏の線路歩く
Holding in both hands their wishes to take flight
ryoute ni wa tobidatsu kibou wo
両手には飛び立つ希望を
Chasing, chasing the fading vapor trails
kieru hikoukigumo oikakete oikakete
消える飛行機雲追いかけて追いかけて
It hasn't changed since the day we crossed that hill
kono oka wo koeta ano hi kara kawarazu
この丘を越えたあの日から変わらず
And never will
itsumademo
いつまでも
And just as we are now, standing tall
massugu ni bokutachi wa aru youni
真っ直ぐに僕たちはあるように
We'll guard the strength of a sea god
watatsumi no youna tsuyosa wo mamoreru yo
わたつみのような強さを守れるよ
Surely
kitto
きっと
Stick close to me.
Run!
Part 1
You can move now.
This is quite troublesome.
You did a good job of keeping quiet.
Don't underestimate me!
I'm not that cowardly.
Hurry up, or I'll leave you behind.
That's the way we came.
It looks like they sent a lot of people after us.
Uraha, you brought a change of clothes for Kanna, right?
The two of you just sit down and take it easy.
Don't move from here.
Ryuya-sama!
Don't worry.
Over there! It's a woman!
She's surprisingly fast!
Don't lose her! Hurry!
The woman fell into the river!
It looks like she fell into the river!
I heard it directly below.
Look! A piece of clothing!
Gather the troops! Hurry!
Downstream! Search downstream!
Throw down your sword.
Answer my questions honestly,
and I'll spare your life.
You're from Edo, aren't you?
Why are you chasing Kannabi no Mikoto?
I don't know.
We were ordered to.
What were you planning to do with Kannabi no Mikoto?
Whose orders are you following?
I don't know!
We were just ordered by our superior!
I see.
Stop it!
You... did you intend to kill him?
If I don't kill him, our lives will be in danger.
You should feel ashamed, you fool!
You just told him you would spare his life.
Do you lie without any thought?
Do you break your promises without any thought?
If the situation calls for it...
So, if the situation calls for it, you will break your promise to me as well?
Do you kill people without any thought?
Kanna-sama.
I don't want to be protected by someone like that!
I hereby order you:
As long as I am your master, I will not allow you to kill anyone.
Understood?
I understand.
Very well.
But do you really think we'll be able to survive without killing anyone?
I feel that it will be easy for you, Ryuya-sama.
Easy for you to say...
You can relax now.
I don't see any sign of pursuit.
That's a relief.
Uraha, sorry to trouble you,
but can you fetch some water?
I think there's a stream at the bottom.
Certainly.
Kanna, are you all right?
Don't talk to me.
You're making my headache worse.
Looks like the heat got to you. Here.
What are you doing?!
It's to cool you down.
Just say something before you do it.
Okay, I'm going to pour water on you.
I was asking you to be more gentle when you do it!
Stop being so fussy!
You arrogant fool!
Oh, my. Kanna-sama is all better now.
See? Children recover quickly.
I'm not feeling better!
I'm angry.
But this is a problem.
The height of summer is just beginning.
If she stays in those clothes,
the heat will get to her quickly.
Don't worry.
I've already prepared a solution for her.
Okay, Kanna-sama. Come here.
I'm fine the way I am.
Now, now, if you intend to be so naughty, then...
Oh, my! You're drenched in sweat!
Hey! Don't touch me in weird places...
I knew it! You're wet all the way through!
Stop! It tickles!
I said stop!
What happened?!
Kanna-sama's kimono was taken by that monkey.
Give it back, you insolent fool!
Step aside.
That was marvelous, Ryuya-sama.
Yes. I expect nothing less from my loyal servant.
Hey, silly! Stop it!
No, I will not.
Intruding while your master is
changing is the epitome of disloyalty!
You just called me your loyal servant.
Don't give me such an unreasonable retort!
Who's being unreasonable here?!
Thank you for waiting.
Where exactly did you find a kimono like this?
I took the laundry someone left hanging to dry by the river.
Of course, I left some money.
It looks good on you, Kanna.
R-Really?
You have strange taste...
No matter how I look at you, you look like any other country girl.
A bit too cute for one, actually.
Maybe a bit too bony, though.
That was unnecessary!
You don't seem to be getting any better at all.
When learning something new, the beginning is the most important.
As long as you have a good foundation, you will improve in no time.
You want me to practice with these?
Beanbags are supposed to be made with stones.
If I make a mistake and they hit me, it will hurt.
If you sense danger, then you will try harder.
No uh, throwing beanbags isn't supposed to be dangerous.
Now is the time, Kanna-sama!
And I'm being ignored...
Kanna-sama!
Hey, are you all right, Kanna?
She's sleeping quite soundly.
You should always exercise if you want to get a good night's sleep.
She's been cooped up in that shrine all this time.
Yeah, she has.
Uraha, you should get some rest too.
We have to hike up mountains tomorrow.
Ryuya-sama, are you not tired too?
I'm fine.
I'm used to it.
To war?
Yeah.
Please rest, even if just for a bit.
I'll keep watch over us.
All right, I'll leave it to you.
I've got a good one for you.
This is quite a big market.
What is a market?
It is a place where goods are traded.
Don't make too much of a commotion.
There are people after us.
I know.
I'm not that stupid.
Uraha! What are these?
They are called 'Ubai'.
It's a medicine for stomach aches.
Oh, that really sour thing.
Oh, they have mochi.
I remember when you tried to eat too many at once and had one stuck in your throat.
I couldn't help myself because they were so delicious.
What's this then?
It's white sake.
I remember when you drank too much and became violent and...
You don't have to talk about such stupid things every time!
Hey, did you already forget I told you not to make a commotion?
Don't worry.
Any noise will be drowned in this much commotion.
Besides, who would be able to distinguish me from others in this crowd?
I'm bony, and I only look like a country girl.
You hold grudges over the stupidest things.
All right, I was wrong.
You're cute. You're magnificently sweet.
You're so charming that you stand out in a crowd, so please be quieter.
As always, your compliments don't sound very sincere.
Hey!
You there.
What are these striped balls?
They're melons.
But melons are softer and juicier, are they not?
There's no way you can bite into it if it's so hard.
Are you a princess from somewhere?
Yes, about ten days away by foot in the mountains—
This girl has been giving me a lot of trouble, since she's slightly retarded.
I'm sorry to hear that.
Who are you calling retarded?!
Who else could it be?!
Uraha, you should say something too!
She's gone...
Uraha!
Where are you, Uraha?
Ouch! Don't bite, don't bite!
That is because you do nothing but perform outrageous acts!
I ended up spending half the day babysitting Kanna.
Where did Uraha go?
I have never seen such an ugly bird like you before.
No wonder you're still sitting here unsold, because of your fidgety clucking.
Cuckoos and scops owls make nicer hoots.
Ouch, ouch, ouch!
You dare mock me even though you are a lowly bird!
How arrogant!
Those ridiculous tail feathers, I'm going to rip them out.
Please stop it.
That's my most prized long-tail.
What are we going to see next?
We have to look for Uraha first.
Oh great samurai, sir.
Oh great samurai, sir, please have pity on me.
I was chased out of my village three days ago, and fled here with nothing but the clothes I wear.
A war?
I don't know.
A group of armored men ordered me to leave and took over my home and fields.
That is very unfortunate.
Oh...
Is the young lady beside you of noble birth?
Oh, you can tell?
Oh, no. I'm not.
I'm only a cute innocent little country girl.
A little bony though.
You're still mad about that?
Don't just stand there like that.
Give him something.
What am I supposed to give him though?
This isn't much, but it might help a little.
Thank you so much.
I will never forget your kindness.
Take care of yourself.
We did a good deed.
Not necessarily.
What do you mean?
He could have been pretending.
If I were starving, even I'd lie and use flattery.
Believing a beggar's story will only make a fool out of you.
You are such a fool.
You could see how thin and weak he looked.
Oh, yeah. I see.
I'm hungry.
The second you impress me, she says that...
Well, Kanna-sama is still growing.
If you're going to grow, instead of a bigger ass, you might as well grow some bigger breasts.
Be quiet, you!
You're quiet. Uraha, what's wrong?
You're not surprised at all...
Whoa!
Uraha, when did you come back?
I didn't notice at all.
You always appear out of nowhere.
Thank you for your insincere display of care.
Where were you?
I'll tell you that later.
Oh yes, I have a gift for for Kanna-sama.
A walnut?
That's rare this time of year.
It's considered good luck, as it comes from a branch at a shrine that bore fruit unusually early.
It is one of Kanna-sama's favorite foods, and is very nutritious too.
Seriously, though, I had a hard time while you were gone.
Oh my, Kanna-sama!
Stop!
Uraha, don't tell me you left without saying anything so you could leave Kanna with me?
Only you would think of something so disrespectful, Ryuya-sama.
Why won't it crack?
Stop, stop. You'll chip a tooth.
Let me do something to help.
I don't feel good about making the two of you do all the work.
Then go collect some firewood.
And leave your walnut here; I'll crack it for you.
Thank you.
Now then, I'm off to collect some firewood.
Yeah.
Don't go too far.
I won't.
They have set up a checkpoint past the market.
They were stopping young girls and checking their bare backs.
They must be checking for wings.
It looks like we can't take the main road anymore.
I'm surprised you found that out.
That was an odd place to hold a market.
I found it suspicious, so I investigated to be safe.
You really are wise about the world.
That was a big help.
Where did you learn such a skill?
I do this just for fun.
But still, I have to keep my skills sharp.
Don't tell Kanna.
I don't want her to give me hell about how walnuts are alive too.
"I will not allow you to kill anyone" – was that it?
Do you really think I'll keep my word?
Kanna-sama didn't want me to tell you this...
but do you remember the night we fled the shrine?
After that, when she heard the whistle of the pursuers...
Ryuya-dono is being chased.
I must go immediately!
If I don't go, Ryuya-dono will be killed!
If Ryuya-dono dies then I... I...
She would not listen to me, even when I told her it was part of your plan.
Is that so?
With all due respect, I believe you will keep your promise not to kill.
What makes you think that?
At that time, if Kanna-sama had ordered you to kill that soldier, what would you have done?
I would've gotten angry.
I would've told her not to take human life so lightly.
Adults have to set an example for children.
That is very true.
I got it!
Is this enough?
Kanna-sama!
I told you to be careful!
Shut up!
I just couldn't see in front of me.
Ryuya-dono...
What?
I have a favor to ask of you.
It's still a little embarrassing...
but would you watch me?
Grasping the white fragments of an interrupted dream
shiroku togireta yume no kirehashi wo tsukamaete
白く途切れた夢の切れ端をつかまえて
A boy runs
shounen wa hashiru
少年は走る
When he lets go, they disappear into the distant sound of the wind
te wo hanashitara dokomademo tooku kaze no ne ni kieteyuku
手を放したらどこまでも遠く風の音に消えてゆく
The kindness I could once see is now gone
itsuka mieta yasashisa wa mou nai
いつか見えた優しさはもうない
I just look at my feet, stepping forward alone
hitori fumidasu ashidake miteru
ひとり踏み出す足だけ見てる
I listened to the singing until it disappeared when morning came
asa ni wa kieta ano utagoe wo itsumademo kiiteta
朝には消えたあの歌声をいつまでも聞いてた
I followed the footprints we'd left behind into the distance
bokura ga nokoshita ano ashiato wo itsumademo otteta
僕らが残したあの足跡をいつまでも追ってた
Next Episode Preview
I've never seen my parents' faces.
Why is that?
I think I was abandoned.
An unsui took me in when he found me crying at the side of the road.
Part 2