Ryuya-dono...
What?
I have a favor to ask of you.
It's still a little embarrassing...
but would you watch me?
We watched the fading vapor trails
kieru hikoukigumo bokutachi wa miokutta
消える飛行機雲僕たちは見送った
They were so dazzling, I ran away
mabushikute nigeta
眩しくて逃げた
I was so frustrated, I released your hand
kuyashikute yubi wo hanasu
悔しくて指を離す
The place she can't reach is still there in the distance
todokanai basho ga mada tooku ni aru
届かない場所がまだ遠くにある
She gazes at  it, keeping her wish to herself
negai hi dake himete mitsumeteru
願いだけ秘めて見つめてる
Children walk along the summer railway tracks
kodomotachi wa natsu no senro aruku
子供たちは夏の線路歩く
Holding in both hands their wishes to take flight
ryoute ni wa tobidatsu kibou wo
両手には飛び立つ希望を
Chasing, chasing the fading vapor trails
kieru hikoukigumo oikakete oikakete
消える飛行機雲追いかけて追いかけて
It hasn't changed since the day we crossed that hill
kono oka wo koeta ano hi kara kawarazu
この丘を越えたあの日から変わらず
And never will
itsumademo
いつまでも
And just as we are now, standing tall
massugu ni bokutachi wa aru youni
真っ直ぐに僕たちはあるように
We'll guard the strength of a sea god
watatsumi no youna tsuyosa wo mamoreru yo
わたつみのような強さを守れるよ
Surely
kitto
きっと
Now then, here goes...
Wait just a moment!
What are those?
Can't you tell?
They're beanbags.
What are you going to do now?
I'm going to juggle.
I was able to juggle three earlier!
Part 2
I can tell you don't believe me.
It's true! I really can juggle three!
Good night.
Don't go to sleep!
Go back to bed.
I'm keeping watch right now.
Your master is going to show you her expert skills.
It is a servant's duty to submit, and watch in awe!
Don't be so unreasonable!
Then I order you.
Hey! Wait, wait, wait!
Don't order me as my master for
something like this! That's cheating.
I don't want to make any more stupid promises.
Ouch! Ouch, ouch!
Ow! Stop biting me all the time!
That's because you always treat me so roughly!
Fine then. I'll watch you, but make it quick.
The way you say things is always...
All right! All right! I want to see it!
I would love to have the honor of
seeing it, so please do it right away!
As always, your words are insincere.
That aside, I'm sure your attitude will change once you've watched me juggle.
I've finally got the hang of it.
Once I learned the trick to it,
it was terribly simple.
I'm as good a juggler as Uraha now.
Uh...
I now understand how important it is to put all your heart and soul into doing something.
Oh?
Behold!
That was an accident.
I'm not lying.
I really did do it.
I never said you were lying.
I'll be watching, so just keep trying.
This time for sure...
You should relax.
Even experts can't do things well if they're nervous.
I guess so.
Here goes.
See? See? I'm doing it!
You did really well.
I don't need your consolation.
I'm not trying to comfort you.
You were able to juggle like that because you tried really hard.
Not knowing when to give up is amazing.
I can't tell whether that's a compliment or not.
It's a compliment.
In any case, you did well, Kanna.
I want to get better.
So long as you practice every day, you'll become an expert.
You're exaggerating.
It's true.
Will you watch me juggle again?
Sure, if you want me to.
Get some sleep while you can.
We've got a long walk today.
Yeah.
We've got to go over all these mountains.
Going over the mountains is the best way to avoid our pursuers.
I'm going to fetch some water.
What's wrong, Kanna?
Ow!
Forgive me... please...
It won't go in...
It won't go in, I said...
Forgive me...
No more... please...
I can't eat any more...
Hey! You'll catch a cold, sleeping like that!
Hey! Don't go back to sleep!
Not for the third time!
Ryuya-sama, that is not enough.
That hurt. What was that for?
Kanna-sama, I am glad to see you in high spirits.
Do I look like I'm in high spirits?
Can't you wake me up a little more gently?
Then, next time I shall adjust my strength.
I'm telling you to stop pulling my pillow away!
You have strange ears.
Don't they get caught in
branches when you run?
With such long ears, you must be able to hear things really far away.
Why, you... How dare you tease me?!
Wait up! Wait, I said!
Hey, wait up! Wait, wait, wait!
Be quiet!
Stay still for a change!
What have you been looking at?
It's a map I found at the market earlier.
This was quite a find.
What are these wriggly marks like worms?
They're the names of rivers.
Kanna, can't you read?
Well, no one taught me.
Of course I can't read.
I'm surprised Uraha let that happen.
I didn't.
Kanna-sama told me that she would never learn to read, at least not from me.
That was your fault.
Don't tell me you forgot about that incident with the poetry collection.
I only did that to enrich your mind.
There's no way my mind could be enriched with that teaching method!
What are you talking about?
At one time, I was teaching Kanna-sama poems.
A little hardship always accompanies learning.
And yet, Kanna-sama...
Memorizing one hundred poems a day is 'a little' hardship to you?!
There were 4500 poems in total, so we could not take our time.
I haven't slept in five days.
You must continue until you've memorized two hundred more.
I'm surprised you didn't die.
Yes, exactly.
I thought I would have been killed at that rate.
So I threw all my poetry books into the stove.
Thanks to that, the six volumes of ancient poetry were used as fuel in the cooking of breakfast.
Breakfast that morning certainly had a poetic flavor to it.
Are those thoughtless words coming from this mouth?!
S-Stop it, Uraha.
A mouth that cannot recite a single poem is utterly useless!
That is completely absurd!
I might as well sew it shut!
What are you doing? Help me!
Hey, I'm scared of Uraha too.
You worthless fool!
I'm so sorry.
I lost control of myself!
Oh, no. Don't worry about it.
Why are you the one excusing her?
You're still talking funny.
Enough!
I'm going to practice my juggling over there.
I'm starting to go crazy over here.
Then I will come with you.
There is no need for that!
Why are you hitting me?
I am taking it out on you!
Kanna! What happened?
A monk... isn't he?
I don't see any wounds.
He probably died from starvation.
Ryuya-dono.
Do you have a moment?
What? Beanbags again?
No, it's not.
Do you have something on your mind?
Something on my mind?
Yes.
If there's something you want to say, just come right out and say it.
Something I want to say...
Then let me say one thing.
Yes, what is it?
There's a caterpillar on top of your head.
Animals and bugs really seem to like you.
Don't just sit there! Help me!
I felt that something might be wrong with you.
Your master asked because she was concerned for her servant.
And this is what comes of it?
Sorry.
I'll tell you, so just stay here.
You're not going to tease me again, are you?
It's not an interesting story though.
Do you really want to hear it?
Go ahead.
I've never seen my parents' faces.
Why is that?
I think I was abandoned.
An unsui took me in when he found me crying at the side of the road.
An 'unsui' is a monk who travels around.
Being called a 'traveling monk' might sound nice,
but in reality they wander homeless, surviving off charity.
The two of us traveled to many places together.
We went north, south, east and west.
So he was your foster parent?
I don't even know if I could call him that.
He was very strict.
Unless he was chanting prayers, he never opened his mouth.
He never even told me his monk name.
It was during the summer when I was about five years old.
Some bandits attacked us at a mountain pass.
The unsui was killed with a single swing of a sword.
Seeing that dead monk back there reminded me of him.
Ryuya-dono, you had no mother either?
Huh?
I don't know if it's right for me to only search for my mother.
Don't worry about it.
It's what I want too.
The unsui was still chanting a prayer even after he was slashed,
praying that even those that killed him would still be able to go to heaven...
Then he died, covered in blood.
I wasn't killed.
The bandits said I wasn't even worth killing.
And then, I was alone again.
After that, I was alone for a long time.
Wait, you little brat!
I did anything necessary to survive.
You're gonna get it!
I stole swords and spears, and took part in wars.
I even killed people.
I did everything I could just to survive.
Until recently that is.
Recently?
What happened recently?
You could call it a change of heart.
Anyone can change, if given the chance.
Those bandits must have deeply regretted it.
Huh?
They killed a great monk.
Of course they'd regret it.
I truly doubt he was a great monk.
Why do you doubt it?
Because his prayers were heard,
the bandits didn't kill you. Isn't that so?
I see.
True enough, maybe the unsui did save me back then.
If only I had realized it sooner,
I might have taken a different path in life.
I wouldn't want that.
If you had, then I wouldn't have met you.
That's true.
I'm glad I met you too.
Ryuya-dono...
I, uh...
I...
What?
I'm not sure what to do next.
So, I'll leave the rest up to you.
H-Hey!
It's embarrassing.
Hurry up!
Um, do you really know what I'm going to do to you?
Don't take me for a fool.
Of course I know.
Uraha told me.
I knew Uraha was behind this.
Well... to me, you are...
I don't know how to say it...
It's like...
Uraha told me that when Ryuya-dono talks about his past, I shouldn't miss the opportunity.
All men talk of their past to the woman they love.
That's what she said.
She read me like a book.
And when he finishes talking, I am to slowly undress.
And it's important to be sure that not all of my chest is visible.
She's an acting coach too...
Did I do something wrong?
Ryuya-dono, do you prefer men instead?
Wait just a moment.
Oh, I know!
I heard that there are some men who like women, but are impotent.
Don't say things like that!
Did I expose too much of my chest?
All right.
Prepare yourself. I will show you that I am a man.
Ryuya-dono, you have a
strange look in your eye.
You're the one who's seducing me.
Be quiet and let me sink my venomous fangs into you.
You have venom?
All men do.
We have a lot of things you don't even know about.
I'll show you everything you need to know.
Hey! Stop!
Stop it!
S-Stop!
Uraha! I know you're hiding around here somewhere.
Come out!
As usual, your intuition is quite good.
Kanna-sama, are you all right?
I don't really know, but I think it didn't go well.
Ryuya-dono...
Did I make you angry?
No, I'm not angry.
Uraha, you knew I wasn't going to touch her, didn't you?
The odds were against me on this bet though.
You'll never find a more harmless man than me.
You could be called impotent as well.
Shut up!
She's sleeping well.
She was practicing with her beanbags quite a bit today.
She does have a pretty cute face when she's like this.
I wanted to teach her the deceptions of love,
before some strange men start making advances at her.
And you used me for practice?
She's still a child.
She hasn't even played with dolls or beanbags before.
Mother...
Are you awake?
I was dreaming.
It wasn't here, but a dream of another place.
I was wearing strange clothes, and I looked different.
Was it really me?
What did you look like?
I don't remember.
But Mother was next to me.
And other kind people were too.
I was very happy.
That's a nice dream, isn't it?
Just make that dream a reality.
You'll meet your mother soon.
Then that dream won't be a dream anymore.
You're right...
If I pray, I'm sure that my wish will reach the heavens.
Look! Look!
I can do it!
They're still going!
You just need a little more practice.
But it was wonderful, Kanna-sama.
If you keep practicing a little more, you'll become even better.
Really?
Will I become good enough to show Mother?
Of course!
It's time to go, Kanna.
What's wrong?
Don't you want to come with us?
Oh.
Is that your mother?
Isn't that nice?
I wish you a long, happy life.
Grasping the white fragments of an interrupted dream
shiroku togireta yume no kirehashi wo tsukamaete
白く途切れた夢の切れ端をつかまえて
A boy runs
shounen wa hashiru
少年は走る
When he lets go, they disappear into the distant sound of the wind
te wo hanashitara dokomademo tooku kaze no ne ni kieteyuku
手を放したらどこまでも遠く風の音に消えてゆく
The kindness I could once see is now gone
itsuka mieta yasashisa wa mou nai
いつか見えた優しさはもうない
I just look at my feet, stepping forward alone
hitori fumidasu ashidake miteru
ひとり踏み出す足だけ見てる
I listened to the singing until it disappeared when morning came
asa ni wa kieta ano utagoe wo itsumademo kiiteta
朝には消えたあの歌声をいつまでも聞いてた
I followed the footprints we'd left behind into the distance
bokura ga nokoshita ano ashiato wo itsumademo otteta
僕らが残したあの足跡をいつまでも追ってた