It might be the other you that I've been looking for.
Somewhere beyond this sky is a girl with wings.
She spreads those wings and continues to be blown by the wind from the distant past,
just like long ago.
My mother passed away before she told me any more details.
Ever since then, my only companions whilst traveling have been that story of the girl in the sky and this doll.
Yukito-san, are you also searching for the same girl as your mother?
Well, there's no way that you're that girl.
Many people dream of flying through the sky.
That girl can fly too, right?
Yeah.
She has wings.
Wow.
I wish I had wings too.
We watched the fading vapor trails
kieru hikoukigumo bokutachi wa miokutta
消える飛行機雲僕たちは見送った
They were so dazzling, I ran away
mabushikute nigeta
眩しくて逃げた
I was so frustrated, I released your hand
kuyashikute yubi wo hanasu
悔しくて指を離す
The place she can't reach is still there in the distance
todokanai basho ga mada tooku ni aru
届かない場所がまだ遠くにある
She gazes at  it, keeping her wish to herself
negai hi dake himete mitsumeteru
願いだけ秘めて見つめてる
Children walk along the summer railway tracks
kodomotachi wa natsu no senro aruku
子供たちは夏の線路歩く
Holding in both hands their wishes to take flight
ryoute ni wa tobidatsu kibou wo
両手には飛び立つ希望を
Chasing, chasing the fading vapor trails
kieru hikoukigumo oikakete oikakete
消える飛行機雲追いかけて追いかけて
It hasn't changed since the day we crossed that hill
kono oka wo koeta ano hi kara kawarazu
この丘を越えたあの日から変わらず
And never will
itsumademo
いつまでも
And just as we are now, standing tall
massugu ni bokutachi wa aru youni
真っ直ぐに僕たちはあるように
We'll guard the strength of a sea god
watatsumi no youna tsuyosa wo mamoreru yo
わたつみのような強さを守れるよ
Surely
kitto
きっと
I'm home!
Hey, freeloader, here's a present for ya!
Oh, a sloth.
Isn't this cuter than that dirty doll of yours?
After all, I need to have you make some money so you can get out of here ASAP.
It's cute.
Episode 2
There's nothing like a drink after work!
I feel like I live for these times!
All right, freeloader, first up tonight is touching love confessions that bring a tear to the eye!
Entertain yourself!
Oh, Misuzu, are you sleepy?
Mm... I guess.
Come over here. You can use my lap as a pillow.
Eh?! I-It's okay. I'm not a child anymore.
I'll go to bed now.
Good night.
Ah, she ran away.
Do you let her use your lap as a pillow a lot?
Idiot! It was a joke.
As if that girl would cuddle up to someone as pathetic as me!
That girl...
Did she say "gao" again today?
Yeah.
I whacked her each time she said it.
When she was little, she thought chicks were baby dinosaurs for some reason.
And so when she saw the chicks at a summer fair, she begged for one.
But we were so poor then; we couldn't buy one.
Ever since then, she learned to say "gao" whenever something happens.
I'm not cut out to be a parent.
I should have stayed alone.
Besides, that girl is a little weird.
Weird?
But she seems to cheer up when she's with you,
so if possible, I hope you'll stay friends with her forever.
There's nothing more I can do for her now.
Come! It's time for a fun puppet show.
What is this?
It's kinda creepy.
It's like something you might see in a dream... I mean a nightmare.
Come on; let's go.
Hey!
Give me my payment!
This doesn't work at all!
Piko!
Oh, you again?
Your name was Potato, wasn't it?
Pikkori.
Piko!
Piko pikoo.
Pikopikopiko.
Piko pika piko piko pika piko pikopiko...
What are you doing?
Is your daughter well?
Yes.
She says white rice tastes great and asks for seconds and thirds, so it makes cooking worthwhile.
Please tell her to be careful of an upset stomach.
I'll tell her.
See you.
Now then...
What have you been doing loitering in front of my place?
Pikapikapika piko piko...
Now, let's go home, shall we...
Hey! Don't ignore me like that!
Piko! Piko! Piko! Piko! Piko! Piko! Piiikoo.
Oh, Potato. What are you doing?
You know him?
Oh, Yukito-kun?
Yukito-kun is talking with Onee-chan.
KIRISHIMA
CLINIC
Piko pikopiko pi-pikopiko piko piko piko!
Wow, that's amazing!
Piko piko piko piko...
It looks like Potato's become your fan too.
Wait, did you say your name is Yukito Kunisaki-kun?
Your skill is impressive, but I doubt you'll be able to make much money with that trick.
Piko piko piko piko...
Piko?
Piko!
Still, I've been traveling from town to town using this trick.
Wow.
That must mean you've made lots of money in this town too, right?
Huh? You haven't?
Would you be interested in working at this clinic?
My name is Hijiri Kirishima.
Since my parents passed away, I'm the only doctor in town.
I've been looking for someone to do odd jobs.
Why bamboo?
I'm so happy!
I've always wanted to try this.
Why are you eating nagashi soumen for lunch?
In this house, if Kano asks for nagashi soumen, we eat nagashi soumen.
Piko piko.
No matter how you look at it, this is an unfair seating arrangement.
Why's that?
You'd eat a lot if you didn't sit there.
Piko!
Well, I'll see you tomorrow at the same time.
You'll pay me better, right?
Okay, as an added benefit, I'll let you put on your puppet shows in front of my clinic.
Don't worry; I'll let you eat lunch too.
It was fun!
Let's play again tomorrow, Yukito-kun!
Piko! Piko!
See you!
Piko! Piko! Pikooo!
Was taking that job a mistake?
Man, this town really doesn't have many people walking around.
I guess traffic accidents are rare too!
NIINUMA  RICE  AND  LIQUOR  SHOP
Oh, I'm so sorry!
Ah, no. It's my fault.
Thank you very much.
D-Don't worry about it.
It's my fault too for bumping into you.
But why do you have so much stuff?
My daughter loves rice and eats so much of it that I just...
Thank you very much.
Oh, it's not much, but...
N-N-No, it's okay.
I can't accept it.
No.
It's not much, but please accept this.
Doesn't anyone in this town use actual money?
Besides, what kind of girl can eat that much rice?
Misuzu's late.
Oh, a sloth!
He's so cute!
She's like a smaller version of Misuzu.
Hey, what happened to your parents?
Huh?
Are you lost by any chance?
Do you want to eat this?
It's yummy and cute.
Decide whether it's yummy or cute.
It's cute and yummy.
Oh.
Oh, Yukito-san, who is this girl?
I think she's lost.
What's your name?
Six-years-old.
What an incredible name!
Yukito-san, keep quiet.
What's your name?
It's what you say before your age, right?
Saika Shino, six-years-old.
Oh, Shino-san.
Bye-bye.
Mm, bye-bye!
I heard that girl has to be admitted to hospital.
She's sick?
Is it serious?
No, it doesn't seem too serious.
And she said the sloth has become her friend, so she'll be all right.
I see.
I had a dream.
That's nothing unusual.
I have them too.
A mysterious dream,
a dream about the sky.
I was in the sky.
It was a world I'd never seen before.
See, when you sit like this, the clouds are above you.
But in my dream, the clouds were beneath my feet.
Between the clouds, I could see the bright blue of the sea.
But I couldn't tell how far it was.
Everything extended endlessly into infinity.
Hey,
did you have wings in your dream?
Eh?
I don't know... I didn't notice.
You shouldn't go around telling people about such dreams.
It's all right.
I've only told you.
Wow, it fits you well somehow.
Don't you have a different one?
The rest are all too small.
Mm, it smells nice.
What's this?
A boxed lunch.
I put all my effort into it, so it's exceedingly delicious.
A boxed lunch?
You went to the trouble just for...
Please deliver it to Kano.
Anything wrong?
Nothing...
Kano is at school again taking care of the animals today.
If you dare eat it on the way there...
I'll deliver it carefully and quickly.
Can we stop by the bookstore?
There are quite a lot of students.
I guess they're here for remedial classes, club activities, or student government.
Piko!
This might be a good place to set up shop.
Everyone, please welcome my puppet show with lots of applause!
YUKITO
FESTIVAL
KUNI
SAKI
Woohoo!
Kunisaki, you're the best!
Everybody, say it!
Love and Peace!
Kunisaki, you're the best!
There's no way that'll ever happen.
Piko?
Hm?
Piko.
If I take this weird creature in, the high school might erupt in a great panic.
Don't move from here until I tell you it's okay.
Pikori.
There's something I'd like to ask.
Yes?
I've come to deliver a boxed lunch to Kano Kirishima.
Do you know where she is?
Kano-rin?
Kano-rin... Maybe she's still in the nurse's office.
The nurse's office?
No, no.
She said she was going to the rooftop because she wanted some air.
She said, "kyuu," and collapsed all of a sudden after mumbling something.
I think she just got a little light-headed.
I see.
So you worried about me.
Are you sure you're really okay?
Geez, you're overreacting.
I just felt a little dizzy.
I see.
The sky is so high, isn't it?
Yukito-kun, can't you fly?
There's no way I can fly.
But you can move a doll.
That has absolutely nothing to do with anything.
Come to think of it, didn't you say something about if you could use magic?
Oh, that!
Yes, because I can use magic.
Huh?
That's not completely true.
I can't use it until I grow up.
But I've already decided what I'll do with my first spell.
What are you going to do?
It's a secret.
I'll tell you what I'll do second, though.
I don't particularly want to hear about it.
What? Listen!
If you don't listen, it'll claw its way out of your stomach
and turn into something so strong that mankind can't even fight back!
"The Earth, the Earth is in great trouble!" Is that it?
Yes!
You've got to protect the Earth!
So, what's the second thing you want to do?
Um, well...
I want to fly through the sky.
Magic to fly through the sky...
Hey!
Yukito Kunisaki!
Don't attack me so suddenly!
Why are you angry?
And after I went through the trouble of calling out to you too!
Shut up!
My head is spinning.
Oh, what a dirty doll!
Oh, that's mine.
It's so tattered.
Poor thing.
You're suffering under a stupid master, aren't you?
Don't say that so poignantly!
All right, I'll save you!
Huh?!
See ya!
Hey, wait!
Come and get me!
SHIMANO
BOOKSTORE
Are you a Butt Swayling?
Hey, where are you going?!
Catch me if you can!
Stop it...
already!
Oh, Minagi!
You're lucky!
You get to have Minagi fix it.
Now, say thank you.
Who are you to act so high and mighty?!
Ta-da.
It's done.
Wow, it's all nice now!
Whoa... you're good.
Ahem.
It must be a very precious doll to you
since you are always carrying it around.
Yeah, I guess.
It's the physical form of a precious memory...
Eh?
Am I wrong?
No,
that might be it.
You ruined the mood!
Shut up!
I present you with a coupon for rice.
YEN
RICE COUPON
Worldwide
YEN
RICE COUPON
Worldwide
YEN
RICE COUPON
Worldwide
YEN
RICE COUPON
Worldwide
YEN
RICE COUPON
Worldwide
Eh?
You're hungry, right?
Isn't Tohno-san great?
Not only is she good at her studies, but she's good at sewing too.
Well?
Where are we headed?
A place where lots of people gather.
If you put on your puppet show there, you'll have many customers.
Oh.
It's Mommy.
Exactly what kind of work does she do?
It's a secret.
I wonder if she went to pray at the shrine.
The shrine?
Yeah, that's where we're headed now.
There's no one here!
It's almost time for the summer festival.
It'll be full of people then.
Lots of kids from town will come.
The kids in this town are all unruly.
Waah, wait!
What is it?
Well, uhh...
Since we're here, I thought we could play some more.
Let's play hide-and-seek.
Huh?
Hide-and-seek.
I want to play it with you.
How old do you think we are?
Then... Then... let's catch bugs.
Gao~
Oh, fish!
I want to catch fish.
You don't care what we play, do you?
It's summer vacation, so I want to play as much as I can.
Hey, Misuzu!
I'm going now, got that?
Huh?
Gotcha!
Come to think of it, do you still believe that when a chick grows up, it'll become a dinosaur?
Geez, I know already!
Chicks grow up to be chickens.
Actually, what I really wanted wasn't a chick or a baby dinosaur.
I heard that you cried all day long.
It didn't matter what it was, as long as Mommy bought it for me.
What a fun day!
Really?
I'm glad.
I've never had so much fun on my birthday before, so I'm really glad.
Today's... your birthday?
Yeah.
Why did you keep quiet about something that important?
Huh? Because...
If I'd known, I would've tried to buy you a present at least.
Rice
Coupon
Yukito-san?
Go on home.
No one would watch a puppet show at night.
Oh, are you done for the day?
Huh?
Show me something, even if it's just a little.
That's amazing.
Hm...
But I don't suppose kids would be interested.
It's none of your business.
Oh, excuse me.
What's this?
I went to visit some friends, but they weren't home.
I'll give it to you.
A thank-you gift for showing me something so unusual.
It's really good.
Aren't you lucky that I was given a cake?
Yup, and the number of candles was just right.
I wonder if he was planning to celebrate someone's birthday.
Didn't Haruko remember that today is your birthday?
Mommy's busy, so...
Pretty...
How is it? Are you satisfied?
Yes, I'm happy.
Then let's go home.
Kano...
Eh?
Hey, Kano!
The shrine again?
I think she went in.
Oh!
Like the number of stars in the heavens,
the number of trees in the mountains,
the number...
Kano!
Grasping the white fragments of an interrupted dream
shiroku togireta yume no kirehashi wo tsukamaete
白く途切れた夢の切れ端をつかまえて
A boy runs
shounen wa hashiru
少年は走る
When he lets go, they disappear into the distant sound of the wind
te wo hanashitara dokomademo tooku kaze no ne ni kieteyuku
手を放したらどこまでも遠く風の音に消えてゆく
The kindness I could once see is now gone
itsuka mieta yasashisa wa mou nai
いつか見えた優しさはもうない
I just look at my feet, stepping forward alone
hitori fumidasu ashidake miteru
ひとり踏み出す足だけ見てる
I listened to the singing until it disappeared when morning came
asa ni wa kieta ano utagoe wo itsumademo kiiteta
朝には消えたあの歌声をいつまでも聞いてた
I followed the footprints we'd left behind into the distance
bokura ga nokoshita ano ashiato wo itsumademo otteta
僕らが残したあの足跡をいつまでも追ってた
Next Episode Preview
At least work enough to earn your wages.
Potato!
Pikopiko!
Magical powers.
There are so many mysteries in the world.
Isn't she always weird?
No, not like that.
Oh, if there's nothing, then it's all right.
What are you talking about?
I won!
V!
Help me!
I can't do it well at all!
Episode 3
Piko! Piko! Pik-