Oh.
What's going on?
Kano!
Wake up!
Hey, Kano!
Don't be so rough!
It hurts...
It really hurts...
Onee-chan...
Wha-?
Yukito-kun?
Where am I?
What happened... to me?
We watched the fading vapor trails
kieru hikoukigumo bokutachi wa miokutta
消える飛行機雲僕たちは見送った
They were so dazzling, I ran away
mabushikute nigeta
眩しくて逃げた
I was so frustrated, I released your hand
kuyashikute yubi wo hanasu
悔しくて指を離す
The place she can't reach is still there in the distance
todokanai basho ga mada tooku ni aru
届かない場所がまだ遠くにある
She gazes at  it, keeping her wish to herself
negai hi dake himete mitsumeteru
願いだけ秘めて見つめてる
Children walk along the summer railway tracks
kodomotachi wa natsu no senro aruku
子供たちは夏の線路歩く
Holding in both hands their wishes to take flight
ryoute ni wa tobidatsu kibou wo
両手には飛び立つ希望を
Chasing, chasing the fading vapor trails
kieru hikoukigumo oikakete oikakete
消える飛行機雲追いかけて追いかけて
It hasn't changed since the day we crossed that hill
kono oka wo koeta ano hi kara kawarazu
この丘を越えたあの日から変わらず
And never will
itsumademo
いつまでも
And just as we are now, standing tall
massugu ni bokutachi wa aru youni
真っ直ぐに僕たちはあるように
We'll guard the strength of a sea god
watatsumi no youna tsuyosa wo mamoreru yo
わたつみのような強さを守れるよ
Surely
kitto
きっと
Can you stand?
Yes.
O-Oh.
Thanks.
Don't worry about it.
Do you remember anything?
No.
I'm sorry.
There's really no need to apologize.
What was that field of pampas grass?
You saw it too?
Kano!
What is the meaning of this?!
Listen carefully, okay?
Yes, I am holding her, but it's not what you think it is.
It's not like I gave an innocent girl some alcohol and took her to a secluded place...
That's enough!
Wait! Wait!
Onee-chan?
Oh.
Episode 3
I can't say it enough, but I am very sorry.
KIRISHIMA
CLINIC
I wasn't aware of the situation, so I became a little upset.
You call that "a little upset"? You old hag.
Did you say something?
Nope, nothing at all.
I have to apologize too.
I'm sorry, Yukito-kun.
And, uh...
Kamio,
Misuzu Kamio.
I see.
Your face seems familiar.
I don't really stand out much.
However, we've met before
since you've been here a few times for checkups.
In the end, lots of weird things really did happen on your birthday.
But that just makes it all the more memorable.
Why don't you become friends with Kano instead of just playing with me all the time?
The two of you might get along pretty well.
After all, you're both pretty weird.
I guess.
Oh.
What's wrong?
I forgot to get my pay for today's work.
Go on home.
Can't you wait till tomorrow?
She might be difficult if I try to pick it up tomorrow.
Hey, where's my-
Hm.
They've gone to sleep already?
How careless...
Eeep!
Geez!
I told you not to turn the lights on so suddenly!
Oh, sorry.
But I can't properly examine you in the dark.
Hm... Kano, you've grown so much.
Hey, stop it, Onee-chan!
Don't touch me in weird places.
This is a proper clinical technique called "palpation".
Examinations don't require caressing!
Huh?
Did you hear that?
What?
Nyaa.
Oh, I guess it was just a cat.
But we don't have any cats here.
Oh yeah.
I guess it was just my imagination.
I guess.
So, Kano, let's continue.
Kano?
Hey, what's wrong, Kano?
I see.
It's back again?
It's been a while.
Again?
Stop it!
Repeating the same words, over and over.
This child is my life,
my only treasure.
No!
Kano is mine!
She's my precious little sister!
What?
What, what, what?
Why is Onee-chan hugging me?
You were falling asleep.
What?
You came and hugged me, so I held you in return.
Huh?
I don't remember that at all.
That's why I told you to hurry up and go to bed.
Okay.
But can we stay like this for just a little longer?
You held me like this when Daddy passed away – remember?
Yeah, that's right.
Onee-chan,
you smell nice.
Wah, a cicada flew in through the vent again!
Wah, the soy sauce bottle fell over!
Wah, the salad oil spilled!
Wah, Yukito-san's bacon and eggs got messed up!
Wah-wah-wah-wah!
Hey, Misuzu!
I won!
V!
Yukito-san?
Is something wrong?
Hey, something happened to this food, didn't it?
Nothing happened, nothing.
Why are you looking at me as if, "wow, he's actually eating it!"?
I'm not looking like that, not like that.
Yukito-san, is it good?
Yeah.
Really?
It doesn't taste like cicadas?
What do you mean by that?!
Nothing, nothing at all.
Yukito-san?
Hm?
We're here.
Oh, sorry.
What's wrong?
Is something bothering you?
Kind of...
Is it about last night?
Well... this and that...
Hmm...
Then I'll see you later, okay?
Okay.
G-Gao!
Hey.
At least do enough to earn your wages.
I've done everything already.
Then I have something else for you.
Come over here.
Why are you looking at me like that?
If you want to say something, just say it.
But a pay raise is out of the question.
That's not it.
Then what is it?
Actually, it's about last night...
Hey!
Have you seen Potato?
Potato?
Now that you mention it, I haven't seen him.
Yes, I've been looking for him for a while, but I can't seem to find him!
Potato!
Piko piko!
Potato, come on out!
Piko!
Potato!
Piko piko!
Potato... Where could he be?
The sun's starting to set now.
What's wrong?
No, it's nothing.
Let's keep looking.
Not here either.
I can't think of anywhere else to look.
Can't you use your magic to find him?
What?
Hm.
I don't think my magic works like that.
I see.
When I was given this bandana,
I was told to keep it on until I become an adult.
I can't take it off until then, no matter what.
When I take it off, I'll be able to use my magic.
Who gave it to you?
I was little, so I don't remember,
but it's been wrapped around my wrist ever since.
It's been troublesome at times, like during swimming and health checkups,
and I was even teased a few times too.
I see.
But, you know, Onee-chan always saved me.
That's how I've been able to make it this far.
Oh.
We've come all the way to school.
There's no way he could possibly be here.
Eh? What is it?
Wait up!
Hey, Yukito-kun, what's gotten into you?
I just realized where Potato is.
Really?
He's right over there.
Right over there?
You mean, at school?
Yeah.
He should be in here.
What?
In here?
Are you sure?
Oh!
Potato!
Pika.
We finally found you!
Geez, don't ever make me worry like that again.
Piko Piko!
But what were you doing here?
And Yukito-kun, how did you know that he was here?
That's... well... uh... what do you call it?
Piko Pikopik-
Well, it's a kind of magic.
Right?!
Piko...
Now listen, Potato.
Don't ever wander off again without telling me, okay?
Piko.
Now you're just saying that.
But I'm glad.
Kano.
Yes?
Do you really not remember anything about what happened last night?
No.
I'm sorry.
I really am.
No, it doesn't really matter.
Yukito-kun, will you listen to something?
Sure, you can tell me anything you want.
I hardly remember anything about my mother.
Apparently, she was never very healthy.
She became sick right after she gave birth to me
and passed away when I was about three.
Dad would often say, "Your mom was like you."
But I still couldn't picture her very well.
Oh, but, you know? It's not so bad; I wasn't that lonely.
Onee-chan was like a mom to me, and Dad was always around too.
But that means that Onee-chan was without a mom for a long time.
Recently, I realized how unfair that was.
Dad was always busy with the clinic, and then he got sick himself from working too hard.
The only thing I could do was watch.
It's still like that.
Onee-chan works and takes care of me, but I can't really do anything to help her.
I'm not much help either.
That's not true, not at all!
If...
If I could use magic,
I...
would use it to meet my mom.
I want to meet her and apologize
for many things.
You should thank her, not apologize.
Eh?
Your mother is the reason that you're here now.
If someone said to me, "I'm sorry that you gave birth to me,"
I'd be furious.
I see.
You're right!
What about your mom, Yukito-kun?
What kind of person is she?
She's not here anymore either.
A long time ago, she went to the same place your mom is.
Is that so?
My mom was looking for a girl in the sky.
A girl?
Yeah.
"Somewhere beyond this sky is a girl with wings."
That was my mom's favorite saying.
I'm looking for that girl too.
Hm...
Then, some day when I can fly, I'll look for that girl for you.
KAMIO
I'm home.
You're late.
Are you alone?
The girl's in her room.
She wasn't feeling very well,
so she's in bed.
Shouldn't you be with her?
If I were there, she wouldn't rest up.
You're her mother, so it shouldn't bother her.
Even though I'm her mother, we do have other issues.
Misuzu, I'm coming in.
Oh, Yukito-san.
I heard that you aren't feeling well.
Yeah, but it's nothing serious.
Sorry I couldn't pick you up today.
It's okay.
After all, you're busy with other things.
Well, okay.
You really like dinosaurs, don't you?
Why does she like dinosaurs so much?
Who knows?
She's always liked them, ever since she was a little girl.
You really don't know anything about her, even though she's your daughter.
Did you forget that it was her birthday yesterday?
Hey, does that girl act strangely during the day?
Isn't she always strange?
That's not what I meant.
Oh, if there's nothing, then it's all right.
What are you talking about?
Now, enough with this trivial talk; it's finally the main event of the day.
The erotic confessions corner!
How did we get to that?!
Oh, just saying the title turns me on!
Are you a pervert or something?!
Romantic?
Yeah, romantic.
Because dinosaurs thrived for millions and millions of years,
but then they faced their end and went extinct.
It's kind of sad and makes me emotional.
Are you still having those dreams?
Yeah, I still am.
In my dreams, I'm going back in time.
How do you know that?
I don't know how to describe it, but I know.
From the scent of the wind, the feel of the breeze on my skin,
the way the air moves, and the passing of the seasons,
I know that I'm going back in time.
I've never heard of a dream like that.
Yukito-san.
Hmm?
I wonder where my dreams are taking me.
Here I come!
Piko!
Potato.
Try not to get hit by accident.
Piko!
So you're cracking watermelons today, huh?
Yeah, Kano wanted to do it.
Piko!
Aren't you spoiling her a bit?
Ready...
Piko!
See you tomorrow!
There's no one here.
So I can't make money here either...
Yukito Kunisaki!
Yukito-san!
Don't crash into me every time!
Why didn't you come yesterday?
Yesterday?
We were waiting for you.
Minagi missed you.
It's all right.
Don't always act so strong!
I'm sorry.
I was a little busy yesterday.
To make up for it, you will live here from now on!
Huh?
Eh?
What are you saying?
To start with, didn't you want me to leave town?
That was different!
Wow! He got up!
I can't figure it out at all.
I win.
It really is mysterious, isn't it?
You have such a wonderful, special talent, Kunisaki-san.
Applause.
Clap clap clap.
I can use a bit of what is called magic.
Magical powers?
There are so many mysteries in the world.
Well then, I have a special thank-you gift.
Ta-da.
YEN
RICE COUPON
Worldwide
YEN
RICE COUPON
Worldwide
YEN
RICE COUPON
Worldwide
YEN
RICE COUPON
Worldwide
YEN
RICE COUPON
Worldwide
YEN
RICE COUPON
Worldwide
YEN
RICE COUPON
Worldwide
YEN
RICE COUPON
Worldwide
YEN
RICE COUPON
Worldwide
YEN
RICE COUPON
Worldwide
Kunisaki-san?
A girl with wings?
Yeah.
I'm looking for the same girl as my mother.
Do you think I'm strange?
When I was a little girl, I had a picture book like that.
A picture book?
Inside the picture book, there was a girl with pure white wings on her back.
As a little girl, I dreamt of flying through the sky with her someday.
There's nothing strange about you,
even if the purpose of your journey is to look for her
because everyone has a destination they wish to reach.
The stars are going to be beautiful again tonight.
Minagi!
Help me!
I can't do it well at all!
I'm coming, Michiru.
A destination, huh?
I'm done with today's homework!
Yukito-san!
Hmm?
Let's play cards.
C-A-R-D-S.
Huh?
Why, all of a sudden?
I've been wanting to play cards with you for a long time.
Play by yourself.
Ahh, we have come from a faraway planet...
I want to play cards.
Misuzu-kun!
Are you there?
Huh?
Kano disappeared again.
Did she come here?
How about the shrine?
I've already looked there.
I'll try the school.
Can you two go that way?
Okay.
Yukito-san, do you have any idea where she might be?
Not really.
We just have to look anywhere we can think of.
Kano!
Kirishima-san!
Whoa!
Piko!
Potato!
Hm?
Pi-ka!
Is he asking us to follow him?
Piko piko piko piko piko piko.
The shrine again?
But she said she'd already looked there.
Kano!
Hey, are you all right?
Tightly clasping my only treasure...
Kano?
Then, perhaps...
with my own hands...
Hey, Kano.
Grasping the white fragments of an interrupted dream
shiroku togireta yume no kirehashi wo tsukamaete
白く途切れた夢の切れ端をつかまえて
A boy runs
shounen wa hashiru
少年は走る
When he lets go, they disappear into the distant sound of the wind
te wo hanashitara dokomademo tooku kaze no ne ni kieteyuku
手を放したらどこまでも遠く風の音に消えてゆく
The kindness I could once see is now gone
itsuka mieta yasashisa wa mou nai
いつか見えた優しさはもうない
I just look at my feet, stepping forward alone
hitori fumidasu ashidake miteru
ひとり踏み出す足だけ見てる
I listened to the singing until it disappeared when morning came
asa ni wa kieta ano utagoe wo itsumademo kiiteta
朝には消えたあの歌声をいつまでも聞いてた
I followed the footprints we'd left behind into the distance
bokura ga nokoshita ano ashiato wo itsumademo otteta
僕らが残したあの足跡をいつまでも追ってた
Next Episode Preview
Yukito-kun, I am writing this to you because I think you'll believe me.
I've finally decided to go to the sky.
I have a feeling that it will make everyone happy.
I have a feeling that I will meet the girl you are looking for too.
I don't know how long it will take,
but I will definitely bring her to you.
I'd be grateful if you could help Onee-chan until I return.
Episode 4