Then, perhaps...
with my own hands...
Hey, Kano.
Ah!
Argh.
Misuzu!
Kano!
Piko!
Piko piko!
Piko pikopiko piko!
We watched the fading vapor trails
kieru hikoukigumo bokutachi wa miokutta
消える飛行機雲僕たちは見送った
They were so dazzling, I ran away
mabushikute nigeta
眩しくて逃げた
I was so frustrated, I released your hand
kuyashikute yubi wo hanasu
悔しくて指を離す
The place she can't reach is still there in the distance
todokanai basho ga mada tooku ni aru
届かない場所がまだ遠くにある
She gazes at  it, keeping her wish to herself
negai hi dake himete mitsumeteru
願いだけ秘めて見つめてる
Children walk along the summer railway tracks
kodomotachi wa natsu no senro aruku
子供たちは夏の線路歩く
Holding in both hands their wishes to take flight
ryoute ni wa tobidatsu kibou wo
両手には飛び立つ希望を
Chasing, chasing the fading vapor trails
kieru hikoukigumo oikakete oikakete
消える飛行機雲追いかけて追いかけて
It hasn't changed since the day we crossed that hill
kono oka wo koeta ano hi kara kawarazu
この丘を越えたあの日から変わらず
And never will
itsumademo
いつまでも
And just as we are now, standing tall
massugu ni bokutachi wa aru youni
真っ直ぐに僕たちはあるように
We'll guard the strength of a sea god
watatsumi no youna tsuyosa wo mamoreru yo
わたつみのような強さを守れるよ
Surely
kitto
きっと
It looks like you might have this bruise for a while.
I've caused you a lot of trouble.
I apologize, Kunisaki-kun, Kamio-san.
Oh, not at all.
It's not a problem.
It started when Kano was still a little girl.
Episode 4
It was the first summer after our mother died.
Look! Look!
Onee-chan, balloons!
BALLOONS
There, there!
Hey, hey, if I bought one, would I be able to fly in the sky?
If one balloon could lift a person, the stall would have flown away by now.
Hm, I see.
Onee-chan, you're so smart!
But then that means I can fly through the sky if I have lots of  balloons, right?
Well, yes, maybe then you could fly.
But we can only afford one.
If it's one balloon, we'll just have to blow it up really big!
If we do that, it'll be able to lift much more weight.
And we won't be able to buy anything else.
Okay!
Here.
Wow, thank you, Onee-chan!
Ah!
Kano always wanted to fly through the sky
because she believed that she could see her mother there.
I told her that her mother was in the sky, watching over her.
Neither Father nor I could tell her
that her mother was no longer around anywhere.
Oh.
Kano!
Then what happened?
Nothing in particular.
Who's playing here?
We put the feather back and went home together.
So I can't go to where Mommy is anymore?
The following morning, Kano started acting strangely.
She became afraid of bright lights,
and she started wandering around outside in a daze,
mumbling nonsense to herself.
One night, Kano was gone before I realized it.
After I rushed to look for her,
I found her in the examination room, pressing a scalpel to her wrist.
I caught her in time,
so it wasn't serious.
But I realized then; she wasn't Kano.
It felt like someone else was pretending to be Kano.
Was it a case of multiple personalities?
It might have been.
This is a magical bandana.
If you keep wearing it until you're an adult, you'll be able to use magic.
So, no matter what happens, never take it off.
I see.
So you were the one who gave Kano the bandana.
If she ever tried to unconsciously cut her wrist again,
she'd see the bandana and come to her senses.
That was the idea.
Kano doesn't really remember it.
There never was any such thing as magic.
I decided to follow in my father's footsteps.
I thought that if I became a doctor, I'd be able to cure Kano's illness.
What was that feather that Kano touched?
I don't know.
Apparently it's been there at the shrine for a long time.
Even the shrine-keeper doesn't know the details.
Perhaps it's the curse of that feather.
As a doctor, I can't accept that kind of explanation.
However, it's possible that the feather was a psychological trigger for her illness.
Back then, Kano was suffering from a lot of stress after losing her mother.
That was probably the root cause.
Are you going to Kirishima-san's place today too?
Yeah.
I have my job there.
Maybe I'll go visit Kano later too.
You should.
Aren't you glad you made a new friend?
Last night, I had another dream.
Eh?
A dream of flying through the sky.
In this dream, I was traveling further and further back in time.
Last night, I was mourning in the sky.
You were mourning?
As usual, my body was soaring through the sky,
but I was overwhelmed by sadness.
I wondered why I felt so sad surrounded by such beautiful, comforting breezes.
It was only a dream.
It's not about you personally.
Right.
When you're not smiling, I also feel...
Eh?
Anyway, just keep smiling.
V!
There's nothing here...
Found it!
What are you doing?
Yukito Kunisaki!
What are you doing here?
That's what I was about to say.
Are you picking up stuff like that to collect garbage or something?
Shut up!
Collecting interesting things from places like this is my hobby.
That's the most pathetic hobby ever!
Leave me alone!
Jeez.
You get to play day in and day out. You're in a very enviable position.
You're pretty much like that too, aren't you, Yukito Kunisaki?
I have a proper job.
In fact, I'm on my way to my job right now to work hard.
Huh?
Hm?
Bathroom?
No! Look over there.
Hm?
That's...
Is that, by any chance, Tohno's mom?
Huh?
What's wrong?
No, it's nothing.
Minagi looks sad.
Eh?
Hey, call Minagi over.
I think she's lonely all by herself.
That's true.
Let's try it.
Tohno!
Kunisaki-san.
What happened?
What brings you here?
Nothing in particular.
I was just taking a walk with Michiru.
Sakuma Cycling Shop
Oh.
Huh?
Where'd she go?
Were you with Michiru?
Yeah, I was with her.
Did Michiru say anything about the person who was with me just now?
No.
She didn't say anything in particular.
I see.
Then it's okay.
That person is your mother, right?
Eh?
I once helped her with a big cart of groceries.
Come to think of it, the two of you are rather similar.
I am a fragment of that person's dream.
Huh?
Piko piko piko pikopiko piko piko piko piko...
Don't run away, Potato.
Here, I'll scrub you.
Piko pikopiko... Piko!
You seem to be doing well.
Ah, Yukito-kun. Good morning.
I'm sorry. It seems that I caused you troubled yesterday too.
It wasn't a big deal.
Don't worry about it.
Oh, you came, Kunisaki-kun.
I have a lot of work for you to do today.
Is Kano-san taking a nap?
Yeah.
I told her to rest because of what happened yesterday.
It's about time for her to wake up.
I'll go check up on her.
Kano!
Huh?
Yukito-kun, I am writing this to you because I think you'll believe me.
I've finally decided to go to the sky.
I have a feeling that it will make everyone happy.
I have a feeling that I will meet the girl you are looking for too.
I don't know how long it will take,
but I will definitely bring her to you.
I'd be grateful if you could help Onee-chan until I return.
I know she is under a lot of stress.
P.S. I'm really sorry about the bruise on your neck.
Oh!
Piko! Pikopikopikopiko.
Pikopikopikopikopiko pikopikopikopikopikopiko.
Piko! Piko piko piko! Piko!
Piko piko. Piko!
Kano!
Wake up!
There are no superficial wounds.
Then what about the blood?
There's no sign of bleeding.
It doesn't seem to be life-threatening,
but what on Earth happened?
Maybe she tried to go up to the sky from here.
Oh?
What's this?
Oh!
What's wrong, Yukito-san?
Somehow, my emotions are acting up,
like I'm nostalgic... or sad.
Lay Kano down.
Kunisaki-kun.
My name is Shiraho.
Please listen to my story.
I remember – it was a beautiful autumn.
My husband and I had our first child.
She had a birthmark on her right wrist.
The villagers said it was ominous, but we never paid them any attention.
When Yakumo cried, I sang her a lullaby that I had learned from my mother.
Yakumo would always stop crying, but that day, she didn't.
I felt that the feather was a charm sent by God for her.
Take them away!
A war started, and my husband, like many others, never returned.
Did anyone in this village pick up a shining feather?
It is cursed! Anyone who has touched it should step forward and confess!
That night, I fled from the village.
And so, I arrived at this village.
The chief priest of the shrine was very kind to us outsiders.
I felt that Yakumo and I would be able to start a new life in this peaceful village.
However, that summer, an epidemic spread through the village, killing many.
Chief Priest, how is she?
The worst is over.
Her fever will come down in time.
However, the villagers believe the two of you brought the epidemic to the village.
No!
It was a mistake to invite the two of you here.
We worship a divine idol here.
The idol gives a sign to those who bring bad fortune.
If the villagers discover her birthmark, they will demand her to be sacrificed.
You're telling me to sacrifice her?!
In this land, we have always averted disasters by doing that.
This child is my life!
She's the only treasure my husband left me!
Don't resist!
Otherwise, you will be killed as well.
Then, perhaps...
with my own hands...
I can't!
I can't do it!
What mother would kill her own child?!
Even if it might destroy the world, what mother could bear to kill her own child?
I will take her place.
Please, somehow, save her.
Please save my child.
Don't do it!
Mommy?
Mommy, where are you?
I'm right here.
Mommy!
Is there anything you want to eat?
No, I'm already full!
Is there anything you want?
No.
Um... I'll go home now.
Onee-chan is waiting for me.
And Potato too.
And a new friend I've made.
Really?
He says he's looking for a girl in the sky.
I kind of wish that I were that girl.
If things are too hard for you, you can come with me, you know.
Um, Mommy?
Thank you.
I don't remember much about you,
and I might have cut your life short,
but...
Thank you for giving birth to me!
Oh!
I just wanted to say that.
Kano,
you don't have wings,
so live happily down there.
kono ko no kawaisa kagiri na ya
この子の可愛さ限りなや
Limitless are the ways this child is dear
ten ni tatoeba hoshi no kazu
天に例えば星の数
more so than the number of stars in the heavens,
yama de haki no kazu kaya no kazu
山では木の数かやの数
more so than the number of trees, the number of grass blades.
obana karukaya hagi kikyou
おばなかるかやはぎきこよう
Flowering grass, bush clover and bellflowers
nanakusa chigusa no kazu yori mo
七草千草の数よりも
More precious than all the flowers
daijina kono ko ga nennesuru
大事な　この　子　が　ねんねする
is my sleeping child
Just now...
Kamio-san, you saw it too?
Yes.
Oh.
Are you awake now?
Kano.
Yukito-kun...
Onee-chan.
Kano!
Pika!
Piko piko piko piko piko piko piko piko piko...
So, what was that feather?
Who knows?
Onee-chan, I met Mommy.
Yeah, I was watching.
I couldn't go to where she was,
but I was able to thank her, just like Yukito-kun told me to.
It's all thanks to Yukito-kun.
No, you're wrong.
That was your magic.
Yeah.
Let it soar into the sky for you.
Okay.
Grasping the white fragments of an interrupted dream
shiroku togireta yume no kirehashi wo tsukamaete
白く途切れた夢の切れ端をつかまえて
A boy runs
shounen wa hashiru
少年は走る
When he lets go, they disappear into the distant sound of the wind
te wo hanashitara dokomademo tooku kaze no ne ni kieteyuku
手を放したらどこまでも遠く風の音に消えてゆく
The kindness I could once see is now gone
itsuka mieta yasashisa wa mou nai
いつか見えた優しさはもうない
I just look at my feet, stepping forward alone
hitori fumidasu ashidake miteru
ひとり踏み出す足だけ見てる
I listened to the singing until it disappeared when morning came
asa ni wa kieta ano utagoe wo itsumademo kiiteta
朝には消えたあの歌声をいつまでも聞いてた
I followed the footprints we'd left behind into the distance
bokura ga nokoshita ano ashiato wo itsumademo otteta
僕らが残したあの足跡をいつまでも追ってた
Next Episode Preview
Bubbles are pretty.
They're empty, just like the sky.
I just get in the way, so I'm always playing by myself.
Did I do something wrong?
My mother couldn't accept reality,
so she chose to live in her dreams.
Is there a use for wings that cannot fly?
Episode 5