That child said he wanted to see the ocean.
But I couldn't take him.
There were so many things I wanted to do for him.
But I couldn't do a single thing,
even though the summer had just begun.
Yukito-san?
Yukito-san,
it's morning.
Yeah.
We watched the fading vapor trails
kieru hikoukigumo bokutachi wa miokutta
消える飛行機雲僕たちは見送った
They were so dazzling, I ran away
mabushikute nigeta
眩しくて逃げた
I was so frustrated, I released your hand
kuyashikute yubi wo hanasu
悔しくて指を離す
The place she can't reach is still there in the distance
todokanai basho ga mada tooku ni aru
届かない場所がまだ遠くにある
She gazes at  it, keeping her wish to herself
negai hi dake himete mitsumeteru
願いだけ秘めて見つめてる
Children walk along the summer railway tracks
kodomotachi wa natsu no senro aruku
子供たちは夏の線路歩く
Holding in both hands their wishes to take flight
ryoute ni wa tobidatsu kibou wo
両手には飛び立つ希望を
Chasing, chasing the fading vapor trails
kieru hikoukigumo oikakete oikakete
消える飛行機雲追いかけて追いかけて
It hasn't changed since the day we crossed that hill
kono oka wo koeta ano hi kara kawarazu
この丘を越えたあの日から変わらず
And never will
itsumademo
いつまでも
And just as we are now, standing tall
massugu ni bokutachi wa aru youni
真っ直ぐに僕たちはあるように
We'll guard the strength of a sea god
watatsumi no youna tsuyosa wo mamoreru yo
わたつみのような強さを守れるよ
Surely
kitto
きっと
Episode 5
Aren't you glad Kirishima-san recovered?
Yeah.
You know, when I saw that feather, I had a strange feeling too.
Yukito-san?
Huh? Did you say something?
You've been spaced out ever since you woke up.
Well...
I had a dream of when I was a kid.
A dream?
Don't worry about it.
More importantly, are you still having those dreams?
Yeah.
Last night's dream was different from any I've had before.
The moon was out and it was so bright.
I was trying to fly up to the sky.
I was sore all over, but I kept trying to go higher and higher.
And then, I heard voices.
Voices?
The voices of many people, trying to restrain me.
They echoed in my ears, so I couldn't climb anymore.
Well, I'll see you later.
Okay.
I'll be going.
Hey, be carefu–
Wah!
LUNA'S
BAR
Asahi
USED
BOOK
STORE
Wow!
It's great, isn't it, Onee-chan?
I wonder how it's walking without any strings.
Oh?
It fell down.
It got up! It got up!
This is the way kids should be.
Piko piko.
Hey, shouldn't you be with Kano?
Piko?
Piko piko piko.
Piko piko piko piko pikori.
Oh, she went to school to take care of the animals today?
Wait, why am I talking to you like it's normal?
Piko?
Hey, we have to go now.
Okay.
Doll-san, see you.
Shake hands, shake hands!
Let's go.
Okay.
So that's what being "close" is like, eh?
Pikori.
I made nothing again.
Misuzu is late.
Munch munch munch.
Chew chew chew chew.
Mumchy munchy munchy munchy munchy munchy.
Tohno.
Hm?
Oh, Kunisaki-san.
Hello.
Huh?
Wa hah hoo hooey hee?
If you're going to say something, swallow first.
Thank you for lunch.
You are welcome.
Have you seen Misuzu?
Kamio-san...
No.
I see.
Hey, hey!
Will you make hamburgers tomorrow too?
Okay.
Yay!
What a little pig!
Let go!
You let go first!
Michiru?
Oh.
You were able to use the shower?
Yeah.
How did you get the keys to this place?
My father was the stationmaster,
but he's not working here anymore.
Did he find work somewhere else?
Oh, yes.
As a token of apology, here.
RICE COUPON
And today...
this too.
That's the bottle I found yesterday!
This is stardust,
sand grains shaped like baby stars.
Wow, is it really?
Here.
Wow!
They rustle!
Kunisaki-san too.
Here.
I can have one too?
Yes.
With this, the three of us...
match.
This sand was given to me by my father, when I was a little girl.
Then isn't it something precious?
Are you sure?
Yes, if it's Kunisaki-san and Michiru.
It looks like Kamio-san has already left.
I see.
Is it possible she stayed late at school?
Maybe.
Oh, Kunisaki-san, are you busy?
Welcome to the Astronomy Club.
Wow!
The stars are already out!
Where are the other club members?
There are no others.
I am the only member.
The only?
That's why I'm club president.
It's a really selective club.
I see.
Does she come here often?
No. This is the first time I've brought her here.
Um, you're not going out of your way to be here, are you?
No.
I see.
I wanted the three of us to observe the stars together,
because she seems to like you, Kunisaki-san.
No, I don't think so.
It's true.
She talks about you constantly when she is with me.
She really likes you, Kunisaki-san.
I can't believe that at all.
I can tell how she feels,
because she is my other half.
Other half?
Michiru and I have always spent our time together, like this.
So cute...
Blush.
Huh?
Kunisaki-san, you're...
Me?
...always traveling alone, isn't that right?
Have you ever spent time like this?
The happiness of spending time with someone else...
The joy of living for someone else's sake...
I'm sure even I have,
though it was a long, long time ago.
See you!
I have to go now!
Mm, see you tomorrow.
Okay, then it's Michiru Dash!
I'm sorry.
You don't have to walk me home.
No. I don't mind.
You're pretty tall.
Do you not like tall girls?
Nah.
A good figure is an advantage.
Blush.
Actually, I happen to be rather proud of it myself too.
Proud of it, huh?
Just a bit.
The taller you are, the closer you are to the sky.
Thank you for walking me home.
Don't mention it.
Please be careful walking home.
Yeah.
Welcome home.
Oh, who are you with?
A new member of the Astronomy Club.
I am?
Oh, I remember you.
Thank you very much for helping me.
Eh?
I told you, remember?
I helped her with some heavy bags the other day.
I'm sorry for having you go to the trouble of walking my daughter home.
Now, come on inside...
Michiru.
What's wrong, Michiru?
Dinner is already ready.
Yeah.
Hey, Tohno.
Goodbye.
I'm home.
I'm
doing my
homework.
Misuzu,
I'm coming in.
Hey, wake up.
You'll catch a cold.
Oh, Yukito-san, good morning.
It's still night now.
You should have told me you had to stay late at supplemental classes.
Sorry, I forgot.
Jeez... Huh?
This...
Are you keeping a picture diary?
Yeah. It's my choice of assignment for the summer.
Maestro!
Why did you betray me?!
You fool!
You think you can conduct this orchestra?!
What a joke!
Yes.
If I don't conduct, who will?
Give the baton to me!
The only way you'll get it is over my dead body!
You!
Appassionato God Fingers!
Geh! Hey!
That was the best part!
Let's play cards.
You're really persistent.
I just want to play cards with you.
Serious?
Yeah, serious.
No matter what?
Yeah, no matter what.
Okay, I'll play with you.
Yay!
Then what do you want to play?
Old Maid?
Poker?
Make it something simple that doesn't require thinking.
Okay then, let's play Memory.
Oh!
Hm? What's wrong?
Eh?
No, it's nothing.
I messed up.
Are you crying?
No, I'm not crying.
I can play.
I have to try my hardest.
What's wrong?
Are you feeling okay?!
I'm all right!
Misuzu!
What's wrong?
Hey!
Get a hold of yourself!
Misuzu!
Misuzu suddenly–
I know.
Do you mind stepping outside for a moment?
Misuzu.
Calm down, Misuzu!
She's been like this ever since she was a little girl.
She becomes like that when she's about to make a friend.
When she's about to make a friend?
I've had the doctor at the clinic look at her, and I've even tried going to a larger hospital,
but it was no use.
They all said it was probably only psychological and that she'd grow out of it.
She actually had an episode at school today too.
They called me at work, so I went to pick her up on my bike,
and brought her straight home.
I see.
I was hoping that she'd be all right with you,
since she's all right when she's with me.
Are you really leaving?
She'll suffer these attacks as long as I'm here, right?
I should keep my distance for a while.
I see.
Tell her that I'll still walk her to and from school, just like before.
Come over for dinner every now and then.
It's my fault that you weren't able to stay at my house.
Aren't you lonely living by yourself?
Even though I'm living alone, I've made quite a few friends somehow.
You have some friends too, right?
No, I don't.
I'm always alone,
because whenever I'm about to make a friend, I start crying.
Everyone always runs away from me.
But you have Haruko, right?
You're not alone.
My mom...
She's not my real mom.
Really?
Haruko-san is actually my aunt.
I was dumped onto her because I was such a strange kid.
Haruko-san didn't want me, but I still ended up living there.
Since I don't want to cause her trouble,
we live our separate lives under one roof.
That's why I don't say anything.
I'm a real burden on her, and I don't want to be any more trouble.
So, I play by myself, looking for weird juices, or playing cards.
Misuzu.
Hm?
Just keep smiling.
V!
Okay then, see you later.
Take care.
What's wrong?
Minagi hasn't come.
She's at school, right?
She'll be here eventually.
She's not supposed to be at school today.
Did I do something wrong?
Give me that for a second.
Wah!
Give it back!
Just watch, all right?
Stop it!
It's an indirect kiss!
Yuck!
Don't talk about adult stuff!
Wow!
Amazing! Amazing!
Do it again!
Wow!
Bubbles are so pretty.
They're empty, just like the sky.
She didn't come.
No, she didn't.
I wonder if something happened.
Let's try going to her house.
Minagi's house?
Yeah. If she isn't coming, then we should go visit her.
What's wrong?
I don't want to go to her house.
You're friends, right?
You've never been there?
Then I'll go by myself.
I have to pick up Misuzu too.
Thank you for walking me home.
Sorry, but I can't stay today.
You're not eating dinner with us?
I have somewhere to go.
See you tomorrow.
Oh!
Who are you?
I met you yesterday, remember?
I'm the new member of the Astronomy Club.
Yes?
I'm running an errand.
May I see your daughter?
Daughter?
Has she gone somewhere?
We don't have a daughter.
What?
Are you sure you've got the right house?
Oh!
Hey!
You're joking, right? Hey!
What are you doing here, skipping work?
Tohno-san's mother has been suffering from a psychological disorder.
I've been checking on her whenever I get the chance.
She's convinced that the older daughter, Minagi-san,
is instead the younger daughter that passed away.
She's believed that for a long time now.
But it seems her condition has suddenly changed.
When she accepted the fact that her younger daughter was, in fact, dead,
she erased Minagi-san from her mind.
In her mind, neither one of her daughters have ever existed.
I was supposed to have a little sister, named Michiru.
A precious little sister.
My mother was sad because I was closer to my father.
The baby she was expecting was supposed to fill the hole in her heart.
If you could have just one dream come true, what would it be?
Umm... Umm...
I want a little sister!
My mother couldn't accept the reality,
so she chose to live in her dreams.
And I became a fragment of that dream.
But last night, she saw herself in a dream having a miscarriage of Michiru.
According to Kirishima-sensei, that made my mother accept the reality.
When she saw me this morning, my mother said,
"Who are you?"
You can't go back?
This is the end of my dream.
It is the end of my dream, which I lived in as Michiru.
My wings have forgotten how to fly,
because for so long I've just been pretending.
Is there a use for wings that cannot fly?
Grasping the white fragments of an interrupted dream
shiroku togireta yume no kirehashi wo tsukamaete
白く途切れた夢の切れ端をつかまえて
A boy runs
shounen wa hashiru
少年は走る
When he lets go, they disappear into the distant sound of the wind
te wo hanashitara dokomademo tooku kaze no ne ni kieteyuku
手を放したらどこまでも遠く風の音に消えてゆく
The kindness I could once see is now gone
itsuka mieta yasashisa wa mou nai
いつか見えた優しさはもうない
I just look at my feet, stepping forward alone
hitori fumidasu ashidake miteru
ひとり踏み出す足だけ見てる
I listened to the singing until it disappeared when morning came
asa ni wa kieta ano utagoe wo itsumademo kiiteta
朝には消えたあの歌声をいつまでも聞いてた
I followed the footprints we'd left behind into the distance
bokura ga nokoshita ano ashiato wo itsumademo otteta
僕らが残したあの足跡をいつまでも追ってた
Welcome home!
Next Episode Preview
Maybe you're more suited to travel than I am.
Why don't you come with me, Tohno?
Eh?
Things can't remain like this after all.
I want to show you the world;
the real world, not a dream world.
Everything started with my sin...
Episode 6