Good morning.
What?
Yes?
Oh, right.
I spent the night here last night.
Breakfast is ready.
Wow.
Did you bring all this from your house?
Yes.
Maybe you're more suited to travel than I am.
Minagi!
Welcome home!
Michiru.
I was worried about you since you didn't come yesterday.
I'm really glad I made that wish.
Wish?
Yup.
I wished upon the stardust that you would come back.
I see.
All right, let's have breakfast, breakfast!
Yay!
I'm gonna eat too.
Hey, don't be such a pig.
What did you say?
Don't be so stingy!
I'm not stingy!
We watched the fading vapor trails
kieru hikoukigumo bokutachi wa miokutta
消える飛行機雲僕たちは見送った
They were so dazzling, I ran away
mabushikute nigeta
眩しくて逃げた
I was so frustrated, I released your hand
kuyashikute yubi wo hanasu
悔しくて指を離す
The place she can't reach is still there in the distance
todokanai basho ga mada tooku ni aru
届かない場所がまだ遠くにある
She gazes at  it, keeping her wish to herself
negai hi dake himete mitsumeteru
願いだけ秘めて見つめてる
Children walk along the summer railway tracks
kodomotachi wa natsu no senro aruku
子供たちは夏の線路歩く
Holding in both hands their wishes to take flight
ryoute ni wa tobidatsu kibou wo
両手には飛び立つ希望を
Chasing, chasing the fading vapor trails
kieru hikoukigumo oikakete oikakete
消える飛行機雲追いかけて追いかけて
It hasn't changed since the day we crossed that hill
kono oka wo koeta ano hi kara kawarazu
この丘を越えたあの日から変わらず
And never will
itsumademo
いつまでも
And just as we are now, standing tall
massugu ni bokutachi wa aru youni
真っ直ぐに僕たちはあるように
We'll guard the strength of a sea god
watatsumi no youna tsuyosa wo mamoreru yo
わたつみのような強さを守れるよ
Surely
kitto
きっと
Why didn't you wait for me this morning?
I came to get you.
Mm, I had something to do.
I'm sorry.
Well, it's okay.
Are you still having those dreams?
Yeah.
Last night, it was about a forest at night.
I was talking with someone in the forest.
Forest?
With whom?
I don't know, but there was someone beside me.
I asked her what an ocean was.
Then, she told me many things about the ocean.
It was really fun just talking to her.
It was so fun that I wanted to wrap her words up and keep them forever.
If it was that fun, then sleep forever.
G-Gao...
Ouch!
Episode 6
A fan, a fan!
Oh.
Kunisaki-san.
Welcome back!
Thanks.
You must be tired.
How did your puppet shows go?
Um... Well... Not good!
What?!
Yukito Kunisaki, you good-for-nothing!
What did you do that for?!
Shut up!
Someone who eats for free shouldn't talk so conceitedly!
What?! Why you!
Playing, eating and sleeping...
She's in a really enviable position.
Last night, I dreamt of my father.
Of your father?
A long time ago, we would often sit here together and watch the night sky.
It was a dream of those times.
Minagi.
In each and every star, there is a god watching over us.
They also purify the hearts of those who watch the stars.
A short time after that, he left home.
After my younger sister died, my parents started to fight.
Where is he now?
He married another woman in a faraway town.
When he left, he gave me this.
Hey, don't you have to work now?
Piko!
I'm taking a break.
Hey, Minagi has run away from home, right?
Huh?
Pikako.
Even if you try to hide it from me, I can tell, because I'm her best friend.
Things can't remain like this after all.
Minagi has to wake up from her dream.
What do you mean by that?
I'm gonna go home now, okay?
See you.
Piko.
Piko pika.
Hey!
Piko!
See you later!
Piko...
I am sorry to have bothered you.
Not at all.
If you need anything, don't hesitate to stop by.
Yes.
She's starting to remember?
Yeah.
She said she lost something important.
She came here just because of that?
I just told her that she would eventually remember when she found it.
The rest is up to Minagi-san's feelings.
Welcome home.
Is something wrong?
I've decided to leave town.
Eh?
I've stayed too long.
I think it's time for me to go.
I... see...
Why don't you come with me, Tohno?
Eh?
I want to show you the world;
the real world, not a dream world.
The world...
Let's go together to discover that world.
I'm ready.
All right. Let's go.
Um...
Kunisaki-san.
Before we go,
I want to say something to Michiru.
Don't worry; just follow me.
Okay, we're finally here.
Why?
Michiru said that she doesn't want to see Minagi looking sad.
Michiru said that?
You must decide for yourself what you are going to do.
If you want, you really can come on a journey with me.
I'll take you along to wherever I end up...
It's your choice.
You, Minagi Tohno, must decide of your own will.
Oh.
Mommy?
Oh?
Minagi...
Mommy!
The stars are amazing tonight too!
Yeah.
Do you think Minagi is looking at the stars too?
Yeah, probably with her mom.
I have to go home now.
Yeah, it's getting late.
If you want, I'll walk you home.
Where do you live?
I have a home to return to.
Michiru?
In the sky, there's a really sad-looking girl.
A girl?
In the sky?
That girl always just sees sad dreams and has nothing else.
She can't be happy, so all she can have is sad dreams.
On her back, she has wounded feathers,
feathers with a really mysterious power.
They're packed with the memories of many people.
I asked for one of the plumes,
because there was someone I wanted to comfort.
Also, I thought if that person became happy, then the girl in the sky would become happy too.
I see.
People can't live without memories, you know.
Still, they can't live on memories alone either.
You have to wake from your dreams sometime.
Because dreams that you don't wake up from eventually become sad.
So I'm going to return the feather.
I don't want to say goodbye to everyone,
'I dont want to say' or 'it's sad to say'
but because I'm just a dream...
Because stars must disappear when the sun rises...
Michiru, are you...
I'm a fragment of a dream.
My being here is just a dream.
But, you know, it was a really fun dream.
I was really happy.
Michiru...
The real Michiru...
wasn't allowed to be born into this world.
I met Michiru for the first time at the station.
Every day, I went to the station to pick my father up, even after he had left.
Father had already quit his job there,
but there was nothing else I could do.
Was it then that your mother started calling you Michiru?
Yes.
But as long as I was Michiru, Mother kept smiling.
Hijiri told me it was around then that you stopped smiling as much.
Yay!
It was one summer afternoon after a rain storm...
I felt like I had seen her before.
I felt that she was always nearby.
My name is Michiru.
I'm...
I'm... Minagi.
Everything started with my sin.
Sin?
If I hadn't wished for a little sister, no one would have had to dream.
I might even have to hurt Michiru,
but even then, I still want her to meet someone, someone very important.
Hey, wait up!
Kei-chan, hurry up, or we won't be able to get a spot at the fireworks.
I know, but wait! Wait!
Huh? I fell asleep?
You were probably tried from playing all day.
You must be hungry.
Shall we have dinner at my house?
At Minagi's house?
It's rare for my daughter to bring friends home, so I made a special dinner.
Oh, excuse me.
I haven't asked you your name yet.
Um... my name?
Yes, your name.
Can you tell me your name?
Tell her.
Are you sure?
Hm?
U-Um...
My name is... Michiru!
Michiru?
Yeah.
Ah, so your name is Michiru?
U-Um...
I'm actually, really, really...
Really...
Michiru.
Yes?
That's a wonderful name.
Eh?
My daughter has always loved hamburgers ever since she was little too.
She always said that when she got a little sister, she wanted her to eat my hamburgers.
Right, Minagi?
Yes.
Here, Michiru-chan.
Eat the hamburgers before they get cold.
You love them too, right?
Yeah.
Thanks for the food!
So, are they good?
Yes, they're really delicious!
These hamburgers are my own recipe.
Here you go.
I taught Minagi how to make them.
Is it ok?
Yes.
It'll make me very happy if you eat lots.
Thank you!
Goodbye...
Mommy.
Then I'll hold on to this for you, okay?
Take good care of it, okay, Minagi?
Yeah.
Michiru?
Michiru!
No. She didn't even say goodbye.
It's not too late.
There should still be time,
because the stars aren't out yet.
Michiru is probably over there.
Oh!
Oh.
Michiru!
Michiru, it's not safe.
It's too dangerous there, so come over here.
I can't.
I have to go now.
I had so much fun, so I have to go.
Don't make a face like that.
Minagi, you have to keep smiling.
Otherwise, I'll be sad.
Michiru...
I was able to be myself thanks to you.
If you leave, I think I won't ever be able to laugh again.
It's all right.
Minagi, you can laugh with people other than me now.
Hey, Minagi,
Yukito Kunisaki,
let's make a promise.
A promise?
The girl with wings continues to have sad dreams in the sky.
I'm going to go back to her.
I'll take the fun memories you guys gave me back to her.
So...
If you find her, I want you to tell her many more happy stories,
and free her from her sad dreams.
Yeah.
Minagi, always keep smiling, okay?
Say bye-bye with a smile, okay?
I can't...
I can't say goodbye with a smile...
Minagi...
...because I won't be able to see you anymore!
It's all right.
Because even after you wake up from a dream, the memories will still be with you.
So smile.
Make your memories of me be happy ones, forever.
This is something only you can do.
Minagi,
it's a promise.
Yes.
Are you smiling now?
Really?
Yes.
Then keep smiling.
Say bye-bye with a smile for me.
Are you smiling, Michiru?
Yeah.
Are you sad to go?
No, I'm not sad.
I'm smiling, after all.
Wouldn't it be wonderful if everyone kept smiling all the time?
The world would be filled with smiles, and everybody would be happy.
Yes.
Minagi.
Michiru.
Bye-bye.
Thank you, Michiru.
Hey, what's up?
Hope you're not running away again.
Is that a rice coupon?
It's a letter from my father.
He is inviting me to come see him during the summer holidays.
To my surprise, it seems that I have a little sister.
He and his current wife had a baby girl.
That girl... Her name is...
To be honest, I was a little hesitant,
but I've decided to go meet her.
Mother encouraged me to go too.
I see.
Tohno!
Wings that cannot fly have a use too.
They're precious memories of when you once flew in the sky.
Isn't that right, Michiru?
You like bubbles?
Yeah.
I love them!
But, but, I can't blow them very well.
Then shall I teach you how to do it?
Really?
Yes.
Let's be friends.
I'm Minagi.
What's your name?
It's, it's...
Misuzu!
I've come to pick you up.
Hm?
I'm doing my homework.
Hey, Misuzu!
Misuzu!
Wake up!
Open your eyes, Misuzu!
Misuzu!
Grasping the white fragments of an interrupted dream
shiroku togireta yume no kirehashi wo tsukamaete
白く途切れた夢の切れ端をつかまえて
A boy runs
shounen wa hashiru
少年は走る
When he lets go, they disappear into the distant sound of the wind
te wo hanashitara dokomademo tooku kaze no ne ni kieteyuku
手を放したらどこまでも遠く風の音に消えてゆく
The kindness I could once see is now gone
itsuka mieta yasashisa wa mou nai
いつか見えた優しさはもうない
I just look at my feet, stepping forward alone
hitori fumidasu ashidake miteru
ひとり踏み出す足だけ見てる
I listened to the singing until it disappeared when morning came
asa ni wa kieta ano utagoe wo itsumademo kiiteta
朝には消えたあの歌声をいつまでも聞いてた
I followed the footprints we'd left behind into the distance
bokura ga nokoshita ano ashiato wo itsumademo otteta
僕らが残したあの足跡をいつまでも追ってた
Next Episode Preview
Yukito-san.
It's not a coincidence that I started having dreams, is it?
I felt that this summer was special.
I wanted to try my best to make a friend.
Then, I met you and started having those dreams.
They're probably all connected, right?
So I want to do my best.
I want to make this summer the happiest ever,
because it's the summer that I met you, Yukito-san.
Episode 7