What exactly happened?
I was shocked when I found you collapsed on the floor.
I suddenly felt dizzy and tripped.
I'm sorry for making you worry.
Maybe you're slightly anemic.
What now?
Do you want to go to the hospital?
No, I'm fine.
I think I just need some rest.
Remedial classes have started already.
It won't matter if you miss one day, right?
Sleep today.
Yeah.
Yukito-san, what about your job?
I'll take the day off.
Day
Month
Day of week
Weather
Clear
Thursday
I went to school with Yukito-san.
It was really fun.
I played with Yukito-san.
A cicada flew into Yukito-san's breakfast.
I went to the train station with Yukito-san.
I went to the shrine with Yukito-san.
Don't read someone else's diary.
Don't you have anything else to write about?
That diary is my masterpiece.
Well, to put it bluntly, you don't have much talent for keeping a diary.
So from now on, write about what you want to do, not what you did.
But that's not a diary.
Yes, that's a diary.
I'll make everything you write come true.
I want to go to the beach with you, Yukito-san
because we've never gone down to the beach together.
I want to dig in the sand and pick up pretty shells.
Jeez...
We see the beach all the time, right?
Gao!
Ouch!
All right.
Eh?
We'll go to the beach,
together.
Yeah!
We watched the fading vapor trails
kieru hikoukigumo bokutachi wa miokutta
消える飛行機雲僕たちは見送った
They were so dazzling, I ran away
mabushikute nigeta
眩しくて逃げた
I was so frustrated, I released your hand
kuyashikute yubi wo hanasu
悔しくて指を離す
The place she can't reach is still there in the distance
todokanai basho ga mada tooku ni aru
届かない場所がまだ遠くにある
She gazes at  it, keeping her wish to herself
negai hi dake himete mitsumeteru
願いだけ秘めて見つめてる
Children walk along the summer railway tracks
kodomotachi wa natsu no senro aruku
子供たちは夏の線路歩く
Holding in both hands their wishes to take flight
ryoute ni wa tobidatsu kibou wo
両手には飛び立つ希望を
Chasing, chasing the fading vapor trails
kieru hikoukigumo oikakete oikakete
消える飛行機雲追いかけて追いかけて
It hasn't changed since the day we crossed that hill
kono oka wo koeta ano hi kara kawarazu
この丘を越えたあの日から変わらず
And never will
itsumademo
いつまでも
And just as we are now, standing tall
massugu ni bokutachi wa aru youni
真っ直ぐに僕たちはあるように
We'll guard the strength of a sea god
watatsumi no youna tsuyosa wo mamoreru yo
わたつみのような強さを守れるよ
Surely
kitto
きっと
That child said she wanted to see the ocean,
but I couldn't take her.
Episode 7
Misuzu fainted?
Yeah.
She hasn't recovered yet.
She's resting in her room now.
Please see her.
She'll only feel worse if she sees my drunken face.
Forget that; I brought sushi.
Let's enjoy it together.
Oh.
That really hurt.
Why did you take Misuzu in?
Huh?
Why did you end up taking Misuzu in?!
Oh, so she told you about that?
I didn't take her in; she was pushed onto me,
even though I said I didn't want her.
That's why she isn't getting the love she needs.
Think about it!
You're the only parent she has!
That girl has an episode whenever she becomes friends with someone.
We never became close.
That's why we can live together.
What is a parental relationship anyway?
I'm not a real parent, so I don't know.
Yuck, wrong sushi.
The girl dreams.
First, it's a dream of the sky.
The dreams keep going back in time.
They start to eat away at the girl.
She starts to feel pain for no reason,
and, gradually, she begins to forget everything.
She begins to forget even her most precious friend.
And in the morning following her last dream, the girl will die.
She is always alone.
If she becomes close to someone, both will become sick.
Neither will survive.
So the girl told me,
"Stay away from me."
She was a very kind and strong girl.
That's why I was able to live.
But she...
In the sky, there is a girl with wings.
She is always alone.
She vanishes before becoming an adult,
repeating such sad dreams endlessly.
You're going on a trip?!
That's right. I'll travel around by myself, visiting hot springs.
What are you thinking?!
What about Misuzu?
I'm leaving her in your hands.
If you don't get too close to her, those attacks won't happen, right?
Wait!
Misuzu is dreaming now.
The dreams are making her behave like this.
Huh?!
I remembered a story my mother told me.
My mother had met a girl with the same kind of sickness a long time ago.
After a while, Misuzu will begin to forget: about me and about you, too.
Then, after having her last dream, she'll probably die.
Oh.
You know, there are jokes you can make and those you shouldn't.
It's not a joke!
Misuzu is...
Move!
Hey!
I'm coming in.
Oh, you're awake?
Yeah.
I just woke up.
I heard Mommy's voice.
Yeah, she's going away for a while.
Is that so?
I love Mommy.
Let's go to the beach.
Take your time. Don't push yourself.
Okay.
Oh, a crow.
Oh!
Misuzu!
Hey, are you all right?
Yeah.
I'm fine.
V!
Even though I've walked this road many times before,
was the ocean always this far?
What's wrong?
I'm sorry.
I... again...
Yet another attack?
I'm sorry!
I'll get better soon... so...
the ocean... tomorrow, instead...
Are you better now?
Yeah.
Hey.
Hm?
You know, I had another dream last night.
This time it was a happy one.
Even though it was nighttime, the sky was really bright.
I think it was a festival.
I was watching it from afar.
I see.
Hey, Yukito-san.
What is it?
The person you're looking for and my dreams are connected, right?
Who knows?
They could be unrelated.
I've thought about this a lot, and I think I know the answer.
Would you listen to me?
My dreams represent my other self.
And that girl is suffering right now.
I'll try my best to dream
because they might help me understand her.
If I do that, I might be able to help her.
Yukito-san, it's not a coincidence that I started having these dreams, is it?
I felt that this summer was special.
I wanted to try my best to make a friend.
Then, I met you and started having those dreams.
They're probably all connected, right?
So I want to do my best.
I want to make this summer the happiest ever
because it's the summer that I met you, Yukito-san.
Hey!
I'm all right now.
I feel much better.
Wah!
Misuzu!
Huh?
What happened?
My feet won't move.
Maybe we should call Hijiri
or even a large hospital.
No.
I don't think a doctor can cure me.
Yukito-san, you know it too, right?
My dreams are making me this way.
Well...
I had another dream last night.
It was about a journey.
A journey?
I was looking for something.
I walked through the forest for days and days.
It was hard, but I kept going
because I had someone special with me.
Someone special?
I know that every time I have a dream, I get a little weaker,
until finally, I, like the girl in the sky...
Idiot!
That won't happen!
I got scolded.
You don't have to think about your other self.
Just worry about getting better for now.
Yup.
Misuzu-chin is a strong girl.
Yukito-san!
Yukito-san! Yukito-san!
What happened?
Nothing.
It can't be nothing with a face like that.
My face has always been like this.
Misuzu, go back to bed.
I can't leave you here.
I'm fine.
Don't make me worry about you.
Okay...
What's with this scar?
It hurts!
Misuzu, hang on!
Misuzu!
I'm fine.
I'll be better soon, so stay here with me.
But if I'm close to you...
It's all right. Stay here...
Why does everyone leave me?
How are you feeling?
I'm fine now.
How about you, Yukito-san?
There's nothing wrong with me.
What now?
Should I call Hijiri?
Or Kano?
Minagi... is out of town.
So maybe someone from your class?
No, it's okay.
I don't want to bother them.
Don't lie.
You want friends, right?
You don't want to be alone, right?
I just want you here.
As long as you're here, I don't need anything.
Does that trouble you?
Idiot!
I want to go to the beach with you.
We're going to play on the beach.
We're going to race and splash water at each other,
and when we're finished, we'll say, "See you tomorrow!"
But for now, I'll wait.
Then I'll be even happier when I finally do go to the beach.
Mizusu-chin, fight!
Misuzu.
What?
I plan on leaving soon.
Eh?
If I stay with you any longer, neither of us will live,
so I've decided to run away from you.
I'll leave this town and go somewhere where I won't ever see you again.
By yourself?
Yeah.
We've become... too close.
Well, I guess it can't be helped.
It can't be helped, right?
I should've played by myself like this all along.
Maybe.
It was fun.
This summer break,
this summer break that I spent with you.
I feel the same.
Really?
Yeah.
There aren't any more buses?
Yukito-san.
Oh.
You see, in my dream this morning, I was locked up in a room all alone.
I was sad.
I was waiting a long time for someone to come and let me out.
I... I want to go with you, Yukito-san.
Is there no way for me to go with you?
It's not that I want to leave this place.
I just have to stay away from you.
If I leave you, you should recover.
That's why I can't be with you.
I see.
That's right.
I'm sorry for saying stupid things again.
No...
Then...
Bye-bye.
Take care.
You too.
Hang in there.
Even if you're alone, stay strong.
Yes.
I'll hang in there even if I'm alone.
I'm a strong girl.
Good.
See you.
Oh.
Misuzu...
What are you thinking now, Yukito?
Do you want your audience to laugh?
If you don't, the doll won't move.
Ocean Taxi Ferry Peer
Just wishing for it to move isn't enough.
You have to reach further.
Only then will it move.
Oh!
You did it!
That child said she wanted to see the ocean,
but I couldn't take her.
Yukito,
this time, I want you to save her for sure.
Inside this doll, there are wishes that were never granted.
My mother, and my mother's mother,
before losing their strength, sealed their power inside this doll
for the day when someone is ready to release their wishes.
So I will become one of those wishes.
How you will use it is up to you.
You can forget about the girl in the sky,
but Yukito...
In a town somewhere, you are sure to meet a girl.
If you really wish to save her, no matter what,
then put your heart and soul into the doll
because I will be with you.
Put my heart and soul... into the doll?
Something's been wrong with this guy for a while.
Maybe he's sick from this heat.
L-Let me go!
Please, help me.
Eh?
I want you to watch this and tell me how I can make it fun so that people laugh.
Wow, it's amazing!
How mysterious.
But it's not that fun, is it?
Yeah.
Why don't you try doing more instead of just making it walk around?
Make it like a story.
Make it dance or something.
D-Dance?
It has to be more original.
Wow!
That was great!
That show was fun!
It was fun and cute!
Is that so?
Thanks a lot for staying this long.
Well mister, good luck!
See you!
Misuzu, I'm back.
I won't go anywhere.
I'll stay with you and continue to make you laugh.
Yukito-san...
I learned some tricks.
They're definitely funny,
so watch carefully.
Misuzu!
Please watch!
Please laugh!
Why didn't I realize it sooner?
I was happy just being here with you and watching you smile.
If I just did that, I was happy.
I won't go anywhere anymore.
Stay with me and keep smiling.
Okay, Misuzu?
Yukito.
You must remember what you need to do now.
I... I want to be with Misuzu.
If I could, I'd go back to when we first met.
And this time...
with Misuzu... forever...
Hmm?
Why is it?
I thought I couldn't get up anymore...
Yukito-san?
Where did you go?
You came back, didn't you?
Hey, I'm better again.
I think I can try my hardest again.
Hey, Yukito-san?
Oh. Argh!
Shōryaku Era: Year 5
Ouch...
You... what are you doing in such a place?
If you have time to talk, hurry up and get off me!
You're... not someone I know.
Senior Assistant Lieutenant of the Outer Palace Guard, Ryuuya.
And you... where do you come from?
You don't know my name?
No.
We just met.
I see.
I guess I'm not that well-known.
I'm Kanna.
What a coincidence.
The winged person I was ordered to protect is also called Kanna.
Oh, that truly is a coincidence.
Yeah, it is really.
How rude!
Grasping the white fragments of an interrupted dream
shiroku togireta yume no kirehashi wo tsukamaete
白く途切れた夢の切れ端をつかまえて
A boy runs
shounen wa hashiru
少年は走る
When he lets go, they disappear into the distant sound of the wind
te wo hanashitara dokomademo tooku kaze no ne ni kieteyuku
手を放したらどこまでも遠く風の音に消えてゆく
The kindness I could once see is now gone
itsuka mieta yasashisa wa mou nai
いつか見えた優しさはもうない
I just look at my feet, stepping forward alone
hitori fumidasu ashidake miteru
ひとり踏み出す足だけ見てる
I listened to the singing until it disappeared when morning came
asa ni wa kieta ano utagoe wo itsumademo kiiteta
朝には消えたあの歌声をいつまでも聞いてた
I followed the footprints we'd left behind into the distance
bokura ga nokoshita ano ashiato wo itsumademo otteta
僕らが残したあの足跡をいつまでも追ってた
Next Episode Preview
A winged person is a messenger of the gods.
In times of famine or disease, they are able to speak directly with the gods
through their spiritual powers and prayers.
Being a family means you can lean on one another.
I want to see her.
I never thought that being alone would be this painful.
Episode 8