How long has it been since you came here?
I imagine you are used to what goes on at the shrine.
My robes seem fitting for this world, but in reality they are no different from a prison.
A winged person is a messenger of the gods.
In times of famine or disease, they are able to speak directly with the gods
through their spiritual powers and prayers.
I thought you would be living a little better than this.
Just because I have wings doesn't make me a messenger of the gods.
Where are your wings?
I'm hiding them.
Normally, I look just like a human.
What are you doing?!
Nothing. It's just that you have a good figure, so...
Do you touch every time someone has a nice body?!
You good-for-nothing!
Oh!
What's so funny, Uraha?
The way you were so embarrassed, Kanna-sama...
Whatever you say.
Just don't sneak up on us every time.
You called Ryuya-sama over again today.
Kanna-sama, it seems you've taking a very strong liking to Ryuya-sama.
That's not true at all!
I'm just trying to teach this good-for-nothing, impolite, despicable fool some manners.
This really is the first time there has been someone like you, Ryuya-sama.
We watched the fading vapor trails
kieru hikoukigumo bokutachi wa miokutta
消える飛行機雲僕たちは見送った
They were so dazzling, I ran away
mabushikute nigeta
眩しくて逃げた
I was so frustrated, I released your hand
kuyashikute yubi wo hanasu
悔しくて指を離す
The place she can't reach is still there in the distance
todokanai basho ga mada tooku ni aru
届かない場所がまだ遠くにある
She gazes at  it, keeping her wish to herself
negai hi dake himete mitsumeteru
願いだけ秘めて見つめてる
Children walk along the summer railway tracks
kodomotachi wa natsu no senro aruku
子供たちは夏の線路歩く
Holding in both hands their wishes to take flight
ryoute ni wa tobidatsu kibou wo
両手には飛び立つ希望を
Chasing, chasing the fading vapor trails
kieru hikoukigumo oikakete oikakete
消える飛行機雲追いかけて追いかけて
It hasn't changed since the day we crossed that hill
kono oka wo koeta ano hi kara kawarazu
この丘を越えたあの日から変わらず
And never will
itsumademo
いつまでも
And just as we are now, standing tall
massugu ni bokutachi wa aru youni
真っ直ぐに僕たちはあるように
We'll guard the strength of a sea god
watatsumi no youna tsuyosa wo mamoreru yo
わたつみのような強さを守れるよ
Surely
kitto
きっと
Episode 8
Kanna-sama, this is for you.
I found this down in the cellar a few moments ago.
It's the height of summer, so it's very unusual to find ice.
I felt that I had to show you, so I brought it with me.
Oh, that is mysterious.
It is a serious crime to go in there without permission.
Oh my, my.
Dangerous, dangerous.
I knew you two were in this together...
Oh!
It's cold.
Ryuya-dono, you should try it too.
It's also a serious crime to taste something that's offered to Kannabi-sama.
You're eating it yourself whilst saying that, aren't you?
The three of us together, eating ice is like...
We're a desperate family with no food, trying to avoid starvation under cold skies.
That's such a beautiful metaphor, is it not?
What is a family like?
Let's see...
Simply put...
Stick.
Hey!
Don't come so close when it's this hot!
Wait, wait. Don't be so sulky.
Come closer.
Stick.
Didn't I tell you not to come so close?
You don't have to go that far.
Stick.
Why are you so close as well?
Well, I just felt like it.
Both of you, get away from me!
So you're teasing me...
Being a family means you huddle together.
How long has Kanna been living like this?
Ever since you took your post here, she has been so much happier.
That's not what I meant.
How long has she been living at this shrine?
That I don't know,
since I haven't been here for more than six months yet.
However, I've heard that for as long as she can remember
she's been held captive like this, being moved from place to place with no-one to talk to.
Ryuya-sama.
It's my shift now.
Oh.
Why are you so nervous?
Um... Well, I have been uneasy ever since I came here.
I fear that I'll be punished by the gods suddenly if I get too close to Kannabi-sama.
From what I've seen, that doesn't seem to happen.
I hear that there are many people who loathe and fear the winged person.
I really want to return to my normal duties as soon as possible!
Is something wrong, Kanna?
Ryuya-dono, do you have dreams?
Sometimes.
What's wrong?
Did you have a scary dream that's keeping you up?
It was a dream of the distant past.
I was a small child, sitting in the dark, just like now.
I couldn't see anything.
I couldn't even tell whether my own body was there.
I was scared and sad.
But even then, I couldn't cry.
The dream was of those days.
Sometimes I see a warm light.
It's the figure of a person.
But if I try to chase it, it disappears.
I've had the same dream not just once, but several times.
Ryuya-dono, do you know who it is?
It must be your mother.
I do not remember anything about my mother.
Dreams are memories of scenes from the past.
That's why you dream things, even if you don't remember them.
My body remembers?
Then I guess it's not a bad dream.
I want to see her.
I never thought that being alone would be this painful.
It has been decided that Kannabi no Mikoto shall be transferred to the north shrine
in order to say prayers for an abundant harvest.
Silence!
She shall leave at sunset of the midsummer Day of the Ox.
Are we to follow Kannabi no Mikoto to her new residence as well?
No. We are to remain and follow the orders of Kaikon to cultivate the land.
I heard what happened.
Something like that happens every year around this time.
I didn't know that until this morning.
That is when I will have to part with you and Uraha.
We don't have many days left.
Is that all right?
Is what all right?
I'm asking whether it is all right for you to be separated from Uraha and me.
I'm sure there will be other interesting people there.
They won't be Uraha or me.
Don't be so arrogant!
Do I look that weak?
I will be fine, even if you aren't there.
I've lived alone like that before.
Weren't you lonely?
Don't you want to see your mother?
I'm telling you that there are some things that will not come true, no matter how hard I wish.
Did your mother... die?
She isn't dead.
She is definitely...
thinking of me somewhere.
Uraha, Kanna—
I'm busy right now!
What are you doing?
Can't you see?
I'm preparing for a journey.
Kanna is the only one leaving.
We're supposed to stay here.
That's why I'm taking her away before that happens.
It's too inhumane for poor Kanna-sama to keep living like this forever.
Can I ask you something?
Why do you worry about Kanna so much?
I'd like to ask you the same thing, Ryuyu-sama.
Let's see...
To put it bluntly,
I don't know anyone worth teasing as much as she is.
That's exactly it, right?
Hey, Kanna.
Wake up.
Good morning.
Intruder!
Shh!
Don't make a fuss.
We need to talk to you.
Don't you want to see your mother?
Mm.
In my duties, I must never disobey Kannabi no Mikoto's orders.
Therefore, if you order me to find your mother, I will risk my life to do it.
Will you give me that order as my master?
You're all right with that?
It's your choice.
Then, I order you to...
lead me to my mother.
I, Senior Assistant Lieutenant of the Outer Palace Guard, Ryuya,
humbly swear to fulfill
Kannabi no Mikoto's command.
Kanna-sama!
Hurry!
Ryuya-sama, please can we rest for a while?
No one seems to have noticed yet.
It's only a matter of time.
There'll be a huge commotion soon.
It's rather late of me to say this now, but we've acted very rashly, haven't we?
Don't say things like that when we've come this far.
Oh!
Look there!
What's happening at the shrine?
I don't know,
but it looks like we should get away from here as soon as possible.
What is it?
It seems that we've been surrounded.
Kanna, Uraha,
we're going to run as fast as we can.
Run!
Throw down your sword.
Answer my questions honestly.
You're from Edo, aren't you?
Why are you chasing Kannabi no Mikoto?
I don't know.
We were ordered to.
What were you planning to do with Kannabi no Mikoto?
Whose orders are you following?
I don't know!
We were just ordered by our superior!
I see.
Stop it!
You... did you intend to kill him?
If I don't kill him, our lives will be in danger.
You should feel ashamed, you fool!
You kill people without any thought?
Kanna-sama.
I don't want to be protected by someone like that!
I hereby order you:
As long as I am your master, I will not allow you to kill anyone.
Understood?
I understand.
But do you really think we'll be able to survive without killing anyone?
I feel that it will be easy for you, Ryuya-sama.
Heh, as if it's easy...
Where exactly did you find a kimono like this?
I took the laundry someone left hanging to dry by the river.
Of course, I left some money.
It looks good on you, Kanna.
R-Really?
You have strange taste...
Kanna-sama is so funny!
When she was changing,
she said she didn't want you to see her wearing clothes that don't look good on her.
Idiot! Don't mention that!
It isn't that good, is it?
When the three of us eat dried food like this, it's like...
We're some court nobles, demoted to some backwater place,
moistening our food with tears of shame.
That's such an elegant metaphor, is it not?
Those are beanbags.
They were in the kimono.
Oh.
But it's unusual for them to be made of cloth.
Usually we use rocks, but it must be made of cloth to prevent children from getting hurt.
Can I try it too?
With a little practice, I'm sure you will become good at it.
Hm...
Not everyone succeeds the first time.
Perseverance is important for everything.
I-It just slipped a little.
You mustn't be so forceful.
Just throw them to about eye level.
I know!
I never knew you were this clumsy.
Oh, Kanna-sama, I feel sorry for you...
Don't be so dramatic!
I heard that your mother is being held captive on a sacred mountain in Kishu.
What sort of place is Kishu?
Is it far from here?
It is.
It's over the mountains, so it's especially far.
Let us proceed carefully, so that we can avoid being caught by our pursuers.
H-H-Hot!
Here, let me.
It's been a whole month already, but you still haven't gotten any better.
I can do it well sometimes.
Three days ago, I did it three times in a row!
Oh?
That is impressive.
You're making fun of me, aren't you?
When we're sitting around a fire in the mountains, it's like...
A handsome man, who has kidnapped a princess,
is regretting it now because he realized how much attention she needs.
That's such a free spirited metaphor, is it not?
It's not really a metaphor. It's almost literally true.
Kishu is right ahead.
We will not have this kind of life for much longer.
Huh?
Why do they all look like they're having fun?
Well, when they dance like that, they can forget about their problems.
That's not all.
They all believe that their wishes will reach the heavens.
Who will deliver them to the heavens?
O-Oh.
That's...
I have wings, but I cannot fly in the sky.
I have tried it many times since I was a little girl.
I can't even fly like a leaf in the breeze, much less reach the heavens.
They're useless wings.
Even then, if I wish, will my wishes really reach the heavens?
They will.
All you have to do is wish with your heart.
They will be sure to come true.
Isn't that right, Uraha?
Yes, that's right!
Hey, Uraha.
That's ticklish.
Hey!
It's so quiet.
Don't let your guard down.
We should already be at the sacred mountain.
It seems that there is a barrier.
Please be quiet.
I have a feeling it's this way.
You can tell?
Yes.
Though... it's just intuition.
Don't make a sound.
Warrior Priests, huh?
This area is off-limits to women!
You look like a country samurai.
What business do you have on this sacred mountain?
I was wandering through the night merrily.
It seems that I was tricked by a wild fox!
No, maybe a wild raccoon dog.
We cannot let you go,
since we won't be able to touch you, once you cross the barrier.
Ryuya-dono, behind you!
I will not allow you to kill anyone.
Ryuya-dono!
Stay away!
What... are you planning?
We will not let you see... the Yaobikuni.
Yaobikuni...
Ryuya-dono!
You've regained consciousness!
I'm glad!
It seems that the worst is over!
How long have I been sleeping?
A whole day.
Don't worry!
We've already crossed the barrier.
The priests cannot follow us.
I see.
I will go fetch some water.
Ryuya-dono.
Ah.
Are you all right, Kanna?
I... ordered you not to kill anyone,
but now... come to think of it... that was... my...
I'm loyal to you.
I'll follow your orders, no matter what they are.
For example, if you order me not to die, I will never die.
Then...
I order you.
No.
This is not an order, but a plea.
Ryuya-dono.
I don't want you to die.
I won't.
I promise.
Is this it?
Yes. I feel something.
Mother is here?
Most likely.
Watch out.
Stop.
Oh!
If you recklessly try to drag me into a war, know that you will not leave here alive.
I am Kannabi no Mikoto's guardian, Ryuya.
Forgive me, but I gather that you are Kannabi no Mikoto's mother.
Kanna?
Is that you, Mother?
My wings can neither flap nor fly.
But, if you have the same wings as me...
Kanna!
Mother!
The person called Ryuya,
take Kanna and get off this mountain right away.
Oh.
Eh?
Grasping the white fragments of an interrupted dream
shiroku togireta yume no kirehashi wo tsukamaete
白く途切れた夢の切れ端をつかまえて
A boy runs
shounen wa hashiru
少年は走る
When he lets go, they disappear into the distant sound of the wind
te wo hanashitara dokomademo tooku kaze no ne ni kieteyuku
手を放したらどこまでも遠く風の音に消えてゆく
The kindness I could once see is now gone
itsuka mieta yasashisa wa mou nai
いつか見えた優しさはもうない
I just look at my feet, stepping forward alone
hitori fumidasu ashidake miteru
ひとり踏み出す足だけ見てる
I listened to the singing until it disappeared when morning came
asa ni wa kieta ano utagoe wo itsumademo kiiteta
朝には消えたあの歌声をいつまでも聞いてた
I followed the footprints we'd left behind into the distance
bokura ga nokoshita ano ashiato wo itsumademo otteta
僕らが残したあの足跡をいつまでも追ってた
Next Episode Preview
What do you plan to do with me?
We will take you away from here.
Then you will live happily ever after with Kanna-sama.
Mother...
Let us live in a small cottage somewhere quiet.
Dreams are not always sad.
It was fun.
Kanna!
Why?
Why does everyone... leave me?
Episode 9