Why?
Why must I leave the mountain?
Forgive me, but I am Lady Kanna's guardian.
I cannot go against her wishes.
What do you plan to do with me?
We will take you away from here.
Then you will live happily ever after with Kanna-sama.
If there were more people like you in the world, our fates might have been different.
Please stand back!
Mother!
You must stay back!
My body has been tainted.
Tainted?
You must not come close to me.
Mother...
We watched the fading vapor trails
kieru hikoukigumo bokutachi wa miokutta
消える飛行機雲僕たちは見送った
They were so dazzling, I ran away
mabushikute nigeta
眩しくて逃げた
I was so frustrated, I released your hand
kuyashikute yubi wo hanasu
悔しくて指を離す
The place she can't reach is still there in the distance
todokanai basho ga mada tooku ni aru
届かない場所がまだ遠くにある
She gazes at  it, keeping her wish to herself
negai hi dake himete mitsumeteru
願いだけ秘めて見つめてる
Children walk along the summer railway tracks
kodomotachi wa natsu no senro aruku
子供たちは夏の線路歩く
Holding in both hands their wishes to take flight
ryoute ni wa tobidatsu kibou wo
両手には飛び立つ希望を
Chasing, chasing the fading vapor trails
kieru hikoukigumo oikakete oikakete
消える飛行機雲追いかけて追いかけて
It hasn't changed since the day we crossed that hill
kono oka wo koeta ano hi kara kawarazu
この丘を越えたあの日から変わらず
And never will
itsumademo
いつまでも
And just as we are now, standing tall
massugu ni bokutachi wa aru youni
真っ直ぐに僕たちはあるように
We'll guard the strength of a sea god
watatsumi no youna tsuyosa wo mamoreru yo
わたつみのような強さを守れるよ
Surely
kitto
きっと
Episode 9
Did you say your name was Uraha?
Are you the one who broke through the barrier and found a way out?
Yes.
It was as if something led me...
You seem to be gifted with special powers.
Powers?
Quiet!
Is that a bird?
It's an arrow!
It signals the beginning of a battle.
An army is trying to invade the sacred mountain.
Duck!
Mother!
I got her!
What?!
That arrow was mine!
Don't look!
So this is the power of a winged person...
Mother!
Don't pull out the arrows!
What are you saying?!
She will only bleed to death.
Oh.
Mother...
You must not...
touch me...
No!
No, no, no!
Kanna!
Kanna-sama!
Mother!
Kanna...
What a disobedient child you are.
I've told you so many times, yet...
Mother...
I had forgotten for such a long time
how warm a human's touch is...
If this is fate...
Kanna,
listen carefully.
The ancient prayer was supposed to die with me,
but I will bestow it upon you now.
If possible, I wanted you to live as a normal girl,
without the burden of a winged person.
Mother.
Strength...
Wind...
Now... the thing... we finally... inherit...
A dream that stars see...
A dream that stars see?
What are you talking about?
Everlasting... spirit... wings...
A way for our souls...
That is all.
Please forgive me.
This is, above all, our duty.
Mother...
Now, Kanna.
It's your turn.
How has your journey been?
Would you like to hear about it?
Um, until recently I was living in a shrine deep in the forest...
Truthfully, I have never been on such a fun journey before.
I have Ryuya-dono and Uraha to thank for that.
Kanna-sama.
It seems that your mother is tired.
Don't you have something you'd like to show her?
I've trained long and hard so that when I met you, I could show you.
I really, really can do it.
Next time, I will definitely throw them well.
There.
This time.
Next time.
Next time will be good for sure.
Why won't you go around?!
We're in front of Mother.
I've been training for a long time just for this day, so why?
Why won't you go around?!
You are very good.
You tried your very best, really.
Mother...
Carry on.
I'll be watching you the whole time.
I understand.
Oh.
Uraha-dono,
please do not think of this mother as heartless.
I won't.
Ryuya-dono,
there's no need for a funeral.
Don't touch my body; just leave it here as is.
I have nothing to regret now.
I... only wanted to share this...
If I could have... spread my wings together with hers...
and fly to wherever we wished in the summer sky.
To fly with her...
Oh!
Mother?
Mother! Mother!
Kanna, that's enough.
Mother!
That's enough already.
Let go!
Leave me alone!
Mother never lies.
Mother said I was good!
If I can't throw the beanbags well, then it will make Mother a liar!
I must do it.
Mother... Mother is watching!
Mother is...!
Kanna-sama!
By such crude arrows...
Kanna-sama...
Ryuya-dono,
thank you for being my guardian...
It was only for a short time,
but I...
I...
Ryuya-dono!
Mother!
Ryuya-sama, have some water.
I'm fine.
Give it to Kanna.
It's my order.
Drink.
Is this all the water we have?
I see.
Let's share it.
Drink all the rest.
When the three of us huddle together like this, it's like...
We're a really close-knit family.
You're the one who said that a true family sticks together so much
that they almost suffocate each other.
That is so true.
The two of you, do you have any wishes?
Where did that come from?
Let's see...
When you ask so suddenly...
To escape this siege, even if it means my life.
At least let Kanna escape alive.
I have one.
I want to live with Kanna-sama and Ryuya-sama forever.
That might be good too.
Let us live in a small cottage, somewhere quiet.
In that case, I could get us food, either by farming or hunting.
If it's near the ocean, we could fish too.
The ocean...
If we're going to live by the ocean, I'd prefer it to be a warm sea in the west.
What is the ocean like?
What, you don't know?
I heard that it's an unimaginably large puddle,
but I've never seen it myself.
It is a puddle, except it's all salt water.
You're teasing me again, aren't you?
It's true, Kanna-sama.
Also, the ocean is as wide as the sky.
What?!
You can eat all the snappers and abalone you want.
Is that true?
Well, that depends on my fishing skills.
There are probably also summer festivals at seaside villages.
Yeah.
They have them everywhere.
Let's dance then, all three of us.
Yeah.
Just watching isn't as fun.
This is a dream, isn't it?
My dream.
Dreams are not always sad.
It was fun.
Kanna.
The two of you, don't move from here, no matter what.
I was able to forget about my wings while I was with you, Ryuya-dono.
Kanna...
This is my final order.
Live...
happily...
forever.
Kanna!
Don't be afraid!
Shoot!
What are those voices?
It's a chant.
The priests are putting a curse on Kanna-sama.
Do not stop chanting!
In order to protect this world from the curse of the winged person,
you must not fear for your our own lives!
Kanna!
Fly higher!
Higher!
Ah!
Kanna!
Ryuya-dono...
Ryuya-sama.
What are you doing?
I don't care who it is.
I'm going to die and take as many of those who did that to Kanna with me as I can.
If you get in my way, I'll kill you.
Kill me, please.
This isn't a bluff.
I'm not bluffing either.
How could Kanna-sama possibly be pleased to see you transform into a monster?
Kanna isn't here anymore.
No.
I can still hear Kanna-sama's voice.
What?
It's faint, but I can hear it,
Kanna-sama's crying voice.
Kanna's?
Oh.
I see that you are Kannabi no Mikoto's servants.
We have come, under orders of our master, to take you.
The person who summoned us was Chitoku, a high priest.
Chitoku already knew nearly everything about Kanna.
A winged person once lived in this temple too a long time ago.
Since then, this temple has watched over and sometimes even helped winged people.
According to Chitoku,
generation after generation of winged people inherit the dreams of stars
and, since ancient times, impart pearls of wisdom to the people.
It is said that one of them is the source of our magic.
Inherited dreams?
Who knows? We do not.
Winged people, because of their power, were held captive by the powerful men of the day
and used as weapons of war.
Kanna's mother had been cursed by all those she had killed in wars.
That's why she said she was tainted.
The army that invaded the sacred mountain belonged to the Imperial Court.
Its goal was to completely eradicate the worship of the winged people
and to unify the people.
According to Chitoku, Kanna was probably the last surviving winged person in this world.
Chitoku-sama, I have a request.
Please give me magical powers.
It was decided that we would live at the temple.
Uraha was said to have talent that only appeared once every hundred years.
Many long months passed.
I shall begin now.
By summoning forth the spirits of the dead,
we shall discover what kind of dreams Kanna-sama is having.
Ryuya-dono!
Ryuya-dono, wake up!
That's an order!
Why won't you move?
Why won't you open your eyes?
I won't forgive you!
I won't forgive you if you die and leave me!
Why?
Why does everyone... leave me?
No!
That's not right, Kanna!
I'm all right!
I'm right here!
That... Is that what Kanna is dreaming about now?
Yes.
Are you saying she continuously dreams this, somewhere in the sky?
It is the curse that the priests at the sacred mountain put on her.
It's tormenting her even now.
And there's the curse that she inherited from her mother as well.
Oh.
They will weaken those who care for winged people,
eventually leading them to their death.
Is that why my wound never heals?
Yes.
I can protect myself using magic, but Ryuya-sama...
When will I die?
I don't think you will last another year.
I see.
The curse that has taken Kanna captive will break someday.
When that happens, Kanna-sama's spirit will descend to Earth in a reincarnated form.
But putting a winged person's spirit into a human is like
pouring the water of the ocean into a small vial.
Before all of it can be poured in, the vial will break.
Kanna-sama's spirit will not have a chance to heal and will continue to reincarnate.
I don't have much time.
Is there any way to save Kanna?
There is just one.
Please father a child.
Huh?
If you father a child, you can leave your will with him, right?
If that child cannot, your grandchild will.
If your grandchild cannot, then your great-grandchild will carry out your will.
And then, someday, a way to save Kanna-sama might be discovered.
I will help you.
I understand.
Then, I shall devote all of my remaining time to you.
Yes!
Time passes slowly.
At the back of the stone house, there is a book on winged people that I compiled.
If our soon-to-be-born child seeks Kanna's spirit, that book should definitely be of help.
And Uraha will teach the child magic.
I'm sure any child with Uraha's blood will be able to excel.
He might be able to follow the path that we couldn't find.
I can continue my journey, overcoming even time itself,
the journey to meet those precious wings again.
There is nothing more I wish for.
There is nothing left for me to regret.
The birds are flying.
Yes.
You can forget if you want.
You can forget about me and Kanna and just be happy.
I don't want to.
I'm not alone.
You and Kanna-sama will continue to be with me and guide me.
I am happy.
I see.
That's exactly what makes you my dear wife.
Yes.
Thank you, Uraha.
Is it raining?
The sky is so high and clear, yet...
Ryuya-sama.
Shall we go, Uraha?
Kanna is waiting for us beyond that sky.
Yes.
I will follow you, wherever you go.
Where is this?
Why am I here?
Oh yeah.
I was with someone just a moment ago.
Someone very important to me...
It's no good.
My mind is so hazy, I can't remember.
Hey, where did you come from?
Where's your mommy?
Mommy?
Can't you fly?
Oh, how cute!
Hm... I wonder if it's okay to leave him here...
All right, I'll walk away a little then turn around, and if he doesn't follow me, then I'll leave him.
Oh, he's following me.
Do you want to come with me?
I see.
Then let's go together.
Ready? Go!
Grasping the white fragments of an interrupted dream
shiroku togireta yume no kirehashi wo tsukamaete
白く途切れた夢の切れ端をつかまえて
A boy runs
shounen wa hashiru
少年は走る
When he lets go, they disappear into the distant sound of the wind
te wo hanashitara dokomademo tooku kaze no ne ni kieteyuku
手を放したらどこまでも遠く風の音に消えてゆく
The kindness I could once see is now gone
itsuka mieta yasashisa wa mou nai
いつか見えた優しさはもうない
I just look at my feet, stepping forward alone
hitori fumidasu ashidake miteru
ひとり踏み出す足だけ見てる
I listened to the singing until it disappeared when morning came
asa ni wa kieta ano utagoe wo itsumademo kiiteta
朝には消えたあの歌声をいつまでも聞いてた
I followed the footprints we'd left behind into the distance
bokura ga nokoshita ano ashiato wo itsumademo otteta
僕らが残したあの足跡をいつまでも追ってた
Next Episode Preview
Summer vacation starts tomorrow.
I'm amazed he's so friendly.
I gave him a name: Sora.
Don't you have another one?
No way!
Piko piko pika.
Pikori.
Piko?
How much longer do I have to live like this?
If I'm all alone, I won't be able to stay strong.
What should I do?
Misuzu, I'll be back.
Episode 10