Class 3-B?
Ms. Kuroi!
Yeah, yeah...
Around 3 cm!
aimai 3 SENCHI
Looks peachy, doesn't it?
sorya puni tte KOTO kai?
Hey!
cho!
Wrapping for a uniform...
rappingu ga seifuku...
Turn-off, ain't it?
daaa furitte koto nai
Ha.
pu.
Just work it ♥
ganbacchau ♥
And do it?
yacchacchau
Don't forget to catch and release yo!
son tokya-cchi & RELEASE gyo
I sweat!
ase
FUU!
I sweat!
ase
And throw in a!
no tanima ni
DARLiN' DARLiN* F R E E Z E!!
FeelING crummy!
nanka DAru-
SomethING's coming!
nanka DEru-
I lOVE you so!
ashiTEru
Oops!
are
I screwed one upsie-up!
ikko ga chigatterunru-
A nail biter!
nayamiNbo-
A steel beater!
koutetsubo-
Gourmet eater!
oishinbo-
Cut that out already!
i-kagen ni SHINASA!
Is that new blushing flower...
tondetta AITSU no hoteru KARADA tte
...considered a normal girl or what?
iwayuru futsu- no onya no KO
Wowzers!
odoroita
Only for me?
atashi dake?
Pork chops!
tonkotasu
Firm noodles!
HARIGANE
Fill 'er up again!
okawari
DA-DA-DA!
Ooh!
Guess what?
My glasses...
Where are my glasses?
But I've been playing the same fighting games lately.
If I don't have my glasses...
BON-BON
Cheerleaders!
o-endan
LET'S GET!
Cherry pie!
CHERI-PAI
RAN-RAN
Welcome party!
kange-kai
LOOK UP!
Sensation!
sense-shon
Yeah!
hai!
Leavin' an impression.
sonzaikan
...asteriods.
•• shouwakusei
Crash!
butsukatte
And burned!
tokemashita
Shockers!
bo-zen
Break into song!
ooi ni utatte
Crunch time!
SHIRENJA-
Take it!
motteike!
I'll still be laughing in the end!
saigo ni waracchau no wa atashi no hazu
'Cause it's a sailor uniform.
SE-RA- fuku dakara desu
← Q.E.D.!
← ketsuron
It's only Monday and I'm already blue.
getsuyoubi na no ni! kigen warui no
What to do?
dou suru yo?
I'd rather wear my summer clothes.
natsufuku ga ii no desu
← So cute!
← KYA? WA! IIv
3 pics incoming!
sekkin 3 PIKUTO
That's a toughie to pick!
suru madette chu-chou da
Ooh ☆
yan ☆
Just work it!
ganbatte
YEAH!
To the limit!
harikitte
YEAH!
MY DARLiN' DARLiN! P L E A S E!!
Thanks for treating us today, Cousin Yui!
Anytime!
Don't mention it!
That was good, right?
Right?
Don't you feel happy when the egg tastes good?
The price of gas went up two yen since yesterday...
Should've filled up the tank...
Why is it that people who spend generously...
...care so much about a one yen difference in the price of gasoline?
There
Over
Here
That's right...
That book I lent you a while ago is
apparently getting turned into a game.
I won't be buying it though.
You're so behind, Kagami.
I reserved the limited edition as soon as it was announced.
I even bought the DVD box set for
the anime and other related goods.
You're more hooked than I am.
It's pretty common for people to become bigger
fans than the people who recommend stuff to them.
That's how Cousin Yui chose her car.
Thanks to someone else's influence.
Her car?!
I lent her a racing manga...
That sure surprised me.
It's scary how much energy people put into their hobbies...
Yesterday was the third win in a row, right?
It's the start of a miracle!
If they keep on winning...
What are they talking about?
...the playoffs and Japan Series aren't out of the question.
Probably pro baseball, I believe.
All the way to the top!
Teacher enjoys it.
Besides, baseball's all about...
Speaking of baseball...
The famous poet, Shiki Masaoka...
...apparently loved baseball a great deal.
He played catcher...
...until he was too ill.
And he took his childhood name, Noboru...
...wrote it using the characters for baseball...
...and pronounced it Noball.
By the way...
The winners of the Major League
are called the world champions, right?
Talking about the Japan Series reminded me.
That's right.
Even when it only includes American teams.
Well, they should beat our team before
they call themselves world champions, right?
She's awfully pumped up...
It sure stinks.
It sure does.
There you are!
Kagami!
Miyuki-san!
Konata.
Teach me how to do these!
This is unusual.
You asking a question about schoolwork.
Some of these problems are quite difficult.
That's cause they're from an arcade quiz game.
I'm not good with academic stuff.
There you go again...
And put more effort into your studying.
You're applying for college.
I may be like this here...
...but they call me a sage over there!
In that case...
...just enroll in that whatever academy of yours.
Which is why I didn't get enough sleep.
How long were you up playing?
You say you're always in bed by eleven, Miyuki-san?
That's early.
Wait.
Now I get it...
「Sleeping helps
you grow ☆」
So I was thinking when I looked at Miyuki-san...
...but you haven't grown much considering how much you sleep.
That's what Big Sister said.
I'm really sensitive about that.
That night, around 9 o'clock
Excuse me for calling so late.
My name is Kobayakawa.
Is this the Iwasaki residence?
Thank you.
May I speak with Minami-chan?
She already went to bed?
Did she always sleep this early?
You're having fun singing.
Yes, we'll make do.
It's okay.
Yes.
I'll let my father know.
After the ground-breaking ceremony.
That's right.
No, of course not!
Please, there you go again...
I'm underage, really.
You've got it wrong!
It's not like that!
Then bye.
Yes.
Yes!
You know, Kagami...
They can't see you gesturing.
I know that!
It's just a force of habit!
Oh, yeah...
When I'm on the phone, I have to concentrate so I stop gaming...
...but then my empty hand starts feeling lonely...
I know what you mean.
So the other day...
...I was using a roller to get rid of dust the whole time.
Roll! Roll!
Stuff like that can get pretty addictive.
Like random doodling or menial chores.
But you know...
Once you get off the phone, that stuff gets old really fast.
It's kinda depressing when only the area around you is clean.
You could just finish the job.
My passion fades with the conversation.
So you just leave it like that?
That guy's kinda stinky, yeah?
I guess it's okay every now and then.
Look!
**cky!
Po***!
I used to do that...
...back in grade school.
Seriously...
Are you a little kid?
But...
Speaking of things we did when we were little...
...I used to stir my yogurt...
...and go, "Bread factory!"
Bread factory?
Haven't heard of it?
Hey, what was that just now?
Bread factory?
Don't be embarrassed. Just 'fess up.
Shut up!
About that game I lent you back during first semester...
Someone else wants to play it.
So give it back.
Gotcha.
Is it for the squirt?
Reminds me...
I've lent a bunch to her.
I should get them back.
But you sure are amazing, Hiiragi.
What do you mean?
Well...
The other day, I found these games and
didn't remember who I borrowed them from...
I'm impressed you can remember.
Hey now...
And there are some I lent to other people that I've forgotten about.
You're way too careless.
Nah.
There's gotta be a Law of Equal Lending.
It's a universal principle.
As if...
Yes?
Hello?
Hiiragi?
It's me.
Misao.
Yeah, what's u—
Damn...
Not bad, Potemkin...
Wh-What?
Is something wrong?
Nah.
No big deal...
Sorry, sorry.
So?
What do you want?
Well...
What was it again?
I wouldn't know.
It was something super important...
Don't forget it if it's important.
I was looking at the numbers for the Autumn Jumbo Lottery...
...but mine were all off.
Guess it's not so easy to win.
I sent in a bunch of postcards...
...but I didn't win any prizes from the drawing.
Really...
That's too bad...
When you never win...
...you start to wonder if the vendors or
editors are running some kind of scam, right?
Konata!
You shouldn't be so suspicious of other people!
No good...
I'm gonna call it a night.
I'll go to the bathroom first.
They tell me that I talk to myself too much.
But that don't matter.
I was really sleepy...
...so why am I so awake after that weird joke?
Next day, dead of night
I really can't do this at night.
I'm not feeling it tonight...
I should get to bed while I'm dozing off.
It's freezing!
I was really sleepy...
...so why am I so awake just 'cause it's cold under the covers?
The day after that, dead of night
It's useless...
It's warm tonight...
Maybe I can fall asleep quickly.
My legs are really hot for some reason...
I can't fall asleep!
Why is that?
Does this only happen to me?
It's the season for baked sweet potatoes!
Well, Kagami...
You know...
Yeah, I know.
I know, so don't say it.
Want some?
Thanks so much.
But you'll gain weight.
You still said it.
But I can't help it!
Once I've made eye contact with the guy...
...it'd be rude not to buy one, right?
You know...
"Will she buy one?"
"My feelings will be hurt if she doesn't."
That look!
I know what you mean.
If you make eye contact at Comiket...
...it's really hard to put a book back.
You don't care when other people have
no idea what you're talking about, huh...
Come on...
I'm talking about when you're hanging around a circle's booth.
When you pick up a book in front of a sales rep...
...you feel pretty bad if you leave without buying it.
But you still put it back, don't you?
There's been an increase in the number
of light novels being adapted to anime.
Looks like it.
The novel I lent you...
...has already had three anime adaptations.
And there should be a new volume coming out soon.
I've watched the anime...
...but I haven't read the novels.
Too much text makes me tired.
That again, huh...
Don't the games you always play have a lot more text?
They should, but it's weird...
It'd really help if they released them in a visual novel format.
Hey!
More importantly...
When are they doing the fourth season of the anime?
Um...
What?
Is that some kind of reference?
Yu-chan...
What are you doing over there?
Th-The lid always ends up crooked.
Well, some people are like that.
I guess it's clumsiness.
I do it all the time.
Here.
You share some cute flaws with Miyuki-san.
Thanks!
You sure are amazing, Big Sister.
What do I do, Big Sister?
Now I can't open it.
Oops.
I used my usual strength.
You sure are a lot of trouble.
You can't open the bag?
Hand it here.
Big Sister!
Thanks!
Huh?
How about we just tear it along the notches?
No!
O-One sec!
I'll open it so hold on!
Fire...
It's okay.
We can just tear along the notches or use scissors.
No, that would hurt my pride!
Or make me feel like a loser!
Big Sister, is it a mosquito?
Mosquito!
Don't you get annoyed when you know something's there?
Even when you haven't been bitten yet.
Once you know it's there...
...you must take it down!
That's the instinct of a hunter!
I was thinking...
If a guy in the same year professed his love for Yu-chan or me...
...wouldn't that guy be a lolicon?
They're in the same class year...
...so technically, they wouldn't.
But in this case, it feels like appearance holds more weight...
Say, if...
...you were a 30-year-old who
looked like someone in grade school...
Then you could say the guy likes older women...
This is a complicated issue.
It's hard to come up with a strict definition.
You're definitely my dad.
Kagami would have just ended it with, "Who cares?!"
So what about you, Dad?
Mom
You fell in love with Mom...
Daughter
...and you dote on me...
...which means you're a lolicon, right?
No, wait.
Hold it right here.
That's not entirely accurate.
I'm not limited to little girls.
I also like normal girls.
So you should say that I'm also a lolicon.
Well, it basically depends on the character.
Either way, you fail as a human being.
Okay...
You know how you're always so clingy?
Would you still be like that if I were a boy?
Of course!
Okay.
I totally understand now.
Aren't you glad I'm a girl?
Uh...
I think the bath should be ready.
You go first, Yu-chan.
Then excuse me.
He chased her away 'cause he was looking bad.
Hey, Dad.
About Mom...
She was short...
...and your childhood friend...
Isn't she like a character out of a gal game?
Right?
She was adorable since she was little.
I can understand why you fell for her...
...but why did she marry you?
I was like, "You wouldn't accept me...
...so I ended up as a gal game lover!"
And she just said yes...
You're despicable!
But it's the truth.
Isn't that coercion?!
No, no...
That wasn't the only reason, obviously...
And she was really happy when you were born...
Oh.
Doesn't this mole make her look like you, Sou-kun?
Well...
She has your eyes.
You can definitely tell she's our child.
But I hope she doesn't grow up like us.
I hope she doesn't inherit my height...
...or your personality...
Pretty harsh...
But why did you suddenly mention her?
I don't know much about Mom.
Konata.
Are you lonely without Mom around?
Not really.
You create as much excitement as two people would.
And Yu-chan's here.
I see...
Kanata...
Konata's grown up to be a good girl.
A little geek
Though she's not as normal as you wanted...
Hey, Konata.
Please don't die before I do.
For now, I have no intention of doing so.
That's good.
Kanata died young...
...but she said she was happy and smiled at the end.
It's hard on those left behind...
...but I want to be like that at the end.
Smiling?
So how do you want to die?
Let's see...
Death by over-arousal?
You're definitely going to have a bizarre death!
That's right...
I bought a digital camera for work today...
I haven't been back in a while.
You're so annoying!
Come on!
I wonder what...
Just one more!
Okay?
Geez! I'm in the middle of a game!
...they're doing right now.
Okay! Okay!
Okay! Cheese!
Come on, Dad!
Okay, one more!
That's enough already.
And Dad, you're way too close.
You're so heartless, Konata.
We're taking photos to commemorate this new camera!
Didn't you buy this for work?
Don't be such a stiff!
Honestly...
Sou-kun hasn't changed.
One more picture!
That's enough.
That's right, you never did...
You're such a pest.
...pay much attention to what other people wanted.
Take that!
Ow.
That hurts, Konata!
You really haven't changed.
But you know...
You feel more and more like Kanata when I hold you.
It makes my heart race.
Hey!
Don't just blurt out risqué statements!
I can see what Mom had to put up with...
What was that?!
Indeed...
Your dad may be like that...
...but don't turn into a bad person.
That's right, Konata.
Teach me that one game once you clear it.
Okay.
That one's surprisingly difficult.
But...
I think I made a wrong choice somewhere...
They play games together...
...so it looks like they're getting along.
I can't make it to the H-scene for the character I want.
Wait!
What are you letting your daughter play?!
Geez...
Is this really okay?
Aren't you teaching her the wrong things, Sou-kun?
Hey.
Why did Mom choose you?
'Cause you're just a perverted, lolicon, old geek.
People usually don't go for that.
That's a little harsh.
You don't go easy on your old man, huh?
For real.
But that's right...
Honestly...
Kanata had really good intuition.
You were always like this...
Always making me almost forget...
Maybe it was fate.
...why I chose to spend...
Even though I failed as a human being...
...my life with this man.
...there was one thing I was absolutely sure about.
One thing you were absolutely sure about?
What was that?
I was...
...the one who loved Kanata most in this world.
That was it.
I just can't beat you.
Results for the New Writer Award
No recipients
He accepts my good and bad parts.
He's willing to show both...
...his good and bad parts.
The place I feel most at ease...
The place that lets me feel most at ease...
Yeah?
Okay!
That's enough reminiscing.
Let's take another one?
We'll do one with Yu-chan later, okay?
The fact that I can no longer be there...
That's enough...
And that would be more than one picture.
...hurts a little.
It's all good.
You bought this for your hobby, didn't you?
Geez.
What are you talking about?
I'm just testing it out before I take pictures for work.
But...
Man...
If I can live on inside them...
...the way the two of them exist inside me...
...I'll continue to watch over them.
There!
Here we go!
May the ones who brought me so much joy...
Okay.
...be blessed with happiness.
Cheese!
I wonder if they'll be surprised.
D-Dad!
This picture...
There's a shadow back there...
A real ghost picture...
H-Huh?
I'm done with my bath.
Yu—
Yu-Yu-Yu-Yu-chan!
W-Wait!
L-L-Look at this!
What is it?
What's wrong?
D-Delete it!
We have to delete it!
We'll be cursed!
S-Stop!
Don't delete it!
Wait!
Deleting it isn't enough!
Don't we have to burn it?
Don't burn it!
Now that I've talked with her...
...I have a different impression of her...
...but Mina-rin still seems a little scary.
But she's really nice.
She's back!
Minami-chan!
Welcome back!
I'm back.
Those two are really close.
You had classroom duty today, right?
Was the teacher still in the faculty office?
This would be...
Yutaka, your tie is crooked.
B-Big Sister..
I mustn't!
I'm looking at my friends weird again...
Maybe it's been building up.
Three!
Two!
One!
Start!
So did you find them?
Can't find them anywhere?
And you can't find their managers?
They ran away...
Well, either way, they're fired.
Uh...
Besides...
It's rolling...
I had a bad feeling about this show from the beginning!
U-Uh...
You know?
Fact...
I actually refused in the beginning.
But all that politics crap.
Grown-up issues and whatnot.
Uh...
Uh, it's rolling.
What's rolling?
Me?
You?
Or the earth?
No, that's not what I meant.
Then what.
I'm saying that the camera's rolling!
Idiot!
Turn it off!
Isono!
What is it, Nakajima?!
Now, please listen to me!
This time!
This time, it's the medley version!
1. Love Legend of Minoru 2. Forgot My Something 3. Sunny Sunshiny Happy 4. How a Man Should Live 5. Take it! Sailor Uniform 6. The Dentistman Song 7. My Dear Santa Monica
One, two, three, four!
Mi-Mi-Miracle!
For-For-For-Forgot my something.
One clear, sunshiny day...
Take it! I'll...
I am...
Santa Mo...
Mi-Mi-Miracle Minorun-run!
For-For-For-For...
One clear, sunshiny...
Take it! I'll...
Dentistman!
Santa Moni...
For-For-For-Forgot my something.
Forgot my something.
That fragment of memory...
Ony clear, sunshiny day...
Take it! I'll still be...
I am Dentistman!
Santa Moni...
I am Dentist...
I am Dentistman!
For-For-For-For-For-For!
Minorun-run!
I am Dentistman!
You didn't change when I blew the whistle.
You kept finishing Dentistman.
Yep.
I did.
Why?
Just switch.
Next Episode
Well, next time on Lucky Star:
I'm Soujirou.
I'm Kanata.
Then Sou-kun...
I'll be heading off now.
Are you leaving?
Take me with you.
I don't know how to leave my body yet...
...but I'm sure I can learn!
Sou-kun, you're talking about manga or anime again, aren't you?
Then see you later.
Kanata!
Next time:
「A Fine Line」
A Fine Line.
Sou-kun!
I can't fly with all the turbulence!
Hey now...