Well, let's get crackin'.
Let's-a-go.
Stop messing around and start!
Around 3 cm!
aimai 3 SENCHI
Looks peachy, doesn't it?
sorya puni tte KOTO kai?
Hey!
cho!
Wrapping for a uniform...
rappingu ga seifuku...
Turn-off, ain't it?
daaa furitte koto nai
Ha.
pu.
Just work it ♥
ganbacchau ♥
And do it?
yacchacchau
Don't forget to catch and release yo!
son tokya-cchi & RELEASE gyo
I sweat!
ase
FUU!
I sweat!
ase
And throw in a!
no tanima ni
DARLiN' DARLiN* F R E E Z E!!
FeelING crummy!
nanka DAru-
SomethING's coming!
nanka DEru-
I lOVE you so!
ashiTEru
Oops!
are
I screwed one upsie-up!
ikko ga chigatterunru-
A nail biter!
nayamiNbo-
A steel beater!
koutetsubo-
Gourmet eater!
oishinbo-
Cut that out already!
i-kagen ni SHINASA!
Is that new blushing flower...
tondetta AITSU no hoteru KARADA tte
...considered a normal girl or what?
iwayuru futsu- no onya no KO
Wowzers!
odoroita
Only for me?
atashi dake?
Pork chops!
tonkotasu
Firm noodles!
HARIGANE
Fill 'er up again!
okawari
DA-DA-DA!
Ooh!
Guess what?
My glasses...
Where are my glasses?
But I've been playing the same fighting games lately.
If I don't have my glasses...
BON-BON
Cheerleaders!
o-endan
LET'S GET!
Cherry pie!
CHERI-PAI
RAN-RAN
Welcome party!
kange-kai
LOOK UP!
Sensation!
sense-shon
Yeah!
hai!
Leavin' an impression.
sonzaikan
...asteriods.
•• shouwakusei
Crash!
butsukatte
And burned!
tokemashita
Shockers!
bo-zen
Break into song!
ooi ni utatte
Crunch time!
SHIRENJA-
Take it!
motteike!
I'll still be laughing in the end!
saigo ni waracchau no wa atashi no hazu
'Cause it's a sailor uniform.
SE-RA- fuku dakara desu
← Q.E.D.!
← ketsuron
It's only Monday and I'm already blue.
getsuyoubi na no ni! kigen warui no
What to do?
dou suru yo?
I'd rather wear my summer clothes.
natsufuku ga ii no desu
← So cute!
← KYA? WA! IIv
3 pics incoming!
sekkin 3 PIKUTO
That's a toughie to pick!
suru madette chu-chou da
Ooh ☆
yan ☆
Just work it!
ganbatte
YEAH!
To the limit!
harikitte
YEAH!
MY DARLiN' DARLiN! P L E A S E!!
Tomorrow's the start of a long break...
Don't forget that you're all students...
...and act with caution.
Precautions
for
Summer Vacation
Yes, ma'am!
Students feel restless around this time of year...
...and many cause societal disturbances.
I am terribly concerned.
Take extreme care to avoid causing any trouble.
Precautions
for
Summer Vacation
In short...
If ya do something bad...
...it'll cut into my vacation...
...so I'm begging ya!
Sh-She's hopeless...
Ace
Shooter
It's finally vacation...
When I think about how I won't have to see your face every day...
...I feel so good.
Sis...
Well, even if it is a vacation...
...I'll still see Teacher every day.
Why?
Do you have make-up classes or something?
We're in the same party on an MMO.
That's just yeah.
MMO?
She plays a wizard, and I'm a tank.
So if we pair up and I pull...
...we can get crazy experience.
Uh...
Well, I'm the only one who's actually busy.
All Teacher has to do is click AOE spells.
The other day, I pulled this huge mob...
...but Teacher had fallen asleep...
It took a whole day to make up the experience lost from death.
Um...
In Japanese, okay?
Good morning.
It sure is hot this morning.
Morning.
Your hair's pretty wild.
Hey, Sis.
How about we turn on the A/C?
There you go again...
Don't be so quick to depend on that stuff.
Just use a fan or something.
Here.
A fan can make it pretty cool.
Right?
I'm hot...
You get tired from fanning yourself...
...and once you stop, you feel even hotter than before, right?
When you use a fan...
Well, I expected this.
Hang in there.
Everybody's wearing yukatas.
Well, our sashes are the pre-tied kind.
The ones you can just attach.
Even then, yukatas sure are hard to put on.
Yours is a real tied-on sash, huh?
Guess I shouldn't be surprised.
No.
A clerk at the store tied it for me.
Tying a sash would be too difficult for me.
I see.
And Konata's wearing one.
Oddly enough.
Did you get also yours tied at the store?
Nope.
My dad did it for me.
Oh, really...
Come on, let's go!
How come her dad knows how to tie a sash?
Hey!
Konata-chan!
A cop?
Do you know her?
She's Cousin Yui.
Nice ta meet ya!
It's a pleasure to meet you.
Hi.
Listen to your elders...
...and control yourself...
...and get home early.
Elders
No, no, no, no, no.
We're in the same year.
Don't use Konata as the standard.
We're all in the same year.
Whoa!
Sorry, sorry.
I'm amazed!
The difference in size got me.
That's okay.
Man...
Girls sure hit puberty early these days.
No.
Like I said!
Don't use Konata as the standard!
We're the normal ones!
It's a shooting game.
Cousin Yui.
Aren't you good at shooting games?
Believe it or not...
...I'm good enough to be known as Sharpshooter Yui-chan.
I can hit five bullseyes in three seconds.
With enough time to flash a peace sign.
Then show us.
Here.
Huh?
What?
You use rifles for shooting games?
What a surprise!
I use pistols.
Can't wait! Can't wait!
Narumi.
What are you so concentrated on over there?
Aren't you on duty?
What?
Okay, back to patrolling.
Let's try this again...
Hey, big guy.
We can have anything over there if we hit it?
They're all okay.
All of them?
All of them.
Whoa, miss.
I'm not a prize.
Summer festivals are all about shaved ice!
It's pretty hot.
Let's have some.
Strawberry
Lemon
Melon
Blue Hawaii
Oh, yeah.
I've been wondering...
I know what strawberry, lemon, and melon are...
...but what kind of fruit is a Blue Hawaii?
What does it taste like?
L-Like Blue Hawaii?
That's right..
That's what you would think.
So Miyuki-san...
Do you know anything about Blue Hawaii?
Blue Hawaii, is it?
Um, let's see...
Is it a song?
B-Blue...
No, that's not it.
I'm not really sure.
I'm sorry I couldn't be of any help.
I'll look it up in the near future.
I'm counting on you.
I don't believe there are any fruits or confections by that name.
Wait.
Shouldn't the person who wants to know...
...be looking it up instead of Miyuki?
Um...
About Blue Hawaii...
I think the name comes from...
...a cocktail with the same name and color.
The cocktail was named with the movie Blue Hawaii in mind.
You're right.
That was very informative.
When you learn something from Tsukasa...
...it feels like you've really failed.
I just realized that I barely have any money left.
Stuff at these stalls isn't cheap.
Use your money wisely.
For crying out loud...
But the whole festival atmosphere makes you wanna spend.
I guess.
It's like how you don't realize how
expensive doujinshi is when you're at Comiket.
Afterwards, you're like, "Whoa, I spent a lot."
Seriously, nobody else understands your world!
You're all exhausted from waiting in line since morning...
...and it's really far between the west gate and east gate.
We don't know what you're talking about.
I love how cotton candy is all fluffy and sweet!
You're not a child.
Eat slower.
It's not as entertaining when two girls do it.
Don't say it.
Why haven't any of us found any romance?
Summer means festivals which means yukatas!
If this was a dating sim...
...you'd probably trigger at least one flag somewhere.
Flag?
And there'd be an event scene.
Since you'd be in yukatas.
And it's outdoors.
Okay, that's far enough.
Aren't you going to play anything, Kagami-san?
Since we're here...
Might as well scoop goldfish or something.
I haven't even made a move!
Why are they running away?
Didn't they sense your barbaric nature and run away?
Guess we've finally got some hard proof.
Look!
There's one right here!
You're right.
Okay...
Gotta catch 'em all!
Yay!
I caught one!
That was amazing!
I'll take care of it.
I'll take good care of it.
Lil' Goldy.
Yo.
Y'all came together.
I heard there was a festival around here...
...so I figured I might as well come.
I love festivals.
Did you come with your boyfriend?
'Course not.
Ain't got one.
There really isn't a shred of romance around us.
Figured as much.
We meet again!
Looks like you're having fun with a new friend.
Hello.
So this is the one who really hit puberty early, huh?
She's our teacher.
For homeroom.
I'm terribly sorry.
I assumed that you were a classmate.
It's okay.
This is Cousin Yui.
She's a cop.
As you can see.
Yeah...
Today's a summer festival...
...so I'm on patrol here.
Man, they make us work in such hot weather.
Work?
Looks like you're just having fun.
Are you also working?
Keeping an eye on students?
Nah.
I was bored so I figured I'd drop by.
Lucky you.
If I wasn't on duty...
...I would have come to play around.
No.
You're having plenty of fun as it is!
Are you also by yourself?
Yes, I am.
I see!
Single
Husband
works far away
Actually, I would recommend Balsamic vinegar...
But the normal vinegar you may have in your kitchen works fine.
Balsamic vinegar.
Balsamic vinegar!
Vacations are kind of boring since you usually have nothing to do.
You get used to sitting around and doing nothing.
If you're going to say that...
...don't ask me to show you my homework later.
I see.
It sure is cute.
All stout and rotund.
And how the outside looks like a froggie.
Yep, yep.
Depleted uranium, huh?
That's cool!
I'll get in trouble if I'm on the phone too long.
Then bye!
I was on the phone with Kona-chan...
...and I mentioned how much free time we have during vacation...
...but she's playing a bunch of games
that have piled up so she has no free time.
I guess some people still enjoy a
full and satisfying summer vacation.
Maybe I should do something, too.
Well...
I suppose that's okay...
But do your homework!
Honestly...
Every single time...
I'll pull one.
I'll pull one
k
lolololo
debuff plz
Your friend nanakon has logged on
Debuff please.
Teacher logged on.
hi
yo (^3^)/
you're on a lot more since it's vacation, huh?
pretty much lol
i've got some time wanna go hunting?
i'm in the cave near chopron village
oh yeah, i'm coming! >w<b
time for some wiz action!
then i'll be waiting by the gate
so anyway, that's great and all but have you done your homework? (-_-)
huh?
been in your room the whole time? (-_-)
don't forget when school starts again (~3~)y-~~~
also, don't stay up late or sleep in just 'cause you're on vacation
You're on a lot more since it's vacation, huh?
I've got some time. Wanna go hunting?
I'm in the cave near Chopron Village.
Then I'll be waiting by the gate.
Teacher...
Stop talking about the real world on an MMO every day...
It's like I'm getting yelled at by Kagami every day.
Yo!
Sure is hot today.
Welcome.
Come on in.
Hello.
You set up an electric fan.
Since it's hot.
Cool yourself down.
I knew it.
I knew you'd do it.
Good morning.
Kona-chan's here.
Yo.
Good morning, my foot!
Do you have any idea what time it is?
It sure is hot.
You too?!
Well, it's the normal thing to do.
It isn't.
But Kagami also did it this morning.
See.
I was seen.
Looks like Comp Festival's pretty popular.
What's that?
If you collect the forms that come in
these magazines and send them in...
...you can get every single limited edition QUO card.
I'm constantly taking magazines to the register like I'm possessed.
You were saying the same thing about QUO cards the other day.
Japanese people are really weak when it
comes to special gifts or limited edition stuff.
That's why it's essential to buy one for
preservation, one to look at, and one extra.
Wait!
You're undeniably a special case!
There aren't many people like you.
Sometimes, I forget who I lent it to and have to buy another one.
Don't forget.
So...
I'd like to order the usual...
Homework!
Again?
I'll teach you the stuff you don't know...
...so try doing the problems yourself.
Balsamic vinegar.
Kagami.
Tell me how to do this one.
For this one...
Kagami.
I don't know how to do here through here.
That was close.
Kagami.
This one is...
You're not even trying to think it through, are you?!
I am thinking it through.
Really...
And I don't know any of the ones past this one.
You aren't thinking after all!
She ended up not telling me how to do them.
Hey!
I'm here to play!
Cousin Yui.
Perfect timing.
Teach me this part.
Math homework?
Let's see.
Leave it to me.
Well...
I must say, as a good police officer...
...my help would not be to your benefit...
...so don't depend on others!
It's such a pain when I don't understand any of the questions...
If you don't know the answer...
...just write something that sounds close.
Because you just have to turn the homework in.
I get it.
You're smart!
But this really weakens what she said before...
I doubt this will be to my benefit...
Yeah...
That's what I did!
I'm exhausted...
I'll do a little gaming for a break.
I'll do some solo hunting for thirty minutes.
Thirty minutes should be okay.
Solo hunting, right? Right?
...becomes fiction.
...what make you strong.
This isn't...
...else.
A rare drop.
Obtained Demonic Sword Laevateinn
What's this
Laevateinn!
I've never seen anyone with this!
It's ultra rare!
found a laeva sword!!!!
RLY?! Σ(@@)
lololo gratz lolololo
i'll be right there so show me show me! >w<ノ
Let's celebrate. Get a bunch of clan members and go test it out o(^^)o
all-nighter for sure lololo
I'm feeling it tonight roflcopterskates
bbq
k. come on
Found a Laeva sword!
Okay. Come on!
Well, where should we try it out?
Everybody's pumped up.
That's right.
I'll buy a bunch of quality potions to pass out.
Let's go back to town first...
Gonna get busy!
Good lucky!
I'm your navigator, Akira Kogami!
We're already on the fifth episode of Lucky Channel!
Let's get even crazier!
Now let me introduce...
...someone who's showing up more
often in the actual show and getting full of it...
I mean...
The hardworking...
Minoru Shiraishi-san!
Clap. Clap. Clap.
Well...
I didn't mean to look like I was full of it...
I'm the assistant, Minoru Shiraishi.
It's a pleasure!
Okay.
We're always receiving lots of postcards.
Today's is from U.S.S. Gatoh in Tokyo.
Occupation: NEET.
This guy sent in fifty by himself...
He must be one sorry guy!
Let's move on to the postcard.
Good day, Akira-san and Minoru-san.
In the actual show, Konata-chan seems to play MMOs.
Do you also play these games, Akira-san?
By the way, I live a happy life playing female characters every day.
MMOs?
Online games?
I'm sorry to say that I've never tried it.
But it's better if you haven't.
Another blunt response...
R-Really?
Too many people getting addicted and giving up on the real world.
I was dumb like that once.
I would log on whenever I had time...
...and stay on forever doing stuff like PKKing.
Back when I was young.
Wh-When you were young...?
Er.
There were a bunch of words I didn't get...
You're better off not knowing.
Well, only half the audience is going to get it anyway.
A-Anyway, so you've played them before?
Then do you have any online experiences you would like to share?
Yep!
You bet I do!
When l first started...
...I didn't know what to do...
...and I got lots of help from some really nice and experienced guys!
They gave me lots of expensive armor and rare items!
Akira was so touched!
R-Really...
It was really fun so you should all play, too!
We're already out of time.
Bye-bee!
Then we'll see you next time.
So you're popular in those kind of games, huh?
Huh?
Akira-sama?
What's wrong?
Cut 12 on page 38.
Yes?
Who the hell is Yutaka?!
That's what you're mad about this time?!
I'm Akira!
Well, that's true...
Bring out whoever's responsible!
No! Uh...
D-Director?
Director?!
Ah, no.
A producer would be better.
The hell is Yutaka?!
Producer would be better!
Hey!
A-Akira-san!
Please calm down!
Please!
You know.
Yes?
Why don't we change Minoru Shiraishi's name...
...to something else?
Like Su-
You rocked, Kagamin!
Cut that out.
So is Tsukasa or Miyuki next?
Me.
Again?!
When did you order a song?!
They were taking too long and it'd be a waste of time.
Sorry.
I need a little more time to decide.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
We can kill some time with Konata's singing.
I know this!
Didn't expect you to go with something mainstream.
Kami rules!
Sparking!
BREAK THROUGH THE SHINING CLOUDS!
FLY AWAY!
A PANORAMA SPREADS THROUGH MY BODY!
EARTH GETS MAD AFTER A KICK IN THE FACE!
AND MAKES A VOLCANO ERUPT!
IF THE MELTED POLAR ICE...
...YIELDS A DINOSAUR...
...I WANNA TRAIN IT TO BALANCE ON A BALL!
CHA-LA HEAD-CHA-LA!
NO MATTER WHAT HAPPENS!
I'LL BE FEELIN' FINE!
CHA-LA HEAD-CHA-LA!
Next Episode
To keep our city clean,
fireworks are banned
between 10 PM and 7 AM.
Well, next time on Lucky Star:
I'm Konata.
When you first start MH2...
...the condition for learning weapons is defeating five Gearnos.
So once you return to town...
...and get sent on a quest by the elder...
...even if you defeat five Gearnos...
...get loads of snow mountain grass...
...and lots of poponotan...
...when you can't go back to town...
...you realize for the first time that you
can't access your supply box yourself...
...and your reward is decreased since
you didn't read the instruction manual...
...and you can't save up money.
Doesn't it make you wonder about
how this applies to the real world?
「Summer Events」
Next time:
Summer Events!
Look forward to next time!