Well, let's get crackin'.
Let's-a-go.
Stop messing around and start!
Around 3 cm!
aimai 3 SENCHI
Looks peachy, doesn't it?
sorya puni tte KOTO kai?
Hey!
cho!
Wrapping for a uniform...
rappingu ga seifuku...
Turn-off, ain't it?
daaa furitte koto nai
Ha.
pu.
Just work it ♥
ganbacchau ♥
And do it?
yacchacchau
Don't forget to catch and release yo!
son tokya-cchi & RELEASE gyo
I sweat!
ase
FUU!
I sweat!
ase
And throw in a!
no tanima ni
DARLiN' DARLiN* F R E E Z E!!
FeelING crummy!
nanka DAru-
SomethING's coming!
nanka DEru-
I lOVE you so!
ashiTEru
Oops!
are
I screwed one upsie-up!
ikko ga chigatterunru-
A nail biter!
nayamiNbo-
A steel beater!
koutetsubo-
Gourmet eater!
oishinbo-
Cut that out already!
i-kagen ni SHINASA!
Is that new blushing flower...
tondetta AITSU no hoteru KARADA tte
...considered a normal girl or what?
iwayuru futsu- no onya no KO
Wowzers!
odoroita
Only for me?
atashi dake?
Pork chops!
tonkotasu
Firm noodles!
HARIGANE
Fill 'er up again!
okawari
DA-DA-DA!
Ooh!
Guess what?
My glasses...
Where are my glasses?
But I've been playing the same fighting games lately.
If I don't have my glasses...
BON-BON
Cheerleaders!
o-endan
LET'S GET!
Cherry pie!
CHERI-PAI
RAN-RAN
Welcome party!
kange-kai
LOOK UP!
Sensation!
sense-shon
Yeah!
hai!
Leavin' an impression.
sonzaikan
...asteriods.
•• shouwakusei
Crash!
butsukatte
And burned!
tokemashita
Shockers!
bo-zen
Break into song!
ooi ni utatte
Crunch time!
SHIRENJA-
Take it!
motteike!
I'll still be laughing in the end!
saigo ni waracchau no wa atashi no hazu
'Cause it's a sailor uniform.
SE-RA- fuku dakara desu
← Q.E.D.!
← ketsuron
It's only Monday and I'm already blue.
getsuyoubi na no ni! kigen warui no
What to do?
dou suru yo?
I'd rather wear my summer clothes.
natsufuku ga ii no desu
← So cute!
← KYA? WA! IIv
3 pics incoming!
sekkin 3 PIKUTO
That's a toughie to pick!
suru madette chu-chou da
Ooh ☆
yan ☆
Just work it!
ganbatte
YEAH!
To the limit!
harikitte
YEAH!
MY DARLiN' DARLiN! P L E A S E!!
Okay.
Who can solve this one?
Shiraishi.
You just called on me!
Really?
Then Izumi.
Izumi?
No, I wasn't asleep.
I didn't say anything yet.
Motivation
Issues
I forgot my English textbook!
Why don't you go borrow Kagami's?
They already had English, right?
Honestly...
You're so careless.
Thank you!
You should double-check everything the day before.
Tsukasa tends to forget stuff a lot, right?
Come to think of it...
...Konata doesn't forget stuff like textbooks much.
That's because I'm surprisingly diligent about those things.
Plus, I never take my textbooks home in the first place.
Oh, yeah...
That's not called being diligent.
But you can't review what we went over in class without a textbook.
I never study at home.
Since you end up cramming the night before...
But Kona-chan's good at putting off stuff till the night before.
That could be why I forget to do my homework.
You don't forget to do it.
You just don't want to do it.
So show me your homework for Japanese this afternoon.
Already at it again, huh?
I've been thinking...
Miyuki's in your class...
Ask her to show you her homework.
How should I put this...
Miyuki-san's such a nice person...
...that it ends up being hard to ask her for anything...
You know what I mean?
There's this sensation you get.
I get what you're saying...
...but I still can't accept it.
Izumi.
Izumi?
What? She's late?
Stop!
I'm not late!
I was late because I had to help someone!
I usually go around with this guy...
...but I just couldn't get away today!
He was like it's okay, we can split up...
...but the other five of us had gotten one...
...and he was the odd one out...
...which kinda left a bad feeling.
When you've been in the same party for a
long time, you wanna help each other out.
So we all backed him up.
Yeah, friends are a beautiful thing.
Really...
So you were up all night playing online games again.
Kept playing after I logged off, huh?
Izumi.
Izumi?
What? She's late?
Stop!
I'm not late!
This girl crashed into me in the shopping district.
Then she suddenly grabbed my hand and took off running.
Eventually, I learned that she'd stolen some taiyaki...
...and was on the run...
I was wondering what any of this had to do with me...
...but I had no choice but to duck into
a café to hide from the taiyaki baker.
So many potential comebacks...
But I can't!
As a teacher!
As a human being!
I'm down with a summer cold.
Izumi.
What's wrong?
Teacher, I'm terribly sorry...
...but I need to take a sick day...
Hey, now.
Too much gaming again?
The same trick won't work every time.
No, I'm sick...
Let me guess. You've got a summer cold, right?
Winter's over and the weather's nice...
...so stop being lazy and get to class!
So she totally treated me like the boy who cried wolf yesterday.
You reap what you sow.
Are you okay now?
It looks like my fever broke...
...but my throat still hurts.
That means you breathe through your mouth.
Huh?
Well...
You can also breathe through your mouth...
...but wouldn't you usually breathe through your nose?
No...
But Kona-chan breathes through her mouth more than her nose.
Because...
You know?
If a virus enters through your mouth, you get a throat infection.
And if a virus enters through your nose, you get a nasal infection.
So people with sore throats probably had a
higher chance of a virus entering through their throat...
This is when we turn to Miyuki-san.
Yeah...
Huh?
So hot...
Don't feel like doing anything...
Kagami?
About your birthday party today...
How about we hold it at my place?
It's so hot that I can't move a step.
We're baking cookies right now.
I'll go.
Hurry it up.
Welcome!
Happy birthday!
Tsukasa and other.
Don't abbreviate me off!
Happy birthday.
Kagami-san and Tsukasa-san.
Thanks!
Thank you!
And it isn't much...
...but I have presents for you.
I'm so excited!
Open it up.
Matching earrings!
I considered a number of options...
...but I had a hard time making up my mind.
And here are presents from me!
Oh, joy.
Open it up.
[Caption: Chief]
What is this?
Brigade chief armband.
Try it on.
Why should I put this on?!
I figured it would fit you perfectly.
It'll go better on you.
Um...
Then what is this...
To Heart?!
It cost a fortune...
Wear it with care.
Don't try to make both of us cosplay!
It's barely any different from our uniform.
That's quite a problem.
If it's too big...
Right?
Just sucks.
And it stinks.
Hey.
It's our birthday.
You could hold back a little.
Tsukasa's cookies are always so good.
I baked them with her this time.
Kinda learned as I went.
What's wrong?
Having heard that...
...some of these cookies don't taste that good anymore.
Weird, ain't it?
What was that?!
Wonder if this is one of Kagami's.
Might as well eat the cake, too.
Kagamin. Only labors industriously on her birthday.
Zip it.
By the way...
...isn't there always a fight over how to cut the cake?
Why?
You know.
When you cut a cake into a bunch of slices...
...how do you divide up the strawberries on top...
...or decide who gets the chocolate decorations?
My older sisters all love chocolate.
Rats...
I was off.
Wouldn't expect that from Kagamin.
What are you talking about?!
Let's eat!
Let's eat.
What?
My strawberry's awfully small.
What is it?
Do I have cake on my face?
I just discovered another facet of Kagamin's charm.
You sound just like Shin-chan so stop it.
It's almost summer break.
That's right.
The beach, the pool, and summer festivals...
Are there any other usual events?
Twitch.
Summer is all about the annual celebration!
The beginning of the battle!
The one and only...
Comiket!
No, no, no, no, no.
That only applies to you.
Is that like cricket?
W-Well...
Everyone has their own different thing to do.
Like visiting relatives or something.
Good morning.
Miyuki...
...do you have some kind of regular summer activity?
Let's see...
I'll be taking a vacation overseas again this year.
Again?
She said again?
Stupid bourgeois!
Is that like yogurt?
You said that you started working at a costume café...
Don't you need a good figure to pull that off?
Man...
I've been lamenting my lack of a chest for a while...
...but then this game said...
"A flat chest is a status symbol!
A rarity!"
Word for word.
And when you think about it...
...there is a demand, right?
Which means I'm valuable!
I want to know how a line from a game can fill her with confidence.
Then I guess I'm okay, too.
Honestly...
We have a test coming up.
Should you be gaming so much?
If you would only use some of that passion for studying.
Your grades would probably go up.
If she's so easily influenced...
...wouldn't she become a genius if
someone released a game that promoted studying?
There's already stuff like Moe Drill.
Wazzup?
There's been a lot of youth crime lately.
Whenever that happens...
...all the neighbors say...
He was such a nice boy.
I never would have imagined that he could do such a thing.
Well...
That just means you can't judge a person on the surface.
If you ever commit a crime...
I always figured she would do something like this.
I'll tell the whole world.
Tired...
It's so hot that I don't feel like doing anything.
I really understand how you feel...
...but you never feel like doing anything.
H i i r a g i
Hello, Kagami.
Yo.
Making progress on your studying for the test?
I was tidying up my room.
You know how kinda get the urge to start
cleaning when you're feeling the pressure?
I can understand...
...but study.
Okay!
Let's get a little studying done today!
I'll take a thirty minute break.
I'm losing my concentration.
Time's already up.
Just thirty more minutes.
Thirty more minutes...
Isn't Haruhi about to start?
They definitely cut corners with those long-winded Nagato scenes.
That Ya***** hasn't been very impressive recently.
They're already flaming away.
It's already two?
Not going to happen today.
I'll go to sleep and wake up early to study.
If I wake up at five...
...I can sleep three hours.
I ended up killing time yesterday by
reading manga and watching anime.
Sounds like something you would do.
Come to think of it...
You sure have some odd taste in manga and games.
You read manga aimed at boys...
...and mainly play dating sims for men.
My dad reads manga and plays games a lot...
...so I was probably influenced.
I've been watching him from the side since I was little.
I can understand the manga...
...but playing dating sims in front of your daughter?
What kind of father is he?
Doesn't your mom have anything to say...
...with both of you like this?
I don't have a mom.
She died when I was really little.
Really...
So I'm always doing housework...
...which is why I'm way better than Kagami is.
Don't say stuff like that...
...when the mood isn't right for comebacks.
Tsukasa's also good at cooking, right?
I'm not sure if I would say that I'm good...
...but I love it!
I wonder how good Miyuki-san is.
She looks rich...
...so maybe she's bad at housework.
Cooking, is it?
To be honest...
I only help out from time to time...
...so I'm not very skilled at housework.
It's quite embarrassing.
Oh! Knew it!
But Miyuki's.so good at everything else...
...that it doesn't really feel the same.
You can't just assume that she's bad when she says she's bad.
I see...
No, not at all...
Then what about our teacher?
I heard that she lives by herself...
...but she looks like she could be a slob.
These days...
...ya can get by without knowing how ta cook!
Ya got your convenience stores.
Just kiddin'!
I can cook.
About as well as your average person.
Please don't make jokes that sound like they're true.
Tsukasa still has my dictionary.
Tsukasa.
Sorry. Could I get my dictionary back?
I-I was doing a little cleaning for a change of pace...
...yeah...
You too, huh?
Yo.
What's up?
The people at work are trying to
come up with a new menu for summer.
So you do stuff like that, too...
And wait, did you give up on studying for the test?
Spicy stuff's good when it's hot outside...
...so how about super spicy ramen?!
Go with something you would usually find in a café.
Then a super spicy parfait!
Could you stop skipping the thinking process when you respond?
I can't stand...
Why doesn't our school have swimming class?
We have a pool...
I'm actually relieved by that fact.
Why's that?
To be honest...
I can't open my eyes underwater...
...so I can't really swim.
It's quite embarrassing.
Why are your weaknesses always anything but?!
The summer Comp Festival is finally about to begin!
That's right...
This is why I started working...
A festival...
You bring so many fond memories!
Why are you pulling out an ancient reference?
Man...
When the customers start getting excited with you...
...doesn't it feel like everyone's pumped up together for the festival?
Use some of that passion on academic endeavors.
Having trouble getting to sleep.
Guess I'll read until I fall asleep.
I happen to have some stuff I just bought.
So much for falling asleep...
It's already morning.
And now...
...I'm feeling really sleepy...
please set your mobile phone to silent mode
and refrain from making calls.
Stare...
I can understand turning off your phones around priority seats...
Because of pacemakers and the like.
But why do they ban cell phone use for the whole train?
Because...
...you'll disturb other people when you talk?
But you know...
Aren't trains already noisy with people talking anyway?
That includes men and women of all ages.
I guess that's true...
Are you going to work at the temple
for summer festivals like for New Year's?
Nah.
I don't work in the summer.
Oh, yeah...
It's getting to be that time of year.
Huh?
Weren't you on a diet?
Nah.
Maybe it's because of all the studying...
When I weighed myself yesterday, it was down.
So I figured it'd be okay.
That was quick.
And like, you're weak.
Good morning!
Kona-chan, good morning!
Huh?
What's wrong with Kagami?
Konata!
My weight already...
...went all the way up in like the blink of an eye...
It's 'cause you let go and started snacking again.
And wasn't that a senryu?
My weight already
went all the way up in like
the blink of an eye
I only...
I only ate a little...
It's not like a kilo or two more or
less is going to affect how you look.
Why do you get so excited and depressed over every kilogram?
This is why women are hopeless.
Aren't you supposed to be a woman?
Good lucky!
Welcome to another episode of Lucky Channel.
Has everyone been doing well?
I'm Akira Kogami, always running at 120%!
Today...
Nyoron!
Just kidding!
I'm the assistant, Minoru Shiraishi.
Hey.
What?
Don't interrupt me!
I'm sorry!
This isn't a kiddy ride.
Learn the job already.
Do you want to be dropped from this role?
I'm terribly sorry!
I'll work hard!
Give it my all!
Okay!
Today...
Ta-da!
We have big news for everyone!
Published in the November issue of Comptiq...
Project Fashionable Akira!
I've already received this many postcards from everyone!
Uh.
I think there was another person involved in that project...
Thanks for all the feedback!
Like cowabunga!
I don't think anyone's going to understand a joke from the eighties...
Then I'll reveal the idea I've selected after extensive review.
Like this.
Um...
This is from a Miss Cherry in Satte, Saitama.
Project Fashionable Akira!
Kagami-san's pigtails look great on her.
What if Akira-san also wore pigtails?
Pigtails, huh...
Sounds—
Wonderful!
That's right.
Hair styling is a woman's life!
If I split it in two...
...it might look lovely...
No ifs or buts about it.
Isn't it impossible with your hair length...
But you know.
It's not like long hair is always a good thing.
Akira-sama.
It's gonna show.
It weighs a lot...
It's really gonna show.
Like if you just twitch!
It's a pain to maintain.
And frankly, it isn't in fashion right now.
Guys run their mouth off about liking long hair on women...
Uh.
...but do they have any idea how much
time, effort, and money it takes to maintain?
You're talking about yourself now.
Uh...
You're not in character anymore.
You're no longer Akira-sama.
And nobody ever notices your efforts...
Are you listening?
Hello?
It's already time to say goodbye!
As for what would Akira look like with pigtails...
You can find out more on our homepage or the radio show!
Hope to see you!
Both hands will be waiting!
I made a funny!
Then please look forward to next week.
What was with the attitude?
By attitude, you mean...
Why did you keep cutting in?
That upset about getting burned in the beginning?
No! Just that...
...I just figured nobody would recognize cowabunga now...
Ah, no.
Forgive me.
Uh...
Why don't we start over again?
You know?
Yes.
I heard they're holding an audition for Minoru Shiraishi.
Seriously?!
This is the first I've heard about it!
You can try out if you want.
Try out? Me?
Good for you.
But I'm actually him!
What?
You're amazing, Kona-chan!
You can sing anything!
As long as it's an anime song.
You can sing well...
...in many different voices.
Singing anime songs...
...is all about staying true to the original song.
Okay.
Guess I'll sing.
What are you gonna sing, Sis?
The title was displayed earlier...
...but I didn't recognize it.
Miyuki, you don't know this?
Guess you aren't any better.
I've heard this before!
Weren't you watching the series with me a while ago?
Really?
I still prefer the movie.
Are you an old geezer or something?
Farewell doesn't mean goodbye.
You're good.
Sis is the best singer out of us sisters.
Just a long promise until we meet again.
If you have any regrets left in the place where our dreams were...
...they'll only serve to chill your heart.
Just stay like this...
As many hours as we can...
I want to hold you in my arms.
Next Episode
Well, next time on Lucky Star:
I'm Miyuki.
Golden Week...
...was apparently derived from industry lingo...
...for the period when movie ticket sales are extremely high.
「Ace Shooter」
Next time:
Ace Shooter.
Look forward to next time!