Class 3-B?
Ms. Kuroi!
Yeah, yeah...
Around 3 cm!
aimai 3 SENCHI
Looks peachy, doesn't it?
sorya puni tte KOTO kai?
Hey!
cho!
Wrapping for a uniform...
rappingu ga seifuku...
Turn-off, ain't it?
daaa furitte koto nai
Ha.
pu.
Just work it ♥
ganbacchau ♥
And do it?
yacchacchau
Don't forget to catch and release yo!
son tokya-cchi & RELEASE gyo
I sweat!
ase
FUU!
I sweat!
ase
And throw in a!
no tanima ni
DARLiN' DARLiN* F R E E Z E!!
FeelING crummy!
nanka DAru-
SomethING's coming!
nanka DEru-
I lOVE you so!
ashiTEru
Oops!
are
I screwed one upsie-up!
ikko ga chigatterunru-
A nail biter!
nayamiNbo-
A steel beater!
koutetsubo-
Gourmet eater!
oishinbo-
Cut that out already!
i-kagen ni SHINASA!
Is that new blushing flower...
tondetta AITSU no hoteru KARADA tte
...considered a normal girl or what?
iwayuru futsu- no onya no KO
Wowzers!
odoroita
Only for me?
atashi dake?
Pork chops!
tonkotasu
Firm noodles!
HARIGANE
Fill 'er up again!
okawari
DA-DA-DA!
Ooh!
Guess what?
My glasses...
Where are my glasses?
But I've been playing the same fighting games lately.
If I don't have my glasses...
BON-BON
Cheerleaders!
o-endan
LET'S GET!
Cherry pie!
CHERI-PAI
RAN-RAN
Welcome party!
kange-kai
LOOK UP!
Sensation!
sense-shon
Yeah!
hai!
Leavin' an impression.
sonzaikan
...asteriods.
•• shouwakusei
Crash!
butsukatte
And burned!
tokemashita
Shockers!
bo-zen
Break into song!
ooi ni utatte
Crunch time!
SHIRENJA-
Take it!
motteike!
I'll still be laughing in the end!
saigo ni waracchau no wa atashi no hazu
'Cause it's a sailor uniform.
SE-RA- fuku dakara desu
← Q.E.D.!
← ketsuron
It's only Monday and I'm already blue.
getsuyoubi na no ni! kigen warui no
What to do?
dou suru yo?
I'd rather wear my summer clothes.
natsufuku ga ii no desu
← So cute!
← KYA? WA! IIv
3 pics incoming!
sekkin 3 PIKUTO
That's a toughie to pick!
suru madette chu-chou da
Ooh ☆
yan ☆
Just work it!
ganbatte
YEAH!
To the limit!
harikitte
YEAH!
MY DARLiN' DARLiN! P L E A S E!!
So I have a pet dog in this game...
...and it's so cute that I start talking to it.
You know how...
...when you talk to animals...
...your voice gets all syrupy?
Except this was in a game.
I know what you mean.
LIL' GOLDY
When I talk to my goldfish...
...I lapse into baby talk.
I get talking to dogs and cats...
...but people who talk to fish must be pretty darn lonely.
What did you say?!
That's discrimination!
What's with the patronizing look?!
Oh, yeah.
I've been wondering for a while...
When people call hot dogs...
...wieners...
I wonder what that means.
U-Um...
It would take a long time if I went into detail...
...but it was definitely derived from a German word.
Okay.
Raise your hand if you just thought of something naughty.
2D
has
Substance
Observations on Gu***m
Oh, yeah...
Gu***m is still ridiculously popular.
Your dad also ***** it.
There are all kinds of Gu***m.
Like V...
And W...
And X...
And I saw 'em all when they first aired!
You could call it passion...
...or my duty as a fan!
In that case...
...would you watch Gu*dam: The Serial Murder Case...
...or Detective Gunda* if they started airing?
As a Gu***m fan...
...I suppose that I have a **** to watch it.
**** is kinda...
But it's a ***** you can't call it by a letter.
All this talk about **ndam has reminded me...
Despite appearances, I'm already *** years older than *muro.
Time passed in a *****.
And in two more years...
...I'll be the same age as B****t-san.
Can't even imagine it!
Well, you know...
B****t-san is a pretty *** character, even in the Gu***m world.
Same goes for Ha**n-sama...
Actually...
You're ***** for your age...
...so I wouldn't use *** for a standard.
You could at least say that I look ***** for my age.
Nah.
You're so cute!
Our neighbor gave us something nice.
A souvenir from vacation apparently.
What?
A pot?
You grew up to be my kind of girl!
Such a cutie.
It's hot, Dad.
And that was a dangerous statement.
Morning already, huh...
I got wasted last night...
...so I figured I'd be out till noon...
Guess I'm still young.
This is the morning news for Monday, July 2nd.
Early this morning, a man at a restaurant...
Huh?
What about Sunday?
What happened to my day off?!
...yelled, "Hey, this ramen sucks!"
I always plan on studying for tests at night...
...but I end up getting sleepy.
So I asked Sis for advice...
You don't like horror movies, right?
If you watched one...
...wouldn't that keep you up all night?
Seeing how you crawled into my bed last time.
And so...
...I didn't get sleepy after watching it.
An older sister knows just what to do.
But then...
...once it's night...
Thump
...the slightest sound from behind would make me jump...
...which made it even harder to focus on studying.
And I ended up not getting enough sleep...
...so I was tired in class.
But for someone who claims to dislike horror...
...you watch those movies quite often.
It's not that I choose to watch them...
My mother's the same way.
Hey, Miyuki.
I rented this.
Want to watch?
It's too scary by myself.
The people who can't stand it...
...actually watch them more often, right?
Perhaps they want to be scared.
You're wrong, Yuki-chan!
In my case, I really can't stand them!
Iwasaki-san.
Do you know the answer to this one?
I worked on it for a while...
...and I couldn't figure it out...
...so I was going to ask Miyuki-san.
I see.
We're really lucky to have
upperclassmen to rely on in these situations.
I was talking with Iwasaki-san about that at school today.
What?!
She has that much faith in me?!
This girl is going to soon discover
how the world is a very harsh place!
Hey, Cousin Yui.
Did you ever study together with Cousin K?
Nope.
That's a common situation in games.
When a boy and girl get together
to study, they can never concentrate.
When you can't concentrate, you
start fantasizing about stuff you like.
Your hidden side starts to show.
Big Sister.
I need help with a part.
Oh, I happen to be busy so ask Cousin Yui.
Study, study...
D-Dirty move!
M-Maybe it's 'cause I went to a different school.
I never learned this stuff.
I see.
I-It hurts...
Now I'm stuck...
Cousin Yui, do you know this one?
You probably don't!
Don't ask if you don't think I know it.
Didn't you see what just happened?
Man...
Maybe I'll call Miyuki-san.
Might be a bother for her though.
Well...
It'll probably be a bother.
Since it's late.
Why does she never...
...turn to her dad in these situations?
Rely on me sometimes!
I'll fix ya real good!
Izumi.
Don't sleep in class.
We live in an age where corporal punishment isn't allowed...
...yet you often hit people like it's no big deal.
Not that I have a problem with it.
That's true.
But I don't hit just anybody.
I choose my targets very carefully, if you get my drift.
Else I could get in trouble.
She actually said it.
Another crazy thing about her.
Besides, it doesn't make sense to ban corporal punishment.
「His life is the story of our era's most perfect man」
Jean-Paul Sartre
John Lennon
「Coolest man in the world」
Che Guevara
「Shoot, coward...
You are only going
to kill a man」
Okay.
That's all for today.
Miyuki-san, sorry.
I don't know these era names.
Yuki-chan.
Teach me how to do this one.
Yeah...
So like...
...why don't you ever ask your teacher?!
Ms. Kuroi!
Izumi, what's up?
Well...
I had a question...
Oh.
Ask away then.
I can't really refuse.
There's this rare item in a game I'm playing right now...
Er, what?!
Teacher?!
No...
That's not what I meant...
It's always sweltering after a hurricane.
We had a lot of instances of good ewather after a storm.
Stormy weather flock together.
Not bad.
By the way, what wasn't bad?
Just to make sure...
...that was supposed to be a joke, right?
Um...
I wanted to ask you something...
What's up this time?
About this morning...
Did Kona-chan say something weird?
I couldn't tell what was wrong...
We watch the news and stuff together...
...so why is she at Konata's level?
Notice for Absent Resident
Why do you people always have such perfect timing...
The pitcher is keeping an eye on the runner on second.
How's the baseball game going?
At this rate, it'll probably go overtime.
Again?!
Sheesh.
I have to change the recording time on the VCR.
Good grief.
They could just give it a bigger time block to begin with.
Besides...
...everybody drags out their motions in pro baseball, right?
Wouldn't they be able to finish on time...
...if they did everything at a brisker pace?
Well...
Some fans like the game because of the pace...
And the players need to concentrate.
Well?
Are you used to school yet?
Yes.
But I'm having a hard time with the huge homework load.
I see.
Third-years focus on studying for college testing...
...so they don't have much homework, huh?
Konata...
You...
Huh..
What's she talking about?
Too hot...
Bellybutton showing!
Konata!
How can you walk around dressed like that?!
What if Yu-chan copies you?!
But it's so hot lately.
You know...
It's like that thing the Diet's doing.
Cool Biz?
Yeah, that!
No, that's something different.
What were you doing?
I was wondering if I'd gotten a reply yet.
Don't you get anxious?
I was reading and I missed my stop.
Your casual slip-ups are always so cute.
Really?
Pretty sure they just cause trouble.
You have no idea.
The way she's all embarrassed when
she tries to make up for the mistake is killer.
It's cuter when you have some kind of shortcoming.
What?
So at your job...
I spilled it!
I'm so sorry, sir!
You do stuff like that?
Kagami.
You seem kinda dumb.
What're you doing?
You're the one who started talking about it!
Though I was the one who acted it out...
So what?
Do you pretend to be clumsy...
...to score points with the customers?
I don't do anything like that.
It's a common stereotype...
...but you'll get in trouble with the manager.
Oh.
I figured you'd be like, "It turns people on," and do it all the time.
You have no idea, Kagami.
Clumsy girls may be cute and a turn-on...
...but it's pretty annoying when they cause trouble in real life.
Though you can just laugh it off in games.
You geeks can be really harsh sometimes...
If we get a perfect answer...
...courtesy of Look JT*...
...we have a one-month journey through the tundra for the prize.
Now, let us begin.
On variety shows and quiz shows...
...they always have a bunch of prizes.
I am currently at Earth's bellybutton...
Isn't it to attract more contestants?
Ayers Rock!
And if they get a big-name celebrity, the ratings will go up.
Today's mystery is located in wondrous Australia.
That's true.
Here you will find kangaroos, koalas, and other wild animals.
Well, I don't really know.
But you know...
If they let the audience participate...
...and gave them the prizes...
This continent, separated long ago by tectonic movement...
...wouldn't that boost ratings even more?
...has transformed into a holy land safe from foreign intrusion.
I have to agree...
...but that's a direct way to do business.
Morning!
Yo.
I was playing a game yesterday when I realized something...
Who's our school idol?
What is this school idol?
Like a Miss contest or something?
Yeah...
That's what you would think...
It's more theoretical in games...
With stuff like personal bodyguards.
Another exhausting day...
So refreshing!
I have to leave early tomorrow.
Guess I should stay off the Internet tonight...
...and hit the sack.
Don't want to be late.
I'm starting to prioritize sleep...
Is it a sign I'm getting old?
When I was in school, I skipped sleep to have fun...
Ta-Tamura-san...
Is something wrong?
You've been making a lot of faces...
Well...
You know how when you're drawing...
...you tend to make the same faces as your characters?
Really...
So you were drawing.
I didn't know that you drew manga, Tamura-san.
They're mostly doujin...
What kind of manga do you draw?
Um...
Normal stuff like four panels...
O-Or romance stuff with...
...game characters I like...
So hard to answer...
The other day, I won 3,000 yen
with a lottery ticket I randomly bought.
I was thinking how lucky I was that morning.
Amazing!
But then my bicycle tire burst on the
way to school so I had to pay for repairs.
And my box lunch was ruined so I had to
buy another one from a convenience store.
The money vanished so perfectly...
My 3,000 yen...
Truth is stranger than fiction...
...I suppose.
But you know...
I figure I can use this story for manga...
...so it's okay...
She's strong...
Th-The drawing hand...
...is an artist's all...
Must defend it with my life...
Sh-She's strong...
You really are skilled.
Nah...
I've been in a slump...
That one's a bust.
But this is probably one of my better recent ones.
Objection
Yeah...
Other people aren't going to notice...
...the artist's habits or subtle touches...
I already knew that...
Crap!
What's wrong, Tamura-san?
I left my favourite pencil on my
desk after I finished drawing yesterday.
Want to borrow mine?
No...
I'm no good without her...
It just feels totally different...
Yeah...
Pencils are all the same, right?
I know it's true...
Of course that's how people would react...
So I ended up lost and couldn't get out for three hours.
What's wrong, Tamura-san?
S-So embarrassing...
The hell are they thinking, wearing that in broad daylight?
A coat?
Aren't they hot wearing so much in summer?
So only people who understand can feel the agony...
Hold on.
I need to message someone.
Welcome!
Sure is crowded.
I'll go write my name on the sheet.
So I was up all night playing games with Big Sister Konata.
Suzaku-sama!
Suzaku-sama, party of three!
They called us.
But Tamura-san...
They called a different name.
In these situations...
...I always want to put down the name of my favourite character.
It, like, makes me feel closer to the character.
Haruhi
Kyon
Yuki
Mikuru
Itsuki
Current Bowler: Haruhi
You can find my people...
...everywhere!
Rely on the Nurse's Office
Thanks.
I wish I could be all slender...
...and tall like you, Iwasaki-san.
Fantasy
I admire you so much, Minami-chan.
So...
Yutaka...
Rely on the Nurse's Office
Reality
You'll still grow.
Perhaps...
...you'll grow even taller than me.
Taller than you?
Fantasy
Minami-chan!
Minami-chan...
No!
That goes against natural world order!
And the last one's totally off!
Calm down, girl!
Tamura-san, are you okay?
You look kinda pale.
Actually...
...today's the submission deadline for an upcoming event...
...and I was up all night finishing...
I just sent it out...
But when I look at how hard I can work on something...
...I feel like I'm shining.
She's strong...
Tamura-san!
What's yaoi?
Which definition are you looking for...
Good lucky!
We're already on the nineteenth episode of Lucky Channel!
Looks like we're finally in the home stretch!
I'm your navigator, Akira Kogami!
And I'm the assistant, Minoru Shiraishi!
It's a pleasure.
Net Darling!
Anyway...
Da-Da Darling!
Akira-sama appears to be in a good mood today.
Can't do anything about adult circumstances.
Did something good happen?
What do you think?
Uh...
N-Never mind...
Being on TV really puts a strain on my nerves.
The stress really builds up after nineteen episodes.
I wish I could just soak in a spa and recuperate.
Maybe I can win that prize they
were talking about in the actual show.
That's like!
In that case...
...you have to start by appearing in the quiz show, right?
Crap...
Oh, yeah!
Traveling is great!
I'd love to travel!
Going someplace you've never been...
...really lightens your mood!
It rules!
Do you like to travel?
But of course!
I love to!
I've actually been to many places!
I've climbed Mt. Takao!
And I've been to Jogashima!
I'm definitely the outdoors type!
So you like to travel.
When you want to calm yourself down these days...
...nothing can beat a stroll through the splendor of a pristine forest!
Sounds great...
A stroll through a pristine forest.
Must really calm the soul.
Right?
Away from the hustle and bustle of the city...
...surrendering yourself to the tranquility of nature...
It heals both the body and soul!
Sounds good.
Nature might be nice.
Isn't nature great?!
Wanna go on a walk through the forest?
Seriously?!
Can I?
Well, if I can...
...I will!
Okay.
Shankya!
Then Minoru's Nature Tour's a go.
Huge.
Take 'em.
Guess they'll come in handy...
Where...
...am I going...
...exactly...
Mt. Fuji.
But...
I've already been to the mountains...
Not the mountain.
The forest.
Go to the forests of Fuji.
The forests, huh?
Who is...
I am...
Uh...
What am I supposed to do there?
Bring me water.
Water?
I wanna drink some of that famous Fuji water...
...so go get me some.
No way!
Don't they sell that stuff at convenience stores?!
I want mine fresh!
I won't be alone, right?
Alone!
Alone?!
Someone's coming with me, right?!
Don't worry.
The director and producer are sacrificing themselves to go with you.
Lucky you.
Oh, my saviour!
Come on!
Stop wasting time!
Don't miss the deadline.
No!
Please let me go!
We're already out of time!
Everybody!
Then...
I'll do it myself!
We'll have a wonderful guest next time...
Stop!
Please stop!
...here on Lucky Channel!
You can expect something great!
Ow!
Ow! Ow! Ow! Ow!
Bye-bee!
Let go of me!
Did we really need to go through all this trouble to get rid of him?
Could have just...
This week, we would like you to enjoy the pleasant image of nature and two young women playing with bubbles.
Part of my body is hot! Hot!
Hello!
Minoru Shiraishi here!
Now, please listen to me!
How a Man Should Live!
I wanna be like him.
Also, please feel free to turn off the sound.
Always looking ahead and moving forward.
Once you've made up your mind...
...never stop.
Once you've grabbed on...
...never let go.
Body and soul are...
...bare naked.
...bare.
Next Episode
Well, next time on Lucky Star:
I'm Nanako.
I'm Yui-chan!
I've been thinkin'...
Summer's like...
You get all excited before it starts...
...but before you know it, it's over and nothing happened, right?
Well, I guess nothing special ever happens.
'Sides, you're not gonna have a long
relationship with anybody you meet during fling season.
I wouldn't know...
Well, we've still got time.
Let's both work hard.
Yes?
Hard to answer...
Next time:
「How to Spend Summer」
How to Spend Summer!
I'm available!