Well, let's get crackin'.
Let's-a-go.
Stop messing around and start!
Around 3 cm!
aimai 3 SENCHI
Looks peachy, doesn't it?
sorya puni tte KOTO kai?
Hey!
cho!
Wrapping for a uniform...
rappingu ga seifuku...
Turn-off, ain't it?
daaa furitte koto nai
Ha.
pu.
Just work it ♥
ganbacchau ♥
And do it?
yacchacchau
Don't forget to catch and release yo!
son tokya-cchi & RELEASE gyo
I sweat!
ase
FUU!
I sweat!
ase
And throw in a!
no tanima ni
DARLiN' DARLiN* F R E E Z E!!
FeelING crummy!
nanka DAru-
SomethING's coming!
nanka DEru-
I lOVE you so!
ashiTEru
Oops!
are
I screwed one upsie-up!
ikko ga chigatterunru-
A nail biter!
nayamiNbo-
A steel beater!
koutetsubo-
Gourmet eater!
oishinbo-
Cut that out already!
i-kagen ni SHINASA!
Is that new blushing flower...
tondetta AITSU no hoteru KARADA tte
...considered a normal girl or what?
iwayuru futsu- no onya no KO
Wowzers!
odoroita
Only for me?
atashi dake?
Pork chops!
tonkotasu
Firm noodles!
HARIGANE
Fill 'er up again!
okawari
DA-DA-DA!
Ooh!
Guess what?
My glasses...
Where are my glasses?
But I've been playing the same fighting games lately.
If I don't have my glasses...
BON-BON
Cheerleaders!
o-endan
LET'S GET!
Cherry pie!
CHERI-PAI
RAN-RAN
Welcome party!
kange-kai
LOOK UP!
Sensation!
sense-shon
Yeah!
hai!
Leavin' an impression.
sonzaikan
...asteriods.
•• shouwakusei
Crash!
butsukatte
And burned!
tokemashita
Shockers!
bo-zen
Break into song!
ooi ni utatte
Crunch time!
SHIRENJA-
Take it!
motteike!
I'll still be laughing in the end!
saigo ni waracchau no wa atashi no hazu
'Cause it's a sailor uniform.
SE-RA- fuku dakara desu
← Q.E.D.!
← ketsuron
It's only Monday and I'm already blue.
getsuyoubi na no ni! kigen warui no
What to do?
dou suru yo?
I'd rather wear my summer clothes.
natsufuku ga ii no desu
← So cute!
← KYA? WA! IIv
3 pics incoming!
sekkin 3 PIKUTO
That's a toughie to pick!
suru madette chu-chou da
Ooh ☆
yan ☆
Just work it!
ganbatte
YEAH!
To the limit!
harikitte
YEAH!
MY DARLiN' DARLiN! P L E A S E!!
Perfect Weather for
Athletic Festivals
On this day...
...the sunniest day in autumn...
...athletic festivals are being held all over the country.
Fathers and Brothers
Enjoying Athletic Festivals
Man...
I came to cheer for my daughter...
...but I didn't expect such a turnout.
This was worth the trip.
Fathers and Brothers
Enjoying Athletic Festivals
I got some great pictures.
Look.
Dad.
Isn't this a great shot?
If you put it like this...
Which daughter are you talking about?
Don't Need Me
to
Have a Blast
Maybe I should cut my hair for the athletic festival.
Go for a really short look.
You're going to cut your hair?
But it took forever to grow it so long.
I wasn't that serious about it...
That profound response...
...must have something to do with a guy!
Stop connecting everything to that subject!
And you stop talking so much!
But if Kagami cut her hair...
That's what I heard...
...but it's not unusual, right?
Ya can't!
Bipolar girls hafta have twin pigtails!
Sorry I have a boring face!
Oh, yeah.
The athletic festival's coming up.
Sounds like a pain.
Wouldn't expect to hear that from a young person.
Kona-chan's good at sports so she's okay...
...but someone like me...
...just drags everyone down.
Don't worry.
What event are you doing, Sis?
Well, it's Kagami, so you know...
A bread eating contest.
I've been wondering...
Are you trying to pick a fight or something?
So what are you going to do, Kagami?
I guessed right?
Did I guess right?
She pisses me off!
So I plan on doing some
independent training for the athletic festival.
Since fall is for sports.
But are you really training for the athletic festival?
Aren't you actually training for the main event afterwards?
What do you mean?
You want me to say it?
She really pisses me off!
So Miyuki's participating in the inter-class relay.
Well, I can understand that one.
She was originally supposed to be in the obstacle course.
Ball Roll
5m Dash
50m Dash
100m Dash
Obstacle Course
Matsuo
Shiraishi
Yamata
Izumi
Takara
Okay.
No more candidates, right?
I've never tried it so I can't wait.
That's no good, Miyuki-san!
Your body sticks out too much for an obstacle course.
Like Here
And Here
You'd have to go through stuff.
Like Here
And Here
After I said that, she was switched to the relay.
Isn't that something a middle-aged guy would say?
Oh, yeah.
Did you guys ever have a scavenger race in middle school?
Sure did.
I was called up once...
Me?
For what?
...but he never told me what the criteria were.
Too many unspeakable things come to mind.
Well, just ask Miyuki-san when you don't know the answer.
Don't ask her something like that.
It's impossible to answer.
And she really went and asked...
A character trait that would come up in a scavenger race...
...that people wouldn't want to tell you about?
Perhaps he needed a person with a mole on her face.
Some people are sensitive about that.
I guess it was expected...
...but that was one masterful dodge.
But I'm pretty sure she's wrong.
I enjoy athletic festivals...
...but we have tests right after.
Once the festival's over...
...there aren't any more events which is kind of sad.
Midterms.
Practical exams.
Finals.
All we have are tests.
The second semester is a drain on your energy with
events like the cultural festival and the athletic festival.
Right?
Midterms are particularly rough.
They also say that fall is for reading...
...so maybe I should read something.
It's also a good season to study for tests.
And there's a whirlwind of new game releases before Christmas!
But finals come first.
Oh, yeah!
You two.
Could you stop trying to avoid reality?
I see.
The athletic festival's coming up, huh?
You know about the starter's pistol?
I thought it was a real gun until middle school.
No way...
That was when I knew I wanted to be a cop.
That misunderstanding led to something totally unrelated.
That's right, Konata.
When's the athletic festival at your school?
This Sunday.
Th-This Sunday?!
Why didn't you tell me such an important thing earlier?
But we just got the notice today.
There's no time to waste!
Why's he in such a hurry?
Okay!
Today's the big day!
Show me the fruits of your training!
Teacher!
I'm the type who does well without ever training!
Don't say that out loud!
Anyway, you better show some backbone in the team chicken fight!
The fundamental strategy is to rush
in from all sides and whack 'em good!
So attack from their weak side, right?
But we only need to take their hat...
Hitting people's kinda...
Don't sweat the little stuff.
That's one of those mistakes of youth.
So we're just boys.
Sis!
Do your best!
Good luck!
Hey.
How is that anpan attached to the string?
It's probably attached to a clip or something.
So you can't take it off very easily.
Bring us victory!
Girls must be elegant!
Like an eating contest could ever be elegant!
Ready!
She did it!
That's Kagamin for you.
That person has an incredible camera.
Man, he's so easy to understand.
Hey.
Aren't you in the 100 meter dash next?
Technically.
How can I learn to run fast like you?
It's important to visualize.
Visualize.
Ready!
Set!
That's one ancient visualization.
Goal!
Like that?
Are you serious?
3 meters and 25 centimeters.
So they measure from where your hands reached.
This is it!
That's Kagami.
Dived straight into the sand, huh?
One, two, three.
I've heard that timing your steps is important for hurdles.
Steps?
One.
Two.
Three.
I get it!
One, two, three.
Set!
One...
Um...
Three, two, three!
One, three, huh?
Um...
I started with my right foot so...
I don't get it!
That was my left foot so...
Three, three, three.
Three, two, three...
She's knocking every single one down.
You could say she's got talent.
Geez Louise.
I totally sucked.
Man...
I told you.
I thought my daughter was in this.
A common occurrence.
It's finally time for the last relay.
Yuki-chan!
Do your best!
No...
I told you that my daughter's...
I'll do my best!
Hold on a second!
I haven't even done anything yet!
Okay!
Go for it!
Pedal to the metal!
Awesome!
We're in second!
Not bad.
Sachi, over here!
Okay!
We've fallen to third.
This is what you call a race.
Keep at it!
Okay!
They're working pretty hard.
This is getting interesting.
Will Yuki-chan be okay?
Okay.
Okay!
Go, Miyuki!
Yay!
Yuki-chan's so cool!
That's our Miyuki-san.
Didn't forget to give the spectators some eye candy.
It's Tsukasa.
Oh, well.
Happy Henry Likes Beer But Could Not Obtain Food.
Hey!
Can you do something about that?
Sorry.
I chose to play the alto part in a quartet for music class...
...but my fingers are getting numb.
Why did you choose the alto part?
I-I thought the lower part might be easier.
Why don't you condition your fingers on an easy song for now?
You missed most of the notes.
So try to match me.
Ready and...
H-Hold on!
Play by yourself.
Somehow seems wrong...
Try blowing a little softer.
If you relax, it might go a lot better.
I see.
Softer...
That's it.
I'll give it a try.
Isn't she doing more breathing than playing?
I was thinking we should try the cafeteria occasionally...
...but it sure is crowded.
It's pretty overwhelming.
And waiting in line is annoying and exhausting.
Sure sucks.
Haven't you gotten used to this kind of thing from those events?
When I'm not eagerly anticipating what
awaits me at the end of the line, it sucks.
True to your desires, huh?
That's right.
I went to a theme park once...
...and thought that I had lined up for an attraction...
...but the line was for the restroom.
It's a fundamental rule to check what the line is for first.
And I waited two whole hours...
I've also gotten in line a few times...
...and when it was finally my turn...
Cream Puffs
Sold Out
...the person before me had bought the last one.
Terrible...
Don't even wanna picture it.
You're just unlucky.
Look, everyone.
What shall we have today?
Deep-fried Tempura
Soba/Udon
Fox
Miso
Ramen
Soy Sauce
Curry
S M L
Daily Special
A Meal
B Meal
Eggs
Special
Well, I guess I'll go with curry.
They can't screw it up...
I'll go with ramen.
Me too.
I was planning on having miso ramen today.
With lots of corn...
...and seaweed, too!
Kagami's probably having ramen, pudding, and an éclair.
If I have enough room to eat more.
You always have more room.
What about you, Yuki-chan?
I'll have a sandwich.
With strawberries.
Sounds like something you would have.
Right?
By the way...
Isn't a strawberry sandwich considered dessert?
Would it count as lunch?
Th-That's true...
You pick some odd issues to be concerned about.
What about those chocolate cornets you always have?
Wouldn't sweet pastries be considered dessert?
Stupid Tsukasa has the gall to give me lip...
Anyway, moving on...
Unfortunately, Miyuki-san...
The line for sandwiches is over there.
Typical behavior.
Walking is healthy.
Look.
It's your turn, Kona-chan.
Curry please.
With extra sauce.
Okay.
You're pretty shrewd.
I'll take what I can get.
Okay.
Next person?
Soy sauce ramen please.
With hard noodles.
Okay, please wait one moment.
Okay.
Here's your curry.
I'll go get a table.
Countin' on you.
Thanks!
Let's see...
Next person?
Yes.
Can I please have miso ramen?
Sorry.
The last person ordered the last of our noodles.
We're out of ramen.
Say.
If you're okay with soy sauce, do you want mine?
I'm okay with fox udon.
Thank you, Sis.
Hey, Sis.
You're the older sister because you came out first, right?
Yeah.
I was thinking that it's a good thing I'm the younger sister.
Why?
Because an older sister shouldn't be asking a
younger sister for help with homework and stuff.
I'm pretty sure that copying homework has nothing to do with that.
Besides, we're twins.
Neither of us is really older or younger.
Stop worrying...
...and do your homework.
But if I were the older sister...
...and all dependable and responsible...
Sis!
Show me your homework!
Again?
You're so hopeless, Kagami.
Hey.
That was wack!
You okay there?
Get a grip.
I did it!
Newtype...
...published my...
...very own...
...postcard!
In the May issue...
Saitama province.
The one that has Akira-chan standing on Shiraishi.
Konata Izumi.
Good for you.
Look at it!
Kinda amazed they published this.
A-Amazing!
What a surprise!
This is pretty rare, yeah?
Like, seriously, huh?
Now I have one more thing to look forward to buying!
You don't need to praise me so much!
1,260 yen...
...and 567 yen, huh?
I'll have enough points after one more book.
Then I should just get something...
No.
Then I'd be falling into their trap.
I'm not so easy to fool.
That would be an unplanned purchase for the sake of points.
That's their strategy.
I'm not dumb enough to fall for that trick.
Oh!
I forgot that the fifth volume was out.
Okay!
This works!
Genius
Your total comes to 2,587 yen.
Oh, well.
Extra, yeah...
I can't get it loose.
I'm sorry.
I don't want to let go.
Yes...
I thought that only ever happened in manga or games...
...but it actually happens in real life.
Guess so.
Which means...
Those two definitely triggered a flag.
Konata...
Fantasy refers to the world of illusion.
Can't tell the difference between dreams and reality?
Good lucky!
I come with a dreamer's heart to spread love again!
I'm Lucky Channel's navigator, Akira Kogami!
And I'm the assistant.
Minoru Shiraishi.
We've already reached the eighth episode of this program.
That's true.
If we don't come up with some fresh material...
...we'll be accused of abusing mannerisms.
What was that?
What am I doing?!
No.
I just wanted to try some new things...
You said it.
You know...
Do it.
That's right!
I was walking around town the other day...
...and someone came up to talk to me.
Was it some salon doing a survey?
Geez, Shiraishi-san.
Do you actually mean that?
Of course, it was a fan.
This would never happen to you...
Right?!
I-I-I-I-It wouldn't!
That's true...
Right?!
You're the assistant...
Well, keep workin' hard.
B-But...
I've already received this many...
A oopsie-daisy.
...fan letters!
H-How?!
Hey, Itou!
Haven't I gotten any?!
Incredible.
I feel like a real voice actor.
So I did get some.
Only one?
Your membership has almost expired...
Hey!
This is that stupid online service!
Everybody who's watching!
Please send me fan letters, too!
Big, big, big recruitment drive!
Akira-sama.
Shouldn't we get to today's topic...
Don't get too cocky.
You're easily replaceable.
I'm so sorry.
Ta-da!
I have an announcement to make!
Wow!
We'll be creating figures on this program!
Akira-sama!
The clipboard!
The clipboards upside-down!
Oh, you're doing it on purpose!
You're a genius, Akira-sama!
Actually...
...this project is...
Peel.
P-Peel. Peel.
Don't touch me.
Peel. Peel. Peel.
Huh?
That's weird.
This project is...
Don't touch me.
This is...
Peel.
What's wrong with this thing?!
H-H-Hey, Seishi!
I got it, okay!
A-Akira-sama, calm down!
That's the name of your manager in real life!
This is my prop!
Could you have...
Of course not!
Okay!
Then we'll decide which figure to make based on your votes!
Have fun waiting for us to turn the character into a figure!
Everyone, please vote!
Okay.
That's all for today.
Look forward to next week's Lucky Channel!
Bye-bee!
A character from the actual show's obviously gonna win the poll.
What's with this?
Like I have a chance in hell.
No, you can't be sure yet.
I see.
They're finally going to make a figure of me.
What are you talking about?
This is...
That was great, Yuki-chan!
Thank you for listening.
I never expected this side of you.
Please...
It's embarrassing.
Hey, Yuki-chan.
Let's sing a song together.
Let's do that.
Sing! Sing!
A duet, huh?
Which song do you know?
Let's see...
Then I'll sing a song while we're waiting.
There's never gonna be a break, huh?!
You should also sing!
What is this?
Journey to the West.
Machaaki's Son Goku was great.
Huh?
Wasn't it Shingo-chan?
That was the third remake.
This one ran from 1978 to 1980.
The original series!
How old are you?!
This is a long intro.
This was when the actors delivered the main narration.
Like I would know!
Here it comes!
You're shouting again?!
Born from an egg on a mountain top.
It's in English. Forget that.
That's it after all this build-up?
Next Episode
Well, next time on Lucky Star:
I'm Miyuki.
When describing an enormously large object...
...it is described as being super-dreadnought.
The word dreadnought in this expression...
...was derived from a British ship commissioned in 1906...
...the HMS Dreadnought.
In other words...
...something super-dreadnought...
...would be larger than a dreadnought-class battleship.
Well, that was the original meaning...
...but now...
...it's being used in the former context.
Next time:
「Just a Feeling」
Just a Feeling.
Look forward to next time!