Well, let's get crackin'.
Let's-a-go.
Stop messing around and start!
Around 3 cm!
aimai 3 SENCHI
Looks peachy, doesn't it?
sorya puni tte KOTO kai?
Hey!
cho!
Wrapping for a uniform...
rappingu ga seifuku...
Turn-off, ain't it?
daaa furitte koto nai
Ha.
pu.
Just work it ♥
ganbacchau ♥
And do it?
yacchacchau
Don't forget to catch and release yo!
son tokya-cchi & RELEASE gyo
I sweat!
ase
FUU!
I sweat!
ase
And throw in a!
no tanima ni
DARLiN' DARLiN* F R E E Z E!!
FeelING crummy!
nanka DAru-
SomethING's coming!
nanka DEru-
I lOVE you so!
ashiTEru
Oops!
are
I screwed one upsie-up!
ikko ga chigatterunru-
A nail biter!
nayamiNbo-
A steel beater!
koutetsubo-
Gourmet eater!
oishinbo-
Cut that out already!
i-kagen ni SHINASA!
Is that new blushing flower...
tondetta AITSU no hoteru KARADA tte
...considered a normal girl or what?
iwayuru futsu- no onya no KO
Wowzers!
odoroita
Only for me?
atashi dake?
Pork chops!
tonkotasu
Firm noodles!
HARIGANE
Fill 'er up again!
okawari
DA-DA-DA!
Ooh!
Guess what?
My glasses...
Where are my glasses?
But I've been playing the same fighting games lately.
If I don't have my glasses...
BON-BON
Cheerleaders!
o-endan
LET'S GET!
Cherry pie!
CHERI-PAI
RAN-RAN
Welcome party!
kange-kai
LOOK UP!
Sensation!
sense-shon
Yeah!
hai!
Leavin' an impression.
sonzaikan
...asteriods.
•• shouwakusei
Crash!
butsukatte
And burned!
tokemashita
Shockers!
bo-zen
Break into song!
ooi ni utatte
Crunch time!
SHIRENJA-
Take it!
motteike!
I'll still be laughing in the end!
saigo ni waracchau no wa atashi no hazu
'Cause it's a sailor uniform.
SE-RA- fuku dakara desu
← Q.E.D.!
← ketsuron
It's only Monday and I'm already blue.
getsuyoubi na no ni! kigen warui no
What to do?
dou suru yo?
I'd rather wear my summer clothes.
natsufuku ga ii no desu
← So cute!
← KYA? WA! IIv
3 pics incoming!
sekkin 3 PIKUTO
That's a toughie to pick!
suru madette chu-chou da
Ooh ☆
yan ☆
Just work it!
ganbatte
YEAH!
To the limit!
harikitte
YEAH!
MY DARLiN' DARLiN! P L E A S E!!
Since fall is for reading...
...I've been doing a lot of reading.
That's unusual.
Even though it's for an educational purpose...
...the expenses are piling up.
You don't have to buy them.
Couldn't you just go to a library or something?
They actually have some stuff you'd want.
Nah.
A library wouldn't have manga.
Reading, huh...
They mean books, you know...
Just
A
Feeling
Studying for Test
Can't concentrate...
Well, you have to take a break every now and then.
Like this.
I'll do a little gaming to relax.
It's Ms. Kuroi.
Hey!
Stop playin' and get to studyin'!
I'll be mighty pissed if your grades are bad.
Phooey!
The authorities can even find me here!
Don't do this to me, Teacher!
This game suddenly isn't as fun with all these interruptions.
How did you study for tests when you were a student?
Played or slept when I couldn't concentrate.
Nothing really special.
That's the same as me.
But as an authority figure, I have to be strict.
I get what she means...
...but it still feels unfair!
This time, I plan on setting goals and studying bit by bit.
Sis, teach me the stuff I don't get.
Then let's study together.
So in this case, x would equal...
What is it?
I just realized that my TV show's about to start.
In today's episode...
...a weekly magazine reporter...
...spreads word of the main character's pregnancy.
So you're going to watch TV?
It's okay.
I'm taping it.
Um...
I get sleepy whenever there's a bunch of questions I don't get...
Which means you're always sleepy?
I probably shouldn't overextend myself right off the bat...
...so I'll call it a day.
Okay.
I see you're already losing your willpower.
I still can't concentrate!
Okay.
You want a trick for studying for a test?
I was wondering how you study.
Let's see...
If you concentrate too hard, you'll wear yourself out.
In my case, I just follow my usual habits.
So I'm pretty confident about today's test.
I feel so enlightened.
Aren't your usual habits a little risky?
You don't do anything.
But it's so cute...
And its claws are venomous.
My...
So it's actually quite frightening.
Yo.
Kagami.
How'd it go?
This one was pretty bad.
Though I maintained my standing.
So you also do bad sometimes.
Because Sis helped me out.
As a result, I did better than usual.
How about you?
Strangely enough, I did bad.
And I was so sure I'd do well.
Nothing strange about it at all.
It was inevitable.
But you know...
...I was feeling that birds of a feather flock together.
For example...
Kagami and Miyuki-san are both class representatives.
Kagami and I both like games.
Well, different genres though.
You play dating sims and RPGs.
And I play shooters.
I was thinking that Tsukasa and I were both stupid...
...but there was a significant gap this time.
Well, I'm not really concerned about doing bad.
Be a little concerned.
If you slack off because everybody else also did bad...
...you'll fall behind.
Actually...
I didn't make any bets with my dad...
...so I'm not really angry.
You're gonna grow up to be a bad person.
If you're gonna copy Miyuki...
...take notes regularly...
...instead of waiting till tests are coming up.
Miyuki-san is really methodical.
Textbook example of a type A person.
Many people have told me that...
...but I'm actually type O.
You're type O?
Never would have guessed.
However...
Blood Type Primer
According to this book...
...I possess many of the qualities...
...characteristic of type O people.
For example...
It's said that type O people tend to be...
...childish and innocent...
...which describes me perfectly.
Type O people tend to be pushy and possessive...
I guess there's another side to Miyuki-san.
You're probably type A.
But a lot of people mistake me for a type B.
Type A people are skilled in social functions and considerate.
They tend to seek peaceful human interaction?
Does this even match you?
I can be really sensitive to the situation.
Only when it's something you're interested in.
I'm gentle and attentive to other people.
When it involves homework.
What about you, Kagami?
Me?
I'm type B.
So you're laid-back, rude, erratic,
unconventional, naive, and insolent, huh?
What about it?
Then Tsukasa's type AB?
What's that supposed to mean?
Why?
Just a hunch.
If you go by personality...
...Tsukasa would be type A...
...and Kagami would be type B.
We're both type B.
And like, we're twins.
That's right.
Brain fart.
And I'm not as laid-back as you are.
Speaking of horoscopes...
...I've also heard of ones for animals and sushi.
Sushi Horoscopes
What are your favorite things?
We'll use your answers to determine your personality.
Sushi?
Let's see...
Miyuki-san is...
So Miyuki would be salmon roe.
Still high-class, I see.
I love salmon roe!
And?
What about Tsukasa and me?
Cucumber roll.
A cucumber roll, huh?
Well, I guess it counts as sushi.
This is pretty accurate.
And what about you?
Me?
Sliced ginger?
It says sliced ginger!
Don't look down on ginger!
Well...
You can't have sushi without it...
...and the horoscope's description is positive.
That's true.
And cucumber rolls count as sushi, right?
Hello?
Konata?
About the blood type conversation today...
Just to make sure you know...
...fraternal twins can have different blood types...
...so your guess wasn't wrong.
Sounded like you got the wrong impression.
Thanks awfully.
You're an honest person.
I'm starting to see the type A in you.
Oh, yeah...
There was a psychic reading on TV.
With those things...
...you'll guess right with some
people and wrong with some people...
...so you'd at least make one correct guess somewhere.
Kagami...
Don't be so pragmatic...
You'll never have fun in life.
Act more like your age.
Tsukasa.
You worked hard this time.
Kagami did worse than usual.
But she still got a higher score, huh...
Good work, girls.
How should I put it...
You did the best you could...
Ooh.
Tsukasa worked hard.
But Kagami still scored higher.
Hey, Matsuri.
Can't you be more considerate?
Good morning!
Oh, good morning.
I envy how the two of you are such fine young ladies.
Not at all.
You're too kind.
To get such wonderful grades at that Ryouou High...
I wish my children had a fraction of your ability.
It's like...
I'm being praised because I'm her sister...
Nah.
We aren't that impressive.
...so I can't really appreciate it.
Tests are over.
Why don't we go all-out and have some fun?
Sounds good.
How about watching a movie for once?
What's in theaters right now?
There's a great one right now.
What is it?
You could call it a splatter film...
...but it still has some
psycho-suspenseful, shocking horror elements.
Then let's do that!
How about we go home first and meet up later?
Let's do that! Let's do that!
This isn't fun...
I can't have fun like this!
Still got time. What should we do?
Konata sure is late.
Is she late again?
Maybe...
She couldn't have come before us, right?
Honestly...
The movie's about to start.
When did she...
I couldn't recognize you without that thing...
Anyway, we're short on time so let's go.
Oh, yeah.
Pretend I'm your sister.
Why?
Well...
Then I can buy a child's ticket without looking weird.
Stupid kid.
She whines about her height all the time...
...but then she exploits it when she can!
That was terrifying, Take-rin!
You're so adorable.
I'm a little hungry now.
Me too.
And Tsukasa's probably hungry after screaming so much.
What should we have?
How about a cake buffet?
Sounds great!
The buffet...
A haven for satiating a woman's desires!
They've got so many cakes and drinks.
Sure do.
I wonder if we'll get through every one.
Piece of cake for Kagami.
This store has a time limit of one hour.
You can find beverages in the drink corner over there.
The cakes are located in the showcase over there.
Please help yourself.
Okay!
Bow.
And if you leave an excessive amount of leftovers...
...you'll have to pay an extra fee.
Please keep that in mind.
Then please enjoy yourselves.
What would be considered an excessive amount?
Some people take a bunch and don't finish.
Come on.
Let's go.
That's a lot...
Can you finish all that?
What about you?
This is normal for cake.
No sweat.
Time to eat!
Delicious!
And that one!
And this one!
I'm in pain now...
We should have slowed down after the first plate.
I've got heartburn.
Peek.
But we have to pay extra if we leave leftovers.
That's bad!
It hurts...
I-I can't do it...
We're almost out of time.
Oh, Kagami!
She's on her second wind!
It'd be a waste otherwise!
Impossible.
No! No!
If you drink too much water...
...you won't be able to eat any more!
Just stuff down what you can...
...and wash it down with water at the very end!
Don't sit there looking impressed
Get to eating!
I can't eat another bite...
You can handle pudding or Bavarian cream!
Here.
Can't you eat it?
I'm stuffed, too!
I'm out, man...
You can just pour the pudding down your throat!
Hurry it up!
This isn't fun...
I can't have fun like this!
C'mon! Get with it!
Tests are over...
...so I did some hardcore gaming...
...which is why I'm so sleepy...
If you studied that hard...
...your tests would have gone differently.
Recent dating sims have a bunch of save points...
...but I can never find a good place to stop.
I'm the do-it-in-one-sitting type.
I've been wondering...
A student shouldn't be able to buy those.
How do you buy them?
I get my dad to buy them for me.
No way!
I've been thinking...
Your family's pretty crazy...
You actually go buy them, Pops?
And don't ask him, daughter.
So I'm really sleepy.
You probably don't play games, Miyuki-san.
I don't have a game console...
...but I have a computer so I occasionally play some games.
What do you play?
Didn't expect this!
Games like Solitaire and Minesweeper.
It can get pretty intense.
They're games...
...but you've got it wrong, Miyuki-san.
But I know what you mean.
It's actually easy to get absorbed...
...in those kinds of simple games.
What kind of scores do you get, Yuki-chan?
Luck is a factor in Solitaire...
...but I often score over ten thousand.
As for Minesweeper, I completed expert in
under one hundred seconds the other day.
These kind of people really get into this kind of stuff...
There was a lot of sports stuff this year.
That one athlete got gold in figure skating at the Winter Olympics.
And there was quite a fuss over high school baseball.
There was that incredibly long match.
And the Handkerchief Prince.
Speaking of baseball...
That one player went to America, right?
Is the Japan Series already over?
A long time ago.
No way!
Were there any bargain sales?
This year's Japan Series was between that team and that team...
...so there weren't any supermarket
or department store chains involved.
But they had a commemorative sale.
But it was probably just a sale on ham.
Did they do that...?
Anyway, I need to remember to do a check next year...
Knowing you...
...you're probably just gonna buy snacks.
I'm not.
I need stuff like salt, sugar, and soy sauce.
Those kinds of household staples.
Well...
Kagami wouldn't understand what I'm talking about, right?
So sorry!
So I suck at household chores!
Eyedrops?
Want me to help?
Thank you so much.
Okay.
Lie down.
Yes.
Okay...
Relax.
Y-Yes.
Then here I go.
Okay.
Relax your muscles.
Yes.
Um...
I'm sorry.
I'm not doing this on purpose...
Your face...
...scares me!
With mail-in prize contests...
...the problem is how it takes forever to receive the item.
That's why I came up with a way to
have fun twice as you play, Kagamin.
What's that?
First, you enjoy the game like you're at a festival.
And by the time you've forgotten, the
item arrives and you can be happy again.
Two for the price of one.
The waiting's what I can't stand...
You're infinitely positive about the stuff you enjoy, huh?
Good lucky!
Yes!
I hope to have a cheerful Lucky Channel today!
We're already on our ninth episode today!
I'm your navigator, Akira Kogami!
And here's the person that the producer, Itou-san...
...is going to say "Hey, Shiraishi. Come here a sec." to...
Really?!
I'm Akira-sama's assistant...
100% charged with energy...
Minoru Shiraishi.
It's a pleasure.
Okay.
Today's the third character introduction.
Tsukasa Hiiragi's turn!
Prop time!
Roll...
Are you supposed to be a clumsy, slow turtle?
Tsu-
Thi-
I'm sorry.
This is finally getting exciting!
Yes!
Time to pull up our loincloths...
...and do our best!
Right, Akira-sama?
Loincloths?
I'm supposed to be an idol...
...so that stuff's kinda...
You handle it.
That's right...
Uh...
When you pull a loincloth up so tight that it gets pinched...
Hey.
I'd like to warn you out of concern.
C-Concern...?
Once an entertainer gets in the gutter...
...it's over.
So I'm an entertainer...
Also...
You've been using other people's material a lot lately...
...so watch yourself.
Yes!
Um...
What are we doing today?
Introducing Tsukasa Hiiragi-san.
That To Hea-
Mi-Mi-Miracle!
Kamigishi...
Minorun-run!
Right?
You can say that?
What do you think?
She reminds me of one of those old idol characters.
Uh, you think so?
Well, I guess you could say she gives off some idol vibes...
Don't make me laugh!
Tsukasa Hiiragi's an idol?
Where did that come from?
Y'know...
You're working with me here.
Learn what a true idol is about already.
Y-Yes, ma'am.
Tsukasa Hiiragi is merely a soothing character...
...with a loser's face.
A loser's face, huh...
Anyway...
...who gives a damn about Tsukasa?
Not even Pops ever hit me!
I'll teach you the basics of an idol right now.
First is the method for having pictures taken.
Now look here.
This will be a useful lesson for you.
So put some back into it.
Yes!
You know how people suddenly
take pictures when you're in the city?
Come on.
Press the shutter.
Fawn. Fawn. Fawn.
Looking like a loser...?
Yeah.
Like that.
Props are also important.
You should always carry them around.
How?
And you won't want to be caught off
guard when you're walking around...
...so always be attentive.
And...
...make sure you have sparkling white teeth.
Like a doll!
Intense.
And then...
...make sure your eyes are all wide and goggly...
...and only smile with these muscles.
Jeepers!
And you want a natural expression.
Like if someone suddenly turns a camera on you...
Akira's, like, whoa!
Like that.
Natural, you say...
Also, as a variation...
...if you're going with a guy into a ho—
Oh, no!
It's time to say goodbye!
So send us any questions or comments about the show please!
You can also send us messages
about the radio show and our home page!
Okay!
Then look forward to next week.
Bye-bee!
We had a photo shoot, right?
Yes, we did.
The one where I was in the cardigan.
How was it?
That was cute...
Shankya!
It was cute?
What's wrong?
Yeah, well...
Everyone said it looked cute.
Guess so.
You were on a roll.
Yep.
Sure was.
Looked fun.
The upturned eyes...
...with the uh...
...arms crossed below my face...
...was really fun!
Yes.
Are you hooked now?
Including the cross-dressing, yes.
I'm hooked.
Did you check the pictures?
No, I didn't.
The manager...
Yes.
...checked the pictures...
...and said there were some questionable ones to be honest.
Well, I had a bunch of stiffy shots...
...so those are probably gone.
Sorry! Sorry!
Made a little oopsie.
I'll actually sing the next one.
And she's already ordering another song.
Let me have the remote for once.
Okay.
Have you guys decided, Tsukasa?
It'll be a little longer.
I don't listen to music much so I don't know many songs.
That's okay.
I'll sing in the meantime.
Hey.
Don't just sing anime songs.
This isn't an anime song.
I've heard this before.
What is this?
It's KyonKyon.
I used to sing this with my dad a lot.
So you've gone from anime songs to oldies.
That's an insult to KyonKyon!
We met amidst the wind.
Tsukasa.
Ever since the day we fell in love...
Why don't you just choose a simple song?
Like a children's song.
...this clueless heart of mine...
I'm looking through that section, too...
I'm sorry.
...has longed for you.
There's no rush.
We still have plenty of time.
Don't cry, tender heart.
As long as wishes come true...
I want to cross that river of tears...
...and forget it all.
You never notice...
...as I secretly yearn for you.
Next Episode
Well, next time on Lucky Star:
I'm Konata.
In world 3-1 of Super (bleep) Brothers...
...there's a staircase near the end of the level...
...where you can jump on the falling turtle...
If you repeatedly hit the A button...
...to jump on the turtle...
...you can get infinite lives...
...which is great...
...but if you overdo it...
...and go over 129 lives...
...dying once leads to a game over.
I won't bother going, "So you can't have infinite lives!"
Maybe it's that.
A public service announcement from
the folks near Kamitobaguchi Station...
...that you're supposed to do things in moderation.
「Aspiration」
Next time:
Aspiration.
Look forward to next time!