Well, let's get crackin'.
Let's-a-go.
Stop messing around and start!
Around 3 cm!
aimai 3 SENCHI
Looks peachy, doesn't it?
sorya puni tte KOTO kai?
Hey!
cho!
Wrapping for a uniform...
rappingu ga seifuku...
Turn-off, ain't it?
daaa furitte koto nai
Ha.
pu.
Just work it ♥
ganbacchau ♥
And do it?
yacchacchau
Don't forget to catch and release yo!
son tokya-cchi & RELEASE gyo
I sweat!
ase
FUU!
I sweat!
ase
And throw in a!
no tanima ni
DARLiN' DARLiN* F R E E Z E!!
FeelING crummy!
nanka DAru-
SomethING's coming!
nanka DEru-
I lOVE you so!
ashiTEru
Oops!
are
I screwed one upsie-up!
ikko ga chigatterunru-
A nail biter!
nayamiNbo-
A steel beater!
koutetsubo-
Gourmet eater!
oishinbo-
Cut that out already!
i-kagen ni SHINASA!
Is that new blushing flower...
tondetta AITSU no hoteru KARADA tte
...considered a normal girl or what?
iwayuru futsu- no onya no KO
Wowzers!
odoroita
Only for me?
atashi dake?
Pork chops!
tonkotasu
Firm noodles!
HARIGANE
Fill 'er up again!
okawari
DA-DA-DA!
Ooh!
Guess what?
My glasses...
Where are my glasses?
But I've been playing the same fighting games lately.
If I don't have my glasses...
BON-BON
Cheerleaders!
o-endan
LET'S GET!
Cherry pie!
CHERI-PAI
RAN-RAN
Welcome party!
kange-kai
LOOK UP!
Sensation!
sense-shon
Yeah!
hai!
Leavin' an impression.
sonzaikan
...asteriods.
•• shouwakusei
Crash!
butsukatte
And burned!
tokemashita
Shockers!
bo-zen
Break into song!
ooi ni utatte
Crunch time!
SHIRENJA-
Take it!
motteike!
I'll still be laughing in the end!
saigo ni waracchau no wa atashi no hazu
'Cause it's a sailor uniform.
SE-RA- fuku dakara desu
← Q.E.D.!
← ketsuron
It's only Monday and I'm already blue.
getsuyoubi na no ni! kigen warui no
What to do?
dou suru yo?
I'd rather wear my summer clothes.
natsufuku ga ii no desu
← So cute!
← KYA? WA! IIv
3 pics incoming!
sekkin 3 PIKUTO
That's a toughie to pick!
suru madette chu-chou da
Ooh ☆
yan ☆
Just work it!
ganbatte
YEAH!
To the limit!
harikitte
YEAH!
MY DARLiN' DARLiN! P L E A S E!!
'Kay!
Everyone, have a seat!
Happy New Year.
The year just flew by, didn't it?
Let's have another good'un.
'Course...
...I'll be biddin' farewell to some of y'all in three more months.
Guess who I'm talkin' about.
Teacher!
You don't mean me, right?!
Savory
Day
I can believe, right?!
People always talk about the New Year's mood...
...but I guess there's kinda a weird atmosphere.
But it changes the second school starts.
Unfortunately...
Well...
It's true that New Year's wields a mysterious power.
Despite the fact that I spent the first three
days of the year busy working at home...
...I gained weight!
New Year's magic, huh?
The cold weather makes it difficult to burn off your fat.
I did a lot of moving around though.
Three days of busy work as a shrine maiden.
But you ate just as much, didn't you?
Shrine maiden. New Year's food!
Shrine maiden. Zoni soup!
Shrine maiden. Snacks!
Snacks! Snacks! Snacks!
Something like that.
But the pictures of having fun during New Year's...
...usually include badminton...
...One Hundred Poets...
...and kite flying...
...but I've never actually seen someone do those.
Well...
These days, it's dangerous with stuff like electric lines and cars.
I just watched TV and read books.
After those first three busy days.
Um...
I did those.
I enjoyed badminton, One Hundred
Poets, and Pin the Tail on the Donkey.
Doesn't match your image.
My family follows western customs...
...but our relatives in the country are more traditional.
We wore kimonos and went to the temple on New Year's...
...and I had fun with my cousins.
An omnipotent god...
Way more Japanese than I am!
More traditional than my family!
Wait, why Pin the Tail on the Donkey?
In One Hundred Poets...
...they're all 31 syllable poems, right?
Yes.
You read out the first verse...
...and look for the card with the rest of the poem.
You must have skills...
Not at all.
I'm just a beginner.
The expert snatch up the cards in a flash.
Well, more like...
I can't stand playing a game that
makes you feel like you're studying.
People like you who view mental games as a
chore are why Japan's going down the drain.
Why couldn't they use One Hundred Poets for like a card battle?
You could summon a monk.
Think there was a Semimaru!
Semimaru uses a shining attack!
Ono no Komachi uses a lovely strike!
Doesn't that sound fun?
Back to your world, huh?
But wouldn't more physical games have helped you lose weight?
Be quiet!
It was those stupid rice cakes...
Rice cakes are loaded with calories, aren't they?
One as big as a matchbox...
...is equivalent to a whole bowl of rice.
Which means that Kagami's eating a bowl of rice with each bite?!
Hey!
You also ate rice cakes, didn't you?!
[zoni soup: a broth eaten with rice cakes; New Year's meal]
My mom's gone, so I've rarely had zoni soup and that stuff.
Actually, I don't really eat rice cakes.
That's a waste.
With zoni soup, sweet red bean soup, soy flour rice cakes...
There are so many fun ways to eat them.
Looks like she's gonna lose to the rice cakes again next year...
...Kagami.
What do you have to eat for New Year's...
...instead of rice cakes, Izumi-san?
Stuff like pizza and pasta.
Our year starts with raw pasta.
My dad cleans out the pasta machine at the end of every year.
Did you know?
That thing rusts if you don't use it for a while.
If you use it without cleaning it first...
...the pasta ends up all black and stuff...
So we clean it out...
...and make pasta and pizza!
Sounds very thorough.
Well, Kagami's house probably orders
pizza and their pasta consists of cup noodles.
More like...
We don't have pizza or pasta on New Year's...
No way!
It doesn't go with traditional foods.
Sure it does!
It goes great with roast chicken!
That's a traditional New Year's food?
Sure it is.
Under western traditions.
That's how it works?
What did you have for New Year's, Miyuki-san?
Me?
Your family sounds all wealthy and western...
...so you probably didn't have traditional stuff or rice cakes.
Maybe you had like a full course French dinner!
Not at all.
I ate traditional foods...
...and I was unable to bite through a rice cake...
...and it stretched like whee!
What's with this walking pillar to elements of turn-ons?
Rice cake goes whee!
But New Year's goes by so fast.
Yeah.
Winter break goes by fast, too.
It's supposed to be a long vacation...
...but after cleaning, writing New Year's cards, and homework...
...you don't have much time to relax, right?
Hold it right there!
You didn't do New Year's cards this year!
And you copied my homework yesterday!
Oh, yeah.
Did you have your first dream of the year, Kona-chan?
Isn't it supposed to be a good
omen if you dream about certain things?
Yep, yep.
Usually, it's one: Mt. Fuji, two: hawk, three: eggplant.
Officially, you would add...
...four: fan, five: tobacco, six: blind man.
It goes all the way up to six!
But you know...
Who ever dreams about that kind of stuff?
What kind of dream would that be?
And why a blind man?
Pretty much...
Hey.
Do you have to dream about all of those at once?
If all of those showed up in your dreams, you'd be really blessed...
...but I believe that just one will suffice.
I thought you would have to dream about
a hawk twice and an eggplant three times.
And quite frankly...
Who really remembers what they dream about?
People who care about that stuff are
having way too much fun with New Year's.
You have a point.
In my first dream this year...
...I opened my shoe locker to find my shoes missing.
So I had no choice but to take
shoes from someone else's open locker...
...but the size was wrong.
I looked up the meaning of this dream in
the encyclopedia for dream fortune telling...
...and it said that it's a sign I am pursuing skills useful to society...
...but it will take a while before I accomplish that goal.
The shoes apparently represent societal standing.
Cheesecake?
Miyuki-san's...
...pretty ambitious.
It's like I kinda understand, but kinda not...
Another person was goofing off on the stage...
...during the coming-of-age ceremony.
Don't they realize they're representing Japan?
Makes you wonder why they even bother going.
No kidding.
I wouldn't want to go to a boring coming-of-age ceremony.
And this girl's gonna grow up to be a bad person.
What are you guys going to wear to your ceremony?
Might as well go with a long-sleeve kimono...
What about you?
Well...
My dad's probably going to have me wear a long-sleeve kimono.
I can see him doing that.
Yahoo!
But...
When you wear one...
...you'd look more like a little kid going to the festival.
Happy New Year!
Hope ya had fun!
Happy New Year, Cousin Yui.
I haven't seen you in a while.
Well, my husband was here.
And a lot happens during New Year's.
Oh, and my sister had a fever.
She's got a weak body.
Whoa!
It definitely wasn't because I didn't
give her any New Year's allowance!
Don't get the wrong idea!
Only a cop would reveal what she was
really thinking before I've said a thing.
A One Hundred Poets tournament is currently underway...
...and it's been one crazy ride so far.
Oh, yeah.
What did you do on New Year's when you were a kid?
When I was a kid?
Well, I did all kinds of stuff...
Let's see...
Um...
Dot.
Sorry.
I forgot.
No clue.
She really just goes with the flow.
I've never heard her say anything serious.
Guess I outgrew my memories!
Tsukasa's always cooped up under the kotatsu these days.
'Cause it's cold.
I know what you mean!
Kotatsus are so wonderful.
Going to the bathroom's a pain though.
Yep, yep.
But you shouldn't say that so loudly...
But we have a surefire way to get a person out of a kotatsu.
How does it work?
Konata.
If you stay under the kotatsu too long...
...you'll get stuck.
So your dad doesn't need a kotatsu.
He likes them as much as the next person.
It's just like a warning.
'Cause we've both fallen asleep together under the kotatsu before.
I know what you mean!
But they say that you'll catch a
cold if you fall asleep under a kotatsu.
Yeah.
So we turn it off once someone notices.
It's like a mix of heaven and hell.
Like right before you turn it on...
...and after you turn it off, it feels even colder.
I totally know what you mean!
And doesn't it really suck when you get out of bed in the morning?
While we're at it, it's totally freezing after you
get undressed and before you get in the bath.
But not enough to make you run.
You might slip and fall.
And doesn't it suck when you need to go
the bathroom in the middle of the night?
I hate that!
Hey.
This is our stop.
And the trip from the bus to the classroom is also hell.
It's almost Valentine's Day.
It always gets a lot more exciting this time of year.
It kinda tickles me how everyone can get so worked up every year.
Having someone special on this day...
...and confessing your feelings...
...and having them reciprocated...
...is a beautiful thing.
You're such a girl.
I just see it as a conspiracy by the chocolate industry.
Well, I guess you could say it's also a special time of year for me.
They have a sale on the unsold chocolate afterwards...
...so I'm looking for chocolate to use in making my own.
And you, you have no dreams.
Money can't buy love!
At least, that's what they like to say...
...but isn't Valentine chocolate a
way of showing love through money?
I guess someone who's only
experienced love in games has some harsh views.
Well, in games, it's all about upping
your relationship level before the day comes.
I don't do anything special for Valentine's.
Guys dream too much.
Nobody managed to trigger the Kagami flag.
What about you?
I'm super popular!
Right...
In your game.
When you talk about flags and relationship levels...
...I seriously get worried about your future.
You can't limit yourself to events in games.
I can't stand those narrow-minded people
who don't know what they're talking about.
So I'm wrong?
Lately, events only take a few hours in game time...
...so Valentine's Day is usually over in a flash.
So what?
But this year, I'm planning on giving chocolate to someone.
Seriously?!
Someone playing the same online game as me.
A friend from your game?
You're giving it to him in person?
I'm not actually going to meet the person.
It'll be in-game.
Since the characters are still human.
Does that even count?
So you just meant a game character.
How dare you insult my bride!
Bride?
We're married in-game, and my character's male.
What?
Wait a sec.
So the guy is giving the girl chocolate?
And wouldn't it be like a girl giving a girl chocolate?
If the other person's a girl...
Don't worry.
The other person's a guy in real life.
Guess it doesn't matter as long as you're having fun!
Got that right.
I wanna go overseas.
That came out of nowhere.
Well, yesterday, Miyuki-san was like...
Females giving chocolates on February 14th is a Japanese custom.
Miyuki-san!
In western society, people of both genders...
...give chocolate and cards to friends and people they like.
That's what she said...
...so a girl like me could still get lots of chocolate!
I guess you could interpret it that way...
...but you sure have a lot of confidence in yourself.
Like you already know for a fact that you'll be popular.
Don't worry.
In foreign countries, little girls...
Okay, stop!
No risqué statements allowed!
Uh...
Will you accept this?!
Happy Valentine's Day!
Here, Kona-chan.
Incredible wrapping...
...for a uniform...
And the inside's all cool and heart-shaped!
I put some effort into it.
Tsukasa's always enthusiastic about this kind of stuff.
She was making them until morning.
And it's only friendship chocolate.
Tsukasa.
You shouldn't give any friendship chocolate to guys.
They'll definitely get the wrong idea.
What?
Anyway, here.
Kagami's giving me chocolate!
Tsukasa was making hers...
...so I just joined in.
You don't want it?
Kagami looking like she's good at everything when
she actually sucks so she secretly works hard turns me on.
Zip it!
Shut up and put it away.
Huh?
Kagami?
Here.
This is for you.
Just so you know, it's a just friends thing.
Friendship chocolate.
S-Sorry the shape's funny.
Silly.
The shape isn't important.
What matters is that you made it for me.
S-Stupid.
I told you it's not like that.
Nothing like that?
No.
Just shut up and put it away.
This is my first time.
The first time's most important.
So did you give anybody chocolate, Miyuki-san?
I gave chocolate to my father and a relative.
I gave chocolate to everybody I'm friendly with.
I gave chocolate to you, Tsukasa, and Miyuki.
Sheesh.
You guys sure had a boring St. Valentine's Day.
Don't need to hear it from someone who lives in an online game.
Oh, yeah.
Your cousin was accepted to Ryouou, right?
She was.
It's pretty far from her home...
...so she'll be living with us starting next month.
She's always been like a little sister anyway...
...so we've been in touch.
Really.
But next to you...
...nobody would be able to tell who's younger.
No, like I said...
She's like a little sister in more ways than one.
She's that small?!
But if she got accepted to our school...
...your cousin must be really smart.
That just sounds like you're being really presumptuous.
Since you're a student here.
But I barely passed the exam.
Exams, huh?
We'll be taking our exams next year.
Guess I'll be spending the whole year studying.
Sounds awful.
Exams...
Should I even take them?
I haven't even picked a major.
You seriously need to start thinking about your future.
Studying, manual labor, and me just don't mix.
What kind of future do you have in mind?
Use a hobby to make profit and make games...
I design games. 'Cause it's my hobby.
Be a self-proclaimed manga artist who can only sell at Comiket...
Megas smoked cheese-nyoro.
Or perhaps, indulge your curiosity
and become a professional writer.
There can only be one truth!
And this isn't it!
No, maybe just a novelist who aims for a niche market.
Since you like computers, I guess art design might work.
Maybe a scenario writer who uses
random material instead of an actual story writer.
Or she doesn't go to college...
Or they're all the same thing?!
What?
What is it?
Manager!
Legendary Girl A...
...has returned!
What?!
She shook us off last time!
Manager!
Today!
We will absolutely make sure she
reaches the goal known as our register!
Giro.
She seems to be at a loss.
Then allow us to...
...help her find her way!
Okay, everyone!
Let 'er rip!
Okay!
Let's go!
Yeah!
Aw yeah!
Manager.
Attempting to determine Legendary Girl A's objective for the day.
Okay.
Countin' on you.
What's the newest comic out?
Yes.
Volume 14 of Sgt. Frog, sah!
Okay!
Raise the height of our goods to the appropriate level...
...to bring them to the attention of Legendary Girl A!
Okay!
And deploy the flyers!
Tama!
Deployment complete!
Sah!
Okay.
Keep an eye on her movements.
And as Legendary Girl A approaches the register...
...deploy our best-selling goods!
Roger!
Sah!
Okay.
Manager!
Legendary Girl A's objective isn't the comics section!
What?!
Manager.
Switch target to the DVD section.
Okay.
Just to be sure...
...block all side paths so Legendary Girl A...
...heads straight to the new DVD section!
Roger!
Sah!
So sorry!
Tama! Tama!
Oh, my!
Forgive me!
Gero-gero-gero-gero build-up!
Tama-tama-tama-tama build-up!
New
Okay, okay...
Manager!
She's...
...picked up the item!
I've finally become a winner today!
Comrades!
Let us have a wild celebration tonight!
Yes!
Sah!
It was a feint!
Ridiculously Cheap!!
I'll have to bring out my trump card!
Come...
Bring that bargain, super-rare, out-of-print DVD to me.
Manager.
She is heading for the register.
Okay.
Keep going!
What a beautiful scene!
The crowd inside me is cheering with applause right now!
We did it!
Sah!
Your total comes to 1,785 yen.
I'm short 3 yen.
Sorry.
Please put that back.
We'll be back!
Good lucky!
Okay!
Let's kick this into gear!
We're already on the thirteenth episode of Lucky Channel!
Okay.
As you already know, I'm your navigator, Akira Kogami!
And...
Yes.
D-D-Drill!
I'm Akira-sama's assistant, Minoru Shiraishi.
It's a pleasure!
That's right.
D-D-Drill!
We're on episode 13.
D-D-D-D-Drill!
Into the second season.
D-D-Drill!
It's like we've reached the fifth station on Mt. Fuji, right?
D-D-D-D-Drill!
Mt. Fuji?
You can drive up to the fifth station.
That's true...
That's right!
I've climbed Mt. Takao before!
Don't you have something else to talk about?
That's true...
D-D-D-D-D-D-D-D-Drill!
Man, uh...
Akira-sama's twin drills look wonderful!
What's so wonderful about them?
The way they go round and round like a shell.
Well...
Uh...
We have a special announcement today.
The results for the Lucky Star figure poll!
Let's have Akira-sama announce the results!
Current Standings 1st: Minoru Shiraishi 2nd: Akira Kogami 3rd: Kagami Hiiragi 4th: Konata Izumi 5th: Tsukasa Hiiragi 6th: Minami Iwasaki 7th: Misao Kusakabe 8th: Miyuki Takara 9th: Kanata Izumi 10th: Yutaka Kobayakawa
The characters that will soon be getting figures are Konata Izumi...
Akira-sama, do a proper job!
Congratulations!
Sheesh, everybody knew this would happen.
What a joke.
No, no, no...
Just means that the higher-ups think the
actual show is more important than this corner.
Of course not, right?
Current Standings 1st: Minoru Shiraishi 2nd: Akira Kogami 3rd: Kagami Hiiragi 4th: Konata Izumi 5th: Tsukasa Hiiragi 6th: Minami Iwasaki 7th: Misao Kusakabe 8th: Miyuki Takara 9th: Kanata Izumi 10th: Yutaka Kobayakawa
Look.
The producers agree.
Yeah.
I'll just fall for your little trick.
I'm already used to being backstabbed.
Little trick?
That's an awful thing to say.
And don't tell me that it says you're going to have a figure made.
Current Standings 1st: Minoru Shiraishi 2nd: Akira Kogami 3rd: Kagami Hiiragi 4th: Konata Izumi 5th: Tsukasa Hiiragi 6th: Minami Iwasaki 7th: Misao Kusakabe 8th: Miyuki Takara 9th: Kanata Izumi 10th: Yutaka Kobayakawa
Of course not!
Okay.
We'll be making a figure of Konata Izumi-san this time.
And the popular Minoru Shiraishi will also get a figure?!
The hell is this?!
U-Uh...
It's time to say goodbye!
So please send us any suggestions or comments you have!
You can leave them on our home page.
Right, Akira-sama?
I'm leaving.
Er, what?
W-Wait!
B-Bye-bee!
Akira-sama!
Wait up!
Okay.
All the staff members can go home.
D-Drill!
Clap for no reason
For-for-for-forgot something.
Forgot...
Forgot my something.
That fragment of memory I left behind on that day.
It's disappeared.
Along with that girl.
The red sunset was so brilliant.
He's annoying
Don't look him in the eyes
On romantic Jogashima.
Couple who readily agreed to be in the production.
Go ahead and laugh at me for being an idiot.
That's how it should be.
Unsurpassable Wall
But...
Every now and then...
...give me a gentle embrace.
Shiraishi couldn't have?!
Coward
Next Episode
Well, next time on Sgt. Frog:
No!
You mean next time on Lucky Star!
Giro-giro.
Comrade, I have a good idea!
Japanese anime is now a global industry.
If we use it to brainwash the people on Pekopon...
...we can complete the invasion of Pekopon in no time, sah!
You're a genius, Sarge!
Worthless.
A soldier should act like a soldier and use brute force!
Shut your mouth, you red dharma doll!
In this age, whoever controls information controls the battle!
Well, your prehistoric mind wouldn't understand that.
You better watch yourself!
In any case...
「Under One Roof」
Next time:
Under One Roof.
Look forward to next time!
G-Gero!