Now, let'ssu begin yoo!
It's gonna come now...
Fungaa!
Now start out already!
曖昧3センチ
Aimai 3 senchi
Unclear 3 centimeters...
そりゃぷにってことかい？ちょっ!
Sorya punitte koto kai? cho!
Is that a puni? Waitasec!
らっぴんぐが制服…
Rappingu ga seifuku…
The uniform's the wrapping…
だぁぁ不利ってことない　ぷ。
Daa furitte koto nai　Pu.
Hey, there's no disadvantage in that, yeah.
がんばっちゃ♥やっちゃっちゃ
Ganbaccha♥yacchaccha
Try your best♥do the thing-cha,
そんときゃーっち&Releaseぎョッ
son tokyaacchi & ririisu gyo
at that time, well, catch & release, gyo!
汗っ、々っ
A-se, a-se!
In the sweaty, sweaty...
の谷間にDarlin'darlin'F R E E Z E!!
No taniai ni daarin daarin furiiーzu!
valley darlin' darlin' FREEZE!!
なんかダるー、なんかデるー
NankaDAruuー, nankaDEruー
Somewhat lazy..., something's coming out...
あいしテるー
AishiTEruuー
I love you...
あれ一個が違ってるんるー
Are ikko ga chigatterunruー
One of those is different, ruー.
なやみン坊ー 高鉄棒 おいしん簿ー
NayamiNbouー Koutetsubou oishinboー
A worrywart, high horizontal bar - an ever-lengthening list...
いーかげんにシナサイ
Iikagen ni SHINASAI
Now get reasonable!
飛んでったアイツの火照るカラダって
Tondetta AITSU no hoteru KARADAtte
The burning body of who flied away right now is...
所謂ふつーのおにゃのコ
Iwayuru futsuu no onya no KO
what is called a "usual girl".
驚いた、
Odoroita,
I'm surprised,
あたしだけ? 豚骨ハリガネおかわりダー!!!!
atashi dake? tonkotsu harigane okawari daaー!!!!
Only me? I get an extra portion of tonkotsu with super hard noodlesー!!!!
BON-BONおーえん団
BON-BON oーendan
Bon-bon cheering team.
Let's get! Cherry pie
Let's get! Cherry pie.
RAN-RAN　かんげー会
Ranraan　kangeーikai
RAN-RAN, welcoming party.
Look up! せんせーしょん
Look up! Senseーshon
Look up! Sensation.
はい！　存在感・・小惑星
Haai　Sonzaikan　tenten　shouwakusei
Yes, feeling of being here・・meteor!
ぶつかって溶けました　呆然　大いに歌ってシレンジャー
Butsukatte tokemashita　bouzen　ooi ni utatte shirenjyaー
Got melt from the collision, dumbfounded and singing a lot, "Shiranger!"
もっていけ!
Motte ike!
Take and go!
最後に笑っちゃうのはあたしのはず
Saigo ni waracchau no wa atashi no hazu
The last one laughing should be me,
セーラーふくだからです
Seeraa fuku dakara desu
because it's a seeraa fuku.
←結論
←Ketsuron
←It's the conclusion.
月曜日なのに！
Getsuyoubi nanoni!
Even if it's monday!
機嫌悪いのどうするよ？
Kigen warui no dou suru yo？
What will you do with that bad mood?
夏服がいいのです←キャ？ワ！イイｖ
Natsufuku ga ii no desu←KYA?WA!IIv
I want my summer uniform←It!Is!Cute!
接近3ピクト するまでってちゅーちょだ　やん☆
Sekkin san pikuto, suru madette chuーcho da　yan☆
Getting closer's in three paces, I'll hesitate until you do 'it' Oh☆
頑張って　張り切って
Ganbatte,　harikitte
Try your best, be on high,
My Darlin'darlin' P L E A S E!!
Mai daarin daarin puriizu
my darlin' darlin' please!
I got another phone one bought for me!
Just try not to wash it this time.
Yeah, I'll put it into a simple place.
Hey! Tsukasa, come and help me!
Yes!
Desire
Barusamikosuu...
Getting
Annoyed
Barusamikosuu...
Oh? Ahh... found it.
I'm sick of this!
I'll hit it for you, so give it to me!
It's annoying!
You don't have to... I'm OK, I'll do it by myself...
I came to play!
Ah, neesan, welcome!
What are you doing?
A gyaruge that was released recently.
Hmm...
Well, I'll be randomly reading your manga then.
OK...
"Well it is a game that has an age limit, but...
she doesn't seem to realize it or she's already gotten bored of these...
Which one of them is it, police officer?"
And so...
They're strengthening the regulations and stuff during the traffic safety week...
Doing detailed checking and telling traffic rules one by one...
This is something terrible again...
I even get yelled at even if they're wrong sometimes...
"But when I always look at neesan, she has no persuasion for rules or "safety"!"
Big sister's surprised!
"I hear that this year's cold is persistant, so...
I must cure it fast, or..."
"If you look at the reception number, it seems that It'll take some time..."
"Let's read while waiting."
Andou-san!
Andou Shigeo-san!
Takara-san! Takara Miyuki-san!
Takara Miyuki-san?
Are you here?
And the next one...
Nishiyama Mariko-san.
Ah! Oh, oh my! Did I get called? The time is?!
I must pay more attention to my surroundings...
In a moment we will arrive at Kamada, the end of the line.
Ah! A-Ah! I wonder where this is!
And so, the other day I told Tsukasa how to write mail.
As she always says that she can't understand it, even though she's playing with it as much...
Hee...
Yay!
And so, she seems to be so happy...
that it led to her sending mail about anything every day.
The side that has to receive all of them every day is troubled as well, right?
But, well, there's no real reason to lose sleep over it, though...
From: Tsukasa
She's the type to be in high spirits first and then get more and more tired about it.
Aah, there surely are such people that are prone to be childlike...
Ah, another came.
They don't give up, they just can't keep their concentration, right?
And, is there enough content to write so much mail?
Even if she's always together with me...
and she seems to have gotten addicted to emoticons...
Look!
"Should we go and buy soy milk cream manjuu on our way home today as well..."
Huh?
What's this that comes after the text...?
The feeling that it's so enjoyable she can't help it does get around...
These are hieroglyphs already...
Oh, I wonder if she got used to it at last...
That's right. But I like the one with the afro.
Is that so? But they're not really doing that
music, right?
Yeah, that might be so.
Is that so...
Hee...
You know...
Aww...!
I do understand the feeling, but couldn't you stop sending mail only to your relatives?
Could I ask you for a moment?
What is it?
You know, I just couldn't understand how to send mail on the mobile phone...
Dondake-...
It's really easy, daddy!
Oh, it just can't be helped... I'll tell you how to do it...
Oh, yes... There are such people who get really proud after they've learnt something...
Ahh, well...
A-ha-ha-ha...
You just cannot say a thing about that smell, really.
Yes, it's really too smelly, now isn't it. Really...
Oh, so you have pretty many entries here...
Ah..! Hey, don't look without permission!
Do you have mail that'd be bad if seen by others?
Not really.
I just said it.
It's a man, it must be a man!..
Even if I say the opposite!..
She really doesn't answer, now does she...
Should I try to call to the house?
"Hello, is it Kagami?"
Oh, Konata?
You know, try to answer to your mobile phone as well!
Well... It didn't ring so I didn't notice it...
"There's completely no reason in it if you don't notice it, right?"
"But where did that phone go in the first place..."
Your mobile phone really doesn't have any reason to be, now does it?
And you know, about the next weekend...
"Ah, I got called for a bit, so wait..."
"Hey! Do it fast!"
"Just wait a bit more!"
"The call's too long, you get me illiterate!"
"I'm sorry, sorry..."
"I got yelled at for having a long call..."
Ah, sorry...
But I thought that your family would be tolerant to such things,...
that's pretty strict.
"No, that's because he was in the middle of concentrating for a saying."
You, say such things faster!
At all times and places, point cards hide magical powers that cannot be seen...
When you notice, you're even buying things you weren't planning for!
You're really planless, now aren't you...
Even though I understand you a bit...
So she did come...
Even though she knows that there are two anime shops - "AnimeXX" and "GAXXXS" in this town...
It's the person that buys the same thing once at both stores...
The Legendary Girl "A"!
It's the Legendary Girl A shift!
Welcome!
The fifth DVD volume of Haruhi has arrived!
Limited Editions, Usual Versions... Everything!
And we're getting goods in one after another!
That's right...
Announce as many newly arrived and
put out things as you can, in any way...
Now she should buy as much as we have...
Ah, today I had AqAge's Priviledge Guidebook on my mind...
I must go to GAMERS.
It's no good!
Lucky Star!
So let's stay for the night and play through the night?
Un!
Ah...
When we play, it's always at our place...
Is your place, Konata, no good?
Nno...
I'd just like to go there once in a while.
Hmmm....
It's not like it's forbidden, but...
my father has to be in the house a lot because of occupation. as well...
Oh, was that so?
Yeah, that's why I'd be troubled as well if I could not take the responsibility...
For what?!
It's a bit fun to see what kind of a house Konata has, right?
Ossu!
Oh, welcome!
Sorry for the disturbance, we'll be asking for your kindness today.
Welcome, I have heard a lot about you.
Your house is a shrine and you're maidens, right?
"What kind of explanations were done?! Or is that the main part for him?!"
I wonder if there are many flowers like this...
Please...
Ah, it's Kona-chan's room!
It's an unbelievable room, as I thought...
Ah!
Cute!
Eh...
Oh...
This door is...
Anyways, behind this there is a space that is always closed, stuffed with things that mustn't be seen, right?
Oh, no, I'm having them kept in my father's archives as usually I'm sharing such things with my father...
Hee, so you share them...
That reminds me, your father is a writer, right?
Yeah.
Well, then do you get hooked on gyaruge or light novels your father has written?
Oh, he doesn't write such things in the first place...
Eh?! Is that so?
Yeah.
Hee, that's unexpected...
Ah, but he likes that world, I wonder if he doesn't want to write them...
Was it called "Read-Only"..? You know,...
As he's playing gyaruge or "raising games" in his own life...
he says that he doesn't feel to be bothered to do them for a living.
He-...
But it's all overwhelming from a while ago... This truly is the Izumi household...
You know, as daddy once came really close to me...
Uh?
I tried and said "Dad, you're annoying!"
Eh? You... That's a bit too bad, isn't it?
And I got yelled at "At the very least say 'I hate you, daddy!'"
No, I have some thoughts about that correction as well...
Hm... I think that what you're thinking about and what my dad thought about are different things.
No, I don't understand it anymore...
So should we gradually take a rest?
KITAAAA!
Lately 2ch.net can really be seen on the TV...
That might be so, even though I don't know that well...
Ah... That reminds me, Konata, even though you're "deep", you don't really use such words...
That's usually...
When I'm chatting and stuff, it's like this.
Ah! This is unbelievable... Is this Japanese?
I think that I'd lose if you'd read it...
Should I help with something?
Well, put the salad on a dish then...
Un!
Itadakimasu!
Huh?
It's good!
Indeed... very well done!
If you'd do housework, you'd be able to do like this.
Kagami could improve a bit as well if she'd do it...
That's none of your business!
Look at it, Konata!
It's perfect!
This scene that I have seen even in my dreams is before me!
Huh?
Aah...
Three high-school girls sitting behind the dining table for one man...
The world is weird... Sakura..., Tousaka... Tousaka is your big sister!
it's unnatural but usual turn of events in gyaruge, isn't it?
Ah, was that so?
It really gets chilly at such time, doesn't it?
I wonder if I should've put something on?
Ah! A shooting star!
I couldn't say my wish three times...
They come suddenly, so it's hard.
But some time I'll get it right and have my wish come true!
Tsukasa surely is a dreamer, isn't she...
But no matter how you think it's impossible when thinking realistically.
As you know that it won't work, it can't be anything else than a superstition...
Oh why there are no dreams at all on this side...
Will you drink as well?
Ah, thank you!
So you changed hairstyles!
Yeah, as a play.
As we just had a bath...
"Hmm... I wonder why the image is still different with people, even if the parts are the same..?"
Ah, it's an album. Is it OK to look?
Oh, it's OK.
Ah, Kona-chan is cute!
You really haven't changed much from long ago!
Or should I say that you really have a good child-parent relationship...
Ah!
Ah, that's my mother!
That can't be! She's young!
Don't we look alike?
I wonder if it's not a crime...
I just tend to think when I look at my dad...
Huh?
Like "What in my dad was so good for my mom..."
As you look like your mom as much as this...
So, for example, what's the type you like?
Mine?
Hm... When you say so it seems that there really is no such...
Is that true? Just say it!
A!
It might be that mom was OK with anything...
She did say that she was childhood friends with him as well...
No, that's a bit...
Putting it on dad only because of looking at him...
You really merciless even for your parents...
But as I looked at mom...
Hm?
Lately in manga and games junior high schoolers look adult-like...
and adults really young-like, right?
I wonder what that is... Could she be wishing for interference...
It would've been better if Yuki-chan had come as well...
Well, if she had something to do...
Yes! I'll send mail to Yuki-chan so that she wouldn't be lonesome!
Miyuki would care about it a bit too much, so don't.
Ah, a reply.
"I am most happy to know you're having fun.
I am cleaning my homework with all my might right now.
The next time, please let me..."
I forgot to do my homework!
Kagami, please do something!
My class doesn't have it, so can I sleep already?
But!..
Ah!
That shooting star...
If I'd make my wish short it might go better...
Well, I wonder about that...
What are you doing?
Research on how to say fast the wish for a shooting star.
Don't fight with reality, try to end finish it fast.
Hey, Yuki-chan!
I just didn't understand this part during the class...
Eh?
Ah, that part?
"Kona-chan" because it's Konata, "Yuki-chan" because it's Miyuki...
Hmm...
Well, Tsukasa, what kind of nickname would you give to Kagami?
Kaga-chan? Gami-chan?
Ah, hmm...
Mirror;
Kagami - Kyou
Kangamiru
I'd say Kyou-chan, if you read "Kagami" another way - "Kyou"!
Ooh, amazing sense!
Powerful;
Kyou - gou - tsuyoi
tsuyomaru - shiiru
It gives a powerful feeling and is just fitting!
Bad luck;
Kyou
You can change it to this Kyou-chan as well!
B-but I didn't have such an intension...
It could be better if you wouldn't say that to oneechan...
And if you'd make one for yourself, how would it go?
Tsuka-chan? Kasa-chan?
I'd think about Hii-chan, it's not so flowing with the name...
Indeed... Tsukasa, you indeed always have the image that you say "Hi-hii."
But it didn't have such an intention as well...
Got it! So I'll call you, Tsukasa, Hii-chan from now on!
Hee?!
"Hee"? Huh? Huh?..
But isn't it somehow unpleasant if you select it yourself?
By the way, what is "that" then?
"That"?
Anything would go.
Will you revenge, Sebastian?
It's Shiraishi!
Hey, Kyou-chan!
Kyou-chaan!
Could she be calling me?!
It's hard to understand, so stop it.
Well, then what way you'd like?
Isn't it OK with Kagami?
Isn't it good to put a nickname on you? Like Kona-chan or Yuki-chan.
Well, then "Kagami-sama".
Hey, Kagami-sama!
Uwa! She really went and uses it!
What is it?
Well, I just called you.
Excuse me for making you wait, Kagami-sama.
Oh!
What happened, Kagami-sama?
That's amazing... Yeah...
I was wrong, so please, call me usually...
Lucky Star.
LUCKY CHANNEL!
Good Lucky!
And fast-pacedly this is the tenth time we plunge into Lucky Channel!
I'm your navigator, Kogami Akira.
Hello! I'm the assistant, Shiraishi Minoru!
It's a bit immediate, but this time it's the fifth time of Character Introductions...
the Hiiragi Kagami edition!
In the main story she is an active "straight man" character as well...
But isn't this namely tsundere?
Really easy to understand... the setting...
I'd like to say something!
Huh?
To designate Kagami-san as a "tsundere" can be thought of as rather hastified...
Well what is she then?
Much less, have we told the true comprehension of the word "tsundere"?
No, it can be said, although I'm afraid to say it, that now "tsundere" has,...
in reverse proportion to popularization, been becoming dimmer as a definition.
Precisely the year 2002, when the word "tsundere" was born...
It was something done over the internet,
but at that time the definition was...
"Cold at first, but before long lovestruck."
Yes! That is to say, something that shows changes in feelings with the progress of time!
Do you really understand what you're saying?
That is now nothing but a word that tells the duality of character,...
regrettably tamely understood as "Cold on the surface, lovestruck in reality."
Let us dare to declare the fact that that is an obvious mistake!
We shall now surely restore the real meaning of "tsundere"...
and it is imperative that we warn this rotten language culture!
Stand, citizens!
You really perform, Sebastian...
Who is that?
If Kagami wouldn't be "tsundere" then what is she?..
Was it about me?!
I don't really understand the hard parts, but...
if you say as much, there is nothing good
to substitute the word "tsundere", right?
Well, I don't think there is not something, but...
something like "kuudere", no that's not it...
"Deretsun"?
You really don't have any sense now don't you...
Isn't it just OK with tsundere?
No, that... That is different!
Ah, now I get it!
Let's give all of our viewers as well a chance to think about the new concept that'll take the place of tsundere! Good Idea!
Leaving it to the others?
And so, everyone sitting before the TV!
Yes, you as well! Wouldn't you think about a proper word to represent a character like Kagami-san?
Let us rewrite the groundings of the modern terminology!
Beginning, "The Tsundere Rework"!
For more details, the radio or the web page's address!
We are waiting for your heated opinion!
Huh?
This'll close it.
Is it OK already?
Lots and lots, lots and lots...
Bye-nii...
Bye-nii!!
Fast Forward!
Ohh, I already spoke a lot today, now didn't I?
The most unbeatable so far!
Oh, Akira-sama?
W-w-what happened?
Satisfied?
Y-yes! Well...
I spoke most tonight, I think I did well.
Well, you know, I'll be eating out with your producer and the boss of your office...
E-eh? Well...
A lot about the future you...
E-e-eh... Please wait for a moment...
E... What is it about?
Well... Whether you can continue or not is not something you'd understand, as well...
Nononono!
You're still working part-time in CoCo XXXX anyways, right?
Well, that's just in the day slot, so it's not like I'm getting that much money...
And a grilled meat place?
Well, no, I'm still doing that as well...
But such things make no difference! Hey, that's too private so stop please!
Next me, right?
Tsukasa, what about this?
Ahh, if it's this... Right, Yuki-chan?
Yes, I know it.
Well, select this then.
Thanks, Kona-chan!
Thank you very much.
No problem...
Did Tsukasa and all pick already?
Yeah!
...ｌｙ くじけそうな姿窓に映して
...ｌｙ kujikesouna sugata mado ni utsushite
Lonely... almost crushed figure reflecting in the window...
This song got popular when we were in kindergarden, right?
I don't really know...
あてもなく歩いた
Ate mo naku aruita
I aimlessly walked...
Excuse me, neither do I...
I remember! Oneechan and all sung this pretty much!
ひとしれずため息つく
Hitoshirezu tameiki tsuku
Unseen, I sigh...
The songs that parents and older siblings sing are of an earlier generation, but...
Ｉ’ｍ　ｐｒｏｕｄ
壊れそうで崩れそな情熱を
Kowaresou de kuzuresona jounetsu wo
I always kept looking for something...
you just end up remembering them naturally, right?
つなぎとめる何かいつも探し続けてた
Tsunagitomeru nanika itsumo sagashitsudzuketeta
that would tie my almost broking, crumbling passion...
どうしてあんなに夢が素直に見れなくなってた？
Doushite anna ni yume ga sunao ni mirenakunatteta？
Oh why did dreams become so impossible to see honestly?
街中でいる場所なんてどこにもない
Machichuu de iru basho nante doko ni mo nai
Not a single place in the city where I could be,...
身体中から愛がこぼれていた
Miyuu kara ai ga koboreteita
love kept overflowing from my the whole of my body...
Oh, she lowered the pitch...
Like I could do something about it, it's high!
ひとごみを・・・
Hitogomi wo・・・
Through the crowd...
And so, the next Lucky Star is?
It's me, Kagami.
It's still OK to order soup at the place you went to play...
but when it splats and just a wee bit hits your clothes you just feel down, right?
Especially if it would be the roux of curry it'd be the worst...
Also if you'd wear your favourite clothes on that day, you'll really get blue for that day...
And, when, after all, you buy soup lunch at a convenience store...
and try to carry it as horizontally as possible, so that it wouldn't spill out...
and later when you open the bag, during the times when the soup has spilled out and it's all soppy...
you just lose any feeling for eating, right?
And then it's still OK to get bags split between warm and cold things, but...
when they end up putting a magazine or something together with a cold drink...
the paper gets all the drips of water and the whole magazine is well up...
and you think "Then for what did you split the bag?!"...
Next Time: The Many Ways To Spend A Holy Night
Look forward to it!
This program was brought to you by Kadokawa Bookshops and the companies visible.