Now, let'ssu begin yoo!
It's gonna come now...
Fungaa!
Now start out already!
I My Something
"I my something"
そりゃぷにってことかい、ちょっ
Sorya punitte koto kai, cho
That's about a puni, is it, cho?
ら、ぐーんぐーんが制服
Ra, guun-guun ga seifuku
Ra, guun guun goes the seifuku,
なぁふりってことない？　うん
Naa furitte koto nai？　Un
Hey, there's no irrationality in this? Yeah.
頑張っちゃ、やっちゃっちゃ、
Ganbaccha, yacchaccha,
Try your best, do the thing-cha,
そんときゃ　じゃリリース料
son tokya　jya ririisu ryou
at that time, well the things for release!
あせっ、あせっ
A-se, a-se!
"A-se, a-se!"
の谷間にダーリンダーリンフリー
No taniai ni daarin daarin furiiー
In the cleavage darling darling free!
なんかたるー、なんかてるー
Nankataruuー, nankateruー
How to cheat, how to win,
あいしてるー
Aishiteruuー
I love you.
あれ一個が違ってる
Are ikko ga chigatteru
One of those is different.
むん　むやみに暴行鉄棒おいしん棒
Mun muyami ni boukou tetsubou oishinbou
Stuffy, violence with recklessness - steel rod is a sweet rod.
いいかげんにしなさい!
Iikagen ni shinasai!
Now get reasonable!
飛んでったあいつの火照る体って
Tondetta aitsu no hoteru karadatte
The burning body of who flied away right now is...
いわゆる普通の女の子
Iwayuru futsuu no onna no ko
what is called a "usual girl".
驚いた、
Odoroita,
I'm surprised,
あたしだけ豚骨針金おかわりダー!!!!
atashi dake tonkotsu harigane okawari daaー!!!!
Only I get an extra portion of tonkotsu with a needle insideー!!!!
ボンボン応援団
Bon-bon ouendan
Bon-bon cheering team.
Let's get cherry pie
Let's get cherry pie.
らんらーん　関係感
Ranraan　kankeikan
Blazing, relationship feeling,
you have センセーション
you have senseeshon
you have sensation.
ハーイ　存在感　点々　小惑星
Haai　Sonzaikan　tenten　shouwakusei
Yes, feeling of being here, here and there meteors.
ぶつかって溶けました　呆然　大いに歌ってシリンダー
Butsukatte tokemashita　bouzen　ooi ni utatte shirindaa
Got melt from the collision, dumbfounded singing a lot, "Cilinder!"
もっていけ、
Motte ike,
Take and go,
最後に笑っちゃうのはあたしのはず
Saigo ni waracchau no wa atashi no hazu
The last one laughing should be me,
セーラー服だからです
Seeraa fuku dakara desu
because it's a seeraa fuku.
結論
Ketsuron
Conclusion.
月曜日なのに
Getsuyoubi nanoni
Even if it's monday,
機嫌悪いのどうするよ
Kigen warui no dou suru yo
What will you do with that bad mood?
夏服がいいのです、かわいい
Natsufuku ga ii no desu, kawaii
The summer uniform is better, cute.
接近賛否それまでって躊躇だ　やーん
Sekkin sanbi, sore madette choucho da　yaーn
Yes and no for getting closer, until that it's undecided, yaan.
頑張って　張り切って
Ganbatte,　harikitte
Try your best, be on high,
ま、ダーリンダーリンプリーズ
Ma, daarin daarin puriizu
well darling darling please!
Oh yes... it's the summer uniform from today...
someone like Konata would still put the winter uniform on, though.
There's about one like that in class always.
Onee-chan, good morning!
Uwa, such a person was so close...
Different
People
Darn it! I forgot to enter the 'Present from Zattere'- contest!
Tsk. And I was hoping about getting it, too. The apron from 'Koi no Apron'.
You didn't have enough love, now did you.
Huh?
Kagami doesn't have enough love, that's why she forgets.
No... Well, I just was busy with comittee and with the test so...
No, no. That's no more than an excuse.
Because I haven't forgotten.
Don't put me on the same table as the only-play you!
And that way you say it really pisses me off!
A-ha!
I wonder how can you win those prizes...
It's all...
about love!
Well, in any case I'm a woman without love.
Well... If you write the same as always, you couldn’t get it anyway.
Kona-chan, how do you write?
So that I could win, of course.
How's that?
The basic of all basics is to write neatly…
You should write a card that the drawer would want to draw.
Like?
For example, using a highlight pen to make a lining to the card.
Ah! Yeah, that'll stand out!
In addition you can add illustrations based on the prize...
Illustrations... Uhm, I might not draw those well...
Such people can...
just get the upper hand with quantity.
Whee..! That's something that can be done!
But!
Even if you try to enter many, many times...
you must write each of them by hand, without printers or copy machines.
Additionally you should do a hundred at a time.
One hundred?
One hundred pieces is just usual.
It's a crazy amount.
You shall get what you want!
Passion and spirit are also needed!
But... aren't there times when it's cheaper to just buy?
There are things in the world that can't be bought with cash.
Huh...
Will one hundred cards fit into a post box?
Un?
You shouldn't send them all at once, but in little parts, little-by-little.
And on different days.
Whee...
Because there are times when the lottery administrator will reject you if the quantity is large.
Well, there are times when being too subtle is no good - and the opposite, too.
Well, what should I do then?
Therefore - it's love!
Well, if you would like to win any way, you should shamble free paper or fold-out leaflet and apply with non-appealance.
Because those have the highest probability of winning.
Yeah, I'll try that!
Is there 'love' in that...
Hm...
Hmm...
You two don't really look like twins.
Ah, that's because we're fraternal twins.
We have the usual differences as sisters.
Identical twins look pretty much alike, but fraternal twins have differences in appearance and personality.
Understood...
Surely Tsukasa is easy-going, but Kagami is violent.
What'cha say?
Whoa!
If you were to match hairstyles and ribbons, you would look more alike…
"Kona-chan!"
Oh, I can't... Cute character doesn't go on Kagami...
Shut up! Don't just imagine what you want and then say something rude!
Do you have telepathy or something?
Huh?
Look. They do say that twins share living habits and...
lover types even if they're grown apart.
The person they marry could be a twin, too.
Then, when one of them gets into danger, the other can tell - being in a completely different place.
There are many strange experiences like that, so wouldn't you, too, have telepathy?
Try it a bit, the wee-wee.
That's from reading too much manga!
Mana-kana too!
Mana-kana?
[ Mana-kana - a Japanese pop duo with two twins. Google. ]
I hear those two have little differences, too.
In a nutshell, Mana always cares and Kana is an optimist.
And they did say that the voices are a bit different, too.
By the way, Mana-Kana always thought they were fraternal twins...
but they just found out that they are identical!
Whoa! Really?
Is that something to be so surprised about?
The definition of identical and fraternal twins did change a bit ago, didn't it?
And so that way Kagami and Tsukasa could be identical...!
What’s common between the two of you...
You both like candy, right?
Yes, I love them!
Well...
Both left-handed!
Yeah!
That's right.
Favourite color?
White..?
Black!
The same as your hearts...
What you say?!
Un?
Somehow I got hungry from talking about eggs and sausages...
We haven't talked about food!
Uwah! It's hot and humid...
If it gets a bit crowded, you'll be sweating fast...
The time has moved to such a season.
It's hot...
It seems they still haven't got an air condinitioner here...
O?
Huh!?
Hey-hey!
Whaaaat....?
To: Izumi Soujirou and Konata
We have filled each other with love slowly, but on June Xth we (Narumi Kiyotaka and Kobayakawa Yui) have decided to goal (get married).
'The Ladybug march - Punk version'...
Well, a sister of a relative of mine's getting married...
Ah, a 'June bride', isn't it?
That's so good...
This... Being such dark and wet season, I wonder why it represents happiness?
Ye-ye-h...
Eh? "Why are people fortunate if they marry in June?"
Yeah!
Generally speaking the 'Ju' of June is said to come from the name of a Goddess in Roman mythology, Juno.
Juno was also a Goddess called Hera in Greek mythology, administrating marriages and childbirth.
So it is said that people who marry during Hera's month, June, are blessed and protected.
Hee...
But Hera is Zeus' wife, isn't she?
Yes, that's true.
Hera has an image of violence and apostle-likeness, so it really doesn't feel like happiness...
Huh? Huh?
What would you prefer to put on for a wedding day? A dress or a kimono?
I would like a dress. It’s been a dream of mine since childhood.
Hmm... I'd want a dress, too...
But after all a kimono is good, too...
Hmmm... I'd want to wear that too...
Heh... Lately there are Minnie dresses and colour-filled dresses, too.
Hee, Minnie's dress...
A design with many frills on the skirt could be cute!
"Many dreams, many frills.", right?
Tsukasa could be Angel Salvia...
no, Angel Daisy by the hair...
So it's decided to yellow on top and to a miniskirt down there.
Huh?!
Tsukasa-san, you would look good in a Minnie.
Really?
And, it's the show, but it's also important what kind of guy the Mr. Partner is.
A "friend of a childhood friend"- type or a "little princess"- type.
You can really sulk over which to choose...
On one side you have a big marriage portion, and you can use the magic of XXX and XXXX.
But sentimentally...
Easily a 'bianca', right?
Ooh, Kagami, how sentimental. And I thought you'd go for the money...
Uwa, no jokes, huh?
Huh?
Ossu! Konata!
Un?
I got something I can't understand in the game I borrowed from you earlier...
Wait a sec Kagami-nya!
Huh?
Aren't such places interesting if you do them yourself?
Yeah...
You do have a point.
Yes-yes.
So, as we have understood each other's achievements, Konata will do her homework alone from now on.
GOH!
Hmph.
The detectives in manga and drama really do have a bit too many murder cases always, don't they?
Like Conan or Kindaichi, you know.
If you won't do it like that the story won't build, now will it?
Is that so? Aren't usual cases OK, too?
'usual'?
Going through whole Japan in the search of a lost person...
Tailing would be pretty good for games, there's thrill and suspence.
Well...
Accepting the investigation requests from a husband thinking his wife is cheating on him...
Something like searching a runaway pet?
Yeah, yeah.
But is it fun to look at things like that?
Nope. I don't think it'd be fun at all.
I said so?!
And, you know, in real incidents they don't use those clever tricks they use in manga and drama.
Well, now that you say it seems so.
Fingerprint forgery or fabrication, or something like deletion of luminol reactions.
E?!
Something like outwitting the chemistic investigation and stuff.
Well, if it'd be that bad it would be outlawed.
Something that couldn't be transmitted.
Aah, that... such hard cases either end before you notice them or they go unsolved...
That's bad in a lot of ways!
Don't you just hate it that there's been a lot of rain recently.
That's so...
Fuuh...
A long time ago I did like rain...
I'm pretty bad with rain. You get wet and the laundry with stuff doesn't dry...
Kona-chan, why did you like rain?
Well, because the the baseball relay got suspended so I got to watch anime as usual.
Undoubtably. That's very Kona-chan- like.
But now there are many more baseball domes...
Lucky Star!
Hmmm...
Did something happen?
In manga it's pretty common for an smart-like guy and a stupid guy to go to the same school...
"Come on and grow up!"
"Shut up! Uranabe Hyouta got into it!"
When you really think about it's pretty weird...
If you say like that, they did ran an anime where the teachers and the pupils were of same age no matter how you look.
More like it being the reverse.
"Sensei!"
What is it, TakaXXXX-san?
The gap of the real age and the physical age is acknowledged at any age in any world.
I don't get it!
Thou shalt not feel a question there.
If there would be one student with completely different marks, wouldn't it be strange anyways?
Yes, I can agree with that, really.
There's still this - Konata really did get into this school.
You're good at doing 'fast rewinds' so don't tell me you passed here like that too...
Hmmm...
Huh? What? Could it be...
Well, indeed there was no such that time.
I surprised...
But you kept studying pretty well, now didn't you?
Did DS or something get a test game?
My dad, you know, gave me some conditions.
Nothing for rank D, a 3DO for a C or a PS2 for a B - like that.
Izumi-dad. You really know how to control your daughter's heart...
I did think, but...
huh?
Hm.
Hm...
The way Tsukasa is in this school is way more mysterious.
Don't say so hard-to-say things so clearly...
Yattaa! I won again!
Darn!
It won't go with fighting games, the amount of things...
Come and challenge me with something else!
Hoho... Is that so... And the next'll be...
Let's battle with a quiz game!
It... can't be... I lost in a game in which I had confidence...
Unbelievable!
Hunn yeah.
She really could've not remembered all the question patterns... now...
Unchangingly unbelievable memory when it comes to games...
What'll we play next?
Don't search by yourself!
Oh... this is strange... You did have a really easy party game here now didn't you?...
Now why do you know the games of another family?
I'd think that even Kagami could win in it...
It was really smelly you know...
Kagami hasn't really eaten much sweets, even though she always eats them.
Oh, there's no big reason.
Ohhh, I got it. Diet for the summer.
It's not like that!
Even if she doesn't have anyone to show her swimsuit to.
Shut up! Mind your own business!
That reminds me, you two were born on Tanabata, right?
It's soon your birthday!
Yeah it's so...
Kona-chan really remembered it.
Yeah.
17, isn't it...
17 is 'maeyaku'.
What happens on 'maeyaku'?
When you look at parent and child, maeyaku is the year when bad omens begin.
Really...
As the birthday got closer I begun worrying more and more...
And because of that I bought a lot of amulets and power stones and stuff!
Seems fun.
It' so! I got a bit carried away while buying, though...
But to say, we have a 'burnt shit' amulet... I mean protecting amulet in here.
"A burnt shit amulet now, is it..."
It feels like "Oh all right now, I'll look at the wellbeing of your traffic safety too"...
Yes yes...
Oh, did you know that your birthday is also the ponytail day?
No, I didn't.
But why is it on 7th of July?
Because Orihime in Tanabata had a ponytail, you know.
Somehow feels like forced...
There's a real "Japan Ponytail Association", too. They give a "Japan Ponytail Prize" out every year, too. To a celebrity who looks good with a ponytail.
Hee, is that so?
But I feel that everyone would look good with a ponytail...
I don't know about that...
Fumu
Hmm... I'm the shortest so I'm on the line...
But aren't small ponytails cute?
It looks good on you too, Kona-chan. You're completely OK with it even when you're as always.
Could that be so...
Yeah, it is.
Onee-chan, too...
Kagami's, you know...
Ok, got it! You're satisfied if I take it off?
Manlyhood- moe like a 'bushi'.
"Oh, I'm sorry!"
You know, drunkards really seem to put their necktie on their head, don't they?
Could that have a reason?
Ah, that. That's when someone tries to take off his necktie upwards,
but gets stuck in the middle?
Hu-umm...
If you say so, it's even more unnatural for them to have boxed lunch with them.
Boxed lunch?
The thing that Kato-chan from The Drifters has.
Um, I don't really get it...
Nowadays if you think about drunk people you think of necktie-on-head and a boxed lunch.
I told you!
It'd be great if Orihime and Hikoboshi could meet this year.
Twinkle, twinkle, twinkle...
It'd be good If that 'burnt seconds' of yours hears your prayers...
Thank you for nothing...
Comp Festival, they're running a competition for all the call cards, right.
Now that you say so, you're always collecting them but do you use them at all?
Hm? No, I don't use them.
Huh? But why would you bother...
When some goods come out for something you love, don't you just want them? As a fan, as a collector?
I don't know... Cards that you can't use...
You mustn't use them! You have to hold them precious!
When you see someone using them carelessly, you just get angered, don't you.
Such items are not something to be used. And selling them on auctions and shops...
is out of the question. That without doubt disqualifies you as a fan, as a collector!
Huf, even if you fuss about it to me...
Well, I think that for me three pieces are needed.
I close one of them in a special case for permament preservation.
And the other one is the one I look at sometimes, for feelings.
And the last one?
For nothing.
What's that?
Doesn't Kagami, too, want at least two or three samples of something you want?
He? Hmmm....
Yes yes, it doesn't go so. In any case I'm an otaku, a weirdling.
Ah, no. But I did understand what you wanted to say, though...
Tsukasa seems to be popular with guys, but you really don't hear such talk.
Eh?
Well, that's because Tsukasa's pretty plain and doesn't stand out really.
Ye-yeah!
Isn't that because a scary onee-chan is guarding her?
Did you say something?
Don't Kona-chan and Yuki-chan just have more personality - not that I'm plain...
Miyuki-san, too, knows a lot, is a beauty and stylish...
and is for 'glasses men', hates dentists and is a natural klutz...
Isn't that getting weird from somewhere?
But now that you mention her, there's no rumours about her, either.
Isn't she just too beautiful and hard to get to?
That shouldn't be so, she's nice and caring.
That's right.
She might get a lot of confessions...
but refuses.
Refusal, now is it...
No, she might just not understand that the person is confessing of love.
That might be so!
Yuki-chan has a pretty literal side, so she might not get it if it is not said straight.
Damn how untidy the guys in your class are, isn't there someone who would have enough guts to...
get Miyuki and just say his feelings aloud with passion?!
There might not be...
There might not be enough mania in our class...
Huh?
Girls like Miyuki are for those with various manias, you know.
Mania now, is it...
Oh my, it's already so late.
I will go now.
Eh, is that so?
Oh, please don't mind me and take your time.
And so, please excuse me.
Yeah, see you later!
Bye-byee!
And yes, there was something to it. In reality that person was...
Ah!
A... O-oh, my... Excuse me...
Did it!
I-I'm sorry...
Oh my my my.
You really do that, I have done that once, too.
Me too.
Everyone really does that once, don't they.
Konata has done that, too?
Nope.
Huh?
That was one of the so-called moe points!
Huu...
Miyuki-san - "Good job!"
Lucky Star
Lucky Channel!
Good lucky!
Whew! Lucky Channel, su-su-super energetic today, too! This is your navigator, Kogami Akira!
O-oh, I am Akira-sama's assistant, Shiraishi Minoru. Greetings.
Yes, yes. This is already the third time we are here by the two of us!
How are you, Shiraishi-san? Did you get used to it all?
Eh... Well, not yet... I'm sorry.
Hmm... It feels that Shiraishi-san hasn't opened his heart to Akira...
And it feels like he's sitting further away than usual...
Huh?
I wonder if this is the image of hearts...
Snif...
Ah, Th-th-that's not the case!
Yes! I'd like to start the show today!
Well, today's output is a very happy project!
The first round of Lucky Star regular attendee introductions! Pon-pokopoon!
Yes. This time we will introduce Takara Miyuki-san.
Well... Good at being at being the class representative, a person of a very clear...
'high morale'
...high morale. Pen and the sword, both inhumanly perfect.
Shiraishi-san, you know about Miyuki-san, right?
The of of 'of course'! Miyuki-san's great now, isn't she?
First, those glasses! And she's a beauty, too! Usually with such a pretty one it's really hard to get closer...
but somehow it just feels easy with her.
Hee...
I'd like you talk as much on radio, too...
So if I let you speak about Miyuki-san you won't stop...
A-aaah, it's not like I said it like...
Oh well... Takara Miyuki-san...
a so-called beautiful girl- character, big-breasted and as an addition a moe-type, like that?!
Oh that's good, pretty-type beauties - they even get liked by manical fans...
But when talking about maniac fans I have on lolicon...
Bye byee! It's already the time to part!
And so, in this part of the programme we look at all your questions and cheers to Akira, and all those comments about the programme...
Please send a lot of 'em!
Oh well, look forward to next time.
See you later!
What kind of person is she really?
Oh, she really is like that.
Can't be! I wonder if she's taking white powder into her nose in the dressing room.
No, she's not Akira-sama so it's OK.
Puh-haa...
Acchii!
It's interesting!
A really unique song.
I'd gradually want to hear songs that can be understood by usual people, though...
Ah, the next one you'll know, Kagami.
Huh?
Let's guess by the intro!
Huh, what was this...
yes...
And, Kagami, what's the answer?
Aah, FMP - it's FMP.
Heee...
Moreover, it's from Kagami's favourite - Fumoffu!
Was that so...
I just read the book a bit and fell into it!
例えばね　涙がこぼれる日には
Tatoeba ne, namida ga koboreru hi ni wa...
Ah, Kona-chan! You're good!
You can make a more adult-like voice, too...
Isn't she just imitating?
その背中を　ひとりじめしたいけど
Sono senaka wo, hitorijimeshitai kedo...
And? What Tsukasa and Miyuki will sing?
Eh... Could I sing something?
I don't know a lot, too...
優しさは時々　残酷だから
Yasashisa wa tokidoki, sankoku dakara...
Anything is alright! Konata's like that so let's sing freely what we want, too!
Well, let's search!
But I have no confidence in singing...
求める程　こたえを見失う
Motomeru hodo, kotae wo miushinau...
It's all OK, we're the only ones to hear it so sing from your heart!
Is that so... well then...
雨上がりの街　虹が見えるなら
Ameagari no machi, niji ga mieru nara...
今　歩きだそう　何かが始まる
Ima arukidasou, nani ka ga hajimaru...
And so, the next Lucky Star is...
I'm Tsukasa. You know, there was a thing I laughed at almost until I couldn't breath some time ago.
Right? At the school in the morning... Ah! There's no more time!?
Next time: The Problem With Motivation
Look forward to it!