Now, let'ssu begin yoo!
It's gonna come now...
Fungaa!
Now start out already!
I My Something
"I my something"
そりゃぷにってことかい、ちょっ
Sorya punitte koto kai, cho
That's about a puni, is it, cho?
ら、ぐーんぐーんが制服
Ra, guun-guun ga seifuku
Ra, guun guun goes the seifuku,
なぁふりってことない？　うん
Naa furitte koto nai？　Un
Hey, there's no irrationality in this? Yeah.
頑張っちゃ、やっちゃっちゃ、
Ganbaccha, yacchaccha,
Try your best, do the thing-cha,
そんときゃ　じゃリリース料
son tokya　jya ririisu ryou
at that time, well the things for release!
あせっ、あせっ
A-se, a-se!
"A-se, a-se!"
の谷間にダーリンダーリンフリー
No taniai ni daarin daarin furiiー
In the cleavage darling darling free!
なんかたるー、なんかてるー
Nankataruuー, nankateruー
How to cheat, how to win,
あいしてるー
Aishiteruuー
I love you.
あれ一個が違ってる
Are ikko ga chigatteru
One of those is different.
むん　むやみに暴行鉄棒おいしん棒
Mun muyami ni boukou tetsubou oishinbou
Stuffy, violence with recklessness - steel rod is a sweet rod.
いいかげんにしなさい!
Iikagen ni shinasai!
Now get reasonable!
飛んでったあいつの火照る体って
Tondetta aitsu no hoteru karadatte
The burning body of who flied away right now is...
いわゆる普通の女の子
Iwayuru futsuu no onna no ko
what is called a "usual girl".
驚いた、
Odoroita,
I'm surprised,
あたしだけ豚骨針金おかわりダー!!!!
atashi dake tonkotsu harigane okawari daaー!!!!
Only I get an extra portion of tonkotsu with a needle insideー!!!!
ボンボン応援団
Bon-bon ouendan
Bon-bon cheering team.
Let's get cherry pie
Let's get cherry pie.
らんらーん　関係感
Ranraan　kankeikan
Blazing, relationship feeling,
you have センセーション
you have senseeshon
you have sensation.
ハーイ　存在感　点々　小惑星
Haai　Sonzaikan　tenten　shouwakusei
Yes, feeling of being here, here and there meteors.
ぶつかって溶けました　呆然　大いに歌ってシリンダー
Butsukatte tokemashita　bouzen　ooi ni utatte shirindaa
Got melt from the collision, dumbfounded singing a lot, "Cilinder!"
もっていけ、
Motte ike,
Take and go,
最後に笑っちゃうのはあたしのはず
Saigo ni waracchau no wa atashi no hazu
The last one laughing should be me,
セーラー服だからです
Seeraa fuku dakara desu
because it's a seeraa fuku.
結論
Ketsuron
Conclusion.
月曜日なのに
Getsuyoubi nanoni
Even if it's monday,
機嫌悪いのどうするよ
Kigen warui no dou suru yo
What will you do with that bad mood?
夏服がいいのです、かわいい
Natsufuku ga ii no desu, kawaii
The summer uniform is better, cute.
接近賛否それまでって躊躇だ　やーん
Sekkin sanbi, sore madette choucho da　yaーn
Yes and no for getting closer, until that it's undecided, yaan.
頑張って　張り切って
Ganbatte,　harikitte
Try your best, be on high,
ま、ダーリンダーリンプリーズ
Ma, daarin daarin puriizu
well darling darling please!
And so, this problem...
Shiraishi.
Huh? But I was just asked!?
Was that so?
Well, Izumi.
Izumi!
Un!
Eh? No, I haven't been sleeping.
But I haven't said anything yet.
Guh!
The Problem
With Motivation
Ah?
I forgot my English textbook!
Can't you go and borrow Kagami's? They already had English, didn't they?
Really, you're always so careless.
Thank you!
You should check the day before!
Ehe...
Tsukasa does forget quite a lot of things, now doesn't she?
Now that you mention it, Konata, you really don't forget things like textbooks, don't you?
It might be surprising to you, but I do take such things seriously.
I always leave my textbooks at school beforehand.
Oh, yes, it was like that.
But that's exactly taking it not seriously!
But if you leave your textbooks at school always, you can't review anything, now can you?
But I dont study at home.
Because you really don't take anything home before the day before the test...
But Konata is good at getting the points, right?
Yes...
Could that be why I always forget my homework?
If it's about you it's not about forgetting...
it's about not trying at all!
So, please, show your Modern Japanese homework for today's afternoon lesson.
Asking already?!
I've always thought about it, but you're in the same class...
so go ask Miyuki.
How should I put it...
Miyuki-san is a too good person, which makes it even harder to ask...
Do you understand this feeling?
I do somehow understand, but that's not satisfactory...
'Izumi.'
'Izumi!'
Oh, she's late?
Stop! I'm not late!
Ou.
I got a bit slown down as I was helping a person in trouble.
That person always moves around together with me, but I just couldn't leave him alone.
Hee...
He was nice to say things like 'I'm OK with it, so let's break up.', but the other five...
tn. She's already using a word that might be unusual, but...
already took pairs, leaving only him, so it leaves a bad aftertaste, now doesn't it?
...only now does it get so...
We've been in a party in a long time already, so at such time...
I said 'Let's all help him!'
Now friends are a great thing to have, aren't they?
Oh, was that so?
So you had an all-nighter in an internet game yesterday, again.
Huh...
It's already been an eternity after I fell out...
'Izumi.'
'Izumi!'
Oh, she's late?
STOP! I'm not late!
Ou...
A girl rushed into me before the shopping area...
That girl suddenly took my hand and started running...
And when asked she told me that she had stolen taiyaki,...
so it was natural of her to run.
I did think about why I had to be dragged into it, but...
tn. KEY's Kanon, anyone...
as I had no options, I entered a cafe in order to hide from the taiyaki seller...
There's so many places to intervene with 'uguu'...
tn. Ayu-neta, anyone?
But it would be wrong to do so...
As an educator, as a human...
Oww, got summer cold...
tn. 38.2 Celsius is 100.76 Fahrenheit, Americans...
Oh, Izumi...
What happened?
"Aww, sensei... I'm sorry but I'd like to take a sick leave"...
"Hey hey, did you overdo with games again?"
"Don't just try to use the same way every time!"
Oh, no... I'd like to call myself in sick...
"Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha!"
Gu...
"Now you wouldn't say something like summer cold, right?"
"The winter's gone and there's a good weather..."
"so don't just always say something like 'I'm lazy', come here fast!"
Huh?
And so, I got a full 'ookami shounen'- treatment yesterday.
tn. ookami shounen - the boy who cried wolf
Something you got on yourself by yourself.
Kona-chan, are you OK already?
It seems like my fever has gotten down, but...
my throat still stings...
Ah, so Kona-chan breaths through the nose.
Huh?
Oh...
Well, she does do that through the throat, too...
But don't you usually do it through the nose?
But, Kona-chan has a bigger rate of breathing through the throat,...
Hu...
Well, you know, when the cold virus gets into your throat you get throat cold...
and when it gets in through the nose you get nose cold, right?
And so people who get throat cold, like, have a bigger propability to get the virus through throat...
Aaaa... Aah...
ku...
At such times let's leave it to Miyuki to burst the bubble...
That's right...
Huh?
It's hot...
I don't want to do anything...
Ah, Kagami?
It's about the birthday party, but wouldn't you do it at my place?
It's so hot I can't take a step...
"Aww... But we're baking cookies here right now..."
I'll go.
Yeah, come fast.
Welcome!
'Happy Birthday!'
Tsukasa plus the other one.
Don't turn it around!
Congratulations on behalf of your birthday.
Kagami-san and Tsukasa-san.
Aah, thank you!
Thank you!
And...
This might not be of your liking, but...
as a present...
What could it be?
Please open them.
Aah...
Paired earrings!
I did think about a lot...
as I couldn't pretty much couldn't decide...
If so, I, too, will give my humble belongings...
Aaah...
What could it be?
Open and take a look.
What's this?
A Brigade Leader armband!
tn. Do I have to spell SOS-dan to you?
Try it on!
Why should I put something like this on myself?!
Wha... And I thought it would suit you perfectly'ga, Kagami...
And it looks like that to you!
Well, this is...
ToHeart?!
tn. ToHeart - a passion of mine; At Cospa those cost 31,290 yen
Oh, that was expensive...
Wear it with love.
Don't arrange sisters and make them do cosplay!
Well, I don't really think that it differs from the ones at our school...
Ah, that's troublesome. When it just is too big.
Yeah, you just get annoyed. Like with the smelly ones.
Hey! It's someone's birthday so try to restrain yourself for just even a bit.
The cookies that Tsukasa made are delicious, after all...
Oh,
this time I was making them with her...
Aah...tsk!
while learning.
Hey, what happened?
It's really weird that after I heard that there's a feeling that some of these are not so delicious...
What did you say?!
This might be Kagami's...
Because you're here, come on and eat some cake.
Only on her birthday did I meet the devotedly working Kagami.
That's annoying.
By the way, don't you just fuss about how to cut the cake?
Huh? Why?
You know, when you cut it into many pieces...
there are the things like 'Who will eat the strawberry on the top?'...
or 'Who will eat the plate chocolate?'
Yeah, you all like plate.
Ehehe...
Uwa!
Oh no, I cut off the point.
You don't really think it's Kagami's...
What isn't?!
Itadakimasu!
Itadakimasu.
Fuwaah...
Hm... What is it?
My strawberry's pretty small...
Hehe...
Oh what is it? Do I have cake on my face?
I only got once more affirmed of Kagami's charm-dazo.
tn. a reference to a popular manga/anime Crayon Shin-Chan
You seriously resemble him, so just stop it.
It's almost summer vacation this year, too.
You're right.
The sea, the pool, the summer festival...
were there any other standard events?
Pitta.
When you speak of summer, the festival that is held two times per year...
The longest rise of the night sun!
Even if I say so...
It's the comike!
tn. Comike - Comic Market, a twice-in-a-year event at the Makuhari Messe
No, no, no... That's only you...
"The red hair?"
We-well...
There could be different events for different people.
Existing and, you know...
Good morning!
Miyuki, do you have any plans for the summer vacation?
Well, let's see...
For the moment we have plans to go abroad again this year.
Gah, 'Again this year'?
Did she have the cash, this bourgeois of-a-kind!?
Is it a yoghurt?
tn. There is a yoghurt brand called Bulgaria's yoghurt in Japan, this is a pun.
You did say that you started working at a costume cafe, but...
aren't such places impossible to get into if you haven't got good looks?
Well, I, too, always had a thing with the fact I had no breasts...
until there was a game, in which it was said that: 'Flat chest is a status item!', 'A thing of Great Value!'
tn. the game is SHUFFLE
Flat
chest
is a
status
item
!
A thing
of
Great Value!
Yes. When you think about it that way, there are such needs!
I'm something valuable!
"I'd like to know why games have such strong self-confidence..."
So I think that I'm OK, too.
Oh, with you... The end-of-term tests are almost here, are you OK with just playing games?
Uun...
If you'd turn that passion even a bit towards studies...
you'd get higher scores, too...
Ah...
"If she's so easily affected, then if some games that'd recommend studying would come out, it'd turn out pretty unbelievable..."
There's the Moe Drill, too...
tn. Mentioned game is the Raki*Suta Moe Doriru for the DS
Dotano?
Lately there are many crimes with young guys...
And those are like, when you ask someone in the neighborhood they all arrange their speeches:
"He was usually quiet and obedient... didn't seem to be a person who'd do such things.". that's what they say.
tn. Higurashi no Naku Koro ni...
Well, that's just how treacherous the appearance can be...
Ah...
If you'd cause some incident...
"I was sure sure she'd do something some day."
tn. Death Note...
I'd testify it like that.
Hun!?
Hmm...
It's so hot I just can't make myself do anything...
Hmm... Well, I do understand the feeling very well,...
but you're saying that you don't want to do anything the whole year!
Buhe!
Lucky Star!
Hn?
The Hiiragi Household
Hello, Kagami!
Ossu! Are you progressing with your test studies?
Hmm... I was cleaning my room right now...
"Huh?"
Well, you know, when you're starting something don't you just want to clean and stuff?
"Well, even though I understand the feeling, 'try your best'."]
Yes! Let's do even a bit today!
Fuaaaaaah...
I'll take a break for only 30 minutes...
I cannot keep my concentration...
Ah...
Oh, it's already such time...
For another 30 minutes, only 30 minutes...
Hmm...
Huwa!
Well, isn't it the time for Haruhi to start already?
Like that...
After all that Nagato's long talk could just be corner-cutting...
tn. Notice the 2ch.net forums on the background...
Eh... The YaXXXXXX nowadays is not that good...
tn. Yamamoto - director of many SHNY episodes
Hufu...
Muwaah!
Waaa, they're 'discussing' it already...
Aww, is it already two-o'-clock? This day was somehow not good.
I'll sleep a bit and study in the morning...
If I wake up at five...
I could sleep for three hours from now...
In the end I just wasted time on anime and manga and stuff...
That's very Kona-chan- like.
Now that you mention it, Konata's preference of manga and games is a bit weird...
You read a lot of shounen magazines and your main is gyaruge, right?
tn. Shounen - young boys / guys - here as 'smthng for XXX'; gyaruge - 'gal games', one way of saying 'bishoujo games', a type of 'eroge' - although 'gyaruge' are not always 'ero'
My father reads a lot of manga and plays games, so I'm influenced by that...
I was looking next to him from the days while I was small.
I can understand shounen magazines, but 'gyaruge' and 'bishoujyo-ge' before his own daughter...
what kind of a father is he?!
Ah, doesn't your mother say anything about both father and child being like that?
Ahh, well it's because there's no mother at our place...
Huh?
She passed away when I was really small...
Was that so...
Because of that I'm always doing chores, so I'm a lot better at them than Kagami!
Don't say unnecessary things when it's already hard enough to comment!
Tsukasa, too, is good at cooking, right?
I don't know how good I am at it, but I just love it!
What about Miyuki-san?
She seems rich, so she could be not so good with housework and stuff.
Eh? Cooking, you say?
To tell you the truth I only help from time to time,...
even though it's embarrassing, I'm not that good at housework...
Oo, so I was right!
Yeah. But Miyuki is just too good at other things, her levels are so different...
that you shouldn't take her minuses literally.
Hmm... oh well...
No... It's not like that...
Then what about our teacher?
She seems to live by herself, but has quite a lax image.
Hahaha!
Nowadays you can live somehow even without knowing how to cook!
We have conbini and stuff...
Huuuh....
As if!
I'm doing it properly!
I can gulp, you know.
"It'd be nice if you'd stop those too fitting jokes!"
tn. It's Kyon-style "...yamete itadakitai..."
Ah! Tsukasa still has my dictionary borrowed...
Tsukasa, I'm sorry but return my dictionary.
Just a bit of a room cleaning because of mood change...
You, too?!
Fuwaah...
Ossu! What happened?
Well we're all thinking about the new summer menu at the place I work...
Oh, so you have such?
Or, did you just give up about the tests?
What about super-spicy raamen? Hot stuff is the best for hot season!
tn. raamen - Japanese wheat noodles
Ehh... Try to think of a bit more cafe-like menu!
Well, what about super-spicy parfait?
Couldn't you just stop with those spinal reflex- ideas?
They just don't stand...
Oh why doesn't our school have swimming lessons even if it has a pool?
For me it's a bit helpful...
Why is that?
To tell you the truth, I just cannot open my eyes in water...
and I can't really swim... even though it is embarrassing...
"Your weak spots are always somehow not fair..."
Hn! Finally the Comp Festival has started!
Ahh, now that I think of it, because of this I started working part-time...
Festival, now is it... somehow it's been so long...
Why are you saying old jokes?
Well, when the customers join us and get the tension up,...
you just feel that you're arousing the overall feeling of the festival, now don't you?
That heat... Try to move it towards the school even for a bit...
I can't fall asleep... I should just read a book until I get sleepy.
I have one that I just bought, too...
Ah...
It's no longer the time to sleep - it's the morning...
And right now it feels like I could sleep well...
I do understand why you have to cut the power while near the priority seats, but...
the thing with pacemakers and...
Un...
Why is it basically not allowed to talk on phones in trains?
Isn't that because you'll annoy people that aren't talking with you?
Hmm, but you know...
Aren't there just people that have a loud voice even without phones...
towards both young and old?
Eh...
Well, that's so, but...
Do you do miko or something during the summer festival like when visiting the shrine for the first time?
tn. 'miko' - a maiden in the service of a Shinto shrine
Nope, we're always not doing it in the summer.
But now that you say about it it's almost that time...
Oh? Aren't you dieting now?
"Nope, it could be the fatigue from the studying, but after I weighted myself yesterday... I had lost weight!"
"So I'm beginning to think that it's OK already and stuff..."
Fast! Or should I say weak!?
Good morning!
Good morning, Kona-chan!
Ohh, Kagami - what is it?
Konata!
The weight...
It got back up in an instant...
It's because you carelessly eat snacks...
But, that's a 'senryuu'...
tn. 'senryuu' - A type of short literature derived from haiku, not restricted by haiku word types and consisting of 17 symbols
The weight...
It got
back up
in an
instant.
I ate just, just a bit...
Why do you get so fussed over a few kilos, even though...
it doesn't even get on your looks if you gain a kilo or two.
Huuh...
This is why them women are so...
If I remember right you should be a woman, too, though...
Lucky Star
LUCKY CHANNEL!
Good Lucky!
Starting on this week, Lucky Channel...
Have you all been energetic?
It's me, always on 120% of cheerfulness, Kogami Akira!
This ti...
Through a 'Nyoro-n', it's me - the assistant - Shiraishi Minoru!
tn. 'nyoron' - It's in the Wikipedia, LOL...
Hey!
Huh, was th...
Don't friggin' enter and interrupt!
A-Aahh... I'm sorry!
It's no 'Gaki no Tsukai', so come on - remember your job!
tn. 'Gaki no Tsukai' - a Japanese comedy show
Do you want to leave this job that badly?
Tsk tsk tsk tsk tsk tsk tsk tsk tsk...
A-Ah! I have no excuses, I will try my best, the very best I can!
And so, this time...
jya-jyaan!
There is a big announcement for you all again -desu!
Those who entered on Comp's November edition! Akira's 'get fashionable'- plan!
We got so much mail from you all so fast!
A... well, it feels that there was another plan like that in there, too...
Thank you for som much reply!
"At the comeback I'll do that, pii-!"
I feel that jokes from the eighties will not be really understood...
And so I will present you one of the ideas judged strictly!
And so...
And so the Akira's 'get fashionable'- plan from Sappishi Chirii-san, Saitama prefecture!
Well, Kagami-san's 'twin tail' looks very good on her, so...
wouldn't you try it, too, Akira-san?
Twin tail... That's so go...
Fuwaah! It's lovely!
That's right, long hair is the life of all women!
If you split it in two, it just gives you... this pretty feeling, you know...
Do it or not, with Akira-sama's hairlength that's not possible, not?!
But, you know, it's not that good to just make your hair long...
A-Akira-sama, we're almost there, almost...
it's really weigthy, plus it's really hard to lower them right...
we're almost there, so...
So to speak the truth it's not popular right now.
Men always easily say that they prefer women with long hair,...
Well, that's... the person inside...
but how much effort, labour and money do you think did it take to keep this style?
The talking of the person inside, it's not Akira-sama! Do you hear me?
And even if I do it this much, no-one ever marks it up...
Heey?
Huwaa! It's already the time to part!
How would Akira look if she'd do twin tails...
let's continue about that on the radio or on the site!
I'm counting on you!
Bye-bye-piii!
Please look foward for the next time...
What was with that attitude?
When you say about 'attitude'?
Snapping on all the time,...
did you get so worked up on the first comment about you?
No such thing, I was just thinking if people would understand noripii nowadays...
Huh?
Eh?
No, excuse me, let's go on a new style...
You know, they're, like doing Shiraishi Minoru auditions...
Yes?
Eh? Is that true?
But I heard that for the first time?!
It seems pretty funny.
Eh, I'm?!
Isn't that great?
To say the real me?!
Eh, what is?
Huh?
Kona-chan, you're unbelievable! You can sing anything!
Well, only anime songs, though...
You really sing well, using many impersonations.
The fast rule of anime songs is to trace the original version as well as possible.
Well, I should sing, too.
onee-chan, what will you sing?
The name just passed on the screen, but I didn't know it...
Eh? Miyuki, you don't know this one?
Yes...
Well, it seems like Kagami can't say so much...
Ah! I've heard this!
tn. The OP song 'Seeraa-fuku to kikanjyuu' from the 1982/2006 TV series and a 1981 movie
Well, you did watch the drama with me until recently.
Ah, was that so?
I somehow fancy the movie...
What are you, an old man?
さよならは別れの言葉じゃなくて
Sayonara wa wakare no kotoba jyanakute...
Oh! She's good!
Onee-chan is the best in singing within our sisters.
再び逢うまでの遠い約束
Futatabi au made no tooi yakusoku...
夢のいた場所に未練残しても
Yume no ita basho ni miren nokoshitemo...
心寒いだけさ
Kokoro samui dake sa...
このまま何時間でも
Kono mama nanjikan demo...
抱いていたいけど
daite itai kedo...
And so, the next Lucky Star is?
It's Miyuki. The 'Golden Week' is a society term, which got it's name from the increase of people entering movie theaters at this time.
Next Time: Famous Shooter.
Look forward to it.
This program was brought to you by Kadokawa Bookshops and the companies visible.