Now, let'ssu begin yoo!
It's gonna come now...
Fungaa!
Now start out already!
曖昧3センチ
Aimai 3 senchi
Unclear 3 centimeters...
そりゃぷにってことかい？ちょっ!
Sorya punitte koto kai? cho!
Is that a puni? Waitasec!
らっぴんぐが制服…
Rappingu ga seifuku…
The uniform's the wrapping…
だぁぁ不利ってことない　ぷ。
Daa furitte koto nai　Pu.
Hey, there's no disadvantage in that, yeah.
がんばっちゃ♥やっちゃっちゃ
Ganbaccha♥yacchaccha
Try your best♥do the thing-cha,
そんときゃーっち&Releaseぎョッ
son tokyaacchi & ririisu gyo
at that time, well, catch & release, gyo!
汗っ、々っ
A-se, a-se!
In the sweaty, sweaty...
の谷間にDarlin'darlin'F R E E Z E!!
No taniai ni daarin daarin furiiーzu!
valley darlin' darlin' FREEZE!!
なんかダるー、なんかデるー
NankaDAruuー, nankaDEruー
Somewhat lazy..., something's coming out...
あいしテるー
AishiTEruuー
I love you...
あれ一個が違ってるんるー
Are ikko ga chigatterunruー
One of those is different, ruー.
なやみン坊ー 高鉄棒 おいしん簿ー
NayamiNbouー Koutetsubou oishinboー
A worrywart, high horizontal bar - an ever-lengthening list...
いーかげんにシナサイ
Iikagen ni SHINASAI
Now get reasonable!
飛んでったアイツの火照るカラダって
Tondetta AITSU no hoteru KARADAtte
The burning body of who flied away right now is...
所謂ふつーのおにゃのコ
Iwayuru futsuu no onya no KO
what is called a "usual girl".
驚いた、
Odoroita,
I'm surprised,
あたしだけ? 豚骨ハリガネおかわりダー!!!!
atashi dake? tonkotsu harigane okawari daaー!!!!
Only me? I get an extra portion of tonkotsu with super hard noodlesー!!!!
BON-BONおーえん団
BON-BON oーendan
Bon-bon cheering team.
Let's get! Cherry pie
Let's get! Cherry pie.
RAN-RAN　かんげー会
Ranraan　kangeーikai
RAN-RAN, welcoming party.
Look up! せんせーしょん
Look up! Senseーshon
Look up! Sensation.
はい！　存在感・・小惑星
Haai　Sonzaikan　tenten　shouwakusei
Yes, feeling of being here・・meteor!
ぶつかって溶けました　呆然　大いに歌ってシレンジャー
Butsukatte tokemashita　bouzen　ooi ni utatte shirenjyaー
Got melt from the collision, dumbfounded and singing a lot, "Shiranger!"
もっていけ!
Motte ike!
Take and go!
最後に笑っちゃうのはあたしのはず
Saigo ni waracchau no wa atashi no hazu
The last one laughing should be me,
セーラーふくだからです
Seeraa fuku dakara desu
because it's a seeraa fuku.
←結論
←Ketsuron
←It's the conclusion.
月曜日なのに！
Getsuyoubi nanoni!
Even if it's monday!
機嫌悪いのどうするよ？
Kigen warui no dou suru yo？
What will you do with that bad mood?
夏服がいいのです←キャ？ワ！イイｖ
Natsufuku ga ii no desu←KYA?WA!IIv
I want my summer uniform←It!Is!Cute!
接近3ピクト するまでってちゅーちょだ　やん☆
Sekkin san pikuto, suru madette chuーcho da　yan☆
Getting closer's in three paces, I'll hesitate until you do 'it' Oh☆
頑張って　張り切って
Ganbatte,　harikitte
Try your best, be on high,
My Darlin'darlin' P L E A S E!!
Mai daarin daarin puriizu
my darlin' darlin' please!
It's been a while since we've worn uniforms, hasn't it.
Ah, It's Kona-chan!
Kona-chan, good morning!
Oh my... Kagami-san, Tsukasa-san...
Bless you. "Twinkle"
Uh... uhh...
My... Oh, Tsukasa-san, did you know that your ribbon is slightly askew?
Oah... Thank you...
...damn...
Konata-chan, what happened, all of a sudden?
Yes... Right now I have for some amount fallen into Marimite...
tn. Marimite - Maria-sama ga Miteru, an anime
Marimite?
What are you? A child?!
Hah hah hah...
The Image
Aah, hah hah hah...
You know, don't imitate things like that all the way to the outlook.
Eh... was it 'cosplay'?
I don't really do it so far.
I wonder if that's true...
It's because I already do that at my part-time job...
Ahh.. Now that you mention it, you were working at such place...
But Konata's milady- look is...
Ahh...
Huh?
"It feels too misplaced, I can't imagine it..."
Right now they're extending the baseball broadcasts too much.
Why are the viewers of new anime always OK with being pushed to sacrifice?
If you want to watch anime so badly, couldn't you just pull a cable?
There are special channels and stuff, right?
Fuh... That's if you can pull it...
I, too, want to pull it. But I was told a lot by the cable TV people, ending with "We can't pull it."...
Haah...
Yuki-chan, good morning!
Good morning, Tsukasa-san.
You look a bit dark, did something happen?
To tell you truth I went to treat my cavities,...
Ooh, so you went to the dentist's! Well done.
Why is it that if you once go to the dentist's, you have to go there many times afterwards?...
Aah, I understand that awfully well.
It has never ended with the first, second time when I've tried.
Miyuki-san, bless you.
Ah, Konata-san. How nice to meet you.
Has your life been as well as always?
Yes, I am fine. Above all things it is really pleasing to see that you, as well, are well.
"Ahh, Yuki-chan, as expected...
She doesn't feel out of place even though they're using the same compliments...
Or should I say that she doesn't have any doubts about her compliments?"
I just saw for the first time a person who used "Bless you." as a greeting!
Ehe, Is that so?
But at a girls' school my friend attends they seem to usually greet each other with "Bless you."...
Aah...
Real ladies' schools are different, they are elegant.
Kuroi told me "Gather the summer homework, and bring it here.", so...
Well done, Sebastian.
"Se... Seba..."
After all, Sebastian is a must if you talk about butlers.
Aah, there really is such an image!
You really say amusing things, Sebastian.
No, that's imposs...
Well, the holidays just ended, but you have no time to sit and daydream!
The plans for the
second semester
It's about time to think about the future, to put effort in your studies.
"About the future" is about moving forward, isn't it?
Certainly the high school life, too, is something I have already grasped...
But you, Kagami, haven't thought about the future very well, haven't you?
Huh? Why'd that be? That's rude!
After all, you wanted to be in the same group as we so hard that you selected social sciences, right?
Ts-Tsukasa! You told her!
Ahh, I'm sorry...
Moreover, of all people, to her!
Well, you should've said it out straight, because you're so easily lonesome...
Ah, there there...
Ah! Annoying!
Yahhoo! I came by again!
Aah... Neesan...
When I gave out the summer homework that I did as you told me by writing something that seemed like the right thing...
I got the lowest grade!
Help me...
I... It's OK,...
but... if you listen to me,
you might get into the lowest group again, in many ways...
"Ran away..."
It's unfair that even though the summer vacation doesn't get extended, the homework does...
Maybe I should borrow Kagami's notebook, after all?
Hngh!
The sound of cicadas in their death throes is like an archaic sleep song...
Ah!
Uhh...
Huh?
Oh...
Yeh...
Huuh...
Ah, like that...
So it got moved because of the extension of the baseball broadcast...
Hmm... So there sometimes are good things, too...
Ah! The recording's off synch!
Ah!
Yuki-chan, what about your glasses?
That is... They broke this morning...
I got careless pretty fast after I forgot that I left them on a chair...
I'm sorry, but can I borrow your notes for today afterwards?
Yeah, it's OK.
Still the same clumsy girl as always...
Uhh... Konata-san, your letters are mysterious...
Konata's notebook
The letters are so dirty
they can't be read normally
Un...
Tsukasa's notebook
Tsukasa-san, fight!
The letters are
too well done
and the text isn't
written to the end.
Those two really are good for nothing...
Here.
Thank you very much.
You got lucky that the teachers in charge are the same.
Err... But, can you please keep this confidential...
As it would turn out like throwing water on their friendliness they can rarely show...
Uh...
I'm starving!
Yuki-chan, let's eat our obentou
Ah, Tsukasa-san, Konata-san. Thank you very much for the notebooks.
No, no, I'm only doing what little I can.
But I thought that there woud be no such thing as me lending a textbook to Yuki-chan...
Well, I think there'll be no more.
Aha-hum... mmm-mm...
Dyuuuu.....
Ah... Is there something on my face...?
In games it's usual that when a glasses character goes to school without them, she suddenly becomes popular...
but in reality it there's no such thing.
No, there sure isn't, regrettably...
A choco cornet really looks like a drill, doesn't it?
Etto...
A drill...
Ah, now that you mention it, we earlier talked about which is the head of a choco cornet, didn't we?
Like that the thin side looks like butt...
Hmm... Now that I think about it again, the thicker side seems to be more buttocks-like...
Buttocks?
Uwah, below-the-waist fatness... Moreover a tan-belly!
tn. Tan - a Japanese measurement unit - 10.91 meters
When you gain weight below the weist, you really have a problem when you're buying a skirt or something.
That's right, when you fit it to the waist your hips won't fit...
and when the hip's just right the waist is really loose.
And when you buy one with a bigger waist as there is no other alternative, the skirt will just go around and around while you walk.
That's right!
The cornet figure of a tan-belly...
When you put it on the side it becomes a figure that's lying down...
When it's lying down it's even better...
A cornet figure...
The timing for laughing isn't understood!
Oneechan, didn't you diet and put off the summer kilos?
Ahh, but even if you lose weight, the waist and the hip really don't change, don't they...
No, Kagami. The results of the diet are seen to me.
Eh, is that so?
Yeah, as if I could touch it.
Huh?
There seems to be a tradition that says that you start losing weight from places you don't have to lose weight from when you diet...
It's enough! Don't say that in front of everyone!
The trick with reading a text is to sense the theme,...
to understand what the writer was meaning...
I see・・・
I heard that people with bad vision tend to get scared when they lose their vision, but maybe that...
depends on the person after all...
Hey! What's that?!
When you now said "depends on the person", you turned your eyes here, didn't you?
I have heard that you look like a beauty when you narrow your eyes.
They say that it feels like you're entroubled when you do it.
Ah...
Unn...
Hey, don't do it!
She's late... What's that Konata doing?
Ah, she came!
I'm sorry! I got slowed down...
You're late! What are you, always complaining about the night game extensions, doing, being loose about the time?!
Ohh... Look, recently they're really always extending them, so...
Ah, maybe even I caught it?
They don't!
So, why did you come late?
You overslept?
No, no... I'm not a child no more...
So try to say an adult reason for being late.
Well, you know...
After I had prepared to leave the house I did still have a lot of time...
but when I started playing a game to pass time, there was no end...
That's the worst, you're lower than a child!
Now that you mention it, there's a lot of events for the cultural festival and the sports festival in the second semester, right?
The tests are soon, too.
You, Kona-chan, are so lucky being good at sports, being able to shine at the sports festival...
You get tired during the sports festival, so I don't like it.
Such opposition to physical labour is rare, too...
I wonder what our class'll do for at the culture festival?
It's not like we'd like to do something, though...
Things like this just don't seem to get decided if there's no-one to say "I'd like to do this."
And no-one really says it as they'd have to do it first...
And you'd have to stay after school, do the preparations...
And you would miss the evening anime, too...
So it's that, after all!
Lucky Star!
Today I'm in charge of the cooking, so I'll have to go 'round to shop!
Hee, what are you planning to do?
Something that everyone loves - chicken curry!
Because all of us like bird meat.
Curry? Now that's good!
They do say that if you let it sleep for a night the curry becomes even more delicious.
So they do...
So should I make a bit more than usually and put it into tomorrow's bentou?
As it'll be left over, anyways...
"Yes, it's the Hiiragis."
Ah, Tsukasa...
"Ah, Kona-chan! What happened, why a morning call?"
Uh... You know, the curry...
"The curry?"
After I left the curry I made yesterday for a night, it went bad...
"Uwah! No way!"
It's true...
"Why? Usually curry doesn't go bad within one day?!"
Right...
"Did you add something weird in it?"
Nope, but it had mold in it this morning...
And, so it's cornet today, too?
But it's good as it's tasty.
If you're good with that, well...
Now that you mention it, I just noticed that Tsukasa's and Kagami's obentou ...
Mini hamburg
Fried eggs
Bacon saute with
peas and onion
Mixed fried asparagus and
carrots, etc.
When it's neat.
are really clearly divided to ones that have the food put in neatly and to the ones that have it put in simplisticly...
Fried salmon
Okra
(just cut)
pickled
vegetables
only that...
When it's really simplistic.
They're clearly different.
It's because we're making bentou on turns...
Mmm?
I'm not that good at housework, so it just ends up simple...
Sorry about that, being simplistic!
What? Is Kagami the type to blow up pots and stuff when she cooks?!
There's no-one like that!
Aah, Yuki-chan's bentou is so appetizing today, too!
It's not that... I just picked up the leftovers from yesterday.
Haa...
So the evening meal at Miyuki's place...
is so glorious...
Moreover, this is what's left over...
Uh, what's this inside the fried eggs?
Ah, yesterday there was some eel left over, so I tried to put that into it.
Aah...
Usually eel doesn't get left over, right?
At our place even if it did it'd just be another mold-curry...
It's not like we're thinking that your place is "usual"!
Morning!
Ossu!
Look, look! I had a cell phone bought to me!
Ah, you got lucky...
It's because I got exceptionally good scores on my achievement test.
Tell me your number, I'll tell you mine, too.
Uhn, I wonder what number it was...
Well...
Ahh... Just wait a bit...
Eetto...
Konata, so you did have a phone!
Yeah, but I pretty much forget it at home.
It's not like anyone else would call me than dad...
That really kills the reason to have one, right?
Is that so?
Keroro!
Isn't he cute?
I had him bought to me with the phone!
Now that you mention it, there was a girl in our class that had all those straps on her phone...
They said that when she weighted it, it ended up 800 grams with only the straps.
Ahh, so much!?
That feels heavy!
After taking off all those straps she said that her stiff neck became better.
Like that it feels like it'd become muscle training with only talking to someone.
The cell phone just makes your heart beat as you never know when someone's going to call, doesn't it?
Is that so?
I wonder if someone'd call me soon?
Don't get so happy today with just a cell phone!
By the way, did the number show up?
Aah, it's still...
In England, due to the Lancaster and York families a large contesting battle had begun...
At both families it was customary to keep a red or a black rose, respectively, while fighting, which is why this war is now called "The War of The Roses".
This was between the years 1455 and 1485...
This...
Huh?
Ah!
Ah! It's me! It's my phone!
Waah, finally, someone called...
Waaah!
Whew...
Huh? Who's that?
Theere! Forfeited!
Aaahhh...!
Come to the teacher's room after school to get it back.
Luckyy! I got it given back!
But I would have not thought that a spam mail would've come so suddenly...
Ah...
Ah, daddy?
No, I'm still at school. It got late as I was talking with Konata and Miyuki...
Yeah, it's OK, as I'm coming home soon. Bye bye.
If you're even a bit out late, this comes...
Wah!
Yes?
Ah, daddy!
No, I'm still at school. I'm together with Kona-chan and all now.
Yeah!
I think I'd understand if I'd call one of the twins...
Fathers are always worrying about their daughters, you know.
Lately it's so annoying, with so much spam.
Aah, if you get them you should change your address to something hardly guessable.
I'm changing it, too.
To a hardly guessable?
Like how?
My e-mail is "Enraged love between glasses girls" in roman characters.
tn. "meganekkogekirabu" or "meganekkogekilove"
Huh?!
I would've liked to change it to "maid" or something, but maids and miko have popularity, they're taken f...
Wait a second! We got it, so don't speak with such a loud voice in front of the public!
Your talk means trouble to the mail administrator!
Eheehe...
Good morning!
Ossu!
Uhh...
What happened, Tsukasa?
My phone... my cell phone...
While in the pocket to the...
So... it passed away...
Ahaahu...
I wonder if I won't get another any more...
Ah! So this guy got out unharmed!
An obstinate guy, isn't he...
Ah, so the mail yesterday night...
The mail that Kagami had said that I hadn't given back the homework notebook...
Was that the last mail?
Yes, it was. Could it be that you answered?
Uhn... Well...
You don't answer back that fast even if you get mail, right?
That's because I'm actively not answering mails to people I can talk to any time...
Answer to mails with mail!
I thought there was no need to reply since we meet every day...
You'll be losing your friends!
Oh well, well, it's not like it was something that was in a hurry...
Don't decide that by yourself!
Ahh, so I didn't get my notebook back, after all...
Tsukasa, I'll be coming in!
Ah, oneechan!
Wah!
W-what happened?
I was so touched by the manga Kona-chan lent me that I cried...
Morning! Kona-chan, thanks for the manga!
It was interesting!
You really laughed at the foolishness, right?
Huh? But I got touched and cried...
A big enough difference in response to think that it's not the same manga...
Here. If you cry, you're the same as Tsukasa. If you laugh, you're the same as me.
I won't read it! As I don't want to be classified on either side.
But I'd like to see it, oneechan's response...
Is it wrong to wish to know more about your own friend?
Uh... So, do you laugh, cry at Attack Number WAN! ?
Laugh
Cry!
And your favourite manga is...
Sgt. Frog!
Ha...
These two either look alike or do not...
Kona-chan, aren't you in the manga workshop? You seem to like manga, and all...
Well, it'd be OK to get into it, though...
They'd seem to understand the times, too...
Drawy drawy drawy...
Is this a seriously drawn one?!
Oh yeah...
By the way, Konata-san, what is it that is drawn here?
This is Tsukasa!
Ah! So this was me!
This is Miyuki-san!
Well, I do understand the overall image with stars...
This is Kagami...
Oh! I'm spouting fire!
Oh my, Kagami-san was a person like her image, wasn't she... A girl to be afraid of!
I told you not to do that any more!
Ah, FMP's getting a new book!
Ah! Now that you mention it, Comp's on sale today, too!
I'll go through GAMERS, won't you go along?
Ahh... I'm sorry. I'll go with the local book shop today. I have plans, too.
Now isn't this the time to go together with me in order to move forward in our friendship?
What's that, today with different colors... All in all the word "friendship" really doesn't suit you...
No, well, look, I just wanted everyone's shopping points as a proof of friendship...
Soon she will get her hands on...
what she wanted
"Oh... So you did wait for me after all..."
So that is your friendship... a cheap one...
Lucky Star!
"It's quiet"
"Could she be angry about mixing the ribbons on the twintails with sunflowers..."
"Ah... Ah... I'll?"
"Eh?"
"Ah-ha..."
"Eh, I will?"
"...to Akira-sama? Is that OK?"
"Ah... Understood..."
Well...
It-it's rolling already...
"It's no good! Before the channel is changed!..."
O...
G-good Luckyy!
Somehow I wanted to say that!
Here you are, Lucky Channel has started this week, as well. It's me, Shiraishi Minoru!
Akira-sama's on a bad mood, s...
Hngh!
Bringing his own name on before Kogami Akira's... Don't you know the word "pecking order"?
Ahh, No! I had no...
Hngh!
It seems like you're getting unuseful popularity here & there lately with those twintails...
Popular... But I have...
Don't you get too carried away!
I have no excuse!
From the beginning everyone was expecting my twintails at the "Akira-sama stylification plan", right?
And what do you...
It is as you say...
Hm...
I'll put you twin-drills!
Twin-drills?!
"Do not tread lightly the speed of a Getter."
The second unit? The age of twin tails is over!
The next coming are twin-drills!
In the second episode Konata did say "Drills are men's romance", right?
Romance, now is it?
And so, everyone, the continuation of this will be on the radio and on the home page!
Please look forward for the next time, too...
Bye-nii!
You know, that twin tail...
Ah, the ones I did?
Yeah, the ones you did live...
Yes?
You had sunflowers in them, right?
Yes, I did.
It feels like I've seen them somewhere...
Eh, that wouldn't be...
How many years ago was it? My...
Please wait for a moment! Gerogero, gerogero!
Huh?!
Ah... I was nervous...
It was good, really cute.
You just get nervous over the first song you sing, right?
If the voice'll come out properly...
The next is Miyuki, right?
I'd like you to sing "Omoide ga ippai"...
Why'd that be?
Ah, can I have the microphone?
Here, try your best!
Uh, this is not really something I am used to, so if there are any things that are hard to listen to, please forgive me...
It's OK, try your best!
Ahhh, low-keyed...
Now I understand, it's that Miyuki- connection...
風の中のすばる・・・
Kaze no naka no subaru...
The Pleiades in the wind...
Ohh, the singing style is low-keyed, too...
砂の中の銀河・・・
Suna no naka no ginga・・・
The galaxies in the sand...
Certainly a new form of "moe"...
Yuki-chan, you're so cool!
みんな何処へ行った
Minna doko he itta
Where did they all go?
見送られることもなく・・・
Miokurareru koto mo naku...
Without even bidding farewell...
草原のペガサス・・・
Sougen no pegasasu・・・
The Pegasus of those grasslands...
街角のヴィーナス・・・
Machikado no viinasu...
The Venus of a street corner...
みんな何処へ行った・・・
Minna doko he itta...
Where did they all go?
見守られることもなく
Mimamorareru koto mo naku
Without even looking after me...
地上にある星を誰も覚えていない・・・
Chijyou ni aru hoshi wo daremo oboete inai...
No-one remembers the star above our ground...
人は空ばかり見てる・・・
Hito wa sora bakari miteru...
People are merely looking at the sky...
And so, the next Lucky Star is?
It's me, Tsukasa.
Is it already time?!
Next Time: "With Vitality, Even If It's Not Me"
Look forward to it!