Yoshimizu Kagami
Theatre
Now, let'ssu begin yoo!
It's gonna come now...
Fungaa!
Now start out already!
曖昧3センチ
Aimai 3 senchi
Unclear 3 centimeters...
そりゃぷにってことかい？ちょっ!
Sorya punitte koto kai? cho!
Is that a puni? Waitasec!
らっぴんぐが制服…
Rappingu ga seifuku…
The uniform's the wrapping…
だぁぁ不利ってことない　ぷ。
Daa furitte koto nai　Pu.
Hey, there's no disadvantage in that, yeah.
がんばっちゃ♥やっちゃっちゃ
Ganbaccha♥yacchaccha
Try your best♥do your thing-cha,
そんときゃーっち&Releaseぎョッ
son tokyaacchi & ririisu gyo
at that time, well, catch & release, gyo!
汗っ、々っ
A-se, a-se!
In the sweaty, sweaty...
の谷間にDarlin'darlin'F R E E Z E!!
No taniai ni daarin daarin furiiーzu!
cleavage darlin' darlin' FREEZE!!
Fan        subs
E
J
B
E
なんかダるー、なんかデるー
NankaDAruuー, nankaDEruー
Somewhat lazy..., something's coming out...
あいしテるー
AishiTEruuー
I love you...
あれ一個が違ってるんるー
Are ikko ga chigatterunruー
One of those is different, ruー.
なやみン坊ー 高鉄棒 おいしん簿ー
NayamiNbouー Koutetsubou oishinboー
A worrywart, high horizontal bar - an ever-lengthening list...
いーかげんにシナサイ
Iikagen ni SHINASAI
Now get reasonable!
飛んでったアイツの火照るカラダって
Tondetta AITSU no hoteru KARADAtte
The burning body of who flied away right now is...
所謂ふつーのおにゃのコ
Iwayuru futsuu no onya no KO
what is called a "usual girl".
驚いた、
Odoroita,
I'm surprised,
あたしだけ? 豚骨ハリガネおかわりダー!!!!
atashi dake? tonkotsu harigane okawari daaー!!!!
Only me? I get an extra portion of tonkotsu with super hard noodlesー!!!!
BON-BONおーえん団
BON-BON oーendan
Bon-bon cheering team.
Let's get! Cherry pie
Let's get! Cherry pie.
RAN-RAN　かんげー会
Ranraan　kangeーikai
RAN-RAN, welcoming party.
Look up! せんせーしょん
Look up! Senseーshon
Look up! Sensation.
はい！　存在感・・小惑星
Haai　Sonzaikan　tenten　shouwakusei
Yes, feeling of being here ・・ meteor!
ぶつかって溶けました　呆然　大いに歌ってシレンジャー
Butsukatte tokemashita　bouzen　ooi ni utatte shirenjaー
Got melted by the collision, dumbfounded and singing a lot, "Shiranger!"
もっていけ!
Motte ike!
Take and go!
最後に笑っちゃうのはあたしのはず
Saigo ni waracchau no wa atashi no hazu
The last one laughing should be me,
セーラーふくだからです
Seeraa fuku dakara desu
because it's a sailor fuku.
←結論
←Ketsuron
←Conclusion.
月曜日なのに！
Getsuyoubi nanoni!
Even if it's Monday!
機嫌悪いのどうするよ？
Kigen warui no dou suru yo？
What will you do with that bad mood?
夏服がいいのです←キャ？ワ！イイｖ
Natsufuku ga ii no desu←KYA?WA!IIv
I want my summer uniform←It?Is!Cute!
接近3ピクト するまでってちゅーちょだ　やん☆
Sekkin san pikuto, suru madette chuーcho da　yan☆
Getting closer's in three paces, I'll hesitate until you do 'it' Oh☆
頑張って　張り切って
Ganbatte,　harikitte
Try your best, be on high,
My Darlin'darlin' P L E A S E!!
Mai daarin daarin puriizu
my darlin' darlin' please!
Yutaka, we'll be going soon!
Here we go...
Here it is, my younger sister!
Your new life starts from today!
Let's go with full power!
Under One Roof
We're here to report on Yutaka's passing, and to say hello!
Ah!
Welcome!
Well, Yutaka!
F-From now on I think I will trouble you greatly in various ways...
But somehow, please, treat me well!
You may make yourself at home.
Y-Yes...
Firstly, congratulations on passing.
Thank you...
I'm really glad that she passed!
Thus you can meet with that handkerchief girl again, right?
My life...is on the winner's side, isn't it...?
Yeah!
Going back in time,
the day of Yutaka's
entrance exam.
Uh... Are you alright?
Should we go to the sick room together?
Right after
the entrance exam.
And so she talked to me...
and even lent me her handkerchief!
I'm so happy, as I think I could become good friends with her!
However, Yutaka, that person might have failed...
That can't be so!
People like her certainly pass!
I do understand the feeling, but...
She must be intelligent, too!
Thanks for that unsubstantiated objection.
But you know, Yuu-chan...
Yuu-chan, what will you do if you fail?
Gyuu... There's always that possibility...
Ah...
Well, in your case it'll probably be OK.
That's right!
On the day of the announcement I might be able to meet her, regardless of the results.
I see...
I have to return her handkerchief, too...
Announcement of the results:
We will inform you via mail, regardless of the result's type.
And so,
the day of the enrollment
explanation meeting and
uniform measurement.
E-Excuse me...
This...
I'm glad I could meet you...
I've thought about giving it back all this time...
...About returning this?
Yes...
On the contrary, maybe it was a bad idea...
as I didn't think we'd meet again,
my intention was to give this to you...
You thought something like I'd fail?
No...
That's right...
The fact that we're both here now...means that we're in the same grade?
I'm sorry...
Ah...
So I looked like a relative of an examinee...
As I'm going by our family car today...
A-All right...
Well, until here...
Well... For the next three years, please treat me well!
I'm so glad, already befriending such a good person at high school...
I didn't ask her name!
When you meet her next time, properly ask for her name.
Returning in time.
The present.
Right!
Ah.
Yuu-chan, are you possibly feeling sick?
Y-Yeah.
I seem to have gotten a bit sick in the car...
I did take the medicine, but...
I'm sorry for worrying you...
Since Yutaka's body really is weak...
No, that's true as well, but at least become a bit aware of your driving habits, neesan...
I'll stroke you
a bit.
Thanks.
Even I get it a bit...
But I'm the only one from my old junior high school going to Ryouou...
And I easily lose my strength, like today.
So I'm worried if I can adapt to the class...
Yutaka is a good girl, so it's all right!
Hmph...!
Treating me as if I were a child!
Ah...
Weak constitution
The thing for
little sisters
A peculiar change...
Pure
Cute
A walking
moe element
If Yuu-chan were paired with our Miyuki-san, it'd be a sight to behold.
Hm?
Ah, that's right.
I'm already in Konata-oneechan's house...
Oneechan, good morning!
Even though it's a day off, you're up so early...
Oh?
Morning!
Or should I say that I'll go to sleep after this...
Playing a net game as an all-night....
The surroundings really did change, didn't they?
So we'll have exams next year, too, huh?
Lately, we've been troubled by many phone calls about cram schools and teaching materials.
If you'd put on the number display function, I heard you could easily recognize such phone calls.
As things of such kind seem to be without displayed number...
I'm home!
Number display, now is it...
I have just come back!
Oh my, is that so?
That must've been really terrible...
No, no - it is like that at our place as well.
Yes, yes...
And now my daughter has come back as well, so...
Yes, then at a later time...
Please forgive me...
From whom was it?
It did seem that the conversation was lively...
It was an advertising phone call.
Uhm, didn't I tell you that you can immediately recognize such calls?
Yes, but you know...
As I had some free time, I just wanted to talk...
I ended up talking for more than an hour...
With two items the amount would be...
What national conquest!?
What happened, Kona-chan?
Ah!
Tsukasa, this world is at constant war!
There's no mercy!
The other day there was this point exchange premium that I slightly wanted...
Should I exchange here...
I was severely troubled to attack or to guard and finally had them exchanged, but...
...No-no, but...
there are other things I want...
OK!
I'll attack here!
But now there's another premium that's been released and it's one I really want!
Look! Over there!
My points don't suffice anymore!
What should I do!?
You really are enjoying life, aren't you...?
Err... The bill...
A nonsmoker or a smoker seat, which would you like?
Well, we are still underage, so, a nonsmoking one, please.
Well, this way, please.
Ah, I'll go to the toilet first.
OK.
Ah!
Hey, Tsukasa!
Over here!
Welcome back.
I've arrived.
Well, you know...
I always wonder about it,
but why is it that the toilet is often on the smoker's side in places like this?
That's right...
Even though we bothered going to the nonsmoking seats...
Hmm... But I really wonder why...
That's because it's good when there's a water resource close by when a small fire or something begins.
As there are buckets and hoses and stuff there.
So there even are hoses and stuff?!
There are!
Of course there are!
Heh... this is why, those who haven't contributed to the society with labour are problematic.
You're annoying!
Like "to cover up something".
tn: "Put a lid on the smelly things."
Or should I say that this topic should be dropped during meals - "smelly things", "toilets" and the like.
Today the incidents of elementary school girls...
in the Tôkyô Metropolitan area being called by someone...
from behind on their way to school have continued...
Recently incidents involving children being targeted have increased,
The board of education has passed warning materials...
haven't they?
to every elementary school.
Yuu-chan, you'll have to watch out, too...
The police are investigating the connection to...
Yeah, that's right...
Outrageous!
Well, I can't say I don't understand the feeling...
So you do end up understanding it...
Even though they're brought up as a big problem every day like now...
The fact that there still are people who call out unknown children is deplorable!
I'd like to say one thing to them!
"I bet you're envious!"
I don't really understand what you're thinking about,
but just stay away from things that'll leave you to be caught by Yui-neesan.
Hm?
This is a free softsub.Not for sale, rent, auction or hardsub.
Not for sale, rent, auction or hardsub.This is a free softsub.
or hardsub.This is a free softsub. Not for sale, rent, auction
Pardon the intrusion!
OK~
Yahoo~ I came!
Welcome!
Come to think of it, where's Kagami today?
She's out with a friend from her class.
Is that so...?
Somehow... It's a bit regrettable or like a feeling of unsatisfactory...
It's lonely, isn't it...?
Lately it has gotten warmer, hasn't it...?
Yeah, that's right.
It's really peaceful during the spring vacation, as there is no homework...
That's right~
Although I think that such a line is to be said by a person who puts effort into their homework, right?
Don't hit weird places!
O-Okama!
You know, do you understand the characters and stuff when you're playing robot games like this?
Yeah, to a certain degree.
Hmm... Is that so...?
Your interest in manga and games was influenced by your dad, didn't you say so?
Konata, oniichan burnt up and turned into nice pretty white ash.
Yeah-yeah.
Well, then...
Could it be that you couldn't keep up with the talk of your girlfriends when you were a child?
Huh? Why is that?
Since I rather had more chances to look at that side, I could keep up well...
Eh...
Ah...
Was that so...?
Huh?
Final Answer?
Yeah! Final Answer!
What a pause like that... My breath gets blocked...
The face is scary and big as well.
Ah...
At this time the question was no good.
It's already the end, too.
Hey, Tsukasa!
Would you stop drawing conclusions about whether the answer's right or wrong...
based on the remaining time from the beginning of the commercials?
Ehehe...
But I can't bear the suspense...
It's also awfully drawn out...
But isn't that the entire thrill of program?!
But it surely is Tsukasa-like, though.
Ossu!
Yahoo!
I'll be introducing you.
This girl is my cousin Yuu-chan.
I-I'm glad to meet you, I am Kobayakawa Yutaka.
My friends - Tsukasa and Kagami!
Ah, so you two are those who oneechan often mentions...
Eh... I wonder what she's been saying...?
Uh...
You!
How are telling her?
Although I can guess, simply by judging by her expression!
See, it was like I told you, wasn't it?
Yutaka-chan, did your graduation ceremony end already?
Ah... Yes, the other day.
Graduation ceremony, now is it...
How nostalgic, isn't it...?
I don't remember graduation ceremonies at all...
Yutaka-chan, did you get the second button from someone or something like that?
tn: It's customary for girls to get the second button of their school uniform during graduation from the guy they like.
Oh no, there's was nothing like that.
As my junior high had a blazer...
Now that you mention it, there are now quite a few of those schools.
Or should I say that people might not comply with "receiving something from your crush" traditions any more?
Is that the only reason?
That's a bit lonesome and depressing.
Although I haven't done it...
When you look at blogs and stuff on the net, it seems like they're more or less still doing it.
Hee...?
But, you know, it's about getting the one from the person you like, right?
Well, isn't it pretty much like that?
Well, it's like basically confessing your love when you go to take it...
So isn't it just better to properly confess and get the said person than to have a button?
GET YOU!
Well, if you say it's the ideal, I agree with it.
That's right!
Yutaka-chan, didn't you have a person you liked?
Eh...
No, no...
I often was absent from school, and even if I went there I'd get sick soon...
As I lower the tension of the people around...
Besides, I'm short and my figure is childlike, too...
I was always made fun of...
There's no way I'd come to like someone or for them to like me...
It's all right!
If you don't select a partner, you'll have sure demand!
"D-Demand"!?
Pocky!
tn: from "pokin" - to snap, also a reference to Pocky
Yuu-chan, show us your graduation album!
Ah, I'd love to see your graduation album as well!
It's somewhat embarassing...
I'm hardly seen as well...
What class were you in, Yuu-chan?
So now you've decided ask that after you've taken a look at the round absentees section, right?!
Ah, so you figured it out?
Eh? The differences between junior high and high school?
Yeah.
Hmm...
There's the fact that you don't have to enter a club...
Doesn't that depend on the school?
Our school is one that focuses on preparation for university,
so the studies probably have a wider content and are faster if compared to junior high school.
Also, it'll take some time to commute to school, so you might have to use some strength.
The decisively different thing is that, as you go from elementary to junior high and high schools, the time for dozing gets longer!
Especially during the lessons you are weak in!
Ah, that might be so!
Teacher's words end up sounding like some foreign language, and when it becomes like that, your consciousness just slips away...!
Take extra caution to avoid turning out like that.
Ah... OK.
Ah, Yuu-chan, so you brought your junior high uniform!
Yeah.
Our uniform's pretty inconspicious, so I thought that I could wear it casually.
This isn't not my local area here either.
I see.
What did you two do with your uniforms?
We gave them to younger girls from the neighborhood.
What about you?
Mine?
Well, but I guess yours weren't taken, right...?
How annoying...!
How impolite...!
Mine are, similar to Yuu-chan's, properly kept for cosplay usage.
C-Cos...
When you say it like that, an unpleasant feeling arises...
But isn't it cosplay?
Even if you say so...it's the old school...
When you reflect like this...you just begin to want to go to your old elementary or junior high school to show yourself after a while.
But lately there are many tresspassing and intrusion incidents,
so it wouldn't be nice if you're wrongly mistaken and looked at suspiciously...
Well, I think that in your case it would be OK, even without worrying like that.
Why do I get the feeling that you're not flattering me...?
Anyway, holidays go by so fast, don't they?
Yeah, that's true.
When you realize, it's already right before school.
During the spring there are body measurements, physical fitness tests and all that which is really bothering...
But Kona-chan, you're lucky, since you've got good motoric nerves.
Hey, Tsukasa...
What kind of a nerve is a motoric nerve?
Hello everyone!
I came a bit late, but Yutaka - congratulations on graduating!
Ah, neesan - welcome!
How about we all go drinking today in celebration of the graduation!?
I'll ask dad to go with us and pay for all!
Oneechan, that's no good!
Oneechan, th-th-that's no good!
It's all about
the juice, right?
But Ms. Police Woman - we're still underage...
Oneechan!
Oneechan, I don't think that we're allowed to go to such places yet...
Huh?
Ah-ha-ha!
If you do such things with company, you won't get caught!
I, too, as a student, did that often, but didn't get caught even once!
So she did do it!
Alright!
That's absolutely no good! For certain!
No, no...
If anything, we'll get caught because of you two relatives...
Oneechan! Onee-
Hm...
I see...
Don't mind...
tn: "Land" - Tokyo Disney Land
As Yuu-chan's at our place, shouldn't we go to the Land for a change?
As it's the spring vacation, after alll.
Ah...
Uhm...
I'm very happy,
but as the case is that I'm the one being cared for here,
you don't have to be so attentive.
Moreover, actually I went there the other day on a school trip.
Ah, now that you mention it, there was such an excursion in my time as well...
But Yuu-chan, were you alright?
Yeah, I my condition didn't even worsen, so I had lots of fun!
As I was together with my friends, too.
No, the height limits in the rides, and such...
Whatever the circuimstances might be, it's already OK!
I'm a high-schooler already!
You see, as I watched some campus dramas,
I thought once again about how junior high and high school are different on many levels, right?
Oh...
I suppose so...
At high school, school lunches and stuff go away, right?
Ah, that's correct...
It changes into either boxed lunches or school cafeteria food...
And then there's bought lunches or something...
Is oneechan making lunches every day?!
Y-You can say so...
Ah...
Amazing...!
It seems like it'll become troublesome after this...
She's great with games and stuff...
Her sphere of communication is wide...
She can cook and do housework.
Lately, I've begun to understand the pressure of being an older sister.
If you get watched like that, you just have to try your best, right, Kagami?
Huh?!
Yui-neesan, who gets enraged in the car!
Ah...
Yahoo...
How are you..?
Yui-neesan who comes into her parents' home drunk!
Homework...?
It's all right if you just write them somehow reasonably...
The just plain irresponsible Yui-neesan!
But I wonder if it's a thing that depends on the person after all...
For now, just try to talk in a way that can be understood...
Please visit us at
http://jeeb.fiveforty.jp/
#jeeb@irc.rizon.net
Final answer!
Ah... I totally can't keep working like this, seriously!
When I finally thought that I had gotten into the program, I checked the same recording and I wasn't shown, was I!?
So she began today, too...
Will she do it this time too?
Oh yes, she will...
I wonder what they're thinking when they make this program...
A sense like that, no brains used at all...
A-Akira-sama! Title call! The title call!
Anyone could've done it, why did I have to...
Huh?!
U-U-Uh...the title call...
S-Small eyes!
Hmph!
Good lucky!
Heh!
I'm telling you that it's not the time for things like that here right now!
It's impossible, I'm sick of it!
Just the voice, just the voice!
I'm telling you that there's no sense in that!
W-Well, I wasn't shown either...
I don't care about you!
What a wind!
Say now...
Did I just ask you something?
Did I just make even the smallest remark about you?
A-Ah...
N-No...
Not a word about me was said...
Well why do you then show yourself there?
Do you just happen to come out time to time?
A fool, aren't you?!
Always, always obtrusing with "Me, me!", that's what is called over self-consciousness!
It's enough for you to do the followup jokes, you're just Shiraishi!
Ah, my mouth will go bad...
You see?
Now the problem is that this me, Kogami Akira, was not seen on the main program!
What am I, the one who broaches the talk!?
I'm an idol, right?
Speaking of idols, it's the face that matters.
It's vital for me to be shown, right?
How is it?
Y-Yes!
Exactly!
Huh?!
Somehow I can't hear you...
The conduct of the staff this time is outrageous!
Huh?
Ah...
Kogami Akira's
revenge plan
for a complete appearance
on the main program
!!!
So!
The wish from Akira.
In order for Akira to appear on the main program everyone's strength is needed!
The World is waiting for Akira!
Send lots of support to the HP or as letter etc!
I'll be counting on your straight support in tens of thousands!
Whatever way is OK!
Just push it hard!
"I'd so, so want to see the great Actress Akira on the main program!"
Ha,
The real announcement...
"It's just the talk of around here,
but the rest of the cast like that,
when compared to the charms of this Akira,
happen to have the unbelievable difference like Hollywood's oscar-renowned actresses compared to kindergarden kids in a play!"
Desperate... This person is desperate...
You, over there, who wants to see a lot more of this pretty and gorgeous performance!
You mustn't let a chance pass while it's in front of you!
With your one letter, with your on comment on the home page, Akira's appearance will become a reality!
What happened, Kamura-san?
So, immediately after this program ends, ready a postcard or turn on the PC at your house...!
Huh?
Stop her? Understood...
U-Uhm... Akira-sama?
You're annoying!
Why do you keep sticking around and talking to me!
It's in a good spot now!
How many times do I have to tell you not to disturb me so that you would understand!
Huh?
Is it over already?
Even though I would've wanted you to know more about my wonderfulness...
I'll let you see my real charm as the main part of my appearance next time!
As if that'd be!
Uhm...
Please look forward to the next time!
Bye-nii!
Ah... It's over...
This is difficult...
Hey, you - come and call the Producer here!
Eh, I have to?!
Above all, you know...
This week's editing copy is incorrect, right?
Right...
What's this program's name!?
Huh!?
Ah, well it's Lucky Channel, but...
It's written "Lucky Paradise", isn't it?
Besides, they sure have a lot of bravery to deal with me like this!
No, but...
Uh, what is it?
Just because the program before hits a bit...
Hey, Producer - aren't you getting the boot!? Hey!
Miyagi-san!
Main Translation: JEEB
Translation Checking: xbe
Hello!
I'm Shiraishi Minoru!
Well then, let's hear it!
Timing: Kei Striker, JEEB
Typesetting: Kei Striker
Encoder: heedly
QC: Kei Striker, xbe
ワクワクしたいと願いながら過ごしてたよ
waku waku shitai to negai nagara sugoshiteta yo
Pass the time wishing for excitement...
かなえてくれたのは誰なの？
kanaete kureta no wa dare nano?
Who granted this wish?
出来そうで出来ないミライ
Dekisou de dekinai mirai...
A future with possible and impossible...
それでもひとつだけわかるよ
Sore demo hitotsu dake wakaru yo...
But I know just one thing...
時間の果てまでＢｏｏｏｏｎ！！
Jikan no hate made Boooon!!
To the ends of time BOOOON!!
ワープでループなこの想いは
Waーpu de ruーpu na kono omoi wa
These warp and loop feelings are...
何もかもを巻き込んだ想像で遊ぼう
Nanimo kamo wo makikonda souzou de asobou
Let's play with an imagination that engulfs anything and everything!
アル晴レタ日ノ事
Aru hareta hi no koto...
On one sunny day...
魔法以上のユカイが
Mahou ijou no yukai ga...
Fun greater than magic...
限りなく降りそそぐ 不可能じゃないわ
Kagiri naku furisosogu fukanou janai wa
Endlessly pours down... it's not impossible.
明日また会うとき 笑いながらハミング
Ashita mata au toki warai nagara hamingu
When we meet again tomorrow, humming as we smile...
嬉しさを集めよう
Ureshisa wo atsumeyou
Let's gather happiness...
カンタンなんだよ こ・ん・な・の
kantan nandayo ko・n・na・no
Such a thing is so e・a・s・y
追いかけてね つかまえてみて
Oikakete ne tsukamaete mite
Chase after me, try to catch me
おおきな夢&夢 スキでしょう？
Ooki na yume&yume suki deshou?
Big dreams & dreams, you like 'em, right?
End of Play
This video was brought to you by JEEB
Well then, the next Lucky Star is?
I'm Iwasaki Minami.
I'm Kobayakawa Yutaka.
Iwasaki-san, I heard that we are going to introduce the story together.
Do you know what kind of subject it has?
I don't know it.
Sorry...
Eh!?
Is that so?
That's problematic.
I know nothing as well...
Well, I'll put the end to it then.
Next Time: "No Sudden Changes"
Even as we haven't said anything, I wonder if it's alright...
Look forward to it.