Yoshimizu
Kagami
Theatre
Ah, the B class of third year?
Kuroi-sensei!
Yeah, yeah...
曖昧3センチ
Aimai 3 senchi
Unclear 3 centimeters...
そりゃぷにってことかい？ちょっ!
Sorya punitte koto kai? cho!
Is that a puni? Waitasec!
らっぴんぐが制服…
Rappingu ga seifuku…
The uniform's the wrapping…
だぁぁ不利ってことない　ぷ。
Daa furitte koto nai　Pu.
Hey, there's no disadvantage in that, yeah.
がんばっちゃ♥やっちゃっちゃ
Ganbaccha♥yacchaccha
Try your best♥do your thing-cha,
そんときゃーっち&Releaseぎョッ
son tokyaacchi & ririisu gyo
at that time, well, catch & release, gyo!
汗っ、々っ
A-se, a-se!
In the sweaty, sweaty...
の谷間にDarlin'darlin'F R E E Z E!!
No taniai ni daarin daarin furiiーzu!
cleavage darlin' darlin' FREEZE!!
Fan        subs
E
J
B
E
なんかダるー、なんかデるー
NankaDAruuー, nankaDEruー
Somewhat lazy..., something's coming out...
あいしテるー
AishiTEruuー
I love you...
あれ一個が違ってるんるー
Are ikko ga chigatterunruー
One of those is different, ruー.
なやみン坊ー 高鉄棒 おいしん簿ー
NayamiNbouー Koutetsubou oishinboー
A worrywart, high horizontal bar - an ever-lengthening list...
いーかげんにシナサイ
Iikagen ni SHINASAI
Now get reasonable!
飛んでったアイツの火照るカラダって
Tondetta AITSU no hoteru KARADAtte
The burning body of who flied away right now is...
所謂ふつーのおにゃのコ
Iwayuru futsuu no onya no KO
what is called a "usual girl".
驚いた、
Odoroita,
I'm surprised,
あたしだけ? 豚骨ハリガネおかわりダー!!!!
atashi dake? tonkotsu harigane okawari daaー!!!!
Only me? I get an extra portion of tonkotsu with super hard noodlesー!!!!
BON-BONおーえん団
BON-BON oーendan
Bon-bon cheering team.
Let's get! Cherry pie
Let's get! Cherry pie.
RAN-RAN　かんげー会
Ranraan　kangeーikai
RAN-RAN, welcoming party.
Look up! せんせーしょん
Look up! Senseーshon
Look up! Sensation.
はい！　存在感・・小惑星
Haai　Sonzaikan　tenten　shouwakusei
Yes, feeling of being here・・meteor!
ぶつかって溶けました　呆然　大いに歌ってシレンジャー
Butsukatte tokemashita　bouzen　ooi ni utatte shirenjaー
Got melted by the collision, dumbfounded and singing a lot, "Shiranger!"
もっていけ!
Motte ike!
Take and go!
最後に笑っちゃうのはあたしのはず
Saigo ni waracchau no wa atashi no hazu
The last one laughing should be me,
セーラーふくだからです
Seeraa fuku dakara desu
because it's a sailor fuku.
←結論
←Ketsuron
←Conclusion.
月曜日なのに！
Getsuyoubi nanoni!
Even if it's monday!
機嫌悪いのどうするよ？
Kigen warui no dou suru yo？
What will you do with that bad mood?
夏服がいいのです←キャ？ワ！イイｖ
Natsufuku ga ii no desu←KYA?WA!IIv
I want my summer uniform←It?Is!Cute!
接近3ピクト するまでってちゅーちょだ　やん☆
Sekkin san pikuto, suru madette chuーcho da　yan☆
Getting closer's in three paces, I'll hesitate until you do 'it' Oh☆
頑張って　張り切って
Ganbatte,　harikitte
Try your best, be on high,
My Darlin'darlin' P L E A S E!!
Mai daarin daarin puriizu
my darlin' darlin' please!
And you know, I'm keeping a dog in the game,
but it's so cute that I just end up talking to it...
You know...
Somehow when you talk to animals, you just use a silky voice, right?
Even though it's a game...
Ah, I can understand that!
Gyopi
Cha~n
My voice turns into a silky one too, when I talk to my goldfish...
Eh... I do understand something like dogs or cats,
but talking to a fish gives an image of a really lonely person, right?..
What'd you say!? That's prejudice, you know!
What's with those pitying-looking eyes!?
Come to think of it, I had been wondering about this for a long time...
What that dog's discipline word,
or should I say order - "Chin-chin" means?
tn : Chin-chin : An order given to a dog meaning "stand"
tn: Chin-Chin : Pe**s
E-er...
I will omit some things, since if I go into detail it'll turn long,
It seems to be sure that it is derived from Chinese.
Yes... Those who just thought about indecent things, raise your hand...
There's essence
in 2-D
Gun00m examination
Now that you mention it, Gun**m still has much popularity, doesn't it?
Yeah! Daddy's a ******, too!
There're many sorts of ***dam, right?
Like "V", "W" and "X"!
Yeah! I've watched every series in real-time!
Should I say it's a fan's feeling, or a feeling of duty!
Well then...
Should stuff like "Gu**am serial murder cases" or...
even "Detective Gund**" start, would you watch them?
They do say that you must look at them if you like Gun**m,
but I really doubt if it can be a Gund*m if it doesn't have an alphabet symbol...
I just suddenly thought when the **ndam talk started,
but even though I don't look like it,
I'm already two years older than Am*ro Rei, right?
Indeed, you're older than A*uro.
After two more years I'd be as old as Br**ht-san!
I can't imagine it!
Oh, well...
As Bright-san's getting pretty *ld, even inside Gun**m.
Ham*n-sama's the same, though...
But still, as you look more lol*-like than you actually are,
daddy has some doubts about putting X as the criteria.
Shocked
Ah...
At the very least say that I look youn*er than my actual age...
Ah, you're so cute...
Ah...
Hn?
I got something good from our neighbor!
It seems to be a souvenir from their trip.
What, a pot?
You've grown to a good girl, to daddy's tastes...
A cute one!
Daddy, you're hot...
Or should I say that that line is dangerous...
Morning, is it?
Last night I was on the border of drinking too much...
Even though I slept soundly during the day...
I wonder if I'm still young...
July 2nd, Monday, we present you the morning news.
This morning, at a restaraunt, a man screamed "This ramen is bad!"...
Huh? What about Sunday!?
Where did my holiday go!?
I am thinking about trying to study for tests during the night, too,
but I become sleepy no matter what...
After I talked to oneechan...
"You can't handle horror that well, right?"
"If you watched things like that,
wouldn't you become unable to sleep during the night?"
"As the other day you got into my futon, as well..."
And like that...
After I watched one I did become unable to sleep,
Big sister, as might be expected, isn't it?
But, you know... Afterwards when it changes to night...
clamp
I've begun to really mind my back or the faint noises,
and I became even more unable to pay attention to studies!
Because of that I have a lack of sleep,
and I get so sleepy during class...
But even though you say that you are weak to such things,
you watch them quite a lot, do you not?
Even though it isn't that I'd want to watch them...
Our mother is the same as well:
Say, Miyuki... I rented this, so wouldn't you like to watch it?
As I'd be afraid by myself...
Especially people who say that they are afraid of such things,
after all pretty much watch them, don't they?
Horror shows are too attractive to be shunned by you, right?...
That's not it, Yuki-chan!
In my case, however, I do really hate them!
Iwasaki-san, do you unterstand this problem?
Around there I was thinking as well...
And if I wouldn't be able to solve it, I thought about asking Miyuki-san...
I see,
We're so lucky that we have...
reliable seniors close to us in such times, aren't we?
And so today I talked with Iwasaki-san at the school...
Err, huh!? Am I trusted as much!?
It'll turn into retirement just because...
of the severeness of the world for this girl...
Hey, neesan?
Huh?
Neesan, have you studied for the exams with Kiin-niisan?
No, I haven't.
Although at games and all it's a usual situation, you know...
If a man and a woman who are in good terms with each other...
would be together there'd be no way to concentrate on something, right?
When your concentration fails,
you just enter into delusions of the things you like, don't you?
You seem to be getting symptoms, huh?
Oneechan...
There's a place I'd want you to tell me...
I'm on a bit of a run right now, so ask Yui-neesan!
Studies, studies...
Huh!? That's foul pl..!
I-I wonder if it's because the school was different?
Oneechan didn't learn this, you know...
Was that so...
It's painful...
Uhh... I got into a deadlock, as well...
Neesan, you can't understand this thing here - you can't, right?
If you're not expecting an answer, try not to ask!
I wonder if you didn't see that exchange right now?
Ah, damn it...
I wonder if I should call Miyuki-san and ask about it?
Although it could be a bother for her...
Ohh, I'd indeed think that it'd be a bother.
As it's late, too...
Hmm...
I wonder why at times like this a parent loses all his will to fight...
Please depend on me from time to time...
I'll fix you!
Izumi, don't you doze off!
Physical punishment being a prohibited one...
Sensei, you hit people pretty ordinarily, don't you?
Although it's alright as for me...
Yeah, you're right. But I don't do that for anyone,
I'm selecting the people I hit, in various ways,
as it could get tiresome in the future.
Waa... She said it clearly...
Such point is also incredible...
All in all, "physical punishment is prohibited" is weird, right?
Che Guevara
Jean-Paul
Sartre
John
Lennon
"I know you are here
to kill me. Shoot,
coward, you are only
going to kill a man."
"The most
perfect
man
of the
20th
century."
"The best-looking man in the world."
By this the class is over for today.
Miyuki-san, sorry...
But I don't know the years of the events and stuff around here...
Yuki-chan, help me with this question...
You all, "Takara, Takara..." - don't you go ask stuff from the teacher!?
Kuroi-sensei!
Ah, Izumi - what is it?
Well, I just happened to have something to ask...
Oh, what is it? Ask anything you want! Oh nothing can be done with you, huh...
It's a rare item in a game that I'm playing right now...
Err... Huh!? Sensei!?
That's not it, it wasn't that...
Ah...
It really is hot after a typhoon, isn't it?
Just for it to be the weather after a typhoon,
this year there was a lot of them, wasn't there?
A lot of siblings...
tn: another writing for "Taifuu ikka" - "the Taifuu family"
Ehe, you're good at those, aren't you?
By the way... what was it that was delicious?
tn: "umai" - good, delicious, again a mistake of kanji from Konata
I'll just hear this to make sure, but that right now was a joke, right?
Ah?
Err...
I'd like to ask you, oneechan, though...
Ah, what is it - talking so person-to person?
It's about this morning,
but did Kona-chan say something weird?
I can't understand the weird point as well, though...
Even though she watches the news with me,
how could she be on Konata's level, I wonder...
Hn?
Information for
an absentee
I wonder why you always come with such a steadily aimed timing...
The pitcher is aiming for the runner at second base,...
How's today's baseball translation forming?
Hn? Well, if it goes on like this it could be extended...
Again!?
Jeeze, it turns just into repeating the recording, huh...
Good grief...
Yet it'd be better if they'd just take more time from the beginning...
All in all, you know...
In professional baseball every movement is slow, don't you think?
Couldn't they keep themselves in their slot...
if the players would do their movement more briskly?
Well, well...
People who like it probably like it together with that...
There could be the concentration on the spirit as well...
How is it? Did you get used to the school life already?
Yes, but there's a lot of homework and all so it's hard...
Ah, I see...
3rd year students are centered on preparing for the entry exams,
so there really isn't that much homework and all, am I right?
Eh?
Ui...
Konata, you...
Ohh, I really wonder what this is about...
Ahh, it's hot isn't it?
Konata! What on earth are you wearing, walking around like that!?
What will you do if Yuu-chan mimicked you!?
But as it's been hot lately...
This is what they're doing even in the parliament!
Cool Biz?
Yeah, that!
No, that's different...
What were you doing from a while ago?
Eh!? Doesn't it just get into your mind...
if you just might get the answer for an e-mail?
I just happened to miss my stop as I was reading...
As always Miyuki-san is cute by her casual clumsiness...
Is that so? I think that it's just terrible, though.
Oh you don't understand, do you...
The shyness while appearing is especially moe'ing, you know.
It's more cute to have a little bit of popular points...
What do you, too, do at the workplace...
Aah... I ended up spilling it...
My customer, I'm so sorry...
...something like that?
Kagami, that's somehow foolish...
What're you doing?
Isn't this the talk you brought up!?
Although I did it!
And what are you saying, that you act clumsy...
and get points from people who fall for it?
No, I'm not doing such things.
It'd seem like there'd fairly be reason for that,
but as the manager gets angry from that, too...
Oh, and I thought that you were doing such things,
calling them moe'ish and all...
Oh, you're not getting it, Kagami...
Surely clumsy girls are cute and moe,
but when it gets to you...
getting actual harm in the real world, you get pretty annoyed.
Even if in games it'd be a place where you'd laugh and forgive.
That's where you people are serious - otakus...
This time as well, should a perfect expert come out,
we will present him a one-month-trip to the Tundra area by Look JT*!
Such variety programs or quiz programs,
many of them have awards or prize money, don't they?
Isn't it because that way appearing people will flock as well?
And so, if a famous TV personality would come,
the audience share would rise as well...
That's right... Although I don't know that well...
But, you know... If they would do it so...
that even the audience could participate in it...
and put the prize money over there,
don't you think that the audience share would rise even more?
I kind of understand it, but that's really straight appeal, isn't it?
Good morning!
Ossu!
I just thought about it suddenly while I was playing a game yesterday,
I wonder who's our school idol?
What's that? "School idol"?
Miss Ryouou, or like that?
Yeah, that's right, it usually goes like that, doesn't it?
In games and what not they're typical, though...
With bodyguards or something?
Ahh, I got tired today as well...
Ahh, I feel refreshed!
Ah!
I have to leave the house early tomorrow, don't I?
Today I just should be without internet and obediently go to sleep, huh?
As it'd be bad if I'd be late, as well...
Sleeping time has become dominant, hasn't it...
I wonder if it's evidence that I've become old...
Even though when I was a student I cut sleeping hours and ran towards my hobbies...
This is a free softsub.Not for sale, rent, auction or hardsub.
Not for sale, rent, auction or hardsub.This is a free softsub.
or hardsub.This is a free softsub. Not for sale, rent, auction
Lucky Star!
Tamura-san, did something happen?
From just now you seemed to have a lot of...
Ohh, when you're drawing drawings,
don't you just unconsciously end up in the same expression as the character?
Was that so...
So you were drawing...
I didn't know that Tamura-san was drawing manga...
Mainly doujin, though...
What kind of manga are you drawing?
Uh...
Err... The usual 4-koma or...
Something like love affair manga...
between my favorite characters from games...
It's hard to answer..!
The other day I won 3000 yen from a lottery coupon I bought just to try...
And I did think "Oh, I'm lucky since morning!", and all,
Wah! That's awesome!
Getting a flat tire on the way to school, there's going to be repair expenses...
And at that time I dropped my lunch...
and bought a new one at the convenience store...
After all, I lost exactly 3,000 yen in total as if intentionally.
"Truth is stranger than fiction", isn't it...
But you know...
I just thought that it's alright...
since it looks like it'd become material for manga...
Tough, isn't she...
Ah...
Ah!
Ah..!
Ugh...
For artists, their dominant hand is even more precious than their lives,
which they must protect at any risk...
T-tough, isn't she...
Ah, so Tamura-san is skillful after all!
Ohh, recently I've been in a slump,
that's a failure, you know...
Ah, but I wonder if this one is one of...
those that went pretty in the ones done recently...
Objection!
Yes, that's right...
Such things like the concerns of an artist and the subtle feeling,
many of those things are not seen by those who watch...
I knew, I knew...
Ah! I did it again!
Tamura-san, did something happen?
Ahh... My favorite pencil...
As I drew drawings yesterday, I left it on the desk as it was...
Should I lend you mine?
No... Actually, it's no good if it's not that pencil.
Or should I say that the feeling of the pencil is completely different...
Hm?
Hmm... Yeah, that's right...
Every pencil's the same, aren't they?
Yeah, I understand that though...
It turns into a response like that, doesn't it...
...and you know, I lost my way and couldn't get out for even three hours...
Ah!
Wa-a-h...
Tamura-san, did something happen?
Embarrassing! What are they thinking, appearing like that on the street...
Coat...
Wah, even if it's midsummer,
I wonder if it's not hot for them like that...
Guah, so is this the agony of people who know...
Wait a bit, I'll e-mail my friends...
Welcome!
Ah, it's crowded, isn't it?
I'll go write a name on the list.
...but I was playing a game with Konata-oneechan until the late night...
Suzaku-sama!
Thank you for waiting, three people under the name of Suzaku-sama!
Ah, we got called!
Eh? But Tamura-san, that was a different name...
Don't you just carelessly begin wanting to write
the name of your favourite character or something at times like this?
Something like the feeling...
of wanting to feel that character close to yourself or something...
Haruhi
Kyon
Yuki
Mikuru
Itsuki
Throwing : Haruhi
Hmm...
So they're everywhere... People like partners-in-type...
Thanks...
It would've been nice if I'd become so slender and tall like you, Iwasaki-san...
Delusion
I wonder if I should call Minami-chan...
something like the person of my dreams...
So...
Yutaka...
Reality
Ah...
Kobayakawa-san, as well,
as you will still grow...
It could be... that you... might become bigger than me...
Ehehe... Bigger than you, Iwasaki-san?
Delusion
Minami-chan!
Minami-chaan...
No good!
That's against the logic of the world, so it's no good!
Or should I say that the last one is clearly different, calm down, I!
Tamura-san, are you alright?
Somehow you look rather pale...
To tell you the truth, today was the day of bringing the materials...
to the press for the next event,
and the manuscript that I finished with an all-nighter...
I just put it onto home delivery, didn't I...
Ah...
But yourself, becoming desperate for something like this,
you do think will shine...
Tough, isn't she...
Tamura-san!
What's "Yaoi"?
I wonder which meaning is the one she means...
tn: yaoi - has two meanings, one is the usual, "a thing that has no meaning", other being the otaku one.
Please visit us at
http://jeeb.fiveforty.jp/
#jeeb@irc.rizon.net
Lucky Star!
Lucky Channel!
Good Lucky!
How quickly time flows! Lucky Channel is already on its 19th time!
Don't you think we're finally coming to the grand finale, do you!?
I'm your navigator, Kogami Akira!
And I am the assistant, Shiaishi Minoru.
My humble greetings!
Even so, Akira-sama, you seem to be in a somehow good mood today...
Darlin' Da-da-darlin'! I'm no happy, preyed on by adults!
Did something good happen?
Do you think there happened?
Ah, no...
It's nothing...
Ah, so after all appearing on TV uses your nerves, huh...
After you do even 19 times, the tiredness'll accumulate, too...
I have the feeling of using an onsen or something and healing myself...
I wonder if a prize from the quiz on the main program wouldn't fall on me...
Justasec!
If so, it'd be no good if we wouldn't begin from the fact that you appeared.
Uh!
This is bad...
Waai! Yes, isn't it good - traveling? I'd like to go as well.
When you journey places you don't know, the heart just gets clearer, doesn't it?
It's the best, isn't it?
Do you like traveling?
Of-of-of "of course"! I love it!
In fact, haven't I gone to many places?
I got up on Mt. Takao, went to Jougashima island as well...
I am a real outdoorsman, ya know!
Hmm...
So you do like traveling...
Lately, even if I'm calming down my heart,
at the grand nature a peaceful walk through the forest is the best!
Ahh, great, isn't it... A peaceful walk through the forest with Mother Nature...
The heart just calms down, doesn't it?
Isn't it so?
Getting away from the noise of the cities,
leaving the body to the quiet nature...
Both the heart and body get healed!
Yes, yes, yes...
It's good... Isn't it alright, nature?
Don't you think so, the nature!?
I'll go there, to a peaceful walk in the forest!
Uh, really!?
Is it alright!? But yes, if it's possible, I'll go!
Yes, then the "Shiraishi Minoru's tour to Great Nature" is decided!
Thanks!
Eh!?
Ah..!
Big...
Take this.
There seems... too much... equipment...
This... Where am... I supposed to go?
Mt. Fuji.
Eh?
Ohh, well... As I already once went to a mountain...
Yeah, not the mountain, but the woodlands.
Go to the woodlands of Fuji.
Aah, the woodlands, huh!?
W-who will..?
Ah... I will...
Yeah
Err... And so as I go... what should I do..?
Go and scoop some water.
Water...
I want to drink the famous water from Fuji,
so go to the woodlands and get some.
Huh!? No way!? Don't they sell that stuff at convenience stores and all!?
Ahhh...! I want it fresh!
I will not be alone, right!?
Alone? Alone!? Someone will go with me, right!?
It's alright, alright.
The director and producer said that...
they'll sacrifice themselves and go with you.
You got lucky, didn't you?
I'm not so happ...
Hey! Let's go right now!
Don't go over the deadline, OK?
No...no! Hey, let me go! No more! Huh!?
Ah! Is it such time already!?
Everybody! Next time we'll be sending Lucky Channel...
I'll try my best! I'll do it!
Stop! Please stop it!
Err, just a minu.. awwwwwww!!!!
while having a look at a wonderful guest!
Look forward to it!
It hurts! It hurtshurtshurts!
Bye-nii!
Let me go!...
Would it not have been alright without even making an excuse for driving him out?
Now get him...
Huh?
A part of my body is hot! Hot!
This time please enjoy the recording of magnificent nature, and of the flowing soap bubbles with two playful women.
Hello! I'm Shiraishi Minoru!
Now, I'll leave you to listen!
"Otoko no Ikizama"!
tn:  (The Way of Life of a Man)
Chan characcha! Chan characcha! Chan characcha! Cha-cha-cha!
はぁ〜　あいつのようになりたいなぁ〜
Haa~ Aitsu no you ni naritai naa~
Haaa~ I'd want to become like him~
Yes, it is all right to shut down the sound to your liking.
まえ〜だけを向いて突き進め〜
Mae~ dake wo muite tsukisusume~
Looking only forward, walking his way~
Translation: JEEB
Translation Checking: Taqmir
一度決めたらどこまでも〜
Ichido kimetara doko made mo~
Once I decide, I'll go to the very end~
Encoding: Heedly
Editing: Ro, Ilaggoodly
Typesetting: Ilaggoodly
Q/C: DarkJug
Chan charan chan-chan!
お〜　食らいついたら離さない〜
Oh~ Kuraitsuitara hanasanai~
Oh~ Once I'll get a bite of it, I won't let it go~
Chan-chara cha-cha-chan!
Haa~ Suppon! Suppon! Suppon!
Suppon! Suppon! Suppon!
Suppon! Suppon! Supopon!
tn: "suppon" - soft-shelled turtle; "supponpon" - all naked
Supopon! Supopon! Supopon!
Suppon! Supopon! Supopon!
うん、心も体も！スッポンポン〜！
Un, kokoro mo karada mo! Supponpon~!
Yeah, the soul and body! All bary-bare~!
Tet-te-ten!
Donsu! Do dotto! Donsu-do-don!
Donsu! Do dotto! Don!
Haa~ Suppon! Suppon! Suppon!
Suppon! Suppon! Suppon!
Suppon! Supopon! Suppon!
Supopon! Supopon! Supopon!
It's sour! Suppon Supopon!
心も体も！
Kokoro mo karada mo!
Both the soul and body!
This video was brought to you by JEEB
Su...
And so, the next Lucky Star is?
I'm Nanako.
Yui-chan it is!
I just thought about it,
but, you know, even before the summer begins you somehow...
really look forward to it and swell the feeling,
when you notice, it ends without anything really having happened.
Un, well, certainly there really are no special things as I think...
I just about can't think that a partner who was acquired...
at a time of such irresponsible thoughts can last long, too.
Unn, I don't really understand ~desu...
But well... There still is time, let's both try our best.
Eh!? Y-yes?
Uhh... It's hard to answer...
Next time: "How To Spend A Summer"!
"How
We're taking applications!