Now, let'ssu begin yoo!
It's gonna come now...
Fungaa!
Now start out already!
曖昧3センチ
Aimai 3 senchi
Unclear 3 centimeters...
そりゃぷにってことかい？ちょっ!
Sorya punitte koto kai? cho!
Is that a puni? Waitasec!
らっぴんぐが制服…
Rappingu ga seifuku…
The uniform's the wrapping…
だぁぁ不利ってことない　ぷ。
Daa furitte koto nai　Pu.
Hey, there's no disadvantage in that, yeah.
がんばっちゃ♥やっちゃっちゃ
Ganbaccha♥yacchaccha
Try your best♥do the thing-cha,
そんときゃーっち&Releaseぎョッ
son tokyaacchi & ririisu gyo
at that time, well, catch & release, gyo!
汗っ、々っ
A-se, a-se!
In the sweaty, sweaty...
の谷間にDarlin'darlin'F R E E Z E!!
No taniai ni daarin daarin furiiーzu!
valley darlin' darlin' FREEZE!!
なんかダるー、なんかデるー
NankaDAruuー, nankaDEruー
Somewhat lazy..., something's coming out...
あいしテるー
AishiTEruuー
I love you...
あれ一個が違ってるんるー
Are ikko ga chigatterunruー
One of those is different, ruー.
なやみン坊ー 高鉄棒 おいしん簿ー
NayamiNbouー Koutetsubou oishinboー
A worrywart, high horizontal bar - an ever-lengthening list...
いーかげんにシナサイ
Iikagen ni SHINASAI
Now get reasonable!
飛んでったアイツの火照るカラダって
Tondetta AITSU no hoteru KARADAtte
The burning body of who flied away right now is...
所謂ふつーのおにゃのコ
Iwayuru futsuu no onya no KO
what is called a "usual girl".
驚いた、
Odoroita,
I'm surprised,
あたしだけ? 豚骨ハリガネおかわりダー!!!!
atashi dake? tonkotsu harigane okawari daaー!!!!
Only me? I get an extra portion of tonkotsu with super hard noodlesー!!!!
BON-BONおーえん団
BON-BON oーendan
Bon-bon cheering team.
Let's get! Cherry pie
Let's get! Cherry pie.
RAN-RAN　かんげー会
Ranraan　kangeーikai
RAN-RAN, welcoming party.
Look up! せんせーしょん
Look up! Senseーshon
Look up! Sensation.
はい！　存在感・・小惑星
Haai　Sonzaikan　tenten　shouwakusei
Yes, feeling of being here・・meteor!
ぶつかって溶けました　呆然　大いに歌ってシレンジャー
Butsukatte tokemashita　bouzen　ooi ni utatte shirenjyaー
Got melt from the collision, dumbfounded and singing a lot, "Shiranger!"
もっていけ!
Motte ike!
Take and go!
最後に笑っちゃうのはあたしのはず
Saigo ni waracchau no wa atashi no hazu
The last one laughing should be me,
セーラーふくだからです
Seeraa fuku dakara desu
because it's a seeraa fuku.
←結論
←Ketsuron
←It's the conclusion.
月曜日なのに！
Getsuyoubi nanoni!
Even if it's monday!
機嫌悪いのどうするよ？
Kigen warui no dou suru yo？
What will you do with that bad mood?
夏服がいいのです←キャ？ワ！イイｖ
Natsufuku ga ii no desu←KYA?WA!IIv
I want my summer uniform←It!Is!Cute!
接近3ピクト するまでってちゅーちょだ　やん☆
Sekkin san pikuto, suru madette chuーcho da　yan☆
Getting closer's in three paces, I'll hesitate until you do 'it' Oh☆
頑張って　張り切って
Ganbatte,　harikitte
Try your best, be on high,
My Darlin'darlin' P L E A S E!!
Mai daarin daarin puriizu
my darlin' darlin' please!
Well, I've been taking a lot of books for a look lately, as it's the "Autumn of reading".
Hee, that's rare of you.
As much as you try to tell that it's for getting yourself more educated, the expenses just get higher, don't they...
Can't you just borrow the books from a library, instead of buying them?
There are more that you'd like to read in there than you think.
No, I don't really think that there's manga in libraries...
Reading, is it...
R-E-A-D-I-N-G...
A Feeling
Like That
Studying for the test
Aah, I can't concentrate...
Well-well-well...
Yes... yes...
Well, you do need rest as well...
Just like this...
A bit of relief with a game!
Ah! It's Kuroi-sensei!
"Hey you! Don't just play around, do the studies!"
"If your grades'll be bad, I'll really get mad!"
"Oh no, an ally, to such a degree... That's not it, sensei..."
When someone tries to command you, the games, too, will suddenly become cold...
"Sensei, what did you do about test studies and so on, while you were a student?"
"When I couldn't do it, I played around or slept...
The same things as now..."
Hee, well aren't we the same?
Ah.
"But I will go hard on you because of my position."
"I do understand you somehow, but it's a bit unreasonable..."
This time I'm thinking about making a target for myself and going for more defined studies...
Oneechan, please explain me the things I don't understand.
Well then, should we do it together?
Like I said, at times like these the value of X will...
Ah, what is it?
Come to think of it, now is the time for a drama to begin.
If I remember right, today's episode was about the heroine becoming an article in a weekly publication,...
...leading to the spread of information about her pregnancy.
Well, will you watch? The TV?
No, it's OK.
As I'm recording it onto tape.
Hey...
Aaah... Well...!
Ehe... I just get sleepy if the things I'm weak in go on...
So you're always sleepy?
Maybe I shouldn't read too much from the beginning,...
and leave it here for today...
Yes. Your willpower has gradually become more visible.
I can't concentrate, after all!
Here!
The secret of studying for tests?
I just thought about how you, Miyuki-san were doing it...
Oh yes... if you try too hard you will propably become mentally tired...
I am just putting as much effort into it as always.
And so I have confidence in myself today!
Should I say that I feel tolerant or...
Isn't your "as always" risky?
I bet you haven't done anything.
Eh... Even if it has such a cute face?
Furthermore, it even has poison in its calcaneus spur.
Aah, it really has an unexpected, dreadful side...
Uussu!
Ah, Kagami, how was it?
This time it was bit bad...
Even though I'm still keeping my high position.
So even Kagami has such times...
Oneechan kept company to me, so...
thanks to that I did better than I do usually.
And how did you do?
Mysteriously, It was went badly...
Even though I had confidence...
However, It's nothing like mysterious...
It's rather logical.
No, but, however, I had a feeling that "birds of a feather flock together"...
For example Kagami and Miyuki-san are class representatives and stuff...
I and Kagami have a mutual interest in games, too.
Well, the genre is different, though...
You're on gyaruge and RPGs, I like shooters.
I thought that we were connected with Tsukasa by being not-so-clever,...
but this time there was a real difference.
Well, this time I don't even mind, though it went badly.
Try to mind a bit about that!
If you're careless just because everyone didn't do well,...
you'll just be left behind.
Huh?
Or should I say that this time I have nothing on stake with my father, so I'm not frustrated at all.
It's sure that you won't become into a proper adult.
If you're about to copy Miyuki,...
take notes not only from the test periods, but during the usual times, too.
Miyuki-san is on the really punctual side...
A typical A-type, isn't she?
Ah, I do get that said to me rather usually,...
but in reality I am an O-type.
Eh, O-type?
That doesn't come to view at all.
Yes...
but...
According to this book...
there are actually quite many things that are characteristic for an O-type and at the same time apply to me.
For example,...
the point where it is written that "The O-type is childish and naive." really hits the nail, for example.
"The O-type is pushy and possesive. As well as destructive"...
Hmm... so Miyuki-san has such a side, too...
Konata is A-type, right?
Yeah, but I get really often mistaken for a B-type.
"A-type has no recollection about surrounding people...
and desires uneventful human relations."?
Does this really hit?
Don't you just often understand that I have kindness in me?
Only to the things that you have interest in, that is.
I can even mildly raise people up.
Only when it's about homework, you know.
Kagami, then what type are you?
Me? I'm a B-type.
Now you're "A my-paced, absent-minded temperamental person, that has a too...
honeyed way of thinking and who sounds her own opinion out loud a bit too much.", is it...
And what is that?
Well, then Tsukasa is AB-type, right?
Huh?
What's with that "well"?
Why do you ask?
No, just vaguely.
It just happens, that, when you image through the personality, Tsukasa seems like an A-type and Kagami like a B-type.
We're both B-type.
Or should I say, as were twins...
Ah, that was so...
I forgot that...
But I'm not as my-paced as you, though...
Speaking of fortunetelling, there were ones with animals and sushi, too.
Sushi?
Well, Miyuki-san is...
Hee, so Miyuki's salmon roe?
A high-class topping here, as well...
I really love salmon roe!
And, what about me and Tsukasa?
Ah...
Kappa-maki?
tn. Kappa-maki - a rolled sushi with cuecumber inside
Kappa-maki, now is it? Well, anyways, it is a sushi.
Isn't this just one the mark?
And what about such you, then?
Me?
Sliced ginger?
Sliced ginger, now is it?
Don't make fun of sliced ginger!
Well, it is a necessary existence to sushi,...
and the content of the fortunetelling is not that bad, either.
Yeah, that's right!
"Even with a kappa-maki, it's anyways a sushi."
Uhi-ng...
Ah!
Hello. is it you, Konata?
About the blood type- talk today, I'll just say to confirm...
that with fraternal twins the blood type can be different as well,...
so your conception was not wrong.
You're the type to really think about that seriously, too...
Thanks for your politeness...
You're really conscientious...
Now Kagami, as well, looks like an A-type to me...
Come to think of it, the other day psychological tests were done on the TV, right?
Or should I say, in such personality diagnoses...
there are matching things and unmatching things everywhere...
and no matter where someone would go, it...
"just feels like it matches that person, right?"
Kagami...
I'm sure that, if you keep talking realistically like that, your life'll surely be boring...
Try to do it more, you know, like your own age...
"Oh, Tsukasa, so she did try this time..."
Hm?
"Kagami seems to be dropping her form in comparison with always,...
but even with that Kagami is higher..."
Both of you, I appreciate your hard work.
Hmm... What should I say, that you did your best...
and overcame it.
Ooh!
Tsukasa, you did well now, didn't you!
But Kagami's on a higher level, after all...
Hey, Matsuri!
Try to read the atmosphere for a bit...
Good morning!
Oh my, good morning...
I'm so jealous that you both, Kagami-chan, Tsukasa-chan are so firm...
Oh, no...
It's not such a big...
You're both such and, as I've heard, your results are superior, too...
There's a great deal that our child could learn from you two...
Somehow it feels like I get praised as an addition to my big sister,...
Oh, no, it's nothing much.
so I can't just rejoice...
Lucky Star!
All the tests are over, so should we just go and have a good time?
Ooh, that's a good idea!
Would you go to see a movie for a change?
I wonder what they're showing now...
They're showing something awesome right now.
Like what?
In a way a splatter,...
but still being a superb horror movie with psychological suspence and shock!
Ooh, so let's go to see it!
If so, let's all go home once...
and meet somewhere?
Ah, let's do so! Let's do so!
It's the newest splatter suspence. A thing that really continues.
That doesn't relieve me, doesn't relieve me at all...
But what's that "I like you"?
We still have time, what will you do?
Konata's slow...
Is she late again?
I wonder how that is...
That girl, there's no way there'd be a time she'd be here before us...
Oh, really... The movie's going to begin's what I say.
Uwah!
When did you...
I didn't see you as you didn't wander around.
For now...
Let's go in as we have no time.
Ahh, now I remember! Could you tell about me as your sister?
Ah? Why?
Weell, that way I can get in as a child without being out of place.
"This child! Usually she minds about her height and stuff,...
but she tightly uses things like this!"
Oh, it was scary, Takemi!
Oh, you're so cute...
It seems like we got a bit hungry.
That's right.
Tsukasa, I bet you got hungry after screaming as much.
Ye-yeah...
What should we eat?
Well what about a cake smorgasbord?
Oh, that's good!
Smorgasbord...
it is where the appetite of a woman becomes even more powerful!
There's an amazing variety of cakes and drinks.
That's true...
I wonder if I could try them all...
If it's you, Kagamin, it'd be a piece of cake...
At this cafe we have a time limit of one hour,...
the drinks are in the drink corner to the north...
and the cakes are in the showcase over there,...
so please take everything freely.
Understood.
Ah, and if you leave unreasonable leftovers, they will end up into a separate pricing,...
so I will say this out in advance.
Then, please take your time.
What are those "unreasonable leftovers"?
Well, there are people who take a lot and don't eat it, right?
Look!
We'll be going now!
You took so much, are you sure you can eat it all?
Eh, but even Kagami...
If it's about cakes about this much is usual, right?
It's completely OK.
Itadakimasu!
I'd like this, too...
this, too...
It's truly hard to put something in now...
We took a bit too much under the influence of the first plate...
I'd like to lie down on my chest...
But they'll take a different price for the leftovers...
Ah! That's bad...
It's difficult...
I-it's no good...
Ah! It'll be time soon!
Oh, Kagami! You went for the second type of eating!
But it'll be a waste, right?!
It's impossible...
It's no good!
If you drink water recklessly, you won't be able to eat at all instead!
At this point just push what you can into your throat...
and in the end pour it all down with water!
Ho...
And don't you just admire, try to eat for even a bit!
It doesn't go in any more...
A pudding or a bavarois will! Listen to me!
There!
Isn't it OK with just Kagami eating?
Even I am already near my limits!
I'm already retiring for all good's sake...
And I'm telling you that you can pour a pudding into yourself!
Look! Fast!
That doesn't relieve me, doesn't relieve me at all...
As the tests have ended, I played games to my heart's content for a change!
And thanks to that I'm really sleepy...
If you'd study as keenly, the tests would've gone differently as well...
The latest bishoujo- games have a lot of save points,...
but I just couldn't stop, you know...
As I'm the type to end them in one stretch, too.
I've always wondered, but you can't buy them as a school student, right?
How do you get them?
Hm...
I'm asking my father to buy them for me...
No way!
I've always thought so, but your place is unbelievable in many ways...
Do you go and buy them for her, father?
Or should I say don't ask for them, daughter!
And so I'm so sleepy...
Miyuki-san, you really look like a person who wouldn't play games.
Ah, we do not have a family game console,...
but we have a computer, so I'm playing a bit with it...
Ehh? What kinds do you play?
It's really surprising!
Solitaire, Mindsweeper and the likes of that...
Sometimes it gets exciting.
"Well...
it's not a mistake but only different, Miyuki-san."
But I understand that...
Quite surprisingly such simple games just get you caught up in them, don't they?
What kind of scores can you get, Yuki-chan?
Solitaire has luck in it, as well, but I pretty much get over 10.000 points.
At Mindsweeper, I recently cleared the hard stage under 100 seconds.
"People like her just keep on doing things that go for their type..."
This year a lot of things happened on the sports side.
Yes, that one athlete took a gold medal in figure scating at the Winter Olympics as well...
High school baseball became pretty exciting as well...
as it became an amazingly extended game.
Yeah, that handkerchief prince, right?
Now as you're talking about baseball, that one player went to the USA as well, didn't he?
Ah!
Did the Japan series end already?
A long time ago, already.
Can't be! Were there bargains and sales this time?
This year's Japan series was over there and there,...
so it didn't have anything to do with supermarkets or department stores.
But they did do opportunity sales, though.
Ah!
But they were sacrifice sales of ham anyways, right?
I wonder if they did that...
In any case, I'll check properly from next year...
As it's about you, don't you just buy a lot of sweets anyways?
That's not right, things like salt, sugar or soy sauce...
I'm buying such flavourings that I use in the house.
Huh?
Well, I guess that it's an incomprehensible talk to Kagami anyways, right?
Oh sorry!
As I'm not so good at housework anyways!
Eye drops? Should I help?
Ah, thank you very much.
Well, lie down for the view then.
Understood...
Yes...
Just relax...
Yes!
Well I'll be going now...
Hey!
Take off your power!
Y-yes...
Uwah!
Oh, I'm very sorry...
I am not doing it on purpose...
Your face is...
scary...
Huh?
With prizes the bottleneck is the time
that is needed for the goods to be sent.
That's where I found out the second pleasure of finding it all out for another time.
What's that?
First you have fun with a carnival feeling...
and when you have already forgotten about it you get happy as it gets to you,...
lookie - there's some profit. Twice as good with one thing.
Well, I happen to dislike waiting in the first place,..
but when it's something you like, you just go thoroughly positive...
Lucky Star!
LUCKY CHANNEL!
Good lucky!
Yes! Today I'd like to cheerfully bring you Lucky Channel again!
As a fast-paced thing, this time we're already on our ninth time!
I'm your navigator, Kogami Akira!
And the one who is going to be called...
"Shiraishi, just come here for a moment..."
by our producer Itou-san later on is here...
Er... Is that so?!
It's me, Shiraishi Minoru, giving all my power into being Akira-sama's assistant.
My humblest greetings.
Yes! Today is the third character introduction:
The Hiiragi Tsukasa edition!
Oh, she still shocks... tame-go-rou...
"Are you clumsy and a blockheaded turtle?"
Hiiragi... ah...
And so...!
Excuse me...
At last we got warmed up to this!
Yes!
I'd like to tighten my loincloth once more and try my best!
Don't you agree, Akira-sama?
"Loincloth"?
I am an idol of a sort, so such things are a bit...
I'll be counting on you around there...
Ah... that is so...
Er...
Wah!? What about "tightening the loincloth again until it's in my skin."?
You know, I'll tell you one thing out of kindness,...
"out of kindness"?...
An entertainer is, you know, done with if he runs down...
So I was an entertainer...
And then the fill-up with jokes...
You're doing that pretty often recently, so be careful...
Y-yes!
And, what was it today?
It was the introduction of Hiiragi Tsukasa-san!
Aaah... That To Hear...
Mi-mi-mirakuru!
...Kamigishi...
Miinorun-run!
Right?
So, you say that, too?
I wonder what it could be, she has a character of an idol from a long time ago...
Aah, well... is that so?
Well, Tsukasa-san really is not a character that doesn't feel like an idol if you say so...
Don't try to amuse me!
"Hiiragi Tsukasa is an idol."
Where did you take that from!?
You too, you know,...
work with me like this,
so try to learn the thing that is "a genuine idol".
Ye-yes...
Hiiragi Tsukasa is merely a "no way"- type with a thick-with-happiness- face, right?
Ahh-haa... "a thick-with-happiness"- face...
right...
It's already so indifferent about this "Hiiragi Tsukasa"...
"Even though I haven't even been hit by my old man!"
Well, let's teach you here the knowledge of idols...
First off how to be taken photos off.
Huh?
You know, this is talk that'll turn into study for you, too, so...
pull your spirit and listen to me!
Ah, yes!
Well, people tend to suddenly take photos of you, don't they?
"Lookie, please push the shutter..."
Some...thing... like... "thick with happiness"?
Well, that's something like that.
Gadgets are essential things, as well!
You should always have them.
"Where?"
And, you know...
it's bad if you get taken suddenly at your usual walk around town,...
so always be tense!
And the thing that'll glisten your teeth ah so white...
Shinjou...
"...passionate."
And you know,
open your eyes at least to the "big round eyes"- position...
and express laughter only here.
"Scary..."
And the gentliness, too. You make it look like natural.
For example, when you get the camera drawn you at suddenly...
"Akira's surprised!"
Like that...
Uhmm... "Naturally", you say...
Oh, yes...
And there's the variation where you go with a man to a ho...
Oh, bye! It's already the time for us to part!
And so, please send us freely to this corner all your...
questions and encouragements to Akira, or your impressions about this show!
We're taking them through our studio or the homepage!
And so, please look forward to the next time.
Bye-nii!
We did a photo session, right?
So we did.
We did with me wearing a pink cardigan...
How was it?
Aah, that was cute...
Thanks much!
What happened?
Was it cute?
Oh, well, everyone said it was really cute.
That's right, we were all in high spirits...
Indeed.
It was really in high spirit.
It looked really nice.
Oh, well... with that upward glance, you know...
How should I say, like, putting the hands under the face and so on was really fun.
Haa, so didn't it become a habit?
Yes...
Well, it, with the inclusion of crossdressing, became a habit...
Did you check the photos?
No, I haven't yet.
Hmm...
Our manager-san, you know, after checking the photos,...
Yes?
actually said that honestly there were some disturbing ones in there as well...
Well, but I have a lot of "bulge" photos, so that thing's OK, right?
Sorry, sorry... I did a prescribary miss.
I'll sing OK the next time, so...
...And while saying such things she's putting more songs in...
Give it to me, too, sometimes.
Hoi-yo...
Did Tsukasa and you already settle on something?
Just wait for a bit more.
I haven't studied enough and do not know the songs, so...
It's alright as I'll do the connections from everything.
Hey! Sing something else than anime songs!
Well, but this is not an anime song.
Ah, I've heard this...
What was this...
It's KyonKyon! I used to sing this often with my dad...
If it wouldn't be an anime song, this time it's a nostalgic melody?
Eeh, if you say "nostalgic melody" it's rude towards KyonKyon!
出逢いは風の中
Deai wa kaze no naka
Our encounter has been in the wind...
Tsukasa, aren't you OK with a simple song?
恋に落ちたあの日から
koi ni ochita ano hi kara
From the day I fell in love.
Something like The Dog Days...
気づかぬうちに心は
Kidzukanu uchi ni kokoro wa
While I didn't understand it myself,...
Well, I did search around there, too...
I'm sorry...
Oh, you don't have to hurry that much.
あなたを求めてた
anata wo motometeta
my heart kept seeking you.
There's still time, too.
泣かないで恋心よ
Nakanaide koigokoro yo
Hey, don't you cry, my love...
願いが叶うなら
negai ga kanau nara
if the dreams'll come true.
涙の河を越えて
Namida no kawa wo koete
After having crossed over the river of tears...
すべてを忘れたい
subete wo wasuretai
I would like to forget it all.
せつない片想い
Setsunai kataomoi
Oh, this painful unrequited love...
あなたは気づかない
anata wa kidzukanai
that you do not recognise...
And so, the next Lucky Star is?
It's me, Konata.
In the world 3-1 of the "Super Chome-Chome Brothers", in a spot before the last stairs...
there is a place where you can get infinite increase in your life if you can skillfully step on the descending turtle,...
and by barraging the A button to jump on it kick-like, which is still OK.
But if you then carelessly get more than 129 lives, the game will go straight to "Game Over" after you die for the first time.
"Well it's not infinite then, is it?!" is a comment we'll leave aside, but I wonder if this is...
You know, an address to all people from the company that resides near the Toufukuji station to...
"Keep everything everything in moderacy".
Next Time: "Desire"
Look forward to it!