Presented by
JEEB & STAR
Now, let'ssu begin yoo!
It's gonna come now...
Fungaa!
Now start out already!
曖昧3センチ
Aimai 3 senchi
Unclear 3 centimeters...
そりゃぷにってことかい？ちょっ!
Sorya punitte koto kai? cho!
Is that a puni? Waitasec!
らっぴんぐが制服…
Rappingu ga seifuku…
The uniform's the wrapping…
だぁぁ不利ってことない　ぷ。
Daa furitte koto nai　Pu.
Hey, there's no disadvantage in that, yeah.
がんばっちゃ♥やっちゃっちゃ
Ganbaccha♥yacchaccha
Try your best♥do your thing-cha,
そんときゃーっち&Releaseぎョッ
son tokyaacchi & ririisu gyo
at that time, well, catch & release, gyo!
汗っ、々っ
A-se, a-se!
In the sweaty, sweaty...
の谷間にDarlin'darlin'F R E E Z E!!
No taniai ni daarin daarin furiiーzu!
cleavage darlin' darlin' FREEZE!!
なんかダるー、なんかデるー
NankaDAruuー, nankaDEruー
Somewhat lazy..., something's coming out...
あいしテるー
AishiTEruuー
I love you...
あれ一個が違ってるんるー
Are ikko ga chigatterunruー
One of those is different, ruー.
なやみン坊ー 高鉄棒 おいしん簿ー
NayamiNbouー Koutetsubou oishinboー
A worrywart, high horizontal bar - an ever-lengthening list...
いーかげんにシナサイ
Iikagen ni SHINASAI
Now get reasonable!
飛んでったアイツの火照るカラダって
Tondetta AITSU no hoteru KARADAtte
The burning body of who flied away right now is...
所謂ふつーのおにゃのコ
Iwayuru futsuu no onya no KO
what is called a "usual girl".
驚いた、
Odoroita,
I'm surprised,
あたしだけ? 豚骨ハリガネおかわりダー!!!!
atashi dake? tonkotsu harigane okawari daaー!!!!
Only me? I get an extra portion of tonkotsu with super hard noodlesー!!!!
BON-BONおーえん団
BON-BON oーendan
Bon-bon cheering team.
Let's get! Cherry pie
Let's get! Cherry pie.
RAN-RAN　かんげー会
Ranraan　kangeーikai
RAN-RAN, welcoming party.
Look up! せんせーしょん
Look up! Senseーshon
Look up! Sensation.
はい！　存在感・・小惑星
Haai　Sonzaikan　tenten　shouwakusei
Yes, feeling of being here・・meteor!
ぶつかって溶けました　呆然　大いに歌ってシレンジャー
Butsukatte tokemashita　bouzen　ooi ni utatte shirenjaー
Got melt from the collision, dumbfounded and singing a lot, "Shiranger!"
もっていけ!
Motte ike!
Take and go!
最後に笑っちゃうのはあたしのはず
Saigo ni waracchau no wa atashi no hazu
The last one laughing should be me,
セーラーふくだからです
Seeraa fuku dakara desu
because it's a sailor fuku.
←結論
←Ketsuron
←Conclusion.
月曜日なのに！
Getsuyoubi nanoni!
Even if it's monday!
機嫌悪いのどうするよ？
Kigen warui no dou suru yo？
What will you do with that bad mood?
夏服がいいのです←キャ？ワ！イイｖ
Natsufuku ga ii no desu←KYA?WA!IIv
I want my summer uniform←It!Is!Cute!
接近3ピクト するまでってちゅーちょだ　やん☆
Sekkin san pikuto, suru madette chuーcho da　yan☆
Getting closer's in three paces, I'll hesitate until you do 'it' Oh☆
頑張って　張り切って
Ganbatte,　harikitte
Try your best, be on high,
My Darlin'darlin' P L E A S E!!
Mai daarin daarin puriizu
my darlin' darlin' please!
The other day I saw a shooting star,
but Kagami said that saying your wish three times is impossible...
when thinking realistically...
A Shooting star, how nice.
I haven't seen them but scarcely...
as the stars cannot be seen that well from our place...
Ahh, yes...
Miyuki-san's house is in the Metropolitan area, too...
If it was me,
I would just be attracted by the vision and would not be able to say a word.
There might be a legend that,
as you look at the glaring, shining, wonderful stars...
and receive that feeling of happiness, your wishes will come true.
Such an honest you is too dazzling for me.
The Many Ways
To Spend A Holy Night
The winter holidays are close already.
But the final exams are before that, right?
Do you two have any plans for the winter holidays?
No, none...
Now that you mention it, we haven't travelled lately...
You know, the other day I went to Asakusa!
Hee, when did you?
Aah, well, you just get sleepy in a train in wintertime, right?
She missed her stop?!
Ah, but isn't that in the opposite direction?
I seemed to have missed my stop until the terminal,
apparently changed headings there, and missed again...
When I woke up, Asakusa was right there...
Hey! Hey!
Even if you say that you "missed your stop," there's a limit to it, right?
Hmm...
But missing a stop is not just about bad things!
I was able to go for a small trip to Asakusa after a long while, too!
That's not something to be done during the test period, though...
However, I had a feeling that a high school girl in a sailor uniform...
with a machine gun passed through the platform for a moment...
I wonder what that was...
I hope you won't say that it was a raid or something...
And, they do say that "sleeping children get bigger," right?
Where do they?!
There are even more unbelievable things!
Our father went for a health certificate after an all-nighter,
took an early morning train, missed his stop,
sat until the terminal, made a U-turn,
woke up to find out that he missed his stop again,
and made a couple of laps like that.
He did start to wake up closer and closer to his station,
but at the last moment he missed it again.
He said that he didn't easily get home,
even though he was tired and wanted to get home fast.
He also said that in the end, when he woke up,
he lost sense of whichever direction he was heading to.
Unbelievable!
But I wake up just before my station, even if I'm sleeping.
Amazing!
I wonder how you do that!
Doesn't she have a built-in alarm clock?
The one in the belly seems to be broken, though...
What's that?
You're always eating sweets, too.
You're annoying!
But in trains you get really sleepy if the seat is warm, right?
Yes, indeed...
Just like when you're dozing away from the warmth...
in a window seat in class on a sunny winter afternoon...
Oh, standing up for each other as people of the same type?
It-It's not like that...
The other day when I woke you up on the train home...
Hey, wake up.
We're there already.
Just another five minutes...
Really...
She said that in a loud voice while being still half-asleep...
and got laughed at by the surrounding people.
One of my friends said that during class, too.
Well, somehow you're really the same partners-in-type...
Eh, you're putting us into the same type?!
But I wonder why it's "five minutes"?
Isn't that because...
if you went to wake someone up and were told, "one more hour,"
you'd get angry, right?
Well, that's so,
but even if it's not about sleeping one often says, "five minutes," right?
Like "wait five minutes"...
Yeah, that's true.
It could be that it's neither too long nor too short...
The five minutes you wait for a train or something feel long, though.
That's right!
That might be so...
But, well, those guys who say "five more minutes" at such times...
just don't follow their time, right?
Don't they say pretty often, "Don't use the phone" or,
"Don't do your make-up" on the trains lately?
But when the person next to you leans to your side...
it's even more annoying, isn't it?
Yeah, it's really heavy,
so even if you just got a place to sit,
there are times when you feel that it'd be easier to just stand...
When a sweaty head just happens to come to you it's like...
You just think "Lean over there!" sometimes,
but they just come down the same way...
even if you put them straight a couple of times...
That's right, that's really strange, isn't it?
When I sleep,
I try to lean towards the free spot...
when there's an old man to one side...
and free space to the other,
but at times I always fall on the old man even if I try many times.
There's always the "it's easier to fall here" side, now isn't there?
I try to compress my body like this when the person next to me falls on me,
but if I do so the elbow touches my side.
Isn't such a person really awake?
Eh, is that so?!
Well, bye-nii!
Goodbye.
You know...
At our school there are people who ride home up the line,
as well as people who ride it down, right?
Yeah.
Doesn't it just give the feeling...
that those who go up the line are more sophisticated?
Yuki-chan's an upgoer as well, right?
That's...
Yes, yes... let us go back to the frontiers, all of us!
Oh... it's the station before mine, isn't it...
Ossu!
Wii!
Yesterday I couldn't study at all...
Hee...
As the opposite, I was really in the spirits yesterday.
Even if saying it myself isn't really...
How much did you study?
Only Four hours!
Even four hours!
Huh...
Kagami, you seem to do everything so shrewdly, don't you...
Well, anyways, I do study and stuff pretty much as well.
Only around here, though.
Surely Kagami has a strong competitive spirit.
Well, somehow said it's the dignity of being the older one...
or should I say that the feeling that I had...
to be one step ahead of Tsukasa was strong, too.
Even though I usually say that there's no "older" or "younger" between us,
a long time ago I still had that feeling...
But there just wasn't enough competition with Tsukasa as your rival?
Eh, well... indeed...
Even if it's Kona-chan!
It'll be Christmas soon, right?
I wonder what present I'll get this year...
So you still receive presents?
Kona-chan, until what age did you believe in Santa-san?
Huh?
Doesn't Santa Claus really exist?
Unbelievable...
At Kona-chan's place Santa-san didn't come even once,
so her father always gave her presents instead.
That's why she always thought that he should be somewhere...
So that guy really wants to show his daughter his good parts...
Hey, Hiiragi!
Yes?
Hiiragi-san, the printout from earlier...
Ah, yes-yes.
And then, Hiiragi-chan...
Hiiragi, you dropped your pencil!
Ah, thanks.
Hey! Kagami!
Yeah?
Kagami-san, these are the printouts from earlier...
Ah, yes yes...
And you know Sebastian was so smelly...
Kagami, you dropped your handkerchief.
Eh, really?
Aah... I wonder if I have shown my face too much in Tsukasa's class...
Lately my bad tooth has gotten painful and...
Oh my, that is unpleasant isn't it...
I dislike the dentist's as well...
Yuki-chan, you did go for the treatment earlier,
but did you get better already?
The dentist... not only takes his time to treat one tooth,
but after he gets done with one, he'll do the next one,
and it'll continue for a pretty long time, won't it?
Because of that I ended up running away involuntarily,
giving various reasons...
I wonder what I should do...
She's talking so cutely, but doing pretty amazing things!
Konata!
Wouldn't you want to play with us on Christmas together?
Ahh, sorry - I have plans for Christmas.
Ah, what, a connection to men?
Hmm, something like that...
Do you have some plans to go somewhere with your daddy or something?
No, I've told my dad that I'll be coming home late...
Don't say... You really have a date with your guy?
When did you...?
I'm sorry to betray your expectations,
but it's just my part-time work.
Ohh...
Though almost only men come there, so it's not wrong.
And I thought you were getting ahead of us...
You really surprised me...
On Christmas we have a special event...
at which we dress as Santa.
You really like such things, don't you...
Hmm...
But you know...
Don't you two do shrine maiden cosplay at your own shrine at new year, too?
Don't call it cosplay!
You know, it's okay for Santa-san to give gifts,
but I really thought "hey, that's tresspassing, isn't it" when I was a child.
Don't look so down on Saints's roots...
What an unpleasant child...
But...
Huh?
Ahh... even if Santa is the one giving dreams to children,
what kind of men are those who seek dreams from a chibi girl like this...?
Oh-oh... Cruel things are being said of me...
But as you mention it, is it OK for you two to have Christmas?
Now that you ask, we did always get Christmas presents, didn't we?
It's because we worship all the countless Gods at our place.
We go to the temples as everyone else...
We've even sung hymns in a church.
Hee, seems pretty peaceful...
Ah... but...
My elder sister, who's a shrine maiden,
said that she'd like to hold her wedding ceremony with a wedding dress...
I wonder if it's okay...
But if it goes as far as that isn't it a bit complicated...?
This is a free fansub
Not for sale, rent, or auction
Yahhoo! It did get cold lately, didn't it?
Ah, neesan - welcome.
What were you watching?
Hmm... A detective drama.
Ohh, was it interesting?
Not really... vaguely, you know.
All right, I got it.
That man is the culprit!
Please wait, Officer...
There's a weird point to this case...
There's nothing weird!
With this the case is solved!
Why do you say such things if you're an outsider?
Ahh, that's why the police force is no good...
But you are that police force...
Ahh... I wonder why someone has to call at such a time,
just when the culprit is about to confess...
How do you know that?
Lookie...
Ahh, so you were the culprit...
It can't be helped, I got known...
I wonder why the endings of 2-hour dramas are so precipitous...
Isn't that because if the person isn't hunted for all the money,
he doesn't live up to the expectations?
Yafuu! How are you?
Neesan-'vening.
What were you watching?
A movie of a popular detective drama...
something daddy rented.
Incindents don't happen in the conference rooms, but on the scene!
No, no, no... that doesn't happen...
There are no such exciting developements..!
So you deny it here...
If I remember correctly,
the actual crime here was not receipt stealing,
but the idea of the Head of Police...
This is why that darn chief is...
Do you know something?!
That reminds me,
in detective dramas the police often gives arrested people katsudon to eat,
but isn't that actually forbidden?
Ahh, as it is fiction, there's a lot of lies as well...
So, aren't there really that many Superintendent's grandchildren?!
The grandchild of the Superintendent...?
No, I haven't seen any...
I would at least want someone like Mai-chan, just for hope...
A wish without a future, now isn't it...
There sure are many cases when adults target children...
Yes, there are...
I just thought about it, but, you know...
If children were taught martial arts,
then such accidents would decrease.
Ooyama-sensei, thanks to his strict training,
became able to bring down a bull unarmed, and, moreover–
with just one blow it seems.
Twenty bears were like the norm for one day and like that...
Was that so...
But wouldn't everything return to the way it was before, after a while?
When those kids become adults, they will be stronger as well...
Hu... Well...
It's that... you know...
When you do martial arts and stuff...
they say that your heart becomes grown straight as well, don't they?
Hmm... Indeed...
But...
as there's an example of someone who does martial arts,
but still has an unclean spirit before me...
What rudeness!
You know,
I have a cousin who's Yui-neesan's younger sister...
and becomes a high-schooler next year...
She has a weak body, but she's honest, pure and really cute.
Hee...
But if you go by the "A healthy mind dwelves in a sound body."- view...
The essence of that beautiful person just suddenly came to feel...
like someone that has two sides and an evil mind...
I don't think everything goes by the proverbs...
There's your example, for instance...
This year is already over now isn't it?
Every year, when it turns December, you think the year passed fast, right?
Will you help your family by being shrine maidens this year as well?
Oh, well...
Remember to come to take fortune slips and all again!
You know,
when you get "bad luck" from a fortune slip...
you just get a bad image with an unpleasant feeling,
but if you get "very good luck,"
won't you just worry about using all of your luck?
Well, they do say that "medium luck" is the best as well...
Hoy! Well, it's an early present from your teacher!
I'll be giving back your report cards!
Kona-chan, how was it?
Sensei! I don't need such a present!
To give acceptable marks for trying is my way of Santa!
Enjoy yourself, with a bonus for the winter holidays homework.
I wonder what kind of a Christmas cake would be good this year?
When you go to a cake shop,
there are all of those cute cakes,
and you get happy by just looking at them, don't you?
I wonder what happens to those unsold cakes after Christmas?
Would it not be that people from the shop take them home?
But if there was no-one to take them, they'd still be thrown away after all.
The marriageable age is often illustrated through Christmas, now isn't it?
Yeah, like "until 25"...
A Christmas cake is just a cake after the 25th as well,
and somehow after one night the decorative cakes become futile...
with the colours fading,
and the feeling to eat it goes away as well...
The other day I talked about Santa-san with Kona-chan,
but until what age did you believe in him, Yuki-chan?
It feels like you'd be like me, believing for a long time.
I, too, believed in Santa-san,
but when I was little, as I tried to send him a letter of gratitude,
I had checked a lot of things...
But as I couldn't find anything out even after asking my mother or father,
I stumbled upon the words,
"the original story of Santa Claus" or,
"the origins of Santa Claus" as I continued intense searching,
and got my dreams torn away at a fairly young age in the process...
Ah...
Miyuki-san, how was it?
Show me!
Yuki-chan, as expected!
That'd be just unbelievable for me...
Hmm... It's a bit frustrating to lose...
Yuki-chan is among the top performers of this year so it just can't be helped.
We just can't beat her.
No, the scores make no difference, but the bust and all... Look, like this!
My belly got empty...
Should I eat something like cup noodles?
I wonder if they're done yet...
These three minutes you have to wait just feel so long...
Let's counter boredom with this today!
Don't you have times when you have done so...
and the noodles got all stretched...
Yeah, I have!
Like when all the water in an instant-yakisoba vaporized!
You two...
I did hear that she'd be late, but this is too late!
It'd be bad if it became a habit...
I guess sometimes I just have to reprove her...
As the male parent...
I'm home!
Konata!
Now come over here for a minute!
What time do you th–
Merry Christmas!
This is a Christmas present from me to daddy.
I bet it was cold at such an hour...
Will you drink hot tea?
Yes, I will, I will!
Daddy's so happy he could die...
Aaaa... Zukonchaa...
Ohh... Yui-neesan has arrived yes!
Oneesan, you smell like alcohol! Drunken driving's bad!
I had something to drink after I parked my car around here...
Even though it's Xmas eve my husband isn't at home today either...
Our plans for the night...
Neesan, couldn't you go to your parents' home for a change...
instead of coming here...?
Ah, hello, Yui?
It's me...
I thought to go home quietly and surprise you, but it's closed...
Are you at your parents' place now?
I'll come home!
I'll go full speed right now!
And tear away all those traffic lights!
So, I'm trying to say that you mustn't do anything illegal!
I'll take you there.
Now that I've taken a stretch, maybe I should log in...
Oh, Sensei is on...
Sensei, let's frolic until the morning...
Please wait for a moment...
Hm?
It's not a leftover... It's not a leftover...
Ku
roi
Na
na
As I bought it away...
ko
years
old
SIN
GLE
I came on last week's Sunday as well, to buy manga.
You really come here often, with all the travel fees...
Even if you say that it's for the points, you still do a lot of it...
You really like it, don't you?
All in all, do you even use the prizes that you get that way?
Nope, I don't...
Oh, well, it's like that isn't it...
Such things are difficult to use, after all...
Indeed, they're so good that you just can't use them...
Well, how should I put it... because the value would drop...
Ehh... So you came like that.
Oh, well...
"No!"
"Yes."
Didn't it hit you, the static electricity?
Nope...
Eh?! I wonder why?
Konata's always sitting before the computer,
so hasn't she just piled up some weird waves?
But the winter is really unpleasant, now isn't it?
There seem to be times...
when you just touch the hand of someone and get struck.
It hurts! It hurts! It hurts! It hurts! It hurts!
Could it be that you two are really on bad te...
How long do they do that?
It hurts! It hurts! It hurts! It hurts! It hurts!
What are you doing?
Oh, well, I just wanted to try again...
Stronger!
Please visit us at
http://www.wing2.jp/~jeeb
#jeeb@irc.rizon.net
LUCKY CHANNEL!
Good lucky!
I am your navigator Kogami Akira!
As a fast thing, Lucky Channel is already in its eleventh time!
As for it, we can inform you of stunning news!
W-Well...
Until now there were many heated requests wishing that...
She isn't listening at all today again...
Akira-san were in the main program as well...
Oh, I'm the assistant Shiraishi Minoru–
Next time, I, Kogami Akira...
You're noisy!
I'll be appearing on the main program!
But the greeting...
From Izumi Konata-san to everyone who wrote a postcard to Newtype,...
Thank you very much!
Hee, so Akira-sama will be on the show as well?
Huh?
Hey, what's with that, "Oh so you're getting in at the 12th time at last?...
I've already been in for a long time... heh-heh-heh..."
-way of speech?!
F-F-Far from it!
To be able to co-star with Akira-sama even on the main part is an honor!
Huh!?
Even if you're speaking about acting,
you only picked up a handkerchief this time, didn't you?!
The time when you even begin to think...
that you could live through in this world IS REALLY DANGEROUS!
Remember that, if you wouldn't like to fade away soon!
I-I'll take it to my heart.
Huh? "Now that I've heard such news I can't wait for the next time!"
"Please do it right now?!"... they say?
Everyone, stand by full of fea... expectation!
Hey, let's cherish our fans' feelings here...
and broadcast it now without any stinginess on the money!
Ehh, no, don't you think that's a bit impossible...
Can't we do anything about that? It's just 30 minutes. I'm begging you too!
But it's over after all...
So, please send your messages to me to the radio or to the site, etc.!
Bye-nii!
Ahh, what should I do? If I endanger the lead that'd be bad, right?
Yes, that is right.
It's pretty common that the friends of the main characters,
the villains or other characters gain most popularity.
Oh, A-A-Akira-sama, what happened?
You know...
Yes?
Is that about yourself?
Arent you getting on high spirits just because you've been popular recently?
Nonono, there's nothing like that!
Are you thinking that you can beat anyone?
Nono, no such thing...
Are you thinking that you're the number one in the popularity poll?!
What are you saying? Something like that...
Now you cut the crap!
There's no way such thing'd be!
Just liste–
Main Translation: JEEB
Translation Checking: xbe
Ohh... And the next one will be the duet between Tsukasa and Miyuki-san!
Yuki-chan, let's go to the front and sing!
Yes...
Timing: JEEB
Snoopy007
Typesetting: Snoopy007
Encoder: heedly
QC: ansonyyp
It really is mysterious that Konata selects the song for Tsukasa and Miyuki...
Opening Karaoke: JEEB
Ending Karaoke: Snoopy007
I properly know various songs, too, they say.
So it's an anime song after all...
Anime songs are unexpectedly useful at times like these.
こんなこといいな　できたらいいな
konna koto ii na,　dekitara ii na
Such nice things, would be great if we could do them.
あんなゆめ　こんなゆめ　いっぱいあるけど
anna yume　konna yume　ippai aru kedo...
We have a lot of different dreams like that,..
みんなみんなみんな　かなえてくれる
minna minna minna 　kanaete kureru
All, all, all of them, will be granted...
ふしぎなポッケで　かなえてくれる
fushigi na pokke de　kanaete kureru
Granted by that mysterious pocket.
そらをじゆうに　とびたいな
sora wo jiyuu ni　tobitai na
Yes, I would like to fly freely through that sky...
Here! Bamboo copter!
That's not similar at all!
アンアンアン　とってもだいすきドラえもん
AN AN AN　tottemo daisuki DORAEMON
An-an-an, I like him very much - Doraemon!
This video was brought to you by JEEB & STAR
しゅくだいとう
shukudai tou
It's my homework shif...
And so, the next Lucky Star is?
It's me, Tsukasa.
Well, you know...
The other day I got really hungry during the night,
but because it was late already, I was troubled whether or not to eat...
And in the end I decided to eat just a bit.
So I went to the kitchen, thinking that those leftovers...
of sweets were still there, but when I opened the fridge...
Ah!? Is it time already?!
"
Let's
Next Time: Let's Go To The Festival
Look forward to it!