Now, let'ssu begin yoo!
It's gonna come now...
Fungaa!
Now start out already!
曖昧3センチ
Aimai 3 senchi
Unclear 3 centimeters...
そりゃぷにってことかい？ちょっ!
Sorya punitte koto kai? cho!
Is that a puni? Waitasec!
らっぴんぐが制服…
Rappingu ga seifuku…
The uniform's the wrapping…
だぁぁ不利ってことない　ぷ。
Daa furitte koto nai　Pu.
Hey, there's no disadvantage in that, yeah.
がんばっちゃ♥やっちゃっちゃ
Ganbaccha♥yacchaccha
Try your best♥do the thing-cha,
そんときゃーっち&Releaseぎョッ
son tokyaacchi & ririisu gyo
at that time, well, catch & release, gyo!
汗っ、々っ
A-se, a-se!
In the sweaty, sweaty...
の谷間にDarlin'darlin'F R E E Z E!!
No taniai ni daarin daarin furiiーzu!
valley darlin' darlin' FREEZE!!
なんかダるー、なんかデるー
NankaDAruuー, nankaDEruー
Somewhat lazy..., something's coming out...
あいしテるー
AishiTEruuー
I love you...
あれ一個が違ってるんるー
Are ikko ga chigatterunruー
One of those is different, ruー.
なやみン坊ー 高鉄棒 おいしん簿ー
NayamiNbouー Koutetsubou oishinboー
A worrywart, high horizontal bar - an ever-lengthening list...
いーかげんにシナサイ
Iikagen ni SHINASAI
Now get reasonable!
飛んでったアイツの火照るカラダって
Tondetta AITSU no hoteru KARADAtte
The burning body of who flied away right now is...
所謂ふつーのおにゃのコ
Iwayuru futsuu no onya no KO
what is called a "usual girl".
驚いた、
Odoroita,
I'm surprised,
あたしだけ? 豚骨ハリガネおかわりダー!!!!
atashi dake? tonkotsu harigane okawari daaー!!!!
Only me? I get an extra portion of tonkotsu with super hard noodlesー!!!!
BON-BONおーえん団
BON-BON oーendan
Bon-bon cheering team.
Let's get! Cherry pie
Let's get! Cherry pie.
RAN-RAN　かんげー会
Ranraan　kangeーikai
RAN-RAN, welcoming party.
Look up! せんせーしょん
Look up! Senseーshon
Look up! Sensation.
はい！　存在感・・小惑星
Haai　Sonzaikan　tenten　shouwakusei
Yes, feeling of being here・・meteor!
ぶつかって溶けました　呆然　大いに歌ってシレンジャー
Butsukatte tokemashita　bouzen　ooi ni utatte shirenjyaー
Got melt from the collision, dumbfounded and singing a lot, "Shiranger!"
もっていけ!
Motte ike!
Take and go!
最後に笑っちゃうのはあたしのはず
Saigo ni waracchau no wa atashi no hazu
The last one laughing should be me,
セーラーふくだからです
Seeraa fuku dakara desu
because it's a seeraa fuku.
←結論
←Ketsuron
←It's the conclusion.
月曜日なのに！
Getsuyoubi nanoni!
Even if it's monday!
機嫌悪いのどうするよ？
Kigen warui no dou suru yo？
What will you do with that bad mood?
夏服がいいのです←キャ？ワ！イイｖ
Natsufuku ga ii no desu←KYA?WA!IIv
I want my summer uniform←It!Is!Cute!
接近3ピクト するまでってちゅーちょだ　やん☆
Sekkin san pikuto, suru madette chuーcho da　yan☆
Getting closer's in three paces, I'll hesitate until you do 'it' Oh☆
頑張って　張り切って
Ganbatte,　harikitte
Try your best, be on high,
My Darlin'darlin' P L E A S E!!
Mai daarin daarin puriizu
my darlin' darlin' please!
Today was the most cheerful day of this fall, at every city in this country sports festivals begin to open.
Ooh, I came to cheer for my daughter, but to be on so high mood was a bit unexpected...
I could take a lot of good photos!
Daddy... Where in the world is that "daughter"?
With Vitality,
Even If It's Not Me
Ahh, should I cut my hair for the sports festival?
Something like drastic short...
Eh, oneechan, you'll cut your hair?
Even though you lengthened them for a long time...
Ah...
Even though I only said it without intensions...
The purposeful reaction right now...
There's definitely a man about there!
Don't join everything there!
Tsukasa, don't you say unnecessary things, too!
But if Kagami would cut her hair...
A rising short, you know...
It's pretty usual, right?
That's no good! Twin-tails are the basis for tsundere!
Well sorry for having an uninteresting face!
Now that you mention it, the sports festival will be soon. How troublesome...
That's not a line for young people to say, now isn't it...
Kona-chan, you're OK because you're good with sports, but I even...
get my feet wrapped around myself...
It'll be OK.
Oneechan, in what manner will you participate?
Iyaa, if we're talking about Kagami, it should be...
that pastrie-eating contest, right?
I did think about this from before, but are you possibly begging for a fight?
And so, Kagami, where are participating, after all?
Huh?
Ah...
Did I hit it? Hey, did I hit it on the head?
This girl's irritating!
And so I'm minimizing my weight and stuff just for the sports festival.
It's the autumn of sports, too.
Hee...
But are you really doing it for the festival?
Actually it's for the performance afterwards, now isn't it?
Now what is?
Hmm?
Would you like me to say it?
This girl really pisses me off...
Ah, so Miyuki's on the team relay race.
But, well, I can understand that...
Well, first she was supposed to be in the hurdle race, but...
Ball rolling
Run
Hurdle race
Shiraishi
Takara
Izumi
Matsuo
Yamada
Lookie! There are no other candidates, right?
I haven't done that yet, so I'm looking forward to it.
That's no good Miyuki-san!
Eh?
Miyuki-san, you can't do hurdles bexause the bumps in your body are sharp.
Various things will pass through, too.
Ehe!
After I said that she was put on the relay race.
You... What are you saying middle-aged old mens' lines...
Now that you mention it, were there borrowing races and stuff at your junior high school?
Ah, yes, there were.
Hmm...
There was one time I got called...
"Me"?
What?
In the end...
they didn't even tell me what borrowing I was called for...
"There's too much knowledge of impossible-to-tell aspects..."
Well, let's hear Miyuki-san about non-understood things.
Don't ask such things, as they're limitlessly hard to answer to...
But she's really asking about it!
A thing that could be called in for a borrowing race,...
a bit hard-to-say characteristic of yours, Izumi-san, now is it?
Hmm...
Could it not be "a person with a mole on the face" or something like that?
According to some people, it's a thing they care about, too.
As expected... or should I say she's really perfected her evasion tactics?
But I don't think that's it...
I'm really looking forward to the sports festival, but the tests are right after it, are they not?
When the festival ends, you feel lonely as all the events go away at the same time.
It's just the midterm examination, the achievement test and the final examinations with tests, too.
The second term is all filled with events and you end up using all your energy during the culture and sports festivals...
Yeah...
Especially the midterm examination is hard, now isn't it?
Ohh...
They even call it "The fall of reading", so should I read a book, too?
And it is really a good season for studies, too.
Before Christmas is the time a lot of new games will come out, too!
But first are the final examinations.
Ooohhh...
Ah, now I remember...!
You two! Wouldn't you stop evading the reality...
Eh-he...
Ah, so the sports festival'll be soon then.
There's the startup pistol, now isn't there?
I thought that it was the real thing until junior high...
That's impossible!"
that was the first trigger for me to dream about police officers...
"Even though it has nothing in common she's so influenced..."
By the way, Konata...
when is your school's sports festival?
Here. It's on the next Sunday.
The ne...next Sunday?! Why don't you say such precious things faster?
Well, I got this information today...
I can't stand like this speaking!
Huh?
I wonder why he's hurrying that much...
Here we are! Today at last is the real thing!
Let's show the fruits of our recent training!
Sensei! I haven't practiced that much, but I have strong feeling about the performance!
Don't say it so plainly!
In any case, let's show people something to see at the cavalry battle!
The basic strategy is to surround them and beat them up like octopuses!
To attack from the low-defence- areas, too, now is it!
But it's only taking the hat off, so to hit someone is a bit...
It's no good to mind about small things, that's what is called "The mistake of youth."!
It's a boy, now isn't it...
Oneechan, try your best!
Please try your best!
Hey, how could that anpan be stuck together with the string?
I think it propably should be attached with a clip or something...
Hmm... So you can't take it off so easily...
Go for the victory!
Girls are to be elegant!
You think there are elegant pastrie-eating contests around?!
Set!
HereIComee!
Ah!
Angh!
She did it!
It's Kagamin, as expected...
Hm?
That person has an amazing camera...
Oh, he's so easy to understand...
Hey, you're participating in the next 100m race, right?
For the moment...
How wonder how could I run as fast as Kona-chan?
In things like this the image is important! The image!
On your mark!
Set!
Boy, surely an old image recording, now isn't it...
Goaly!
Like that...
Are you serious?!
3 meters twenty-five!
Aah, so it's counted to the point your hands touch the ground...
ComeNGetSome!
Here!
Ah!
Yes!
Uwah!
Kagami, as always... So she shoves herself even into the sand...
1-2-3, 1-2-3...
"It seems that hurdles go well when you match the timing by the number of steps."
"By the number of steps?"
"It's 'one, two, three'."
"I see..."
But... 1-2-3...
1-2-3...
Set!
1-... Wah!
Err... 3-2-3...
1-3... Huh?
Wah! I started from the right foot, so...
Wah, why...?!
Wah, I just don't get it! Now it's the left foot, so...
3-3-3, 3-2-3... Ah!
Ooh, she's perfectly knocking down all of them...
A talent, in a way.
Ah... Ajyapaa...
Heheh... It was completely hopeless...
Well, you know, I thought my daughter would be in the race...
A usual turn of events...
At last it's the last relay race!
Yuki-chan, do your best!
No, as I said... My daughter's... Hey, wait a minute! But I haven't done anything yet!
"Yes! Get there! Kanna, go for it!"
Ooh...
Ah, we did it! Look, we're second!
They do it quite well...
Sacchi, here here!
There!
Got it!
We're going to be third...
It's a worthy race just because of that.
Do your best!
Here! Got it!
They're quite trying their best.
It got pretty interesting...
I wonder if Yuki-chan'll be OK...
There! Got it!
Ooh...!
Unh...!
Do you best, Miyuki!
You did it! Yuki-chan, you're so cool!
Miyuki-san, as expected... She doesn't forget about spectator service, either...
Lucky Star!
Aah...
And...
Ah, It's Tsukasa...
Oh, well...
Sailor, Liebe...
tn. A way of learning the first ten atomic-numbered chemical elements in Japanese
my boat...
and...
Ah...
A... ah...h...
A... ah... h... h... a-a-ah...
Hey! Can't you do something better a bit?
I'm sorry...
I did select to do the alto on the music class's recorder quartette...
but my fingers are about to get cramped...
Ah...
Why did you select the alto?
So-somehow I thought that the lower part would be easier...
Hmm... For now, why don't you try to get your fingers accustomed by playing something simple?
Yeah!
Aah...
Phew...
Mostly missing now aren't you...
Well, I'll try to match, so...
One-two!
He-hey...
Try to play by yourself now, Tsukasa.
Someway different...
Why wouldn't you try to play, well, more easily...?
It might go surprisingly well if you'd take off the power...
Ah, so... Easily, it is...
Yeah, I'll try!
Phew...
Aah...
Aah!
Ah...hui!
Isn't she sucking more than she's blowing?
I did think that sometimes it's good to go for the school dinner...
but they're crowded, now...
It's really astounding... queues are so troublesome, and you get tired...
You just hate it, don't you...
Aren't you accustomed to these at events and all?
Before that I don't like queues without happiness and nervousness...
You're the one really loyal to your desires.
Now that you mention it, when I went to a theme park earlier...
there was one time when I thought that I was lining for an attraction, but it was the toilet line...
It's the basis to check for what the queue is first...
Even though I waited for two hours...
Ah, I, too, when already thinking that it was my turn after queueing,...
had several times when something was sold out for the person before me...
Ah, calculation... I even hate to imagine it...
It's just that Tsukasa doesn't have luck.
Ah, look, everyone! What will you take today?
Well, I think curry'll be good... There's no chances for bad in that...
I'll take raamen.
Me too!
I thought I'd take miso raamen today, with a lot of corn and soft seaweed!
Kagami, you're twin-clear both raamen and pudding, right?
If I'd have room after it...
Isn't there always?
Ngh!
What about you, Yuki-chan?
I'll pick the sandwich, the strawberry one, for now.
Aah, that's so Miyuki-san- like.
Indeed.
By the way, isn't a strawberry sandwich a dessert?
I wonder if it can be classified as "main"?
Y-yes, that is true...
You dwell upon the strangest of things...
Ah!
Kona-chan, what about the chocolate cornet you're always eating? Aren't sweet rolls snacks?
"Even Tsukasa slams now..."
Well, let's leave that aside...
It's really unlucky, but Miyuki-san... the line for sandwiches is over there.
That's so like her...
Walking is a nutrient, too...
Ah, look, it's your turn, Kona-chan.
Curry please, with much roux.
Yes, yes.
You're really in your heyday.
When I can get something, I take it.
Yes, the next person!
Soy raamen, please.
With stiff noodles.
Yes, just wait for a second...
Yes, here is your curry.
I'll go on front and take the seats!
I'll count on you!
Thanks!
Err, the next person.
Ah, yes. I'd like miso raamen.
Aw, sorry... The noodles ended with the last person, raamen is now sold out.
Ah!?
You know, if you're OK with soy taste, will you eat this?
I'll be OK with the kitsune udon, too.
Thanks, oneechan...
Oh, oneechan?
Huh?
The "big sister" and "little sister" were determined by the order we got out, right?
Yeah, that's true.
I just thought that I got lucky with being the younger one.
Ahahah, why is that?
Well, because it'd be a bit miserable if the older one would get notes shown or helped with studies from the younger...
Well, I just think that for now it has nothing in common with showing homework and stuff...
And as we're twins, there's no "older sister" or "younger sister"!
Don't think about it and do your homework now.
Yeah!
But if I'd be the older one, I'd be as firm as oneechan...
Oneechan, show me your homework!
Again? Oh, there's nothing I can do with you, Kagami...
Heey, are you OK? Keep yourself in one piece.
Aah, it's getting really weird!
Dadan!
My own postcard...
got on...
Newtype!
It's on sale in May!
Saitama prefecture, Izumi Konata...
The blistered one...
Oh, you got lucky. It's really impressive that this got on...
...just look at it...
Hmm...
This is great! I'm really surprised, there's really not much things like these!
Oh, you, really... Now should I say there's one more pleasure in buying. Don't you praise me that much...
Ooh...
1260 yen and 567 yen, now is it...
With another volume I'll reach the points...
Oh, well, something for now...
Hmm...
No, that'll turn into what they'll want...
That's not how the wholesale store'll get it sold!
To make people buy something they didn't plan for the points... That's their trick!
Huh-huh... I'm not foolish enough to get caught in something like that...
And!
Oh, I forgot that the fifth volume was already out! This'll be OK!
Fuwa-an-an...
It'll be 2587 yen.
Aaah...
Aaaah...aah..aaa.hhhahaha.hhhhh
Oh, well...
For propagation...
Ahh, I'm sorry...
They don't break... Yeah, they don't want to get loose...
Yes...
I thought that such things only exist in manga or games, but they really are in reality, too.
That's true.
That means... That those two just got their flags up!
Konata... Fantasy is written with "to feel illusions"...
Wouldn't you just split your dreams and the reality?
Lucky Star
LUCKY CHANNEL!
Good lucky!
Today too, bringing out love with a dream-coloured heart, it's me - the navigator of Lucky Channel, Kogami Akira!
Similarly, I'm the assistant - Shiraishi Minoru!
As a fast thing, this programme is already on its eight time on air...
That is true. Now if we won't gradually think about new things they'll call us stale.
What did you say?
What should... What should I do?!
No... I just... thought that it'd be good to do different stuff...
Then do...
Ah, yes yes!
When I was walking around town some time ago, I got called!
Was it a questionnaire for a beauty lounge?
Oh, Shiraishi-san, was that seriussly sed?
Noo, of course it was a fan...
You just don't have things like that,...
RIIIGHT?!
No-no-noo, I don't...
Yeah, I thought SO!
You're the assistant,...
RIGHT?!
Oh well, try your best.
Kyahaa!
But there's so many fan letters -here we go- shouichitto- to me!
Annn! W-Why do you have?!
Hey, Itou! Haven't I gotten any?!
Hmm... This is amazing... like a voice actor...
RRR, Now isn't there? What?! Just one?!
"Your membership card's validness limit is getting closer..."
Hey this... isn't it Men-Terebi written in here?!
Everyone sitting in front of the TV, please send me fan letters, too!
A really, really, really big recruitment!
Akira-sama, shouldn't we proceed to the mai...
Don't you go riding on your spirit...
You can be easily replaced...
Ngh!
Excuse me...
Jya-jaan! I'll be announcing now!
For a surprise, we've ended up with a plan to make a figurine plan at this show!
Akira-sama, the clip art is upside-down!
You're so good, Akira-sama, doing it while you understand it yourself...
To tell you the truth, the project this time is...
peron, pe-peron...
"Don't touch me..."
Pero, pero, pero...
Oh, this is strange...
Err, the project this time is...
"Don't-Touch-Me."
Err, this time is... Hu-h?!
De... Pero! Pe-pe-pe...  Ngh!
Waah! What's with this stuff?!
Tsk, Aaah...
He-hey! Seishi!
Aa..! Akira-sama, please calm down! That's the name of the manager for the person inside! Hey!
You're tearing it away! Tearing! I'm telling you not to tear it away!
You... Don't say you did thi...!
I can't even read it!
Yes! And so...
we will decide what kind of character will be made into a figurine this time by your votes!
I bet you're having a bit of hot feelings about getting this character put into a figurine!
Gwah!... Everybody, I'm counting on your voting!
Yes, and so we will be ending this around here.
Please look forwards to the next Lucky Channel!
Bye-nii!
Isn't it understandable that with such markers it's sure that a character from the main series will take the lead?
What's this? I'm not feeding this to the watchers!
Oh, it's not decided like that yet.
Ah, is that so? A figurine version of me.
What are you talking about? This is...
Yuki-chan, you're great!
Oh, the pleasure was mine.
I think I just saw one of Miyuki's unexpected sides...
That is... it's embarrassing...
Hey, hey! Yuki-chan, then let's sing together!
Ah, let's do like that!
Ooh, sing sing! Is it a duet?
Which do you think you could sing?
Oh, let's see...
And well, to this empty spot this me will...
Are you going to sing on Tsukasa's turn?!
Kagami, just sing more, too.
What's this?
Monkey!
Masaaki's Son Goku was really good...
Ah, not Shingo-chan?
That's the third remake. This is the original series version that was shown from 1978 to 1980.
How old are you anyways?!
Now this is a long intro...
Here the famous narration by Akutagawa-sensei goes by!
We don't know that!
Ah, it's coming!
あじゃーん！
Ajyaan!
Shouting again, is it?!
Born from an egg on a mountain...
Amg, amg, oh this was english - I don't want it...
You lead us repeatedly and now this?!
And so, the next Lucky Star is?
It's me, Miyuki.
When you express the large appearance of things, you can use the word "choudokyuu".
But the "do" in it derives from the British Navy's Dreadnought battleships, that entered service in 1906.
That is to say, the original meaning of "choudokyuu" was "a Bigger class than the battleship Dreadnought",...
which, with time, seems to have altered into and used with the meaning I expressed on earlier.
Next time: A Feeling Like That
Look forward to it!