Yoshimizu Kagami
Theatre
Now, let'ssu begin yoo!
It's gonna come now...
Fungaa!
Now start out already!
曖昧3センチ
Aimai 3 senchi
Unclear 3 centimeters...
そりゃぷにってことかい？ちょっ!
Sorya punitte koto kai? cho!
Is that a puni? Waitasec!
らっぴんぐが制服…
Rappingu ga seifuku…
The uniform's the wrapping…
だぁぁ不利ってことない　ぷ。
Daa furitte koto nai　Pu.
Hey, there's no disadvantage in that, yeah.
がんばっちゃ♥やっちゃっちゃ
Ganbaccha♥yacchaccha
Try your best♥do your thing-cha,
そんときゃーっち&Releaseぎョッ
son tokyaacchi & ririisu gyo
at that time, well, catch & release, gyo!
汗っ、々っ
A-se, a-se!
In the sweaty, sweaty...
の谷間にDarlin'darlin'F R E E Z E!!
No taniai ni daarin daarin furiiーzu!
cleavage darlin' darlin' FREEZE!!
Fan        subs
E
J
B
E
なんかダるー、なんかデるー
NankaDAruuー, nankaDEruー
Somewhat lazy..., something's coming out...
あいしテるー
AishiTEruuー
I love you...
あれ一個が違ってるんるー
Are ikko ga chigatterunruー
One of those is different, ruー.
なやみン坊ー 高鉄棒 おいしん簿ー
NayamiNbouー Koutetsubou oishinboー
A worrywart, high horizontal bar - an ever-lengthening list...
いーかげんにシナサイ
Iikagen ni SHINASAI
Now get reasonable!
飛んでったアイツの火照るカラダって
Tondetta AITSU no hoteru KARADAtte
The burning body of who flied away right now is...
所謂ふつーのおにゃのコ
Iwayuru futsuu no onya no KO
what is called a "usual girl".
驚いた、
Odoroita,
I'm surprised,
あたしだけ? 豚骨ハリガネおかわりダー!!!!
atashi dake? tonkotsu harigane okawari daaー!!!!
Only me? I get an extra portion of tonkotsu with super hard noodlesー!!!!
BON-BONおーえん団
BON-BON oーendan
Bon-bon cheering team.
Let's get! Cherry pie
Let's get! Cherry pie.
RAN-RAN　かんげー会
Ranraan　kangeーikai
RAN-RAN, welcoming party.
Look up! せんせーしょん
Look up! Senseーshon
Look up! Sensation.
はい！　存在感・・小惑星
Haai　Sonzaikan　tenten　shouwakusei
Yes, feeling of being here・・meteor!
ぶつかって溶けました　呆然　大いに歌ってシレンジャー
Butsukatte tokemashita　bouzen　ooi ni utatte shirenjaー
Got melt from the collision, dumbfounded and singing a lot, "Shiranger!"
もっていけ!
Motte ike!
Take and go!
最後に笑っちゃうのはあたしのはず
Saigo ni waracchau no wa atashi no hazu
The last one laughing should be me,
セーラーふくだからです
Seeraa fuku dakara desu
because it's a sailor fuku.
←結論
←Ketsuron
←Conclusion.
月曜日なのに！
Getsuyoubi nanoni!
Even if it's monday!
機嫌悪いのどうするよ？
Kigen warui no dou suru yo？
What will you do with that bad mood?
夏服がいいのです←キャ？ワ！イイｖ
Natsufuku ga ii no desu←KYA?WA!IIv
I want my summer uniform←It!Is!Cute!
接近3ピクト するまでってちゅーちょだ　やん☆
Sekkin san pikuto, suru madette chuーcho da　yan☆
Getting closer's in three paces, I'll hesitate until you do 'it' Oh☆
頑張って　張り切って
Ganbatte,　harikitte
Try your best, be on high,
My Darlin'darlin' P L E A S E!!
Mai daarin daarin puriizu
my darlin' darlin' please!
Hey, everyone! Get to your seats!
Congrats on the new year!
Somehow last year went so fast, but treat me well this year, too.
But then there's someone who's only going to be treated well...
for another three months...
I wonder who am I talking about...
Sensei! It's not me, right?! I can believe that, right?!
A Delicious Day
They do talk about the "New Year's feeling",
but there's certainly a mysterious atmosphere, right?
And when the school begins the atmosphere suddenly changes, unfortunately.
Oh well... Certainly during the New Year mysterious powers are on the move...
Even though helping my family during the first three days of the year was so hectic...
I still...
gained weight!
Haa... New Year's magic now is it...
As it's cold it is hard to burn fat, now isn't it...
Even though I moved quite a lot...
I was busy with the shrine maiden job during the first three days as well...
But you made up for that eating-wise, didn't you?
Like miko-newyearsfood, miko-ozouni, miko-sweets, sweets, sweets, sweets, sweets, miko-sweets!
But you see hanetsuki, playing cards of the famous 100 poems,
and rising a kite portrayed as the ways of enjoying New Year,
although practically you don't see people do that, right?
Well, now they're telling...
that it's dangerous due to electric lines and traffic, too.
I watched TV and read books then.
After the busy first three days, that is.
Err, I did.
I enjoyed hanetsuki, card play and fukuwarai and the like...
Eh? You certainly don't look like it...
Certainly our house is western- styled,
but the one in the countryside is heavily Japanese- style...
I did also go to the first shrine visit in a kimono, and played with my cousins.
"Even when the gods
Held sway in the ancient days..."
tn. Seventeenth poem from the Hyakunin Isshu
Far more Japanese than me!
More Japanese-styled than our place!
But isn't fukuwarai...
If I remember right Hyakunin Isshu contains only waka, right?
tn: waka - Japanese poetry
Yes. It is a play where you read the first part...
of a poem and take the card with the last part.
It's amazing you can do it.
Oh no, I am not that good yet. Those who are, move very furiously and fast.
No, I rather meant...
that I don't like it as it's like studying the classics...
and doesn't feel like playing...
People like that who don't want to do intellectual games...
are making Japan into a no-good country.
If you're already at it would card battling with the Hyakunin Ishuu be no good?
Look! As a buddhist priest, was it Semimaru?..
tn: Semimaru - a Heian age poet
The sparkly-sparkly attack forces of Semimaru!
The lovely attack of Onono Komachi!
Isn't it interesting?
That again?!
But if you'd done some of those bodily plays,
wouldn't you've lost some weight?
You're annoying! It's the fault of the omochi...
tn: omochi - a Japanese rice cake made of glutinous rice pounded into paste and molded into shape.
Omochi has high calories.
I've heard that at the size of a matchbox they have the calories of one bowl of rice.
So Kagami had a bowl of rice every time..!?
Even you ate omochi, right?!
At our place there's no mommy, so we haven't really eaten ozouni...
tn: ozouni - a Japanese soup meal, usually with omochi
Or should I say that we don't eat omochi itself that much...
Uwah! What a waste!
With soup, azuki bean soup or mushrooms...
Even though there are so many tasty ways to eat omochi...
Ahh... This feels like you'd fail again due to omochi next year too, Kagami...
Izumi-san, what is eaten at your home during the new year instead of omochi?
Pizza and pasta and stuff...
Our year starts with raw pasta!
Every end of the year dad cleans the pasta machine.
Did you know? If you don't use it for a while it rusts.
And if you use it without cleaning, the pasta turns out, you know... black...
So we first clean it, and then bake raw pasta and pizza dough.
Genuine, now isn't it.
Well, at Kagami's place pizza is a delivered one,
and pasta is from a can anyhow, right?
Ahh... I mean, we don't eat pizza or pasta during the new year either way...
Can't be!
It doesn't mix with New Year's food, now does it?
It does! It's perfect with roasted chicken, right?!
Now is that for New Year?
Huh? Yeah, it is.
It's a western New Year's dish.
Eh? Is it such a thing?
What kind of things did you eat at your place, Miyuki-san?
Me?
Miyuki-san, your place seems like a rich western one,
so it feels like you wouldn't eat New Year's dishes or omochi...
A French full course or the likes, right from the New Year?
It's not like that...
I ate New Year's dishes and couldn't bite the omochi off skillfully,
so I just kept on doing the "unyo~n"...
What's with this walking 'moe' element?!
Omochi unyo~n.
But the New Year just seems to pass so fast...
Yeah, that's right. The winter holidays end fast, don't they?
It's a long vacation of a kind, but you really don't have that much time to rest...
with all that cleaning, writing New Year's cards and doing homework.
Wait a sec!
I haven't gotten a card and you copied my homework yesterday, didn't you?!
Ugu~
That reminds me, Kona-chan - have you had your first dream of the year?
N... Ah, was it the thing that if you see one, it's a good sign?
Yes, yes.
Generally it's said as "Ichi-Fuji, Ni-taka, San-nasubi", right?
tn: One-Mt. Fuji, Two-Hawk, Three-Eggplant, visit "Hatsuyume"@Wikipedia
Besides the formal ones,
tn: Four-Fan, Five-Tobacco, Six-Blind Musician
there seem to be "Yon-sen, Go-tabako, Roku-zatou" as well.
Hee, so there were six in total...
But, you know...
You don't usually see dreams with things like that, right?
What kind of dream? With a blind musician?!
Oh, well...
Hey, hey! Do you have to see all of them at once?
If you saw all of them you'd have unbelievably good fortune,
but if I remember correctly it is enough to see one of them.
I thought that you'd have to see two hawks, or three eggplants.
Or should I say bluntly...
You don't really remember your dreams in the first place, right?
People that sense them are really enjoying the New Year, don't you think?
Certainly...
My first dream was that as I opened the shoe box, my shoes were gone...
and as I reluctantly tried to go home using the shoes of a person inside,
the size didn't match - a dream like that,...
I checked its meaning in an Oneiromantic encyclopedia...
and it seemed to be a suggestion that I seek social power,
but that it will still take more time before I gain it.
The shoes seem to imply a social position.
Cheese Cake?
Miyuki-san... You're quite an ambitious person... I understand and also don't...
It seems that some people climbed onto stage...
while in full swing and went wild at the coming-of age celebration hall again.
I wonder if they aren't conscious that they had become a part of Japan's face.
I wonder why they do it all the way in the hall.
Indeed...
The coming-of-age celebration is so bothersome...
you don't want to go there, right?
I guess this gal'll become a useless adult if she stays like this...
What will you two put on for your coming-of-age celebration?
It's a rare occasion, so I think I'll go with a furisode,
tn: furisode - a long-sleeved kimono
what about you?
Ohh, well, I think it's gonna be a furisode because of my dad's suggestions...
Ah, if it's your dad...
But...
tn: 7-5-3 - the festival day for children aged seven, five and three
If you wear a furisode,
it's closer to 7-5-3 than to a coming-of-age celebration.
NewYear, treatmewell!
Oh, neesan - congratulations. Even if it's a bit late.
Ohh, my husband was home...
and a lot happened during the New Year, too...
Oh, and then my younger sister got fever...
That's because she has a weak body...
Just a moment!
By no means was I stingy with the New Year money, don't be mistaken!
Revealing the truth without being asked, that's an officer, huh...
A contest in hyakunin isshu was held, causing great excitement...
That reminds me,
what did you play during the New Year when you were a child, neesan?
When I was a child?
Oh, yes, I did do a lot... Yes, well...
Dot, dot, dot, dot...
This is a bit embarrasing, I don't remember at all...
Neesan is really living only on the upbeatness...
I haven't ever heard her say something seriously...
I even outran my memories!
This is a free softsub.Not for sale, rent, auction or hardsub.
Not for sale, rent, auction or hardsub.This is a free softsub.
or hardsub.This is a free softsub. Not for sale, rent, auction
Recently Tsukasa has stayed in the kotatsu all the time...
tn: kotatsu - Table with a heater installed beneath. Very common in Japan.
That's because it's cold...
Ahh, I understand. Kotatsu are good, aren't they...
When you're in one it's even a hassle to go to the toilet...
Yes, yes.
But I think it would be better not to say it that loud...
But there's a clincher at our place...
that moves people from their kotatsu even if they don't want to.
Hee, what kind of?
Konata, if you are in the kotatsu all the time, I'll put it away.
So your dad is OK even without one?
Although he does like it usually, maybe to punish me?
As there are times when we fall asleep together in a kotatsu...
Ahh, I know that!
But don't they say that you'll catch a cold if you sleep in a kotatsu?
Yes, that's why we always shut it down once noticed.
Somehow doesn't a kotatsu have both heaven and hell in it?
Eh?
It's the same before you first turn one on,
but kotatsus that aren't lit somehow feel unresonable cold as well...
Yeah! I understand that awfully well!
Isn't it hard when you get out of bed in the morning as well?
Yeah, but if you say so,
it's really cold in a bath on the way from the dressing room to the bathtub...
But you do have doubts about running naked...
As you slip, yeah...
And then,
isn't it unpleasant when you want to go to the toilet during the night...
Aww, that I know...
Hey! We're getting off!
From getting off the bus until reaching the classroom is hell, too, isn't it?
Yeah...
It's soon Valentine's, isn't it?
During this season, the atmosphere becomes brighter, doesn't it?
Every year again...
Even while just living along as usual,
the oscillating atmosphere of nervousness tickels you.
I think that on days like this, when everyone feels special,
if people would confess together, and the feelings were to match,
that'd be very lovely.
Ahh.. Tsukasa is a pure girl, now isn't she?
Even I can't say that it's a conspiracy
made by the confections companies, though.
Well, you could say that it's special for me as well...
Since the unsold chocolate becomes cheap every year,
I'm aiming for the chocolate I can use as material for a self-made one.
Or should I say that you have no dreams at all...
It is often said that "You can't buy love with money!",
but in a way the valentine chocolate is showing love with money, right?
A severe thing said by a gal that has only had romance in games...
Oh well...
In games it's more important to...
earn as much favor as possible before the day comes...
But even if I think about it,
there's nothing unusual for me on Valentine's day...
Guys see too many dreams, as well.
So no-one could raise that "Kagami flag"...
What about you then?!
Yeah! I'm coveted!
Yes, yes... In the games, right?
Hearing about "flags" and "gaining favor" sometimes really...
gets me worried about your future...
Only thinking about game events, that's really...
Ahh, I hate people who don't know jack and are prejudiced...
Oh? Is it different then?
As I recently quit after a short while even measured in in-game-time,
I often don't even get scratched on Valentine's day...
So what!?
But you know, I really have plans to give out chocolate to a person this year.
Huh?! Seriously?!
Yeah... To a person playing the same online game, you know...
To a game friend?!
Yeah.
You don't say you will give it to him personally?!
Nope. It's not like we'd really meet...
Huh?!
I'll hand it out through my character in-game, the player's a human, after all.
Can you really call that "to a person"?!
Isn't that just another in-game character?!
What are you saying to my wife?!
Huh?! "Wife"?
Yeah, we got married in-game, and because I'm a male character...
Just wait a second!
Is that like a guy giving chocolate to a girl?
It's rather like a girl giving chocolate to a girl, right?
If the other player's a woman, that is.
It's alright, since the player is male.
Huh?
Ohh... In cases like this it's OK if everyone's enjoying it, i guess.
Yeah, that's right...
I might want to go abroad...
Without any logical connection, again...
Well, yesterday Miyuki-san said that...
For a girl to give out chocolate on the February 14th is peculiar to Japan.
In the west they seem to give out sweets and cards...
to friends and the people they like, regardless of sex.
Heee...
As she said so, doesn't it feel like I'd get a lot of...
confectionery and all, even though I'm a woman!
Simple-mindedness is one thing,
but you have great self-confidence in many ways...
Is being popular something you can presume already?
It's alright, they love them small girls abroa...
STOP! Dangerous talk prohibited!
Err... Would you not mind...
Happy Valentine!
Kona-chan, here you go.
Ohh, incredible wrapping... is the uniform...
Ohh, the inside is incredible as well... Moreover a heart-form...
Ehhehe... I ended up trying my best...
Tsukasa's just enthusiastic about such things, isn't she...
tn: "giri" - obligation, duty - a chocolate that's just given to someone without further meaning
Doing one after another until the morning...
Even though it'd just be a giri.
Tsukasa,
it'd be better for you not to give anything to guys...
even if it's giri, it'll be misunderstood for sure...
He? What?
Ah...
As for the time being, here.
Kagami? You give me chocolate?!
As Tsukasa was doing them, I made some as well. Don't you want it?
Seemingly almighty,
but causing imaginations of her working secretly...
with great effort - that's Kagami moe...
You're annoying! Just be quiet and put it away!
Oh, Kagami?
Here! I'll give you this!
Just so you know, it's just a giri! Just a giri!
S-sorry for making them all distorted in shape!
You little fool.
Isn't the important part that you made them for me, not the shape?
Wh- Y-you idiot... I said it's not like that...
There's nothing like that?
No, there ain't, so be quiet and put it away!
I'm a first-timer for things like these...
The first time is essential.
So, Miyuki-san, did you give out any chocolates?
I gave them to my father and to a related elder brother of mine.
I just gave some to everyone who's nice to me usually.
I gave some to you, Tsukasa and Miyuki.
Oh, so everyone had a dull St. Valentine's day, it seems.
I don't want to be told so by a person who lives in a world of games...
That reminds me, your cousin took the entrance exam for Ryouou, right?
Ahh, I heard that she got in!
It's a long way here from her home, so she'll come to our place next month.
She was like a younger sister to me from the beginning,
and we had a lot of contact, too...
Hee, so it was like that...
But if compared to you, people wouldn't know whom is the younger one, right?
Noo, you know - she's like a younger sister to me in a lot of ways.
Is she so small?!
But passing the test here easily means your cousin's quite intelligent, right?
Depending on who hears that, you could sound a bit presumptuous.
You're a student here too, right?
As... I only barely passed for sure...
Entrance exams... We have exams next year, too.
Ahh, I guess this year will be drowned in studies...
Eh... That's not nice...
Exams...
I wonder if I'll be doing them, haven't thought about the future at all yet...
I think you should seriously think about your future.
Ahh... The words "study" and "work" are really not in my dictionary...
I wonder how it'd be if she embraces the future like that...
Turning her hobby of creating games into profit?
Well you know, it's really just my hobby.
Something like a self-styled mangaka that only earns money at the Comike?
You know, just to try a "Cheese nyoro~n"...
Or perhaps a writer who revives the spirit of inquiry.
"There's only one truth!" Yeah, this is it!
No, a writer that suddenly pinpoint-gets...
Yeah, but... right?
all the popularity could be believable as well.
As she's good with computers, a web designer is possible as well?
J-Ju-Just twist it here!
A scenario writer that brings out more jokes than story.
Ah, so you understood it already?
Then unprobable university pass...
It's all the same situation?!
Huh? What?
Ah!
Smile!
The Customer
is King!
What is it?!
Manager! That "Legendary Girl A" has come again!
What!?
As I got thoroughly left out the the other day...
Manager!
Manager! Manager!
Let's indeed have that Legendary Girl A...
follow our command to reach the cash register today!
Giroro... She seems to be somehow hesitating...
Fufufu... If that is so, shouldn't we solve that hesitation?!
Listen, everyone! Let's get some voice out and go!
Yes!
Alright! Let's go!
Yeah!
Let's go!
Go! Keroron!
Manager, I am probing Legendary Girl A's purchase objective of today.
OK, please do so.
The newest comic is?
Yes, it is the 14th volume of Keroro!
OK! Raise the piled goods until they're in the...
field of vision of Legendary Girl A!
Moreover, deploy pops!
The deployment is complete!
OK, briefly watch over her movement!
What's more, deploy well-selling products...
on the Legendary Girl A's line of flow to the register!
Understood!
Manager, the Legendary Girl A's purchasing objective is not comics!
What?!
Manager, objective changed to DVDs.
OK. Just to be sure,
block the passageways on the side so that...
the Legendary Girl A gets straight to the department of new DVDs!
Understood!
Aah, excuse me...
Tamaa, tamaa...
Oh my, sorry...
Geero-gero-gero-gerogero-iinchou.
Good, good...
Manager, she... finally did... take a product into her hands!
At last, I became the victor here today!
Everybody, we shall be befuddled with joy tonight?
Yes!
It was a feint!
If it comes to this... the last resort is...
Well, bring that bargain ultra-rare out-of-production DVD to me...
Manager, she's heading for the cash register.
Yes! This is good!
This is an emotional scene! Right now everything in me is applauding!
We did it!
That'll be 1785 yen!
Ah!
Ah, I'm short of 3 yen...
Excuse me, please put that back.
I'll be back!
Please visit us at
http://www.wing2.jp/~jeeb
#jeeb@irc.rizon.net
LUCKY CHANNEL!
Good lucky!
Yes, I'll be moderating in high spirits today as well!
As a fast thing, this time Lucky Channel is already on its 13th time!
Yes, your navigator is the completely familiar Kogami Akira!
And...
Yes! I am Akira-sama's assistant, Shiraishi Minoru! My humble greetings!
Yes, that is true. Today's the 13th time, plunging into the second half!
I wonder, if you say it through Mt. Fuji,
it's like climbing until the fifth camp, isn't that so, Akira-sama?
Ah? Mt. Fuji? Can't you just go to the fifth camp with a car?
Ah! Well, that happens to be so...
D-Drill, D-d-drill...
Ah, yes! I have once climbed onto Mt. Takao!
tn: Mt. Takao is a 599m high mountain near Tôkyô...
Huh? Aren't there more important things to talk about?!
Ah, yes that is so...
D-d-d-d-drill!
Ahh that.., these Akira-sama's twin-drills are really good!
What is in what way good?!
Ah... Like a spiral shell, spiralling...
Huh?!
Oh, well...
D... d... drill...
Ah! Well, today a special project!..
The announcement of the Lucky Star Figurine modelling project's results!
Let's have Akira-sama announce them right away!
Yes... The popular character to become a figurine is Izumi Konata-san...
The newest results: 1) Shiraishi Minoru 2) Kogami Akira 3) Hiiragi Kagami 4) Izumi Konata 5) Hiiragi Tsukasa 6) Iwasaki Minami 7) Kusakabe Misao 8) Takara Miyuki 9) Izumi Kanata 10) Kobayakawa Yutaka
Aah... Akira-sama, please read it properly!
Congradulations!
Oh, it was sure to come out like this, what is this - a bought race?!
Oh, oh, oh, oh...
Aah, after all, you know,
the bigwigs like the main program more than this corner...
It's not like that, right?
The newest results: 1) Shiraishi Minoru 2) Kogami Akira 3) Hiiragi Kagami 4) Izumi Konata 5) Hiiragi Tsukasa 6) Iwasaki Minami 7) Kusakabe Misao 8) Takara Miyuki 9) Izumi Kanata 10) Kobayakawa Yutaka
Yeah-yeah.
See! The producer says that, too...
Yes-yes...
I'll let them deceive me as many times as they'd like...
I'm used to betrayal anyways...
To deceive... that's disrespectful...
Speaking about which,
The newest results: 1) Shiraishi Minoru 2) Kogami Akira 3) Hiiragi Kagami 4) Izumi Konata 5) Hiiragi Tsukasa 6) Iwasaki Minami 7) Kusakabe Misao 8) Takara Miyuki 9) Izumi Kanata 10) Kobayakawa Yutaka
you didn't think about something as unbelievable...
as being able to have your own figurine?!
Ohh... Nothing like that!
Here... The figurine this time is to be Izumi Konata-san,
and the figurine of Shiraishi Minoru, who shined..!
What's up with this?!
Well... Oh, the time for us to part has come!
And so, please send a lot of impressions, cheerings and opinions...
about this program afterwards as well.
As we're taking them on the web page etc.
Isn't that so, Akira-sama?
He..Hey?! Just a moment!
I'm going home...
Bye-nii!
A-Akira-sama, please wait!
And, whole staff assemble!
Drill!
Clapping without a reason.
Main Translation: JEEB
Translation Checking: xbe
WaWaWa-忘れ物～
WaWaWa-Wasuremono~
FoFoFo-Forgotten thing~
Timing: JEEB, xbe
Typesetting: Snoopy007
OmegaPhil
JEEB
俺の
Ore no...
My...
俺の忘れ物～
Ore no wasuremono~
This forgotten thing of mine~
Encoder: xbe
QC: Kei Striker
あの日あの時　置き去りにした記憶のカケラ～
Ano hi, ano toki...
Okizari ni shita kioku no kakera~
The fragment of my memories that I abandoned then on that day~
消えっちまったのさ～
Kiecchimatta no sa~
just happened to disappear~
あの子と共に～
Ano ko to tomo ni~
Together with that girl~
赤い夕日がやけに眩しい　恋の城ヶ島～
Akai yuuhi ga yake ni mabushii,
koi no Jyougashima~
The red sunset is violently bright, Jougashima of my love~
How annoying...
You mustn't look at him.
The couple that cheerfully agreed to be in the video
馬鹿な奴だと～
Baka na yatsu da to~
Laugh at me, saying~
笑っておくれ～
Waratte okure~
that I'm a foolish man~
それが俺には　お似合いさ～
Sore ga ore ni wa, oniai sa~
since it really matches me~
Uncrossable Wall
Karaoke: JEEB
だけど～
Dakedo...
However...
ルルルル～
rurururu~
Uncrossable Wall
ルルルル-ルルルル～
rurururu-rurururu~
時にはやさしく～
Toki ni wa yasashiku~
remember to sometimes~
抱いてくれ～
Daite kure~
hold me tight~
This video was brought to you by JEEB
Shiraishi, don't say!?
Coward
And so, the next Sgt. Frog is?
Ni, wrong! It's "the next Lucky Star is?", right?!
Gerogero... I came to think of a good thing!
Japanese animation is now a global video industry.
If we use it to brainwash those puny people,
we could accomplish a puny people invasion at once!
Sergeant-san, you're so clever!
Hmph! How low! If you're a soldier, you go soldier-like with force!
Be quiet, you red daruma!
Wha!?
Now is the time when he, who controls the information controls the battle!
Oh, well, Giroro, you with your old head might not understand.
Wouldn't you just say it?!
And so, the next time "Under One Roof".
Look forward to it ~desu.
Ge-gero~