Yoshimizu Kagami
Theatre
Ah, the B class of third year?
Kuroi-sensei!
Yeah, yeah...
曖昧3センチ
Aimai 3 senchi
Unclear 3 centimeters...
そりゃぷにってことかい？ちょっ!
Sorya punitte koto kai? cho!
Is that a puni? Waitasec!
らっぴんぐが制服…
Rappingu ga seifuku…
The uniform's the wrapping…
だぁぁ不利ってことない　ぷ。
Daa furitte koto nai　Pu.
Hey, there's no disadvantage in that, yeah.
がんばっちゃ♥やっちゃっちゃ
Ganbaccha♥yacchaccha
Try your best♥do your thing-cha,
そんときゃーっち&Releaseぎョッ
son tokyaacchi & ririisu gyo
at that time, well, catch & release, gyo!
汗っ、々っ
A-se, a-se!
In the sweaty, sweaty...
の谷間にDarlin'darlin'F R E E Z E!!
No taniai ni daarin daarin furiiーzu!
cleavage darlin' darlin' FREEZE!!
Fan        subs
E
J
B
E
なんかダるー、なんかデるー
NankaDAruuー, nankaDEruー
Somewhat lazy..., something's coming out...
あいしテるー
AishiTEruuー
I love you...
あれ一個が違ってるんるー
Are ikko ga chigatterunruー
One of those is different, ruー.
なやみン坊ー 高鉄棒 おいしん簿ー
NayamiNbouー Koutetsubou oishinboー
A worrywart, high horizontal bar - an ever-lengthening list...
いーかげんにシナサイ
Iikagen ni SHINASAI
Now get reasonable!
飛んでったアイツの火照るカラダって
Tondetta AITSU no hoteru KARADAtte
The burning body of who flied away right now is...
所謂ふつーのおにゃのコ
Iwayuru futsuu no onya no KO
what is called a "usual girl".
驚いた、
Odoroita,
I'm surprised,
あたしだけ? 豚骨ハリガネおかわりダー!!!!
atashi dake? tonkotsu harigane okawari daaー!!!!
Only me? I get an extra portion of tonkotsu with super hard noodlesー!!!!
BON-BONおーえん団
BON-BON oーendan
Bon-bon cheering team.
Let's get! Cherry pie
Let's get! Cherry pie.
RAN-RAN　かんげー会
Ranraan　kangeーikai
RAN-RAN, welcoming party.
Look up! せんせーしょん
Look up! Senseーshon
Look up! Sensation.
はい！　存在感・・小惑星
Haai　Sonzaikan　tenten　shouwakusei
Yes, feeling of being here・・meteor!
ぶつかって溶けました　呆然　大いに歌ってシレンジャー
Butsukatte tokemashita　bouzen　ooi ni utatte shirenjaー
Got melted by the collision, dumbfounded and singing a lot, "Shiranger!"
もっていけ!
Motte ike!
Take and go!
最後に笑っちゃうのはあたしのはず
Saigo ni waracchau no wa atashi no hazu
The last one laughing should be me,
セーラーふくだからです
Seeraa fuku dakara desu
because it's a sailor fuku.
←結論
←Ketsuron
←Conclusion.
月曜日なのに！
Getsuyoubi nanoni!
Even if it's monday!
機嫌悪いのどうするよ？
Kigen warui no dou suru yo？
What will you do with that bad mood?
夏服がいいのです←キャ？ワ！イイｖ
Natsufuku ga ii no desu←KYA?WA!IIv
I want my summer uniform←It?Is!Cute!
接近3ピクト するまでってちゅーちょだ　やん☆
Sekkin san pikuto, suru madette chuーcho da　yan☆
Getting closer's in three paces, I'll hesitate until you do 'it' Oh☆
頑張って　張り切って
Ganbatte,　harikitte
Try your best, be on high,
my darlin' darlin' please!
My Darlin'darlin' P L E A S E!!
Mai daarin daarin puriizu
Kagami, good morning!
Ossu! You're on good mood, what happened?
I, as well, changed my cell phone to a newer one.
Ohh, so at last...
Really? Isn't she a child to our surprise?
So you became able to set songs and wallpapers to ringtones, right?
J-just wait a sec, I'll watch anime or something!
I have already put my favourite to it.
Or should I say that's an unbelievable song...
But, you know...
As you must answer before it hits the climax of the song, isn't it regrettable -
- or don't you feel that you get stressed with it?
And it'll cut off even if you don't answer it.
I'm not that concerned about that, but is it like that?
Ring
If I should say which Kagami is... she'd be an orc!
Why? Am I the only monster!?
Ah, yes - this is Hiiragi speaking...
Ah, no, no... Just because of my habit of being out...
Even though she was hitting me back until just now...
You know, I ate sandwiches with balsamic oil sauce today,
I wonder why women can change their mood so quickly...
but I wasn't able to judge the taste well.
But earlier our mother...
I have come home now!
Yes, hello?
Huh, Miyuki?
Ahh, honestly..!
Miyuki, here's the phone! It's Konata-chan!
Err... Have I made some kind of mistake.!?
No, our mother is an honest person...
If she'd be angry, she's the type to answer "as is".
She presumably has hit her leg into a corner of a table...
Yeah... But that's a bit different from being two-faced...
She is a person who is as-is, so...
As Miyuki is a knowledgeable, mommy really is saved...
as I can immediately hear about things I don't know.
As I was so glad of my mother's praises,
checking various things became a habit of mine.
Miyuki-chan knows more than mama!
Even though now it's because knowing is pleasing.
So, in other words, I wonder if that means that the way I raised you was good?
...we had a conversation like that...
What's with that natural talk?
For now, I have understood the thing that Miyuki-san...
certainly looks like her as her daughter.
Do we look alike?
Severely on the genetic level!
But... Miyuki isn't just good at studies, she really knows things well.
Nowadays there are many sources of information, too -
- so it's fun, learning various things.
It's impossible for me...
No motivation, I want to play -
- I'll rely on someone if I'm in trouble..!
They do say that the only children and the oldest ones get selfish, but...
Come to think of it, is Miyuki an only child, as well?
Even if you're a similar only child, it all depends on the person, after all.
No...
As in our place we have something that can be called an example,
a presence like the oldest daughter... As we have such a person...
Cleaning is troublesome,
I get tired of washing,
is it OK to have dinner as home delivery?
At our place, there are even two older sisters,
so it gets tough as the meals turn into scrambles.
Wai! It's sukiyaki!
Eat a lot.
Itadakimasu!
And, you know, then Kona-chan said,
that when the mobile phone is out of range,
it's "Because some particles are dense."
Is that so...
And then, you know, they seem to say that...
it's "Complete Silence" when the battery goes dead.
Hmm... The children nowadays do use weird words...
Hey! Let's leave Tsukasa's share, too!
Tsukasa, I'll give you my share...
Thanks!
Saying things like that... Weren't you, Kagami, eating muchingly, too?
Ahh, so having many siblings has it's sides...
And the only children in family have all kinds of things, as well...
Oh, yes-yes! Yuki-chan sometimes ends up gazing vacantly, right?
"Vacantly", is it?
Look, the day before, too...
I sympathize with "Bafun-uni" since they are called by such name...
tn: Bafun-uni, a species of sea urchin, also a reference to Keroro episode 99
What happened?
As I walked while thinking...
I happened to hit the door...
Miyuki-san, you have enormous power for concentration, don't you?
There's a lot of such times.
No, on the limits of embarassment...
Huh? But if you start thinking about something else while doing something,
doesn't that mean that you have no power for concentration?
Huh? Which is it?
That certainly is Miyuki-like, isn't it?
Yes, that is true.
The other day as I was heating a drink, too...
Oh, I forgot!
I must heat it up once more, don't I..?
After Some tens of minutes have passed.
Oh!
I must do it again...
Ah! Again!
Ah..! Haa...
Oh, Miyuki - so you forgot it again?
Excuse me... Carelessly...
Ohh, it can't be helped... Mommy will bring it to you...
Thank you very much.
Like this...
After Some tens of minutes have passed.
I forgot it!
Truly a parent & child with a mission.
Even though it is embarassing...
Miyuki-san, since when have you worn glasses?
I think since middle years of elementary school...
So your eyes weren't so bad by birth...
When I was a child...
I really liked the book my mom read to me before sleeping,
but as my mother always ended up falling asleep first,
I got this after trying to read in that dark room,
, as I really wanted to know how it would continue...
Gradually my eyes...
But, like in your place, Miyuki -
- parent and child being in friendly terms - is the best.
The fact that children recently are indifferent, dry...
Isn't the number one reason for that lack of love,
or should I say physical contact, coming from the parents?
That reminds me, I wonder around when...
did I have my mother hold me in hands tightly?
As you, Tsukasa, were a child who nestled to your parents,
you were close until the first year of Junior High...
Eh, was that so?!
But that's why you could be such a good girl...
At our place my father comes all close to me even now...
So - in a way - you haven't been raised...
As you talk about children,
there are many abduction, imprisonment cases and all...
Somehow you're really observant about such things...
Although, above all things, my father is what I'm worried about...
Don't say such scary things so freely!
Well, I guess they get a little influenced by the games and all,
but as other users get annoyed by that I'd like them to stop...
Or should I say that, at the very least...
such things don't come out in games that I play...
Ah, come to think of it, it's the first anniversary soon, isn't it..?
Of what?
Of my experience at part-time work.
Everyone at my workplace said that they'd someway congratulate me...
Now that you mention it, as I haven't gone there yet,
I wonder if I should go and peek at your workplace the next time...
As a revenge for the new year...
Yeah! OK!
Is it OK!? Shouldn't you usually dislike something like that?!
As half of my job is like being watched...
Was it called a cosplay cafe, right?
Yeah, but just to make sure, please contact me before coming.
As there are times when the place is pretty crowded, too.
I'll do so!
Hey, you girls! The class has begun, though..!
This is a free softsub.Not for sale, rent, auction or hardsub.
Not for sale, rent, auction or hardsub.This is a free softsub.
or hardsub.This is a free softsub. Not for sale, rent, auction
Ah, hello?
We just came out of the station.
Eh?
Yeah-yeah... I'll buy it for you.
Yeh, alright.
Did Kona-chan say it was OK?
It's alright,
but she said that I'd buy her this month's Comptiq and LeLouch's manga there.
I wonder if we'll find them fast?
She said that I shouldn't forget to get the seller's stamp...
onto the receipt, but that's confusing, isn't it?
Excuse me, is it alright?
I ask to take one of you...
Eh?
I'm not Kamigishi...
I'm Hiiragi...
Hey! You!
What're you doing!?
I ask one piece here as well!
Ohh, don't take them any more!
Then, excuse me...
Could you please say "Hiroyuki-chan"?
Eh... Hiroyuki...-chan...
We're going now!
This is the first time I have come to such a store,
but it's really wide and you end up confused, don't you..?
Although she said that I'd be able to see it immediately on the phone...
So it's understandable to Kona-chan,
I think that I'd become lost here by myself...
Ah, so it was this?
And then the LeLouch comic, isn't it..?
There is no such...
It can't be found, now can it..?
Excuse me, but where could the LeLouch's comic be?
Ah, If you'd like that it'd be this.
Code Geass?
Just tell us the title or so, so that we can understand it...
Is it OK to bring the point card with me during the next time I come?
Well, then please bring it together with this receipt.
Yes.
Thank you very much!
So what's left is to go to Konata's place, right?
Oneechan, I'm hungry!
My work will end in a moment, so wait a bit...
How can she say to come with this!?
GAMERS
Here
Just to make sure,
I checked on it, so...
I think that it is to this direction.
Yuki-chan, as expected!
After all the one who is dependable is Miyuki, isn't she?
It's here, right?
Yes, the third floor here.
Welcome back, my master!
Here, please.
The first hour is 800 yen and soft drinks are free to drink!
The games are free to play, too - as the molded confections are to eat!
I want this una-juu.
There's no such now.
Well, then I'll have a shrimp pilaf then.
Can't do that now.
Huh?
Well, then it's OK with meat spaghetti...
The time required is 15 minutes.
Permission is...
All right. Do it.
I wonder if they get on in business like that...
You all!
What will you take as drinks!?
Wait a second!
Do it fast!
There's a penalty if you're slow! Penalty!
Is that an attitude to be taken towards customers?
Here this is the style.
You've already chosen, right!?
I'll take a melon soda!
I have no interest in the usual menu!
Heh?
I'd like to ask a milk tea.
Which do you want?
Aren't I choosing right now?
An unworthy slowness for a brigade member!
When did I become a brigade member?
It's a setting like that.
It's a hundred years too early to disobey the brigade leader!
Confusing, now isn't it..?
Then it's OK with an iced coffee.
It's a brigade leader's order - wait!
Good grief...
As it was smelly after a long time...
We'll be doing a stage show from now, so watch it!
Breathtaking!
Everyone is very skillful, as I see...
Like this... like that...
This girl's an overseas student,
she's a first-year-student at our school.
My name is Patricia Martin. Treat me well.
We're even releasing a CD.
Lookie!
Is it alright to release a thing like that?
Excuse me, can I have some tea?
Is it alright as hot?
Yes, hot please.
I'd want a melon soda, please!
Understood!
Well... What kind of a drink is this "Special mix juiche"?
A prohibited issue.
It's the style, the style...
A cafe that's unspeakably tiring, this is...
M-my height...
It's alright... Since you surely will grow more later.
Y-yeah, that's right...
Ah, oneechan!
Ohh, Yuu-chan!
Suddenly an example that crushes hope is close...
Huh?
O-oneechan, how much longer did you grow after entering high school?
Boy, not only length, but none at all on the sides as well...
Yuu-chan should prepare for that as well.
Eeh!?
Feel
Ah!?
No complex, no complex... You have demand, you know.
Hey, you two... have you gone to a class reunion?
I haven't yet...
I haven't as well...
But why do you ask, all of a sudden?
The "You haven't changed at all.", that you hear often,
is usually a flattering comment, right?
But people who get happy from it are those who have changed...
In many places...
So you were minding about it a bit...
Hey!
The thing is that the Golden Week is going to begin already, but is it OK..?
After-holiday- tests are so as well,
but be aware that you are examinees already,
and spend your holidays in an earnest way.
And then...
the workdays in between are not in the holidays!
I won't allow even thoughts about skipping those days with "cold".
Kamchatka!?
That aura, vibrant from all over her...
I'm certain, that's the Legendary Girl A!
The target today is that newest publication, or the goods!?
Think well!
Do not forget about the fact that we're now in...
the spring A-V (Audio-Visual) Festival!
Not yet!
Fully draw her, and recommend merchandize when she's off guard!
Yes, just like that! Wait for her to get closer, slowly!
Like that!
Now! Call her!
I'll go!
Welcome!
Here is what we have received recently!
Ah, Kagami? Did you get here already?
Yeah, I'll be there right away.
Spending time while waiting for someone!?
When you boil vegetables,
you cut them particularly randomly, which is called "ran-giri".
Ah, is that so?
It is said that that way the surface area increases,
and that the taste penetrates better.
After you take the scum off the broth,
it's approximately 10 minutes with medium fire.
If you overboil, it will fall apart,
so it's OK when the skewer goes through it.
I see.
It's really mysterious that when it comes to home economics class,
Miyuki seems to feel like someone who is under the average...
I understood very well how Kagami was looking at us...
Hiiragi-chan, combining mutual help,
wouldn't you want to go and do test study together in the library?
Oh, it's alright.
Before the exams the club activities always suddenly end,
and there's nothing to do, right?
That's why you study, right?
For that they aren't on, either.
Well... I do understand that, you know...
But when usually the time to spend in the club is free,
I wonder if it's called like a different world coming to view...
When you think so, you can't do studies, right? As it'd be a waste!
Fidgeting and being excited.
For the time being,
try to become aware of the fact that we're doing this half for you...
this study group...
I'm tired!
Fast!
Let's take a short rest..!
Isn't it because of you not having a sense of goal that you can't concentrate?
Don't you have dreams or something of the future?
Dreams, huh...
This might not be about something of the future...
but don't you think at this time,
that you'd want to win in lottery or something and live easily?
I feel somehow lazy...
Minegishi, do something about her!
When you use your head, after all sweet things are needed!
When we'll go home,
I'll bring the cookies I baked the other day, so let's try our best.
Hee, so you make sweets and stuff?
Even though I'm not as good as the boy named Ajiyoshi...
No, I think that you're much better than Ajiyoshi...
Studying is tiresome..!
Oneechan, I tried to make a Madeleine!
What happened?
Well, err...
I don't think the proverb "Like attracts like" is always correct,
but I just wondered if similar types of friends gather together automatically...
Aren't you thinking that it's just a canker sore, and disregarding it?
Lately such medical-treatment-programs have increased, haven't they?
I agree...
As there are many things that are close, they're scary, right...
Especially for someone like me...
Or should I say that as you look at this,
don't you gradually come to think of "I'm going to go soon!",
as there are too many things close to you?
Let's stop the close, negative talk, shall we...
I'm asking you, please live...
Ah, oneechan - tell me this!
Well... "Carl's like chickens...
come home to roast?"
This is you know... "Carl likes chickens...
when he comes home there is a roast chicken..."
I think...
Ah, neesan - try to translate the continuation here.
Which, which?
"When you make the contract..."
I wonder if I learnt things like this...
Yeah-yeah. The other day, when being a shrine maiden, a foreign guest...
came to talk about the origin of the word "torii".
Hee, what did he say?
In the old days it was thought that birds ("tori") carry the dead,
and as those were the trees for the birds to rest on, they are called "torii".
As he was a lot more familiar about Japan than we are...
I wonder if it would've been faster to ask Kagami-oneechan...
Please visit us at
http://jeeb.fiveforty.jp/
#jeeb@irc.rizon.net
The Sea of Japan, entering into the piercing cold...
Where is that person who loves?
Lucky☆Channel
Produce:
Kogami
Akira
BIG
SHOW!!
☆
Swimming alone through the raging waves...
of the world of entertainment...
Let us hear her sing, Kogami Akira-san with "Misoji Misaki"
Hey! What part of this is a "live"!?
This was the limit with the program's support!
I'm not....!
Who do they think I am!?
"Is it alright, for me, to talk by myself?...
I silently hummed to a sea gull."
"A woman, holding her single-minded, naked heart,
which was frozen by a sea breeze from the north!"
"Oh return! Even verses of malice from a strayed and broken heart...
The drinks sure take their time to get here...
Yes?
I have brought the ordered drinks.
don't arrive to you, far away..."
Ah, thank you.
"Standing still, in these floods of tears..."
H-h-h-hey! That brown one is mine, so that you know!
"This cape of my thirtieth year on earth..."
Lucky☆Channel
Produce:
Kogami
Akira
BIG
SHOW!!
☆
Ahh... This is good...
"Even if I would break into tears...
Err... Where was " Fed-up life returns..."
in that shelter of us alone,
regret that night I made love..."
"Men, doing nothing but mere selfish promises...
all of them end without becoming true."
Yes?
"Oh, if I would throw myself into the splashes of the waves...
Ah, yes-yes-yes...
Extension is...
Ah...
Oh, it's not needed.
Yes, I'll leave that to you please.
It'll be another 5 minutes!
it feels like I could meet you, being far away..."
Now let's clean up - clean up...
Bye-nii~!
"I wish to sacrifice myself for this loneliness...
Ooh, I'd like to publish a song or something as a solo as well...
The spirit of my thirty years of life!"
T-T-T-This forgotten thing of mine...
一人語りしても　いいですか
Hitorigatari shitemo　ii desu ka
Is it alright, for me, to talk by myself?...
Translation: JEEB
Translation Checking: Senoby★
Encoding: Heedly
かもめにそっと　つぶやいた
Kamome ni sotto　tsubuyaita
I silently hummed to a sea gull.
Editing/QC: ro
女一途な　真心乗せて
Onna ichizu na　magokoro nosete
A woman, holding her single-minded, naked heart,
北の海風　凍てついた
Kita no umikaze　itetsuita
which was frozen by a sea breeze from the north!
はぐれ恋散る　恨み節さえ
Hagure, koichiru　urami bushi sae
Oh return! Even verses of malice from a strayed and broken heart...
遠いあんたにゃ　届かない
Tooi anta nya　todokanai
don't arrive to you, far away...
たたずんで　泣き濡れて
Tatazunde　nakinurete
Standing still, in these floods of tears...
三十路岬
Misoji misaki
This cape of my thirtieth year on earth...
This video was brought to you by JEEB
And so, the next Lucky Star is?
Dark! Nagato, like that no one would watch.
I'd like to ask you to say that more like a person...
who faces the living room at 6:30 in the evening,
on sunday, cheerfully addressing people.
Well, once more then. OK!
And so, the next Lucky Star is?
And it doesn't change!
Oh, forget about it...
Next time: "Under The Sun"
Look forward to it.
Wait a sec! No...
Rock-Scissors-Paper!
Ufufufufu...