Now, let'ssu begin yoo!
It's gonna come now...
Fungaa!
Now start out already!
I My Something
"I my something"
そりゃぷにってことかい、ちょっ
Sorya punitte koto kai, cho
That's about a puni, is it, cho?
ら、ぐーんぐーんが制服
Ra, guun-guun ga seifuku
Ra, guun guun goes the seifuku,
なぁふりってことない？　うん
Naa furitte koto nai？　Un
Hey, there's no irrationality in this? Yeah.
頑張っちゃ、やっちゃっちゃ、
Ganbaccha, yacchaccha,
Try your best, do the thing-cha,
そんときゃ　じゃリリース料
son tokya　jya ririisu ryou
at that time, well the things for release!
あせっ、あせっ
A-se, a-se!
"A-se, a-se!"
の谷間にダーリンダーリンフリー
No taniai ni daarin daarin furiiー
In the cleavage darling darling free!
なんかたるー、なんかてるー
Nankataruuー, nankateruー
How to cheat, how to win,
あいしてるー
Aishiteruuー
I love you.
あれ一個が違ってる
Are ikko ga chigatteru
One of those is different.
むん　むやみに暴行鉄棒おいしん棒
Mun muyami ni boukou tetsubou oishinbou
Stuffy, violence with recklessness - steel rod is a sweet rod.
いいかげんにしなさい!
Iikagen ni shinasai!
Now get reasonable!
飛んでったあいつの火照る体って
Tondetta aitsu no hoteru karadatte
The burning body of who flied away right now is...
いわゆる普通の女の子
Iwayuru futsuu no onna no ko
what is called a "usual girl".
驚いた、
Odoroita,
I'm surprised,
あたしだけ豚骨針金おかわりダー!!!!
atashi dake tonkotsu harigane okawari daaー!!!!
Only I get an extra portion of tonkotsu with a needle insideー!!!!
ボンボン応援団
Bon-bon ouendan
Bon-bon cheering team.
Let's get cherry pie
Let's get cherry pie.
らんらーん　関係感
Ranraan　kankeikan
Blazing, relationship feeling,
you have センセーション
you have senseeshon
you have sensation.
ハーイ　存在感　点々　小惑星
Haai　Sonzaikan　tenten　shouwakusei
Yes, feeling of being here, here and there meteors.
ぶつかって溶けました　呆然　大いに歌ってシリンダー
Butsukatte tokemashita　bouzen　ooi ni utatte shirindaa
Got melt from the collision, dumbfounded singing a lot, "Cilinder!"
もっていけ、
Motte ike,
Take and go,
最後に笑っちゃうのはあたしのはず
Saigo ni waracchau no wa atashi no hazu
The last one laughing should be me,
セーラー服だからです
Seeraa fuku dakara desu
because it's a seeraa fuku.
結論
Ketsuron
Conclusion.
月曜日なのに
Getsuyoubi nanoni
Even if it's monday,
機嫌悪いのどうするよ
Kigen warui no dou suru yo
What will you do with that bad mood?
夏服がいいのです、かわいい
Natsufuku ga ii no desu, kawaii
The summer uniform is better, cute.
接近賛否それまでって躊躇だ　やーん
Sekkin sanbi, sore madette choucho da　yaーn
Yes and no for getting closer, until that it's undecided, yaan.
頑張って　張り切って
Ganbatte,　harikitte
Try your best, be on high,
ま、ダーリンダーリンプリーズ
Ma, daarin daarin puriizu
well darling darling please!
Yeah, it's smelly, isn't it?
Yes, it is.
The golden week will soon end...
..., are you two OK with your homework?
Actually, I'm still...
On a long break you just can't help playing, can't you. I'm in trouble now.
Isn't it so, nee-chan?
Sorry.
I'm almost nearly finished already.
Even though she played with me all the time...
The Effort
and
The Result
Thank you for the meal.
It's about this...
There's no way I could
understand something
you can't, is there?
Ain't you a university student?!
Now go and wake
Tsukasa up already.
No. Because she won't
wake up anyways.
Now wake up already!
Hngh...
Daddy and all are quite late.
Wasn't he going to a
Ground-breaking
ceremony in the morning?
What... time is it now?
I'm home!
It's noon already.
Welcome home!
Good morning...
It's already noon.
It's incredible that
you can sleep like that.
Ehe...
Did you see the last episode of
Koi no Apron yesterday?
tn. Koi no Apron - a Japanese cooking-battle show
No, I didn't.
I fell asleep during it.
Eh, was that sleeping?
There was awesome
developement!
In the end the guy who put
the red basin on his head...
Kagami!
Hm?
A call from Miyuki-chan!
Got it!
Wouldn't you do a study workshop, for the comparison of our answers?
Ah, that's good! Let's do so!
Kagami!
It's a call from Konata-chan!
Unnn... I thought 'bout a study workshop, for the comparison of our answers?
Wait a sec!
In your case it's just about showing my homework, isn't it?!
So, show your homework.
You're so straight, aren't you?
It's OK for me to show my homework,
But you will get terrible results on the after-vacation tests if you don't do some studying yourself!
That's right...
It doesn't do good for yourself.
I'm pretty good at getting the point so I'm OK.
So show me.
You try to worry for a bit, too!
I'm here.
Ah,
Welcome!
Oh my, is Izumi-san in the study workshop, too?
Nope, she's only copying.
Unh!
But you haven't done that at all?!
What did you do on the holidays?!
Well...
The first day
Hmm... math is 23 pages...
..., world history is 20 pages...
At last I got to the Okofu's gate...
and English is 30...
Hun, he-he-huun...
It's a five-day holiday...
If I would do 5 hours,
no - 4 hours per day...
Hu-uun!
After 1 hour of math
it's 15 pages...
The Second Day
Suprisingly .... doesn't it...
It's bad!
I've not done anything today!
...Gets confused and level up...
Well there's three more days...
...so should I do
6 hours per day?
Oh, some money...
The Third Day
"I still can't get everyone to remember the name of senpai who wanted to come along..."
"It's Yutaka, yu..."
If I try my best for two,
for two more days...
The Fourth Day
The golden week will soon end...
Are you two OK
with your homework?
Ah!
Ah, I thought 'bout a study
workshop, for the
comparison of our answers?
Eeeeehhh...
I tried to do it all by a plan...
A failed plan...
It was useless resistance.
You're still bad!
Uhuh...
Ah?...
So she did try by herself in the end...
With all, this girl is serious in her heart.
But the rate of right answers can't be overturned...
It's terrible, too terrible...
Ussu! Did you all enjoy the long weekend?
Even if I say so, there was a lot of homework and there's the intermediate test, too.
So you couldn't just lay around there, now could you?
It didn't even feel like relaxation!
It might be bad for ya, but I had a great time!
Sensei!
Yes?
I, too, had a great time without limits!
Wha-?
Aren't those done so that you can't take them?
Hmm... it depends on the thing...
Because there are some things that are done to be hard...
So it is like that... I don't even want to try that.
Ah! That's great!
Well, it was what I wanted...
Hee...
Now if I'd try that I...
"...Even might get one?"
Might you be thinking so?
No... It's not like that really...
Fuhehe-fuhehehe-hehe...
But I thought about trying it only once...
Onee-chan, try your best!
Aaaaa....
Even if I thought I got it...
A pity...
Are?
Uwah!
Nih!
Huwa!
Can't be!
Why?
A great man once said - "Ufo catchers are money boxes."
That guy was clever...
Yume yume suki deshou?
Uh, a-again!
Oh, I can't!
Fuwaah...
Hmm... I couldn't do it at all...
And now the results!
Red team - first dan of taiko!
Kona-chan has an impressive rhytm sense.
Blue team - fifth dan of taiko!
No, it has nothing to do with rhytm sense...
The skills you learn from gaming don't really help in everyday life, don't they...
I can understand that when I look at you...
Kona-chan's strong!
Well, a bit...
How much does she put into these machines...
Izumi?
Today Izumi seems to be absent...
Kuroi-sensei, it's a call from Izumi-san.
Yes, speaking...
Uhm, sensei, excuse me, but I would like to call myself in sick today...
Oh, Izumi. That's rare, is it cold?
No, the FAS's bad and I'm really feeling lazy...
tn. Freshman's Apathy Syndrome
Huh?
Whatever, just come in FAST!
Hey, we're going home!
Huh?
Why is your bag so full?
The tests are from tomorrow, so I'll have to take them all home and get back on tracks.
Just don't say you always left that all in there...
There's no way it's going to be OK if you take the books with you on the day before!
Huh? But I've always overcome them this way...
Great confidence you have there...
Well let's see how well you can do...
1st  Term     Intermediate Exam
Modern Literature
Math
English
Hey, I'll be givin' back your tests from before!
Well It went somehow...
How did you do?
More like "Don't ask"...
I did try my best...
And how's our one-nighter going...
Quite well, actually.
I don't understand it!
Lucky Star!
I feel lazy... I don't want to do anything...
Hey, we're going home!
Uuungh...
Even if you say something you will still come along...
Ah! Comp Matsuri!
Service for all cards! If I could get 'em all...
Yosh! I'll start a job or something!
You're really easy to understand...
I have never heard about someone trying to be absent because of FAS...
Even if we can understand the feeling...
Isn't it a reputable disease because it has the "illness" in it?
Are you seriously saying that?
Yeah...
What's an FAS, by the way?
Miyuki, tell them...
Well, the feeling of success after achieving some big goal, like passing an entrance exam or entering a company...
and the "not going as planned" new human relations from April...
with the feeling of not being able to clear the gap between the imagined new life style...
bring up the feelings of powerlessness and boredom.
So to call plain laziness FAS is a bit...
And as we are sophomores already it doesn't even fit us...
But I am trying my very best every spring so...
Is that so...
But, not about Konata, but this season is strangely lazyness-ful.
Somehow even if I come home I have no strength to do homework...
Hey, that's me, too.
You don't have to go to the same level because you're lazy...
Haa...
What's wrong, Yuki-chan? Even sighing.
Like with the contacts, it's embarrassing at this age...
...but I fear and run from the dentist. And now I've got a hole...
Enough to make a striking pain when I drink water...
Eh, is that not normal?
I, too, have a weak mouth.
But why didn't you go to the dentist even while in pain?
Huh?
It's strange but even if there's pain in the teeth...
...you just don't want to go to the dentist, right?
You just seem to select not to go to the dentist while you can tolerate the pain.
Is the dentist's such a scary place? I don't know because I've never been in one...
You've not visited a dentist?
I'm envious...
The tension of waiting and the scent of drugs particular to dentist...
And before everything the sound of the drill revolving...
A marked duel...
It's really scary.
But the boys could like the dentist.
Why?
Well, they do say that drills are men's romance.
Dinosaur engraval!
It seems that elegant battles with drills as weapons make men mad!
Huh? But I think getting your teeth chipped is not something to be liked...
I've always thought so, but aren't there many beauties in the reception of dentists?
Now that you mention it, it seems so...
Hmm... Why would that be?
It could after all be a criteria of the employer.
They only have beautiful girls and drills...
If you say it's directed at men, it could be so.
And if you'd go to a dentist for girls what would that be like?
Well firstly the scent should be deleted.
And then the treatment chair could be soft, reclining, massagic chair.
If so, why not aroma therapy?
Getting your legs massaged while in treatment...
Ah, that could be good!
And in order to make the treatment softer some games...
Games could be a little hard to play...
But it'd be good to be able to relieve yourself.
Getting your favourite songs played with headphones...
Un, that'd be good!
That would be good, too.
Yeah.
But...
After all I hate dentists...
Yes, so it is...
And!
What happened?
Well, there's another thing I like that's going to be animated,...
but the cast is completely different from the drama CDs...
Hmm, I don't really understand...
It might be the doings of the unseen god's hand. CD or money?
I'm the type not to buy drama CDs,...
so I think everyone's good as long as the character matches the original...
It doesn't just go like that Kagami!
For those people who have become accustomed to the drama CD voices there will be an unpleasant feeling,...
and it takes time to get rid of it, you know...
Heee...
But hey, there's one merit to this, too...
Eh, what kind of?
Drama CDs and anime, you can enjoy two worlds with two voices.
Twice as tasty with one piece.
You're a strong customer, ain't you?
Well, it just happened that one of us can eat the nugget Miyuki-san left, but...
let's give it to the winner of a staring game?
Ugh, childish again...
Staring game? Interesting.
But Kagami seems to want to stop it...
You said something?
And so, Ni-ra-mek-ko-shi-ma-sho! Pupui!
That's bad already!
Wow!
That's not a human face!
You two are just overdoing it...
Sorry for making you wait!
Un.
The toilet was full...
Ah, did something happen?
Hey, show that face to Miyuki, too.
Eh, I don't want to...
Miyuki, this is just special, a face I've never seen before!
Well...
This is great any time I see it!
That would be really good at a one talent- oriented exam.
Yeah, Konata, try to go to a university with that, I'm sure you'll pass!
I don't really feel happy...
On the TV it was said that people should go from manga to regular books
in order to refresh the amount of people studying by themselves.
Manga is a bit...
I think about if ranobe are counted in?
Eh, I'm not sure... But I think light novels are OK.
And what about picture books?
When you call it a book it seems to mix...
Even if it's the same fantasy, some people call "Harry Potter" or something a usual book and mystify people...
What is a "usual book" after all?
Hu-huuun...
Additionally, in the end they said on TV that the young people read remarkably less and ended the programme...
Now you can use the net to search and come around various sites and blogs...
I'd think that the chance to read a printed word should be even bigger...
Uhn, I feel like I understand and don't...
Hey, you two! Let's go home!
Wait a sec...
Eh, I'm sorry, I can't go home together with you guys today.
Do you have something to do? How rare...
Yeah, because I started to work a bit part-time.
Hee...
Huh? She really started it? Is it that important to her, Comp Festival?
Even so, I was surprised by Konata's actions...
Yeah, she's really starting to work!
Even if I thought it was a joke...
Yeah, there's that...
Huh?
I'm just surprised that there was a place that'd take her...
That's a bit harsh...
Mainly I can't even see her doing labour in my mind...
Well, there is...
I wonder where she's working...
Not a book store, she loves manga?
Excuse me, I'd like this...
Wait a second, I'm busy right now...
Huh?!
Got it!
It'd be nice if they didn't sack her...
What about a convenience store?
Excuse me, this...
Itsh fourhundrethnaintyeith yen.
I'l teik she sam...
Shanksalot.
Uhh, that's a not...
What about fast food?
A Smile
It's a smile, what about it?
It seems a bit impossible...
No...
Family Restaurants aren't OK for the same thing...
Welcome...
Really, what is she doing...
Huh...
Traffic researcher?
Nope.
Rental Video Shop?
I don't know...
A bar?
No, that's not it...
Pizza delivery?
No license...
The registry at a mart...
Impossible.
A cram school teacher?
That couldn't be!
Bread factory!
Huh?
Then there's... hmm...
Let's ask tomorrow.
Hey, Konata, at what kind of a place are you working?
Yeah, tell us!
Huh?
Aah!
In a usual cosplay cafe.
Uwaa! Just too exact!
But is it OK to be in there?
Lucky Star!
LUCKY CHANNEL
Good Lucky!
This is Kogami Akira!
Now this is the second Lucky Channel!
Akira brings it to you high and high!
And so, together with me is, helping Akira, this lovely onii-san!
Shiraishi Minoru-san!
Paupau-Daudaa!
Wawawa, I am Akira-sama's assistant, Shiraishi Minoru!
Wawawa-wasuremono? - anyone?
I'm just a novice, so please just try to remember my name.
Yes...
Clappy clappy clappy
Now, this corner has just started, but...
there's already a lot of messages from different people coming!
Akira is super happy!
Thank you!
No, this is really unbelievable. This, too, is a way of Akira-sama's popularity showing itself...
Phew...
E...eh?
I saw it, by the way...
Yes?
It was shown...
Eh?
In this volume!
It was shown, right?
Eh... Yes, I got it out...
Hmm... Well, it's OK...
Oh my, in what scene were you shown?
Hm, if I remember correctly it was the cut 45 of part A.
The scene of "Classroom after a long weekend".
Ah, ah, ah, now I remember. I didn't feel you were there so I forgot.
In the end it was just one line so...
What? Is that dissatisfaction that I hear?
Oh, no, there was no s...
Ha'ah, I don't really know... A newcomer saying such things...
You know, when I debuted...
How old were you at that time?
Eh? Three years old. At that time, you know, I was very happy just by getting lines!
The heart of lines is not in their numbers.
Oh, this time, aspiring from a really higher senpai, it's been a continuation of stress.
I've learned a lot!
You were a bit stiff, though...
Eh?
It was Tick-ticky, trying to do it and showing it bluntly...
You know it's a bit "that" for it, so...
try it right here once again.
Eh? You say... here?
There's a chance that you will be seen later too, right?
Ah... well...
If so, you'll have to practice some more. I'm saying I'm going to teach you!
Eh?
Aa! I understand!
Please!
Lend me the script.
What cut was it?
Cut 45.
Ah, this...
Well, I'll be Kuroi-sensei...
Please.
Be ready...
ACTION!
"Ussu! Did you all enjoy the long weekend? Even if I say soo...
the..
"There was..."
re...
was a lot of homework...
...and there's the intermediate test, too...
So you couldn't just lay around there, now could you?"
"It didn't even feel like relaxation!"
What's that?
Eh?
Utterly useless... Your line doesn't reach!
Reach?
Here! It doesn't come here with power!
Sorry...
Even monkeys can repeat lines!
Eh, but monkeys can't...
Huh?!
Funyu!
Uwaa! It's already the time to part!
Happy moments pass so fast, don't they?
And, so - all your questions and cheers to Akira,...
and all those comments about the programme, please send all of 'em!
Well, let's meet next time.
BYE BYE!
And, how was being "regular"?
When you say "how"...
How could I put it, could someone be leaving and stuff...
Aren't they all non-friendly?
Eh, I think that that isn't so...
Then you'll tell to me!...
Kona-chan, that's incredible!
Really passionate.
Konata, wait a sec. Are those two other songs like this, too?
No, I've added anime to special-effects-movies, too.
Not that! Sing a song that we can understand, too!
Eh? It's free to sing whater you want, isn't it?
Eh, the remote...
Here, Tsukasa. If we won't enter something, we'll be listening to her anime song medleys for an eternity.
But I'm OK with even that...
This is pretty fun as it is, actually.
Wait a sec, Miyuki too?!
I'm sorry front as I'm going to be standing while singing.
What's she up to now?
If you don't stand when singing, then the voice doesn't get up from the stomach.
Are you planning on singing even louder?!
Ah! Original footage!
Ah! Looks somehow great!
It just looks like taken long before we were born...
Zarado! Iraado! Galadoo!
I'm on fire-un-un-fire!
Dorat Kakuu!
Uh, oh-oh! Donata wo chikaredoo! ...
Here are your drinks!
Tripuru de kaeyoo!
Excuse me...
Thank you! Ehil, Emiru, Ehii!
Sakura wo o-ho-ho-hoo!
The person with Olong tea!
Ah, that's me.
The person with ice lemon tea?
Tsunari jyankkeru, hatsubaita, ATREE!
That is me.
The person with orange juice?
That's me.
The person with Ginger ale?
Yuku michi hitotsu yo, tada hitotsuu!
Ah, excuse me, please leave it around there.
And so...
Lucky Star next time is...
I'm Kagami.
When you buy juice from a vending machine with 200 yen and get 50 and 10 yen back...
you will think that you've won.
But to the contrary, when you'll by 150 yen train ticket...
You will put in 100 yen and think that you've got five pieces of 10 yen..
...you will put up to four of them in, but then get that you haven't got five of them and...
without options putting another 100 yen in...
and when talking about defeat when you get back nine 10 yen coins, there's no such thing...
Next Time: Different people.
Look forward to it!
This program was brought to you by Kadokawa Bookshops and the companies visible.