Opening Ceremony
Collecting Ideas
Reception Period
Application Outlines
Culture festival, is it? It's the season, isn't it?
The tests are close, too...
Since there really are many things to do in the second semester, it is really troublesome isn't it?
Don't you have anything else that you feel...
before your last high school culture festival?
Ah...
"Opening Ceremony"?
What is this?
At the Outou Festival, volunteers are gathered every year,
and the first thing on the appointed day's program is the time for presenting the performances...
Ah!
I thought of a good thing!
Pending
Bazar
Labyrinth
Mansion of Fortunetelling
Teeth-brushing excercise
The History and Making
of a Paulownia Drawer
And so, our performance has been decided...
as the "Mansion of Fortunetelling",
so please think of the fortunetelling...
each of you will be doing by the next Homeroom class!
Teeth-brushing excercise
The History and Making of a Paulownia Drawer . . .
Haunted Mansion
Ah...
You tried your best! I'm impressed!
And so, I'm thinking of doing a Cheer Dance!
Cheer...
The opening ceremony you talked of this morning!
It's the best performance to arouse the festival!
Hee, indeed it's showy and seems fun!
Isn't it?
With this, everyone will talk about us!
"We"...?
Eh, Are we in that, as well?
After asking a teacher,
I was told that it's no good if it's not a proper plan...
to some degree, including  participants...
I was told so, so...
Ah!..
Yutaka, how do you think about it?
Eh!? I?
Yuu-chan is a bit... on the strength side...
I wonder... if I should try...
Uh?
If its not an inconvenience, I'm thinking about doing it, or something...
Inconvenience? It's not like that at all!
I really welcome you!
A-are you alright?
I do think that it'll be hard work,
and I did think that I might hinder everyone's performance, but...
I thought that this time I'd like to try and attempt...
Look! As it's that Yutaka is saying like that,
how about it, you two as well?
Oh...
Should it be something like that...
Well, should everyone be doing it...
I have gotten good friends, haven't I!
Hee, fortunetelling is it...
But can you do something like fortunetelling?
Nope, not at all.
And what's that...
Hey! You're the one who said about it, right!?
Fortunetelling like the one done during culture festivals...
is alright even if done vaguely right...
Ah!
That reminds me, what will oneechan's class do?
Oh, well...
It's a bit stereotypical, but we're doing a Haunted Mansion.
Hee...
Hmm... The "royal road", isn't it?
As other interesting ideas didn't come out as well...
Uh...
Is there something..?
No, I just thought that it's fitting...
What do you want to say!?
A real demon got angry!
I thought you'd say that for sure...
And, you know, then Pattie-chan said that she wanted to do cheering...
Ah..!
And so, I as well thought a bit about trying my best... or something...
Ohh...
Oh!
Why again!?
I've always been absent,
and don't have anything that I've accomplished with everyone, right?
But lately I've put out just a bit of spirit...
and begun to think that the thing I've wished for until now...
and what Pattie-chan is wishing now might be same...
But after all I think that it's hard...
And so, as we can't get numbers at all,
Pattie-chan proposed if I could ask your participation, oneechan...
So it comes like that..?
Oneechan, you're good at sports as well...
I'm feeling like I could try my best to the end...
if you and Minami-chan were there...
If you have that much will and Pattie says so...
Ah?
Uh?
Yes, hello?
Good evening, Konata!
Ah, Pattie, is it you?
I just heard about it and was thinking about what to do...
Pim-pom-pam-pam!
And now, a quiz.
Right now I am holding a certain ticket in my hand.
Well now, what kind of a ticket could it be?
Hmm...
Hm!
I-it couldn't be!
Hmm...
Konata, you were all 'moe' at Gekisou, weren't you?
Wouldn't you like to exchange a hot handshake with Haruhi?
Ooohhh!
The handshake event!
Yes, I'd really want to go!
A live..!
By the way, Konata, you were saying something at the beginning, right?
Ah!
Yuu-chan...
Hm?
Should we try to make memories?
Y-yeah...
And so, the age is cheering, you two!
What kind of reason is it?
Pattie said that she would be doing...
cheering at the opening ceremony, you know...
Hee, certainly it seems to match her...
And then, it was decided that you, Tsukasa and Kagami, would dance as well.
Eh?
Ah!
Are there no other people in your class, Kagami, that could be capable?
J-just wait a second!
Don't decide things by yourself!
B-but I feel like I couldn't do things like that...
Aah, but there probably won't be such occasions after this...
It's a once-in-a-lifetime thing, you know...
Hm...
As we're doing it among familiar people, too...
It's a Festival!
Wouldn't it be fun if we all brought up some noise?
I wonder...
Ah...
Ah..!
Yeah, it might be so!
Yes-yes...
Tsukasa gets carried away easily...
I don't like it.
As I have class' preparation, too.
Hi-oi-oi-oo...
Even though I just thought that it would be great...
if we could all make some memories together during our last Culture Festival...
The friendship you talk of is always sudden, you know!
Isn't the acting just obvious!?
This time Yuu-chan really got motivated, you know...
H-hee...
But is it alright?
I as well did say that it'd be better to quit it, but...
She was really desperate in wanting to accomplish something...
specific together with everyone, you know...
I-is that so?
But you know...
I heard that they can't get numbers well...
That's why the talk came over, though...
Ah...
Yeah... Indeed, maybe I was pushy...
Anyway, insistence is bad, so I'll try to get someone else...
I got it...
Ah...
Eh? What?
I got it, I'll do it!
Oneechan!
Eeh...
Is it alright?
It can't be helped, right?
For there's a substitute for me in my class,
but not here, right?
Hmm... So after all Kagami is cute, isn't she...
C-cheerleading, is it?
Although I have no confidence that I could do it well...
Well...
Right now a lot of things are dubious, you know...
Big Breasts
Especially volume and such...
Although it would have a really nice feeling should we have you participate...
Is that so...
Understood.
Should I be of help...
Ahh!
Thanks, Boin...
No... Miyuki-san.
The tests ended as well,
and you'll be entering into the real Culture Festival's preparation from now on,
but don't let your attention go lax!
Hmph... Oh really...
Even if it'd be alright for them to reduce the number...
of tests at least during the times when there are many school events...
Ossu!
Hm?
Hey, Konata! What's up with the cheer?
Now that you mention it...
Before the tests...
I did hear that "The plan has passed!",
but from then on I haven't heard anything from her...
Huh!? Irresponsible, isn't it!
Isn't it soon bad if we don't begin training..?
Or should I say, isn't it about late already!?
Should we go ask her?
Sorry!
I still haven't decided a bit on the choreography and such...
"Haven't decided"!?
What'll you do!?
Some time went for the selection of the song and such...
As it doesn't quite become like HareHare...
What did you say!?
Ah...
In any case...
If you were having trouble with it, would it have not been better to have consulted with someone?
As you're the proposer,
just take the responsibility for schedule management around there!
I cannot understand difficult Japanese!
What are you saying after speaking so fluently?
Anyway, decide on some choreography today!
Odd things will be corrected into properness while training!
You ask stuff you don't understand from people with whom it is easy to talk!
As I and Miyuki will do the general schedule organization...
and the reservation of training place,
I'm really counting on you!
Aah...
Kagamin'ya...
Huh?
Even though you were as reluctant...
You're like...
being the most eager it seems...
Ah!
You're annoying!
Miyuki-san, what will you do?
I'm on tarot fortunetelling.
Hee...
And so, Tsukasa?
Uhh...
That hasn't been decided yet...
Yuki-chan, I wonder if there is anything even I could do?
Let's see...
How about fortunetelling by looking at a shape?
U-uhh...
Ueeh...
Ua-ah...
T-this shape...
could be revealing that your romance fortune is overall good...
Tsukasa...
You thought of it just now, right?
H-however..!
"My darling, darling please..!"
Ahh....
W-wait a second!
Are you going to do this from now?
Is it no good?
More than "no good"...
I think that it could be rather hard...
Hmm... Since we have no time...
there's nothing else to do but to...
do the hard parts while making them easier, right?
What was she thinking..?
However!
But after you've gotten over it, the great emotion..!
Like you should be saying that!
Ah...
The tape ran out...
Eh...
Can't help it, I guess I should go to buy stuff, huh?
Well, I'll ask for magic marker as well then.
A replacement blade for a cutter as well!
Cardboard!
Playboy!
Glue!
Ah, some weird ones get mixed in as well...
Or I should say that, should you have as much things...
that need to be bought, someone go right now instead of playing around!
What was the name of the yakisoba?
It's "A breath of spring that has a scent".
And the "Scattered drops of the sun" is?
That's the okonomiyaki.
Argh, it's a menu in which you can't know what is what just by calling the name, isn't it!
Japanese culture - interesting!
Although I think that this plan really has a lot of bias in it as well...
Yahoo!
Now what were you, Yuu-chan and all, doing?
Err...
tn. Dzuka - Takaradzuka Revue was an all-female revue
Dzuka-style Tea House...
The play of class 1-D for the Outou Festival
Dzuka Tea House   "Kazegumi"
Elisabeth
Lucheni
Joseph
Tod
Sophie
Lucanor
Leon
Coelestina
Delbares
Granados
Wah...
Huh!?
W-What kind of!?
Basically, it's a tea room where you can enjoy Dzuka-like, short shows!
I can appoint girls in glossy dresses,
and ones in manly male clothing as waitresses!
Twice as delicious!
Male clothing...
Ah, yes-yes!
Yuu-chan and Minami-chan are going to serve the top!
The dazzling world of bi...
When did it become like this...
Oh...
I'm thinking about the cheering as well, but I wonder if this is alright as well...
Ahhh!
Those two are as expected, aren't they...
Minami-san, I see you are good at this...
Yes, indeed...
So, let's try it once more...
The spirit is just right as well, isn't it.
Here!
By the way, I wonder if that's Miyuki-san's S play?
One!
Or maybe Minami-san's M play?
Indeed...
Takara-senpai's dynamic dance...
might be a pressure for Minami-chan...
How much...
You two! It's enough already so train!
This is a free softsub.Not for sale, rent, auction or hardsub.
Not for sale, rent, auction or hardsub.This is a free softsub.
or hardsub.This is a free softsub. Not for sale, rent, auction
Lucky Star!
The cheer's costumes got done!
Aaah!..
Again...
Yeah...
It is indeed lovely, but you do end up being a bit embarrassed, don't you...
Such costumes are pleasing for the watching side, you know...
As it's a clothing that was chosen by a person...
who actually gets pleased by watching such...
Ahh... The one I heard earlier in talk,
the one who should be feared, Tamura-elder-brother!
Please anticipate the Dzuka costumes as well!
Come to think of it, Yutaka and all - you were doing cheering, right?
Nyoro~n!
Y-yeah...
I wonder if it's alright to record it...?
Ahh...
Should it be inside the patterns of common sense...
Ge...
I will be careful...
However... Well, we haven't succeeded even once yet, and it's quite uncertain...
As I will give you my power via injection, try your best!
After you get neesan's power,
it seems like you'd get uselessly cheerful and unnecessarily tired...
Like that, you know...
Even though we have no more time, it's hard...
Culture Festival, is it...
I wonder what we did during our time..?
Your dad's class did...
You know...
The thing that is now called a "manga tea house"...
Boys in our class brought along manga books, didn't they?
Eh... You were quite advanced from the time, weren't you?
Although nowadays it seems like it's normal to take such to school as well...
During daddy's times it was strict, you know...
Such things would be "only if it's a festival", you know.
Well, there are people who bring,
but as it's not like it's fundamentally acceptable...
Hee, Mansion of Fortunetelling, is it...
Please tell everyone in before to tell a good fortune, should mommy come.
B-by that, the meaning of "fortunetelling"...
By the way, how were such things in your time, mother?
Hmm...
I wonder if we did some shows by class or club?
The shows were something like Haunted Mansions...
or Okonomiyaki restaurants, as well...
The standard things were many, weren't they...
It surely does feel mysterious that...
it's the same manner now and then, doesn't it...
By the way, examination of such cultural items as paulownia drawers and such,
I wonder if there were no such shows like that?
Hu-hu-hu, what's that...
Even if you do such, it won't be interesting at all, right?
Yes, it's like that... it is like that...
Alright! Once a rest!
At any rate, it seems like we got pumped up and it feels like we can do the performance...
Well, as it's not like it's perfect yet,
so let's brace ourselves to the end and do it properly.
At times like this it really does help that Hiiragi,
you are around and commanding us.
Well, the fact that only I have no memories with all of you is somewhat hard, too...
W-what is it!? Don't you look here!
The 16th
Outou Festival
The Now So Glorious Time. . . .
Oh, is that so..?
Thank you, excuse me...
Not at all...
It seems like today is a day only for the students, with only rehearsals...
And!?
We, the usual people,
aren't allowed to get in before tomorrow, they said...
That's why! I did say to come only after properly checking, didn't I!?
But...
As I heard that Akira-chan would be here today...
Aahh! The train fair was a waste!
Student Presentation Day
Public Presentation Day
16th
Outousai
November
Should I have had that money,
I could've had such luxury as buying a hamburger or something!
Ooh...
This not-completed condition is good, isn't it?
Leave it alone!
Or should I say, will you be wandering around looking like that?
Isn't it alright like this, being an advertisement?
Kona-chan's costume is cute, isn't it?
"From the shape onwards", you know.
I'll be fully fortunetelling today!
"You will buy an ice cream cone after 5 minutes and 15 seconds,
and after 5 minutes and 28 seconds, you will drop it..."
Isn't that not fortunetelling but prophecy?
And after 7 minutes and 6 seconds, you will hit your head into a signboard...
As it was, huh!?
Oohh...
Senpais, you're all lovely, I see.
But we're not losing as well!
It's barely late,
but it became perfect at last!
Ah!
It's cute!
It is really lovely, isn't it.
Although it is really embarrassing to walk around in this costume...
What an appearance!
Ah!
Well, it's cute though...
Senpai, Kogami Akira's stage is just about.
Ah, is that so! I'll be right there!
I'm glad to meet you, sensei. I am Kogami Akira.
I will be asking for your assistance today!
Ah, I'm Sakuraba... am.
Today is something like a rehearsal,
so I'll leave it for you on the level of checking...
Regards...
Hey, Shiraishi! I'll leave the rest to you.
Ah, yes.
I am the executive chairman, Shiraishi.
I will be counting on you.
I will basically leave the rest to Shiraishi,
so should something happen, tell him...
please...
Yes!
Huh!?
Hey, you! Say something!
Huh?
You should get out on some ghost meeting...
Zaa!
Something happened!? ...Did?
No, it isn't anything...
After arranging it became a bit lively...
Huh!
For now, Akira-sama, you are a welcomed guest,
so I will treat you reasonably.
And?
After this...
We will have you do a Misoji Misaki mic test on the Lucky Channel.
I will be asking you to do free talk after that tomorrow.
Well, I'll do it smoothly.
I'll be asking you to go onto the stage side...
Even though it's Shiraishi...
Lucky☆
Channel
Miserable...
Good Lucky!
Everyone, thank you for gathering around for me!
Please enjoy a lot today!
That heart of the dear one...
On what day should you reach it?
Flowing in the stream,
Not knowing the words of that day,
The Sixteenth Outou
The Sixteenth
Outou Festival
searching for those remnants to whereever...
Let us have her sing!
Kogami Akira-san with "Misoji Misaki".
"Is it alr..."
Yes, that's alright!
Hey! What're you doing with that interruption!?
There now, didn't I tell you it was a test!?
We have no time!
Like I'd know somethi...
It seems like you don't understand difficult Japanese, can't you!?
Everyone! Are you ready?
This is the last dress rehearsal!
It was an idea I said out in a whim,
but now I am glad I had been blessed with such...
a chance of being able to do something with you like this!
More than thinking about success or failure,
it would be the best if we could do it enjoyably!
曖昧3センチ
Aimai 3 senchi
Unclear 3 centimeters...
そりゃぷにってことかい？ちょっ!
Sorya punitte koto kai? cho!
Is that a puni? Waitasec!
らっぴんぐが制服…
Rappingu ga seifuku…
The uniform's the wrapping…
だぁぁ不利ってことない　ぷ。
Daa furitte koto nai　Pu.
Hey, there's no disadvantage in that, yeah.
がんばっちゃ♥やっちゃっちゃ
Ganbaccha♥yacchaccha
Try your best♥do your thing-cha,
そんときゃーっち&Releaseぎョッ
son tokyaacchi & ririisu gyo
at that time, well, catch & release, gyo!
汗っ、々っ
A-se, a-se!
In the sweaty, sweaty...
の谷間にDarlin'darlin'F R E E Z E!!
No tanima ni daarin daarin furiiーzu!
cleavage darlin' darlin' FREEZE!!
なんかダるー、なんかデるー
NankaDAruuー, nankaDEruー
Somewhat lazy..., something's coming out...
あいしテるー
AishiTEruuー
I love you...
あれ一個が違ってるんるー
Are ikko ga chigatterunruー
One of those is different, ruー.
なやみン坊ー 高鉄棒 おいしん簿ー
NayamiNbouー Koutetsubou oishinboー
A worrywart, high horizontal bar - an ever-lengthening list...
いーかげんにシナサイ
Iikagen ni SHINASAI
Now get reasonable!
飛んでったアイツの火照るカラダって
Tondetta AITSU no hoteru KARADAtte
The burning body of who flew away right now is...
所謂ふつーのおにゃのコ
Iwayuru futsuu no onya no KO
what is called a "usual girl".
驚いた、
Odoroita,
I'm surprised,
あたしだけ? 豚骨ハリガネおかわりダー!!!!
atashi dake? tonkotsu harigane okawari daaー!!!!
Only me? I get an extra portion of tonkotsu with super hard noodlesー!!!!
BON-BONおーえん団
BON-BON oーendan
Bon-bon cheering team.
Let's get! Cherry pie
Let's get! Cherry pie.
RAN-RAN　かんげー会
Ranraan　kangeーikai
RAN-RAN, welcoming party.
Look up! せんせーしょん
Look up! Senseーshon
Look up! Sensation.
はい！　存在感・・小惑星
Haai　Sonzaikan　tenten　shouwakusei
Yes, feeling of being here・・meteor!
ぶつかって溶けました　呆然　大いに歌ってシレンジャー
Butsukatte tokemashita　bouzen　ooi ni utatte shirenjaー
Got melted by the collision, dumbfounded and singing a lot, "Shiranger!"
もっていけ!
Motte ike!
Take and go!
最後に笑っちゃうのはあたしのはず
Saigo ni waracchau no wa atashi no hazu
The last one laughing should be me,
セーラーふくだからです
Seeraa fuku dakara desu
because it's a sailor fuku.
←結論
←Ketsuron
←Conclusion.
月曜日なのに！
Getsuyoubi nanoni!
Even if it's monday!
機嫌悪いのどうするよ？
Kigen warui no dou suru yo？
What will you do with that bad mood?
夏服がいいのです←キャ？ワ！イイｖ
Natsufuku ga ii no desu←KYA?WA!IIv
I want my summer uniform←It?Is!Cute!
接近3ピクト するまでってちゅーちょだ　やん☆
Sekkin san pikuto, suru madette chuーcho da　yan☆
Getting closer's in three paces, I'll hesitate until you do 'it' Oh☆
頑張って　張り切って
Ganbatte,　harikitte
Try your best, be on high,
My Darlin'darlin' P L E A S E!!
Mai daarin daarin puriizu
my darlin' darlin' please!
We did it!
It was a great success!
Oh gosh!
It's enough for a big one!
What, you guys? Were you still staying here?
As we were doing practice for the cheering!
Was that so? And... How's the state of it?
Well, that'll be something to look forward to!
Sensei, I'm thirsty!
Ah...
Well, I guess it's alright.
I'll treat hard-working youngsters to something like a drink!
Ah, lucky!
Is it alright?
It's alright.
As it's such a time, it's special!
For that, bring to life the first shot of the Culture Festival!
Yeah!
What happened, Tsukasa?
I wonder how it's called...
It just seems like I feel this strange feeling...
Yes, indeed...
To tell you the truth, I feel a bit touched as well...
They do say that a festival is most delighting...
when you're preparing for it as well...
Ah, yes... Tomorrow's the real thing, isn't it...
Indeed...
There might be no more times to stay in school until so late...
When you think like that, you feel a bit lonely, doesn't it?
Eh...
T-tamura-san... Your face is all stiff!
Err... Somehow... my stomach hurts...
Tsukasa, it's all stiffy, isn't it?
Such you, you seem not to be as calm and composed as always.
Being nervous, your concentration will rise!
Ah... I might have become unable to move by excess nervousness.
Aah... tes-tes...
And so, right now I shall open the Outou Festival!
Today's first presentation is...
an idea of our overseas student, Patricia...
Cheerleading of gathered friendly members!
And so, I will right away ask you to...
Ah, er... Excuse me, a mobile phone...
Ahh! It's mine, this is bad!
Dang..! Hu!? Ah!
And in the end of it all with a trouble!
All the power came out and I was close to falling down!
What an awesome timing!
Isn't this like really shameful?
They do say that troubles are accompaniments...
Well, should you say that that is like us, it surely is.
There's no more tense feeling at all...
Err, so...
Well, how should I put it...
Yes! Really excuse me! With the usual mode, somehow excuse me!
Now!
Well, then, let us say it once more to re-take the mood!
It's the "Take it! The sailor fuku!"
Please visit us at
http://jeeb.fiveforty.jp/
#jeeb@irc.rizon.net
Lucky Star!
またあなたの気まぐれが動き出した
Mata anata no kimagure ga ugokidashita
Your caprices have started moving again,
悲しいわこれっきりね
Kanashii wa, korekkirine
it's sad, this is the end, isn't it...
またあの娘の夢を見ているのでしょう
Mata ano ko no yume wo mite iru no deshou
I guess you are seeing a dream of that girl again...
ため息でSo long in my dream.
Tameiki de, So long in my dream.
With a sigh, so long in my dream.
She is an Angel (NO!)　She is a Devil
She is an Angel (NO!) She is a Devil.
Ah　あなたにとっては甘い罠をかける女
Ah, anata ni totte wa amai wana wo kakeru hito
Ah, for you she's a person (woman) who spreads sweet traps...
あなたの愛はパラダイス
Anata no ai wa paradaisu
Your love is a paradise,
くり返しては消えた
Kurikaeshite wa kieta
that faded away after repeating itself...
I love you　口唇の中
I love you, kuchibiru no naka
"I love you, within my lips..."
もしか　もしか　愛はもしかして
Moshika, moshika... Ai wa moshikashite...
Could it be, could it be... Oh, could it be that love is...
ほおり投げた　ブーメラン
hourinageta buumeran
a tossed boomerang?
もしか　もしか　愛はもしかして
moshika, moshika... Ai wa moshikashite...
Could it be, could it be... Oh, could it be that love is...
ほうり投げた　ブーメラン
hourinageta buumeran...
a tossed boomerang?
This video was brought to you by JEEB