Now, let'ssu begin yoo!
It's gonna come now...
Fungaa!
Now start out already!
I My Something
"I my something"
そりゃぷにってことかい、ちょっ
Sorya punitte koto kai, cho
That's about a puni, is it, cho?
ら、ぐーんぐーんが制服
Ra, guun-guun ga seifuku
Ra, guun guun goes the seifuku,
なぁふりってことない？　うん
Naa furitte koto nai？　Un
Hey, there's no irrationality in this? Yeah.
頑張っちゃ、やっちゃっちゃ、
Ganbaccha, yacchaccha,
Try your best, do the thing-cha,
そんときゃ　じゃリリース料
son tokya　jya ririisu ryou
at that time, well the things for release!
あせっ、あせっ
A-se, a-se!
"A-se, a-se!"
の谷間にダーリンダーリンフリー
No taniai ni daarin daarin furiiー
In the cleavage darling darling free!
なんかたるー、なんかてるー
Nankataruuー, nankateruー
How to cheat, how to win,
あいしてるー
Aishiteruuー
I love you.
あれ一個が違ってる
Are ikko ga chigatteru
One of those is different.
むん　むやみに暴行鉄棒おいしん棒
Mun muyami ni boukou tetsubou oishinbou
Stuffy, violence with recklessness - steel rod is a sweet rod.
いいかげんにしなさい!
Iikagen ni shinasai!
Now get reasonable!
飛んでったあいつの火照る体って
Tondetta aitsu no hoteru karadatte
The burning body of who flied away right now is...
いわゆる普通の女の子
Iwayuru futsuu no onna no ko
what is called a "usual girl".
驚いた、
Odoroita,
I'm surprised,
あたしだけ豚骨針金おかわりダー!!!!
atashi dake tonkotsu harigane okawari daaー!!!!
Only I get an extra portion of tonkotsu with a needle insideー!!!!
ボンボン応援団
Bon-bon ouendan
Bon-bon cheering team.
Let's get cherry pie
Let's get cherry pie.
らんらーん　関係感
Ranraan　kankeikan
Blazing, relationship feeling,
you have センセーション
you have senseeshon
you have sensation.
ハーイ　存在感　点々　小惑星
Haai　Sonzaikan　tenten　shouwakusei
Yes, feeling of being here, here and there meteors.
ぶつかって溶けました　呆然　大いに歌ってシリンダー
Butsukatte tokemashita　bouzen　ooi ni utatte shirindaa
Got melt from the collision, dumbfounded singing a lot, "Cilinder!"
もっていけ、
Motte ike,
Take and go,
最後に笑っちゃうのはあたしのはず
Saigo ni waracchau no wa atashi no hazu
The last one laughing should be me,
セーラー服だからです
Seeraa fuku dakara desu
because it's a seeraa fuku.
結論
Ketsuron
Conclusion.
月曜日なのに
Getsuyoubi nanoni
Even if it's monday,
機嫌悪いのどうするよ
Kigen warui no dou suru yo
What will you do with that bad mood?
夏服がいいのです、かわいい
Natsufuku ga ii no desu, kawaii
The summer uniform is better, cute.
接近賛否それまでって躊躇だ　やーん
Sekkin sanbi, sore madette choucho da　yaーn
Yes and no for getting closer, until that it's undecided, yaan.
頑張って　張り切って
Ganbatte,　harikitte
Try your best, be on high,
ま、ダーリンダーリンプリーズ
Ma, daarin daarin puriizu
well darling darling please!
The summer, the sea!
And so, I ask you to lead us today as drivers, sensei, neesan.
Ossu!
Even so...
Huh?
Both of you have a lot of free time.
Ungh...
The Standard
for Summer
Excuse us, on a holiday.
No, please don't worry about it.
Narumi-san, you are a traffic safety policewoman, right?
That's right, you can leave the traffic rules to me!
Ah, I got passed!
Huh?
That bastard...
Just... Hey, is that traffic safety?!
When neesan gets behind the wheel, she usually gets reckless...
I'll have Kagami and Tsukasa to be the sacrifices...
Hee, was that so?
Even though she's a policewoman...
Uh, huh...
This is strange, I strayed away from them...
Wha?!
Ahh! Sensei, you're going on the wrong road!
Sensei, that's a one-way street!
I was careless...
I didn't think they'd both...
Lucky☆Star D: RX-7 FD vs '97 Subaru VIVIO RX-R
That car's just unbelievable! Who is that?!
A perfect downslope braking drift! FD's losing on the corner entries!
The leaving's good, too!
Ah, unbelievable! So close to the guardrails!
The attack points are...
the next five consecutive hairpin curves, huh?
It's overspeeding!
Did it lose its brakes?
It passed him!
What's with this Chome-Chome D- like driving?!
Nanako-san, you know...
you're really good at driving a car...
Huh, is that so?
Konata, you know, really gets sick when she rides in a car...
That's why I brought my anti-sickness drugs with me...
But with Nanako-san's driving style I didn't get sick at all!
Huh?
But in this position I have no place to intervene!
Wheeh...
Aah... Ahh...
Ahh... Aah...
And so...
Let's search for a ryokan, shall we?
tn. Ryokan - a traditional Japanese inn
Waah!
It's really good weather out there, the best thing for swimming.
Really... Yesterday I really thought how it was all going to be...
I'll put on the swimsuit right away!
You're still saying such childlike...
things...!
Konata-san, are you serious 'bout that?
And I haven't heard about school swimsuits at this age...
There are needs for things like this, too, Kagami'n...
From what time is that swimsuit?!
tn. 6-3, the sixth year of elementary school...
Why did you take a float ring with you even though you've got pretty good motorics...
Well, you don't have to crawl around the sea even if you can swim, right?
The feeling's 'leisure'!
Lei-su-re.
And when you adapt into these 'needs' you can't separate the school swimsuit and the ring!
But isn't it so that people of such needs won't come to the sea?
Hm...
Hmm...
In anime, manga and stuff 'suika wari' is a regular,...
tn. Suika wari - A Japanese summer beach tradition of breaking a watermelon
but in reality people don't really do it.
Well I have seen it, but maybe because it's something too good to waste...
Indeed, the watermelon's going to be in utter mashup the day they'll start destroying them with guns.
You're watching too much anime!
Miyuki-san, have you done it? You're rich, too...
No, I have not.
Uhm... When you think well about it, it has an image that rich people won't do it no matter what...
When you say so, it seems reasonable.
Ah!
Eh...
Hmm...
Ah!
Hoi!
Hm...
I did know it, but you don't really become like in manga, after all...
I'm sorry for not meeting your expectations.
Oh, well, I think it's a bit lonesome for us both, having to watch over them...
coming to the sea as women in a good age...
Ah, you're mistaken...
But if it'd be like them coming in his arms, I have no problem with being girls-only!
No, that's...
Because lately more and more people tend to get married later in life, too.
You can go and take it easy when choosing, you know...
"You've mistaken! It's just that my husband has been transferred away from home for some time. I'm a married woman!"
Aahh...!
Even though the sea is the mecca of nanpa, there's no chances for us...
tn. Nanpa - 'picking up' girls
Well, it's good that it's not annoying...
But aren't they just thinking that we're sisters with our family because there's one like this around?
Right there-shouichi'tto...
What is it?
Well, you know... It was just a bit unpleasant to just sit, while being wet...
Yes, I understand that.
Well, Tsukasa will put up with just cookies, then.
Quite excessive, now aren't you!
Hmmm.... hmmm...
Uuuhh...
What is it?
My neck hurts...
Is that so?
Yes, as I expected!
What are you so happy about?
Well, I got served something that is like from a painting of a Sea House! Look at this curry without ingredients!
This is truly a Sea House!
Indeed!
Even if they'd be so-so if eaten usually...
When they're eaten in a place like this, they just seem to feel delicious, don't they?
Puhhaaa!
Beer at the sea is the best, after all!
Sometimes there are some lukewarm ones, though...
But it's a bit ridiculous that one frankfurter costs 300 yen, though...
Exactly! Half-cooked, too.
But you just eat it without minding.
To tell you the truth I like the oily and over-spiced and some other parts of this chicken...
Such plain yakisoba is quite good, too.
That's enough to say 'Ah! I'll take this home' and stuff. But that's just a bit...
And that was so...
Konata's touched!
It's not that good, but the oil just makes it better...
Hey...
Is this so good that you get on such high spirit?
Not really.
It's not good enough to run the sea with just a sumoist's apron on.
Is that another anime-joke from somewhere?
Aah... I drank too much...
There's nothing to do about it... Shall we stay for another night?
Yui-neesan, how's your work?
I've taken tomorrow on the deadline, too. So it's OK, OK.
Hiyayayayayahahagegegegege...wa...
It's... friggin'... cold...
Ah-haha, sensei, you're overreacting!
Here we go...
It's not c... jyuwawawawaaaah! Haai!
tn. Please check some of the references on our website
Lucky Star!
tn. A melody we know, right?
I wonder why after being in sea the hair will get so jarred?
I'm not sure... Could be something to do with salt or something?
Isn't that so, Miyuki?
That is so. The most substansial causes seem to be salt and ultra-violet rays.
Well why is that so bad?
The hair's always exposed to UV rays, right?
Well, if I would explain that further, it would become a bit longer...
Un-un.
Well, then...
Khm...
The cause of hair damage in sea is the effect of intensive ultra-violet rays, that become so...
because the salt, consisted in sea water or sea wind, adheses onto the hair and removes the moisture from it.
Also, when hair is exposed to strong ultra-violet radiation in open air,...
the melanin pigmentation changes colour, which becomes the cause of hair becoming tawny.
I hear that even if foreign matter such as salt or chlorine will remain on hair,...
it will still dry and become the cause of hair becoming light brown.
Ultra-violet rays and foreign matter are the reason of hair becoming damaged, especially in summer.
These end up resulting from the damage of the cuticle.
When you get showered by strong ultra-violet rays, the binding systems that are said to preserve hair are disconnected...
Look, look!
Timotei, timotei, timoteeei!
What's that?
Uhh...
Aaaahh...
I wonder how we appear when looked at from the side...
I don't know...
The talk just won't go on, now doesn't it...
Don't you think that 'family' or 'relatives' could be safe to think?
It could be so...
"Is there no catch?!"
Neesan, neesan!
Timotei, timotei, timoteeei!
Aww, how nostalgic! I did it too!
I did it! That was the reaction I wanted!
How old are you, anyways?
Mmm...
Mandom.
You can already stop the old man- jokes.
What happened, Kona-chan?
There's a flag standing right now.
What are you talking about?
Here you can invoke an event!
For the present, before the selection, in order to see the both...
Save frequently!
"Are you throwing rocks?"
The image is complete!
It's perfect! Now, come!
I can no longer follow...
Ahh...
Mostly, you know... Because you're like that even today...
Today what?
You know, nanpa. Nanpa!
Hmmm...
Be-because it was a thing you brought up at first...
B-but I don't really think about such things at all...
Aaah... Kagami wanted to be nanpa'd...
Th-that's not it!
Kyaaa!
Damn! I missed it!
Ahh...
What is it?
Uh, nothing...
I just wondered how do you, Tsukasa, deal with hair...
I'm pretty smooth, so I don't do anything.
Uh-huun...
How about you, onee-chan?
Ah, me?! Well, I guess I'm doing the usual...
Hmm....
Ah...
Actually it was pretty risky today...
Uh, what was?
No, it's just that...
'that' was...
Ah!
just about to come...
Ahh, 'that'.
Was that so? That went well.
Were you, Tsukasa, completely safe?
Yeah, I was completely.
Ending a week ago, I thought that the timing was perfect.
It's so bothersome when it comes at such times...
Uh, you said it...
It's lonesome to be the only one not able to enter the sea...
And it's a bit... to use 'that'...
Oh, yes... you just hesitate...
I haven't used 'it' at all.
Uh, huh, huh...
Such shameful-looking talk, you two...
Well how about you, then, speaking like that!
Ah!
Perhaps...
What's with that face?
Nothing really...
This seems to be a truly happened story,...
but a certain person from an imaging software wholesale company...
was trying to go home after finishing his job...
He sat into a bus, late at night, like any other day.
It seems that his house somewhere at the end of the line,...
and halfway through all the passengers gradually got off...
In a moment he became the only passenger...
The driver seemed to have mistaken that there was no longer anyone on board...
and...
started to sing 'DANZEN! Futari wa XXXXXX Cure' in a loud voice!
Kyaaa!
Completely shocked!
Such a rumor was around...
Naah
There's no such...
Eh?!
Huh?
Huwa...
How lucky... I was really scared...
Hahahaa, to tell you the truth, I...
It's me, Sukekiyo.
Kyaaaa!
Out...
From where did you bring up that mask?!
Well then, good night.
All right, good night...
The Inugami family.
Hyau-uu...
She sure has an effect for shocks...
Would you sleep at last?
Hey! We're going!
Ah... OK!
"I cannot speak such interesting things...
It's me, Tsukasa...
It's me, Tsukasa..."
Huwaaaah!
Onee-chan!.... uhn, uhn... It was so scary...
Huh?
Uh, what happened?
It's the moment when a girl climbs on another step of adulthood, Kagami'n.
Huh?
The Comp Matsuri seems to be popular.
That's because Japanese are really weak for the word 'limited edition'.
If their sales sales would go up with such one word, shouldn't they just do it every month?
But that way the value will vanish, won't it.
"I really asked about it."
"Yes. Is it really true that if you take more than three types of the same thing to a walk it will alwa..."
Both of you, try to deal with your room cleaning and stuff while on vacation.
Let's se...
Ah, how nostalgic. This is a junior high book!
Onee-chan, look at this album!
Isn't this dad a bit awful?
Yeah, I've been paying attention to dad's 'that' from that time...
It seems really nice, but is your clean up going on?
Ah!
Let's see...
Hey, you wouldn't want these clothes?
Ah. If you don't need them I'll take them.
Well, I'll leave them then.
Yeah, thanks.
oops-a-daisy...
Hey, you need this?
Uh... Well, should I take that then?
And what about this?
and this?
Huh?! Don't say she's just using me as a trash can?!
You just carelessly take a look at albums and get slower.
Ah, I understand that. If there's a magazine behind something you just read it.
That's right, isn't it...
That reminds me, where's Tsukasa?
Ah, that girl doesn't really throw stuff away, so she just takes her time.
She's doing it today, too.
Aah, Tsukasa just seems to keep everything.
On the opposite, Kagami seems to bluntly throw anything away.
I wonder why my image in your head is so aggressive?
Aah, so you kept your junior high textbook..
Don't you have such?
I left such islands together with my memories at my old school.
No, take them with you. It's an inconvenience for the school.
At last I ended my cleaning...
You just can't throw stuff away, as you remember the times you used them, even though you think that you're not going to use it again.
There really are people that'll want to keep anything.
Tsukasa really seems to be that type.
You, instead, seem to throw even needed things away.
Because you leave your textbooks and stuff.
Hmm...
Miyuki, remember to go to nose treatment before the school begins.
I do understand it, but I'm so weak with it...
Hmm...
If you say as much it's a bit hard to make you go...
If it's no good to go, let's have him come over.
To the visiting doctor.
P-please wait a second!
Lucky Star!
LUCKY CHANNEL!
Good lucky!
As a fast thing, already in its sixth time, Lucky Channel!
I'm Kogami Akira, already willing to say that this corner has gradually become familiar to me!
KAT-TUuN!
Splash...
WAH!?
Huh, did you say something?
A... ah...
Ah, aaahhh...
The assistant Shiraishi Minoru still seems to be in a tense condition...
It's scary... S-she can just do anything she wants to me...
It's like he's still fluttering with excitement about you all.
No-one ever says her anything because she's Akira-sama...
I'd just want him to get accustomed to this job...
Yes! I did go to the sea!
Especially, how many times do I have to say that you should watch your tongue when speaking to an elder...
It's on purpose, even if I'm doing my best at making this programme funnier...
Yes... the dams are just too big, there's now 54 of them...
Honestly I hate it!
And so, I'd like to introduce today the already popular character on Lucky☆Star, Izumi Konata!
You just can't all 54 of them, but she says that I should do it...
Oh what should I do...
Tte, you're so noisy...
Maicchinguu-!
Well, Izumi Konata-san, 17 years old. Her hobbies are games, anime, reading!
If you depend on the material, it seems that she somehow checks new books and shows without them being mentioned...
Her weekends seem to be storms of netoge until the morning!
In brief, a wota?
ヲタ (wota) - a version of the word 'otaku'
Well, it seems so...
Mm....
"Think of something, I!"
Oh, otaku seem to be House- typish people, right?
They tend to cry after seeing 'A Dog of Flanders' and stuff.
Huh?! How old is your vision of otaku?!
Are studying properly?
Stop saying vague things!
No, that's...
Oh well, indeed there were cute 'moe' characters in 'A Dog of Flanders', mutual with healing.
But a girl like me is much better than some dog!
Do you understand that they're seeking a magnificent, as kawaii as cute maiden?!
If I'd go right, they'll go too!
If I'd go left, they go too!
They can't even take a bath because they're lining for the concert through the night.
They want to meet me even if it gets serious with the stains!
With that devotedness, in the middle of being burnt by the freaking hot tropical sunshine, they wait for my arrival!
Even if it would become so that the bandana on their heads would be completely wet!
Huh...
But, well, they're customers, too...
Even if they wouldn't let me end my words at a handshake party...
Even if they intervene with not reading the mood as MCs... The well-going's a limit, right?
Ahh... Thanks to them 'I' now am.
And for those people I must do my best, like that...
Is it so...
You, too, will once understand. The toughness of being an idol.
The sour, the sweet... when you bite it the real taste will come out.
Even if there were fans or clients you didn't li...
Uwah! Just at the right time!
Everyone, did you approximately understand Konata-san's character?
Well, let's meet again on the next Lucky Channel!
Bye-nii!
Or should I say that it turned into introduction of otakus more than Konata's!
Haa...
A-Akira-sama, are you alright?
Do it.
Huh, understood!
'At that time, the thing that was seen by the correspondent!'
It's not interest...
Yay, Kage's good after all!
Oh, got it got it...
So, Tsukasa, did you put something in?
Yeah, I did.
Tsukasa-san's singing voice is really pure now isn't it?
Uh-huh-huh, I wonder if I can sing well...
Oh, Miyuki, what are you going to sing?
Songs are not something I really know of, although it's embarassing...
Oh!
So it came at last...
Tsukasa-san, try your best!
明日は特別　スペシャル・デイ
Ashita wa tokubetsu　supesharu・dei
Tomorrow's a particular special day...
一年一度のチャンス
Ichinen ichido no chansu
the one and only chance in a year.
OH BABY...
L-O-V-E - lovely Tsukasa!
OH BABYって　LOVE　YOU
OH BABYtte　LOVE　YOU
Oh baby, oh, I love you.
Hey hey...
L-O-V-E - lovely Sayuri!
And who's that?!
誰もが浮かれて　カーニバル
Daremo ga  ukarete　kaーnibaru
Everyone's so merry, it's a carnival.
彼氏のハートを射止めて、OH BABY!
Kareshi no haーto wo itomete、OH BABY!
I'll make my boyfriend's heart my own, oh baby.
It's not Kuninama Sayuri, right?
OH BABY!
Who is that, anyways?!
What was her member number, anyways?
甘い甘い恋のチョコレート
Amai amai koi no chokoreーto
This sweet, sweet chocolate of love...
あなたにあげてみても目立ちはしないから
Anata ni agete mitemo medachi wa shinai kara
even if I'd try to give it to you, it won't stand out,...
You're too damn noisy!
私ちょっと最後の手段で決めちゃう
Watashi chotto saigo no shudan de kimechau
so I tend to choose at the last chance a bit.
バレンタインデイ・キッス、バレンタインデイ・キッス
Barentain dei・kissu、barentain dei・kissu
The kiss on valentine's day, the kiss on valentine's day...
バレンタインデイ・キッス!
Barentain dei・kissu!
The kiss on valentine's day!
リボンをかけて
Ribon wo kakete
Put the ribbon on me!
Sha-la-lala, such a lovely...
And so, the next Lucky Star is?
It's me, Kagami. When I tried to take off the point of a hangnail in my finger, I happened to pull a bit too deep part of it...
There really are times when you feel pain...
And then the timing of taking off the crust!
When it becomes itchy and you start wanting to take it off, it seems OK when you begin...
taking it off gradually from the grip side, but as you take the middle off fast, there is blood.
That, too, is pretty damaging...
Next Time: Image!
Look forward to it!