Yoshimizu
Kagami
Theatre
Ah, the B class of third year?
Kuroi-sensei!
Yeah, yeah...
曖昧3センチ
Aimai 3 senchi
Unclear 3 centimeters...
そりゃぷにってことかい？ちょっ!
Sorya punitte koto kai? cho!
Is that a puni? Waitasec!
らっぴんぐが制服…
Rappingu ga seifuku…
The uniform's the wrapping…
だぁぁ不利ってことない　ぷ。
Daa furitte koto nai　Pu.
Hey, there's no disadvantage in that, yeah.
がんばっちゃ♥やっちゃっちゃ
Ganbaccha♥yacchaccha
Try your best♥do your thing-cha,
そんときゃーっち&Releaseぎョッ
son tokyaacchi & ririisu gyo
at that time, well, catch & release, gyo!
汗っ、々っ
A-se, a-se!
In the sweaty, sweaty...
の谷間にDarlin'darlin'F R E E Z E!!
No tanima ni daarin daarin furiiーzu!
cleavage darlin' darlin' FREEZE!!
なんかダるー、なんかデるー
NankaDAruuー, nankaDEruー
Somewhat lazy..., something's coming out...
あいしテるー
AishiTEruuー
I love you...
あれ一個が違ってるんるー
Are ikko ga chigatterunruー
One of those is different, ruー.
なやみン坊ー 高鉄棒 おいしん簿ー
NayamiNbouー Koutetsubou oishinboー
A worrywart, high horizontal bar - an ever-lengthening list...
いーかげんにシナサイ
Iikagen ni SHINASAI
Now get reasonable!
飛んでったアイツの火照るカラダって
Tondetta AITSU no hoteru KARADAtte
The burning body of who flew away right now is...
所謂ふつーのおにゃのコ
Iwayuru futsuu no onya no KO
what is called a "usual girl".
驚いた、
Odoroita,
I'm surprised,
あたしだけ? 豚骨ハリガネおかわりダー!!!!
atashi dake? tonkotsu harigane okawari daaー!!!!
Only me? I get an extra portion of tonkotsu with super hard noodlesー!!!!
BON-BONおーえん団
BON-BON oーendan
Bon-bon cheering team.
Let's get! Cherry pie
Let's get! Cherry pie.
RAN-RAN　かんげー会
Ranraan　kangeーikai
RAN-RAN, welcoming party.
Look up! せんせーしょん
Look up! Senseーshon
Look up! Sensation.
はい！　存在感・・小惑星
Haai　Sonzaikan　tenten　shouwakusei
Yes, feeling of being here・・meteor!
ぶつかって溶けました　呆然　大いに歌ってシレンジャー
Butsukatte tokemashita　bouzen　ooi ni utatte shirenjaー
Got melted by the collision, dumbfounded and singing a lot, "Shiranger!"
もっていけ!
Motte ike!
Take and go!
最後に笑っちゃうのはあたしのはず
Saigo ni waracchau no wa atashi no hazu
The last one laughing should be me,
セーラーふくだからです
Seeraa fuku dakara desu
because it's a sailor fuku.
←結論
←Ketsuron
←Conclusion.
月曜日なのに！
Getsuyoubi nanoni!
Even if it's monday!
機嫌悪いのどうするよ？
Kigen warui no dou suru yo？
What will you do with that bad mood?
夏服がいいのです←キャ？ワ！イイｖ
Natsufuku ga ii no desu←KYA?WA!IIv
I want my summer uniform←It?Is!Cute!
接近3ピクト するまでってちゅーちょだ　やん☆
Sekkin san pikuto, suru madette chuーcho da　yan☆
Getting closer's in three paces, I'll hesitate until you do 'it' Oh☆
頑張って　張り切って
Ganbatte,　harikitte
Try your best, be on high,
My Darlin'darlin' P L E A S E!!
Mai daarin daarin puriizu
my darlin' darlin' please!
Round
hhSushih
Neesan, Thank you for treating us today.
Don't worry about it, we can do something like this anytime!
It was tasty, wasn't it?
Yeah.
If the egg is delicious, you somehow become happy, don't you?
Ahh! Gasoline prices are up 2 yen from yesterday...
I should have filled up then...
Even if the person is generous with money, I wonder why they dwell even upon 1 yen difference when it comes to gasoline prices.
The
Yonder
Here
Speaking of which, I heard the book I had lent you some time ago is going to be made into a game.
Although I don't buy games.
Kagami, your information is old.
In my case, I reserved the limited edition the moment the information was out.
I bought the anime DVD box and goodies, too, you know.
Wow, you're more addicted than I am, aren't you...
It often happens that the person to whom it was recommended becomes more addicted than the recommender, doesn't it?
As Yui-neesan bought a car like that - being influenced...
A car!?
Yeah, after I lent her a racing manga...
I got surprised that time...
The energy of hobbies is scary...
They won their third straight game yesterday, didn't they?
Yeah! It's a beginning of a miracle, you know!
Japan series will be still within range.
What're they talking about?
I think it should be probably about professional baseball.
It would be an unexpected run with crushing force!
About the one that's sensei's favorite...
First of all, baseball is...
Ah, speaking of professional baseball,
I heard Masaoka Shiki, a famous poet, liked it very much...
Izumi!
Yes!
the catch-ball of the souls,
the collisions of each one's willpower,
and was kept playing as catcher...
the wordless communication,
until he became unable to continue due to his sickness.
or the friendship among players, who are sacrificing themselves on mound,
It seems that he selected his pen name...
by using his childhood name "Noboru"...
and the hot guys who try to respond to that!
and by writing it as "Baseball", "Nobouru".
By the way,
the overall winner in the Major League...
is called the "World Champion", is it not?
It's just that the Japan Series reminded me of it...
Huh? Yeah, although that's only in America
Well, if they want to call themselves the champions of the "World",
they should do that after they've beaten our team, right?
Eh... She's getting excited, isn't she...
It's pretty smelly, isn't it?
Yes, that is so...
Ah, so you were here! Kagami, Miyuki-san!
Oh, Konata!
Help me with these questions.
Rare, isn't it, to have you ask something about studies.
There are some pretty hard questions in here as well, I see...
Ah, well that's because those are the questions from an arcade quiz game.
I'm no good at learning and all, you know...
You, saying such things again...
Or should I say, devote yourself more to your studies!
Since you're also an examinee...
Ha-ha-ha, although it's like this at school, I'm called the wise one over there!
Hmm... What should I say, maybe you should already apply to that something academy.
tn: A joke on a Japanese quiz game "Quiz Magic Academy"
So, because of that I'm a bit lacking sleep...
Until when did you play it?
Miyuki-san, was it that you always went to sleep at 11 o'clock?
Yes.
Early, isn't it...
Ah! I see...
Sleeping kids
Grow ☆
...and so, I thought while looking at Miyuki-san,
but Yuu-chan, even though you sleep a lot, you haven't grown up, right?
Auu...
And oneechan said that, even though I'm sensitive about it...
That night, about 9 o'clock
Ah, excuse me for calling at such a late hour,
I am Kobayakawa, but is it the Iwasaki residence?
Ah, excuse me, could I speak to Minami-chan?...
Eh.. Has she already gone to sleep..?
Did she always go to sleep so early?
Pittan, La La Moji Pittan.
Oh, you sure are singing pleasantly...
Yes, yes... Yes, Somehow... it is alright.
Ah, yes. I will tell so to my father as well.
Yes, after the ceremony to sanctify the ground...
Yes. That is right.
Eh!? No, no - far from it...
No, saying that again...
As I'm underage, really...
That's not it! It's not like that!
Yes, well then... Yes... Yes...
Kagami, you know?
Even if you use gestures, they can't be seen by the person you're talking to.
I know that!
It's subconscious!
That reminds me, during calls, as I have to concentrate on the dialogue, my hands will indeed stop while gaming,
but then the free hand happens to feel a bit lonely, you know...
Ah, I know what you mean.
So, the other day, while I was on the phone, I was cleaning the dust off the floor with a roller, you know...
That rolling one.
You end up doing such things, don't you...
Something like mindless scribbling or simple stuff.
Yeah... But, you know...
You just lose interest in such things as soon as you hang up, right?
Somehow, the circle of clean floor that is only around you is sad, you know...
Couldn't you have finished?
Passion disappears along with the conversation, you know...
So you leave it as is after all, huh?
That person's fairly smelly, right?
I do think that it's okay once in a while though...
Look! **cky, Poc**!
Ahh. I used to do that... when I was in elementary school...
Really... What are you, a kid!?
Boo!
Ah, but speaking of games we did as kids,
we used to make "Bread Plant" by mixing yoghurt, didn't we?
"Bread plant"?
Eh...? You don't know it?
Yeah.
Hey, what was that "Bread plant" right now?
You can tell me, don't be shy!
You're annoying!
You know, the game I lent you in the first semester...
There is another person who wants to play it, so give it back.
Alright. For that small one?
Yeah.
That reminds me, I lent her some as well...
I guess I'll have them given back.
But, you are amazing, Hiiragi.
What is?
Well, the other day, I found some games that I couldn't remember whom I had borrowed them from...
I just thought that you remember well and all...
Oi, oi.
There are others, that I can't remember to whom I lent them...
How sloppy are you!?
No, no! There is a law for forgetting things if a person both borrows and lends for sure!
This is the truth of the universe, you know!
Yeah, right...
Yes... Hello?
Ah. Hiiragi? It's me, Misao.
Yeah-yeah, but why d...
Damn you... You really do it, don't you, Potyomkin...
W-What? Did something happen?
Err, no. Just a bit. Sorry, sorry.
And how may I help you?
Yeah. You know...
Ah... What was it...?
Like I know...
Something really important...
If it was important, don't forget about it...
I took a look at the results of Autumn Jumbo,
but none of mine won...
As you can imagine, you don't win that often...
I too sent a lot of cards,
but I didn't get any prizes...
I see. Sadly...
Sigh.
Since we can't win very often you start thinking about the possibility that the sales clerks and editors are cheating, don't you?
Konata, you musn't doubt people like that!
It's no good... I'll go to sleep already.
Before that, let's go to the bathroom~tto...
I'm being told that I murmur a lot in class...
But it's not like that matters!
Although I was so sleepy, I wonder why I'm so restless now after saying such a weird gag...
Next day, late night
At night it's no good, after all...
I'm not having any urge today as well, I'll try to sleep since I'm dozing off...
It's cold!
Even though I was so sleepy, I wonder why I'm so awake after getting the shivers when entering bed...
Still the next day, late night
I can't do it any more...
It's warm tonight, I wonder if I can fall asleep quickly...
Somehow only my feet feel hot, I can't sleep...
I wonder why...
Do things like this only happen to me?!
This is a free softsub.Not for sale, rent, auction or hardsub.
Not for sale, rent, auction or hardsub.This is a free softsub.
or hardsub.This is a free softsub. Not for sale, rent, auction
Lucky Star!
It has become the season when baked sweet potatoes are delicious, hasn't it?
Err, Kagami... You know...
No, I know... I know, so don't say anything...
Would you eat some?
Thank you very much. But you'll gain weight...
And she says it after all...
But it can't be helped!
As I happened to look at the guy, you know...
Isn't it bad not to buy anything, right?
Look! That "I wonder if she is going to buy something...
I'll be broke if she doesn't", kind of gaze...
Ah, well I do understand you...
Even at a place like Comike, it's really hard to put the book back after you've caught the gaze, right?
You just keep talking regardless of whether you understand or not, don't you?
No, no... It's about when I search for certain things in front of doujinshi groups.
After you've picked up the book in front of the clerk,
it does feel awkward to go to another shop without buying it, doesn't it?
But you put it back in the end, don't you?
Ogohogono...
Lately light novel- based anime has increased, hasn't it?
It seems so.
The novel I lent you a while ago has already been made into an anime three times.
The newest book should be coming out soon as well.
Although I've seen the anime side of it, I've yet to read the novels...
And I get tired by the masses of characters they have...
You go for that again?
The games you often play have far more characters, though, don't they?
That's true, but its mysterious, isn't it ...
Should they release it as a gyaruge it'd be nice...
Hey!
More importantly, I wonder when the fourth anime will come out...
Err, what? Is that a joke on something?
Huh?
Yuu-chan... What were you doing just now?
T-the cap just ends up slanted no matter what...
Ah, well there are such people, aren't there?
A bit clumsy, or something like that...
I often do it...
Here.
Such cute weakness are similar to Miyuki-san's, aren't they...
Thank you.
As expected, Oneechan, you're awesome after all...
Oneechan, What should I do...
Now I can't get it open...
Ah, I did it again... I did it like always...
A girl in distress, aren't you...
Can't open the bag?
Let me try.
Ah, onee-chan, thank you.
Huh?
Huh!?
Shouldn't we just open it at the jagged point?
No! W-w-wait a sec! I'll open it properly, so give me a minute!
It's alright already, let's open it at the jagged point, or with scissors...
Well, that would! My pride! I feel like I have lost...
Oneechan, is it a mosquito?
A mosquito! Don't you just get irritated by the fact you know that it's here?
Even before you get bit!
As I know that it's here, I can't leave without squishing it!
That is the thing called "The instinct of a hunter", you know!
Just a random thought, but...
If Yuu-chan or I were to be asked out by a student in the same grade,
I wonder if that person would become a lolicon?
Since it's the same grade, if you'd say that he's not, then he wouldn't be...
However, in this case I feel that there's the matter of appearances as well...
Hmm... If you were a 30-year-old woman who looked like an elementry school student,
on the other hand, you could say that he prefers older women...
Quite a complicated subject this is...
Defining is difficult, isn't it...
He's my father, after all...
If it were Kagami, it'd end with "Isn't it irrelevant!?"
Well then, how about you, Daddy?
The fact that you fell in love with with mother who has gone to a better place,
and dote on me, means...
that you, daddy, are a lolicon - right?
No, no. Wait a second, that is a bit different...
I don't just like petite girls, but the normal ones too,
so "you are a lolicon as well" is right.
In short, it all depends on the character, doesn't it.
Either way, you're a no-good human, right?
Well then, daddy - you always come and stick to me,
but even if I were a boy, would you touch me the same way as now?
...Isn't it obvious?
Okay, I understand you...
It was good that I was born a girl then.
Well... It's about time the bath has gotten hot, isn't it?
Why don't you go in before us, Yuu-chan.
Yeah. well, then please excuse me...
He looked bad, so he sent her away...
Hey, Daddy...
Huh?
Mom, you know... She was small and a childhood friend of yours, daddy...
tn : gyaruge--->a game with fanservice & good girls, a bit like eroge
Isn't it a bit like a character of a gyaruge?
You think so, too? Kanata just was cute from childhood, you know...
I do understand that you, Daddy, were really in love with her,
but I wonder why mom married you...
Hm...
"As you never turn to me, I have become such a gyaruge-loving man!"...
after I said that, she did pretty easily...
You are the lowest!
But it's the truth...
Isn't that intimidation!?
No, that's not all. Of course.
She was really pleased when you, Konata, were born, too...
Oh, I wonder if this mole comes from Sou-kun...
No, her eyes and such are all yours.
However you look at it, it's our baby.
But I'd like her development to be different from ours.
So that the height wouldn't be like mine, and that the personality wouldn't be like Sou-kun's...
You sure are severe...
But why did you suddenly ask about Kanata?
Well, as I don't really know much about my mom...
Konata, are you lonely without a mother?
Not really.
Daddy, you have the liveliness of two people, and right now there's Yuu-chan as well...
Is that... so?
Kanata, Konata is growing into a very good girl.
Although she is not quite what you wished for as "normal"...
Small & Maniacal
Small & Maniacalmy name is alex what is your name
Hey, Konata...
Um?
I beg you, Konata, please don't die before me...
For the time being I have absolutely no such intention...
Good. Good.
Although Kanata happened to pass away at a young age,
She said smilingly that she had been happy in the end.
Although the one left is still lonely...
I want to die like that in the end as well...
With a smile..?
What kind of death would be good?
Hmm, let me see... Moe with death, or something.
Daddy, You'll never be able to die properly for sure!
Ah, by the way... I bought a digital camera for work today.
Ah, it's been a while since I have last come back here.
You're rubbing up against me! That's it!
Well, let's take another one!
I wonder what they are doing right now...
I'm in the middle of playing game!
Yeah, yeah-yeah!
Here, "Cheese!"
D-Daddy, you!
Yes! Let's take another shot!
It's enough already, isn't it?
Or should I say, daddy, you're coming too close.
You are cold, Konata!
We are in the middle of capturing memories with our new camera, you know
Wasn't it for your job?
Don't say such stern things, you know. One more!
Well, Sou-kun is as always.
That's enough... Or should I say, you're stubborn...
That reminds me, you never payed attention to to other people's convenience, did you...
Get off me!
Kicking like that is cruel, Konata!
Take this!
Really, it hasn't changed at all...
But, it's that...
The feeling of holding you in my arms has begun to resemble that of Kanata more and more,
it sure makes my heart beat fast...
Try not to make such dangerous comments so nobly!
Ehh... I can imagine Mommy's hardships...
What!?
Indeed...
Your father is like that, but you musn't become a delinquent...
Ah, yes - Konata.
That game of the other day, if you beat it - tell me how, too.
Its alright...
That's unexpectedly difficult, don't you think?
But, since they're playing a game together as parent and child, it seems like they're going well along.
I think I probably missed some right choices somewhere,
as I just couldn't reach the ero-scenes of the character I wanted to.
Wha-Uwa! What are you letting your daughter play, darling!
Uhh, I wonder if it's alright...
Isn't your moral education wrong, Sou-kun?
Hey, why did my mother select you, daddy?
Eh!?
As you're an otaku, lolicon and an elderly lech, you know.
Usually you don't select someone like that.
So she says as far...
You are mean, aren't you.
Really...
But, let me see... As Kanata had quick wits, so...
Really, he is always like this, so...
...I always almost forget that...
I guess she saw through that.
...why I ...
Even as the hopeless man I am,
...got together with him...
There was one thing that I had absolute confidence in.
The only thing you absolutely had confidence in? What's that?
Huh? Mufufu...
Yeah. That's the fact that in the whole wide world, I love Kanata the most.
That's it.
After all, this isn't fair, is it...
Life and Science
Anime/TV zines
New Face Award
The Announcement of the Winning Candidate
None
Person suitable
Selectors
Selector's Reviews
He recognizes both my good and bad points...
Shows me all of both his good and bad points...
My most reassuring place.
The place where I feel the safest.
Like that... Hahaha...
All right! After cherishing the memory, should we take another photo?
And let's take some together with Yuu-chan later on, shall we?
I'm chagrined a little that I cannot be where I am now...
It's enough. And it won't be just one photo, you know.
Daddy, so you did buy it for your hobby, after all... Really...
What are you saying!?
Daddy is just trying to get used to it before the research.
But...
Oh, really...
Just as Sou-kun and all are in me,
should I keep living on inside Sou-kun and all,
I'll keep an eye on them from now on, too...
Uwo, Lookie-look! Let's start!
So that they, who gave me all that happiness, could be happy...
Say... cheese!
Ah, I wonder if they'll be surprised...
Ow! Daddy! This picture...
Ugo!
Something like a silhouette of a human can be seen...
A real psychic photograph...
Eh... Huh!?
I'm back from the bath!
Yuyuyu - Yuu-chan!
H-Hey!
L-Look at this!
Eh, What is it? What happened? Uwawawa...
Erase... We must erase it, erase!
We'll be cursed!
S-stop! Don't delete it!
Wait! Not just erasure, don't we have to burn it as well?!
Don't burn it!
I've pretty much become able to talk with her, and how I look at her has changed a bit,
but I still happen to have a bit scary impression of Mina-rin, you know...
Even though she really is kind...
Ah, she's come back!
Minami-chan, welcome back.
I'm back.
Those two, they really go well together...
Was it that you were you on day duty today?
Yeah.
Was the teacher still in teachers' room?
Ah... This is...
Yutaka, your tie is crooked.
O-onee-sama...
No good! I'm looking at my friends again with such eyes...
Maybe it's all accumulating..?
Huh?
Please visit us at
http://jeeb.fiveforty.jp/
#jeeb@irc.rizon.net
Lucky Star!
3, 2, 1, start!
And so, did you find them?
Eh!? They are not anywhere?
Couldn't even find the manager?
So he ran away...
Well, in any case, they'll be fired, you know...
Err...
In the first place, you know, I did think that this program itself was somehow risky...
It's rolling...
But, well... You know, I refused at first...
Err...
Well, however you put it... It's called the power of administration or adult circumstances, right?
Err... It's rolling!
Huh? What is rolling... You? Me? Or is it the Earth?
No. Not like that...
Then, what?
As I've said, the camera is rolling!
Idiot! Stop it!
Isono! Isono!
Translation : Senoby
What? Nakajima!
Kieeeeeeee!
Let me sing this song.
Encode : Heedly
Medley version this time.
1, 2, 3, 4.
Mi-mi-miracle,
FoFoFo-Forgotten thing...
Timing & TLC: JEEB
On one sunny day...
Suppon! Suppon! Suppon!
Take and go! The...
I am...
Typesetting : Ilaggoodly
Santa Mo...
Mi-mi-miracle, Minorun-run!
FoFoFo...
Editing : Ilaggoodly!!!
On one sunny...
Suppon! Suppon! Suppon!
QC : DarkJug, Kylaran
Su...
Take and go! The...
Shikaider!
Santa Moni...
FoFoFo-Forgotten thing...
This forgotten thing of mine,
then on that day...
FoFo... O-o-on one sunny day...
Take and go! The last one...
I am Shikaider!
Santa Moni...
I am Shikai...
I am Shikaider!
Wa! Wa! Wawawawa! Minorun-run!
He wouldn't change even if I blew the whistle!
You're finishing the Shikaider, aren't you?
Yeah!
Why? Even though you're told to change it!
This video was brought to you by JEEB
And so, the next Lucky Star is?
I'm Soujirou.
I'm Kanata.
Well then, Sou-kun. I'll have to go around now...
You end up going?
Eh? Yes.
Take me with you.
Although I still can't do astral projection,
but I'll probably learn it!
Sou-kun, so you're talking about anime and manga again, aren't you...
Well, see you later.
Ah!! Kanata!
"
Next time - "A Subtle Line"
Sou-kun! I can't fly well because of turbulent airflow!
Now, now...