Yoshimizu
Kagami
Theatre
Ah, the B class of third year?
Kuroi-sensei!
Yeah, yeah...
曖昧3センチ
Aimai 3 senchi
Unclear 3 centimeters...
そりゃぷにってことかい？ちょっ!
Sorya punitte koto kai? cho!
Is that a puni? Waitasec!
らっぴんぐが制服…
Rappingu ga seifuku…
The uniform's the wrapping…
だぁぁ不利ってことない　ぷ。
Daa furitte koto nai　Pu.
Hey, there's no disadvantage in that, yeah.
がんばっちゃ♥やっちゃっちゃ
Ganbaccha♥yacchaccha
Try your best♥do your thing-cha,
そんときゃーっち&Releaseぎョッ
son tokyaacchi & ririisu gyo
at that time, well, catch & release, gyo!
汗っ、々っ
A-se, a-se!
In the sweaty, sweaty...
の谷間にDarlin'darlin'F R E E Z E!!
No taniai ni daarin daarin furiiーzu!
cleavage darlin' darlin' FREEZE!!
Fan        subs
E
J
B
E
なんかダるー、なんかデるー
NankaDAruuー, nankaDEruー
Somewhat lazy..., something's coming out...
あいしテるー
AishiTEruuー
I love you...
あれ一個が違ってるんるー
Are ikko ga chigatterunruー
One of those is different, ruー.
なやみン坊ー 高鉄棒 おいしん簿ー
NayamiNbouー Koutetsubou oishinboー
A worrywart, high horizontal bar - an ever-lengthening list...
いーかげんにシナサイ
Iikagen ni SHINASAI
Now get reasonable!
飛んでったアイツの火照るカラダって
Tondetta AITSU no hoteru KARADAtte
The burning body of who flied away right now is...
所謂ふつーのおにゃのコ
Iwayuru futsuu no onya no KO
what is called a "usual girl".
驚いた、
Odoroita,
I'm surprised,
あたしだけ? 豚骨ハリガネおかわりダー!!!!
atashi dake? tonkotsu harigane okawari daaー!!!!
Only me? I get an extra portion of tonkotsu with super hard noodlesー!!!!
BON-BONおーえん団
BON-BON oーendan
Bon-bon cheering team.
Let's get! Cherry pie
Let's get! Cherry pie.
RAN-RAN　かんげー会
Ranraan　kangeーikai
RAN-RAN, welcoming party.
Look up! せんせーしょん
Look up! Senseーshon
Look up! Sensation.
はい！　存在感・・小惑星
Haai　Sonzaikan　tenten　shouwakusei
Yes, feeling of being here・・meteor!
ぶつかって溶けました　呆然　大いに歌ってシレンジャー
Butsukatte tokemashita　bouzen　ooi ni utatte shirenjaー
Got melted by the collision, dumbfounded and singing a lot, "Shiranger!"
もっていけ!
Motte ike!
Take and go!
最後に笑っちゃうのはあたしのはず
Saigo ni waracchau no wa atashi no hazu
The last one laughing should be me,
セーラーふくだからです
Seeraa fuku dakara desu
because it's a sailor fuku.
←結論
←Ketsuron
←Conclusion.
月曜日なのに！
Getsuyoubi nanoni!
Even if it's monday!
機嫌悪いのどうするよ？
Kigen warui no dou suru yo？
What will you do with that bad mood?
夏服がいいのです←キャ？ワ！イイｖ
Natsufuku ga ii no desu←KYA?WA!IIv
I want my summer uniform←It?Is!Cute!
接近3ピクト するまでってちゅーちょだ　やん☆
Sekkin san pikuto, suru madette chuーcho da　yan☆
Getting closer's in three paces, I'll hesitate until you do 'it' Oh☆
頑張って　張り切って
Ganbatte,　harikitte
Try your best, be on high,
My Darlin'darlin' P L E A S E!!
Mai daarin daarin puriizu
my darlin' darlin' please!
You've been doing a variety of things from just now, but can you distinguish?
Aren't they all like the same?
Eh, isn't this common knowledge?
If you don't do this, no matter how much money you have, it won't be enough.
This "Common knowledge" you speak of has quite a narrow strike zone, doesn't it...
At the very least there's nothing...
like that in the common sense of a usual person...
How To
Spend
A Summer
It's not just figurines,
there are people who go after the cards and all when they buy stuff.
How on earth can you tell which one has the card?
Don't they weigh the same?
There were legends and rumors...
about card collecting from long ago, you know...
Things like : "there are places where the good cards are put"...
or "they're marked" or "the pattern's rigged"
In other words, if it's a particularily rare card,
I can just about get the one I was aiming for.
If the package has just been opened, there's a pattern, you know...
With pride
Normally thinking, this would be unbelievable,
but I just can't bring myself to praise her...
If it's so easy to tell where they are, don't the valuable ones disappear quickly?
Yeah, you're right...
In places where there are a lot of experts,
something like rare cards or secret figurines run out quickly, don't they?
When you got to the store, and it looks like it has been eaten by a worm,
the feeling of despair starts to appear...
But when you think "perhaps...", you end up having a slight hope and...
it ends problematically.
A troubling habit indeed, I see...
I've heard that among such collectors there are...
people who buy a lot at the same time, is that so?
Ah, yes there are... Yeah, yeah...
By buying them at the same time, you can quickly complete your collection,
and the pattern of arrangement gets easier to read, too.
Is that so...
Well I wonder if it's about adults expressing...
their financial power by buying lots of stuff?
My reason for part-timing.
Ah, buying lots, huh...
They do say that it's adult shopping, but what they're doing is childlike, isn't it?
Should I say that the desire of monopolizing everything is strong,
or should I say that they begin to want to have it all to themselves.
Uhh... You might be right about buying a lot...
Am I the only one who thinks that it'd be...
worthwhile for you to do something else so fervently?
Lately Akihabara, of all places,
is picked up by the media every so often, isn't it?
Yeah... but the content is extremely painful, you know...
Features are alright,
but they just can't be seen as really favourable content...
Well, of course it could be exaggerated...
but isn't that because the source is like that, too?
But compared to that, in dramas and songs and all,
there are times when otaku culture was the forerunner.
Even news and TV gossip shows...
constantly use songs from anime and games, too...
No... Don't they use them so that most people wouldn't understand it?
Speaking of otakus, you know..
I do often see on forums that otaku guys want to have an...
otaku girlfriend with whom they can talk and discuss mutual interests,
but you don't hear at all that otaku girls...
would like to go out with an otaku guy, do you?
I wonder why? I wonder if they fall harder for 2-D once they get into it...
Aren't they just concerned about their future based on the image of an otaku guy?
Although I think that most of them have a proper job...
Or should I say - don't ask me about that!
Ah!
After it got hot they suddenly started to appear, didn't they?
I hate them because they're noisy and quickly fly away.
They're filthy, too...
They do say that Miyamoto Musashi could catch a fly with chopsticks, though...
Oh! Seriously!?
It's impressive that he would touch...
such a thing with something that you eat food with...
Disgusting!
That aspect, huh?! Although, I can understand it...
Ah!
Abeshi!
Impressive, isn't it!
I just can't squash mosquitos you know...
Ah, why?
Somehow, it feels gross when it...
gets squashed and its blood oozes onto your hand...
Indeed...
That's my blood, you know.
But, you know, what would you do, should a mosquito land on your arm?
I'll do something like "Go away!, Go away!"
or I'll try blow hard at it.
Did you know...
If you flex your arm while a mosquito is biting it,
it becomes unable to take its proboscis out.
Can't be!
Just look...
Aahhh...
You're already dead...
You're already being eaten!
If you flex even more, the mosquito will burst!
Ah! Stop it, please!
Aah... It's itchy, itchy, itchy, itchy, itchy, itchy...
Wouldn't it have been better to just hit it?
Miyuki-san, will you go abroad or somewhere again this summer vacation?
No, I think going this year too is a bit...
But I think I will go back to my hometown.
The girl from my neighborhood that entered Ryouou...
often goes with me to the countryside summer festival, as well.
As she's like a younger sister to me...
Iwasaki-san, so you're going to the summer festival!
It looks like a yutaka or something would really look good on you!
Such...
gloomy
depressed
I do understand that she's flattering me...
Somehow I can't honestly be pleased by it...
It seems like she's telling me I have no...
Izumi
Dog
Mm... I'll come right away...
Uiiss...
Good morning...
Did you wake up now!? Slovenly, aren't you?
Well...
But lately there's been one thing that has really been on my mind...
What's that?
Like, "I wonder if the alarm clock rang..."
or "Someone else didn't turn it off, right?"...
Ah, that happens, doesn't it!
And when you realize it, the switch is off, right!?
Though, when daytime comes around...
you just can't sleep because its so hot, right?
It's already sufficiently daytime, you know!
Kona-chan, it's morning already...
Wake up!
Izumi-kun, let's eat lunch together.
I just thought if I could go back together with Konata-kun...
Hey, Konata...
Hmm..?
Why do main characters of these kind of games...
never fail to become so popular?
I wonder...
Isn't it because if they didn't get popular to some degree, there would be no game?
Ohh... It's no good if you don't do the homework properly!
I-it's not like I'm worrying about you, you know...
I understand... If, Konata, you say so, I'll do so...
Hey, Konata?
Hm?
Why don't the heroines of such games...
have boyfriends even if they're so cute and have good personalities?
Can't they just take their pick?
I wonder...
Isn't it because there would be no game if they'd have?
Ossu! Konata!
I came to play!
And to check out Yutaka's situation!
Ah, neesan - good evening.
Konata? Your father's calling you...
Alright...
Yutaka began doing her homework, so lend me manga!
But...
Konata, are you alright without studying?
Haven't you just been playing from some time ago?
No! You're mistaken!!!
When I get into resting, neesan, you have bad timing...
Grinny
Grin
Hmm...
But doesn't that just mean that you take a lot of breaks?
And like that, there's the appearance I keep in-house...
and I do think about turning towards the desk,
but even so, I tend to take breaks...
Really...
It turns out like that because you usually don't do it seriously.
But well... It's not like I can't understand the feeling...
Does it remind you of something?
Well... When I happen to read a bit of a book I'd like to read as a break,
even if I start studying again, I'll soon want to take a break...
You just can't stop such things halfway, can't you?
With manga, as well, you think you'll stop with another volume,
you have times when you end up...
reading all of them, sometimes in the dozens...
When you rent a DVD of the love drama that you missed,
you just end up watching the next one, too...
But if you watch it, it might continue to a good-for-nothing end...
I see... mister director...
Oneechan, is it alright to change the channel?
And so, it is doll play. right?
It's alright, as I was just somewhat looking at it.
I wonder where you peeped?
Do you have something you'd want to watch?
Eh? Around the room?
Should I say that there were many figurines...
Yeah, they'll be doing a country-wide sweets special from now on.
Ah! As you, Yuu-chan, like sweet things, too!
Kagami's place would seem to watch that, too!
It's the HareHare dance of mandarin sweets!
Ah! It looks delicious!
Things like this, you know...
Even if there's some that you like,
usually the store just happens to be far away and you give up?
When you live in Saitama, even if you're told that it's in Nagoya or something...
It's always like that, it' just depressing, isn't it...
Regrettably...
time
Summer-
course
Doyo
nnn
Ahh...
Yuki-chan, good morning!
Or should I say, what happened?
Yesterday I went to the dentist's,
So you were still going there...
but I ended up running away in the middle of it...
Ah!
Please tell me if it hurts...
No!...mmhh...
Ah, as it will be done soon...
Hay!...
...and like that...
Yeah, that's right... He won't stop, right?
It already hurts by hearing it...
To add to the fact that even if we have writing courses,
the fact that we even get homework is something you can't accept, right?
In the so-longed summer vacation...
You... You wouldn't do it by yourself anyways, right?
Effectively, different from elementary school and junior high,
as there is nothing like free study periods or remark texts...
Isn't this still on the easy side?
As it's enough to just do them...
There were handicraft and posters, too, right?
Things like that, you know...
Like... If you get help from your parents or something...
Don't some heated-up parents do it to the end?
I've gotten a prize from such a thing!
From a poster or something...
Ah... Yes, now that you mention it, there was something like that...
"It's thanks to daddy!"
After I said "I saw you in a new light!", daddy seem to get happy!
Isn't it a place for a parent to get angry?
This is a free softsub.Not for sale, rent, auction or hardsub.
Not for sale, rent, auction or hardsub.This is a free softsub.
or hardsub.This is a free softsub. Not for sale, rent, auction
Lucky Star!
Ah!
Buy at least five at one time!
For the Thirst of the world
king-sized Har
On time-limited sales!
Brigade
Leader's
must have
Every time I see this commercial, I think I'm envious...
In childhood as well, when I read the...
children's story where there was a house of sweets,
I thought that I'd like to eat as many sweets as I could!
I know...
Even if it's something you love, when you actually get a lot of it...
the interest just happens to drop off somehow, doesn't it...
Is that so...
Yeah!
It's been smelly for the whole year!
And so, I just happened to think...
the homework for the summer vacation, you know...
It must be so hard because I think I want to...
do it all at once at the end of the vacation.
Sudden, isn't it...
Or should I say that it's just natural, though...
I just thought I don't need to get upset if I'd grind...
it through little by little from the beginning...
At this age you've finally understood!?
In any case, as you're a third-year- student already -
- do it without cutting the pace!
And so, as I will be coming tomorrow, please treat me well.
I will bring a gift, too!
So doing it little by little was like that!?
Huh, are you thinking about coming here during the whole summer!?
About every week...
You're annoying!
Ouess...
Hot, isn't it?
Ossu! Completely, isn't it?
There's an air conditioner in the room.
Aah, Pleasant, pleasant!
You're pouring out your heart's misery...
It feels like every year the summer goes by...
like this without any enthusiasm coming out...
By the time I've noticed, the summer vacation has already ended...
Don't use such slacker phrases...
This year set a quota or something, do the homework and all properly.
Well... I do think about trying my best...
every year before the vacation, you know...
Oh yeah?
Even in manga or something there's a lot of stories...
with "I haven't done the homework!" at this time, aren't there?
Yeah, that's right...
When you see stuff like that, don't you begin to think...
that it could be alright without doing them as a theory?
When you think everyone's so...
Like there are excuses!
Do them! And if that's what you think of it, don't come to copy!
I feel thirsty...
I guess I should bring barley tea or something?
Ah! Oneechan!
Sorry! While you're doing that, could you bring...
me my math workbooks from my room, please.
Got it, got it...
Uwa! It's hot!
I try to ask someone to do something when someone's going out of the room,
as I don't want to go out of the well-air conditioned room,
but there are times when people just don't go out, aren't there?
tn: "kotatsu" - A low wooden table covered by a futon, with a heater underneath.
During winter, as you don't want to go out of the kotatsu,
you do ask when someone's getting out, don't you?
Hey!
Ossu! Hot isn't it?
Ossu!
Welcome.
This is the ice cream for a present.
Select any of them that you like and just take freely!
Since I'm not going to be that helpful in studies...
Huh!?
You know, the eyes of Marimokkori were...
Eeh...
I wonder why at times like this somehow you...
end up thinking that you'd prefer the one someone else got..?
I'm reading the manga about Toudai entrance exams, you know,
Ah, that one...
but when you read it, don't you begin...
to think "Even I could go to Toudai!", or something like that?
If I tried like that!
Again greatly simple-minded, aren't you?
Even if you could get into Toudai that way...
Friends who will be with you even to dump the usual lessons,
teachers who give you such lessons...
and the instructors who take the command -
- isn't it no good if you don't assemble all of them and everything?
Is that so... So it doesn't go so smoothly, huh...
There's a fair amount of such...
who are influenced by manga or dramas or something,
and think they can easily change themselves...
Well, I do think about trying my best and studying,
but I simply get sleepy, you know...
I wonder if there's no good way to keep yourself awake?
But it seems like it's better to take a nap than to try to be awake by force...
Ah, so it's like that?
I've heard that, so I'm always doing it though, you know...
But naps always turn into real sleep...
Don't they?
Her desperateness is weak, huh...
Good day!
Yutaka-chan, good day!
Err... Is it alright for a moment?
What's the matter, Yuu-chan?
Ask anything from these sisters!
It seems like my friend from junior high got a loved one,
so I was asked "What should I get as a birthday present?"...
But as I really don't know...
Aeh!?
What should I do!? It feels really awkward...
For now - you know, Yuu-chan...
There are places on the internet where you can ask such advice,
so try to see through such places.
As there might be a similar thread, I'll lend you the PC!
I-I'll do so...
There are things like Densha **toko, but you can even ask advice on such things?
As it's already gotten pretty usual...
Ah! So they already have anything?
Yeah, that's right...
Somehow there even seem to be the answers for maths drill there...
I do think that the elementary and junior high...
school students nowadays have it easy...
It seems like that with the development of technology and communities and all,
the ways of thinking and nature of users are becoming "no good"...
When I look at her...
Huh?
Huh? Weird, isn't it...
Even though it should just be about copying homework,
as a slight deviation from the usual,
since there's audience, something like pride is coming out!
Come to think of it, when's the festival at your place?
What're you talking about? It's already over.
Wh!?
It was so last year, wasn't it?
I wonder why you couldn't tell me!
As there are the exam studies, as well....
If I had told you, you would've wanted to go there for sure...
We haven't taken part in it, too.
Particularly, isn't it alright for you to go...
to your own place's festival, instead of ours?
Did it end already?
My neighborhood's...
Now that you mention it, I wonder when it's on...
Oh yes there are...
Even if they go show up around other festivals,
people who are careless about their local stuff.
Are you the type that doesn't want to meet the local friends?
Ah...
Ah... Even as an exam student, you can't keep it up by just studying...
That reminds me, tomorrow...
there will be a fireworks display close to our place...
That's it!
Let's all hang out together at least once!
Yeah... You're right...
It might be good for a change.
Come to think of it, tomorrow there's a...
fireworks display close to your house, Minami-chan, right?
Yeah...
Hee, I'd want to see Japanese fireworks...
Well, let's all go to watch, Minami!
Minami-chan, are you free tomorrow?
It's alright...
Well, then it's a done deal, isn't it - Minami?
Let's go, Iwasaki-san!
Uh...
Err... Iwasaki-san!?
It's a pretty famous fireworks display, isn't it?
Mi... Iwasaki-san...
Awww... A way of calling someone...
that has already fixated is quite hard to change...
Ah, but the place's far away, and well-known, so people will come, too?
Yuu-chan, are you alright?
You had a cold until the other day, right?
Ah! Tomorrow it seems like it'd get hot, so should we go some other time?
No, you don't have to worry about me...
As it's something that always happens, too...
Since I, the helper of the nurse's office, am with you... it's alright...
Yutaka...
Ah, I see...
Yeah, you're right!
Thank you, Minami-chan!
And so we decided to go to the fireworks display,
but it just isn't any fun as we don't play because...
"We're exam students!" or "We have to study for the exams!", right?
As Kagami and them are all serious.
Well, although I can understand that...
Konata, you should do like you'd want to do.
I, as well, used to push Kanata round forcibly...
and made a lot of memories, you know...
I did get yelled at, but you know - the youth won't wait!
Well, then I wonder if I should...
get a boyfriend and make some memories of my own...?
That you absolutely mustn't do!
I won't acknowledge a boyfriend!
No, daddy - what you're saying now is absurd...
Ooh, to hear that from Konata...
Ah, Yuu-chan, won't you come too? To see the fireworks?
This severely hurts!
To tell you the truth, I'm going as well.
Don't follow my steps!
I'll meet up at Minami-chan's house.
To lock doors, to have to go to the neighbor for help!
Ah, was that so?
We'll be off!
Have a nice day.
The train is here!
You're late, you know.
Oh, sorry for keeping you waiting!
Ah, so even Yutaka-chan came!
Ah, err...
Hey!
Here! Here!
Hello there!
Oh, ello! {maybe use "ello"
Ah, Patricia-san!
Konata-san and all, are you going to the fireworks display as well?
Yukata looks good on you, doesn't it?
What's this!?
Ahh...
Iwasaki
Ehh...
Huh..?
Eeh...
So when Miyuki-san talked about a neighbor,
it was about Minami-chan, wasn't it?
What a coincidence, isn't it...
Really a surprise!
Yeah...
Welcome.
Here, please.
Ah...
Thank you very much!
Oh, isn't there one missing?
There's enough, isn't there...
Mother, perhaps you are counting yourself in as well...
One,
two,
three,
four,
five,
six,
seven,
eight,
Nine.
Ah, oh my... really!
I see...
Sorry for the disturbance!
Ah, so this is Minami-chan's house...
Uwa! What a big dog, scary...
It's completely alright!
It doesn't growl at all, and it's friendly!
Ah, is that so... When big ones are like that...
they, to the contrary, feel cute, don't they?
Huh!? It's growling for some reason...
I wonder if she's the type that gets howled at...
Ahh...
You know, when you were a child, you wondered...
whether or not fireworks look round even from the side, right?
Eh, huh, don't they look flat?
Oi-oi...
Fireworks displays are broadcasted live on the TV from time to time, though,
as I expected, it's better to have the atmosphere when you watch them live.
Yeah, you're right...
But, you know, I've been thinking for a while...
Doesn't it just break the mood when they...
announce the name of the store in the shopping district,
like "It was brought to you by "XXXX", every time a big firework is rising up?
Y-yes, that's right...
Ah, Yuu-chan, you look a little pale...
Ah... It's alright...
Ah...
It's alright, so everyone - go and watch it.
But...
As I'm... staying here...
Minami-chan...
Ahh...
Ahh!
Ahh..!
It was lovely, wasn't it?
Ah, well...
It was just what you would call "summer", right?
But, you know...
It doesn't work out like manga... just having the beautiful memories, right?
I really got eaten by mosquitoes...
It's really itchy!
They do say that it gets even more itchy if you scratch...
And when you take the yukata off,
the mark of the string that was on the stomach gets itchy, as well...
Ah, yeah - you're right!
Beautiful...
It really was beautiful, wasn't it...
But I'm sorry, causing you trouble...
Ah, there they were!
O-hoy!
Were you two alright getting eaten by bugs?
Ah, yeah...
We haven't been eaten.
Ah, yes there are... People who easily get bitten by mosquitoes,
and those who really don't get bitten...
How good...
No... didn't the mosquitoes just read the mood, too?
Please visit us at
http://jeeb.fiveforty.jp/
#jeeb@irc.rizon.net
Lucky Star!
Lucky Channel!
Good lucky!
I'm your navigator, Kogami Akira!
And I'm the assistant - Ono Daisuke.
How quickly time flows! Lucky Channel is already on it's 20th time!
So you're not a crow today, it seems...
tn: Ono Daisuki played the crow in AIR
I see you are not a dog today, it seems.
tn: Akira's voice actor voiced Poteto in AIR
Peko...
Well, let's see just to be sure, the broadcast...
Studio
woodlands
Yes, I wonder around where he is walking right now, Shiroishi-kun...
Waah! Mt. Fuji is beautiful!
Oh well...
Oh well, bye-nii!
Bye-nii...
Shiraishi-kun?
peko-pe...
Shiraishi-kun!?
Ma'am, this is what you wanted, right?
Ma'am!
this is what you wanted, right?
Hello! I am Shiraishi Minoru!
Translation: JEEB
Encoding: Heedly
Well, let's have you hear it then!
"The Rumba of The Son-In-Law!"
1-2-3-4
TLC: Senoby
Typeset : Ilaggoodly
Editing: Ilaggoodly
Izumi Soujirou
幸せの声響く
Shiawase no koe hibiku
The voice of happiness sounds...
6月の教会
Rokugatsu no kyoukai
it's the church in June...
QC: Izumi Soujirou
幸せの絶頂は
Shiawase no zecchou wa
The peak of happiness is...
まさにこの時
Masa ni kono toki
exactly this very moment.
あぁ～、こんなことになるのなら
Aa~, konna koto ni naru no nara
Ah, should it turn out like this,
一戸建てなんて買わなきゃよかった
Ikkodate nante kawanakya yokatta
it would've been better if I hadn't bought that house...
花嫁に逃げられるなんて
Hanayome ni nigerareru nante
To have your bride run away...
漫画みたいなシチュエイション
Manga mitai na shichueishon
is such a manga-like situation...
あわててお婿ルンバ！
Awatete omuko runba!
Panicking all the way - Rumba of the son-in-law!
誰か助けて「Oh my god!」
Dare ka tasukete "Oh my god!"
Someone save me - "Oh my god!"
これからどうするの
Kore kara dou suru no
What should I do from now!?
女子もきてるのに
Joshi mo kiteru no ni
Even though the girls are coming...
一、二、三。二、二、三。お婿ルンバ
Ichi, ni, san. ni, ni, san. omuko runba
One, two, three. Two, two, three. The Rumba of the son-in-law!
Go!
Chara!
Charara!
Cha!
This video was brought to you by JEEB
And so, the next Lucky Star is?
It's me, Misao.
It's me, Ayano.
Hey, Ayano - Hiiragi's really cold, isn't she?
She soon goes to where that chibi girl is, too.
Well-well...
Doesn't our love reach Hiiragi?
Next time - "Pandora's Box".
Ayano's cold as well...