Now, let'ssu begin yoo!
It's gonna come now...
Fungaa!
Now start out already!
I My Something
"I my something"
そりゃぷにってことかい、ちょっ
Sorya punitte koto kai, cho
That's about a puni, is it, cho?
ら、ぐーんぐーんが制服
Ra, guun-guun ga seifuku
Ra, guun guun goes the seifuku,
なぁふりってことない？　うん
Naa furitte koto nai？　Un
Hey, there's no irrationality in this? Yeah.
頑張っちゃ、やっちゃっちゃ、
Ganbaccha, yacchaccha,
Try your best, do the thing-cha,
そんときゃ　じゃリリース料
son tokya　jya ririisu ryou
at that time, well the things for release!
あせっ、あせっ
A-se, a-se!
"A-se, a-se!"
の谷間にダーリンダーリンフリー
No taniai ni daarin daarin furiiー
In the cleavage darling darling free!
なんかたるー、なんかてるー
Nankataruuー, nankateruー
How to cheat, how to win,
あいしてるー
Aishiteruuー
I love you.
あれ一個が違ってる
Are ikko ga chigatteru
One of those is different.
むん　むやみに暴行鉄棒おいしん棒
Mun muyami ni boukou tetsubou oishinbou
Stuffy, violence with recklessness - steel rod is a sweet rod.
いいかげんにしなさい!
Iikagen ni shinasai!
Now get reasonable!
飛んでったあいつの火照る体って
Tondetta aitsu no hoteru karadatte
The burning body of who flied away right now is...
いわゆる普通の女の子
Iwayuru futsuu no onna no ko
what is called a "usual girl".
驚いた、
Odoroita,
I'm surprised,
あたしだけ豚骨針金おかわりダー!!!!
atashi dake tonkotsu harigane okawari daaー!!!!
Only I get an extra portion of tonkotsu with a needle insideー!!!!
ボンボン応援団
Bon-bon ouendan
Bon-bon cheering team.
Let's get cherry pie
Let's get cherry pie.
らんらーん　関係感
Ranraan　kankeikan
Blazing, relationship feeling,
you have センセーション
you have senseeshon
you have sensation.
ハーイ　存在感　点々　小惑星
Haai　Sonzaikan　tenten　shouwakusei
Yes, feeling of being here, here and there meteors.
ぶつかって溶けました　呆然　大いに歌ってシリンダー
Butsukatte tokemashita　bouzen　ooi ni utatte shirindaa
Got melt from the collision, dumbfounded singing a lot, "Cilinder!"
もっていけ、
Motte ike,
Take and go,
最後に笑っちゃうのはあたしのはず
Saigo ni waracchau no wa atashi no hazu
The last one laughing should be me,
セーラー服だからです
Seeraa fuku dakara desu
because it's a seeraa fuku.
結論
Ketsuron
Conclusion.
月曜日なのに
Getsuyoubi nanoni
Even if it's monday,
機嫌悪いのどうするよ
Kigen warui no dou suru yo
What will you do with that bad mood?
夏服がいいのです、かわいい
Natsufuku ga ii no desu, kawaii
The summer uniform is better, cute.
接近賛否それまでって躊躇だ　やーん
Sekkin sanbi, sore madette choucho da　yaーn
Yes and no for getting closer, until that it's undecided, yaan.
頑張って　張り切って
Ganbatte,　harikitte
Try your best, be on high,
ま、ダーリンダーリンプリーズ
Ma, daarin daarin puriizu
well darling darling please!
Eeh... You will enter a long holiday from tomorrow, but do not forget your position as students...
Be sure to behave reasonably.
Yes!
At such season there are many students that get into a frivolous feeling, and cast a nuisanse over the local community.
I am deeply worried about it.
Be sure not to get into any trouble.
In other words, if you make any trouble, my holidays are over, too...
So I'm counting on you, please!
This... is no good...
Famous Shooter
Finally the holidays started!
When I think about the fact that I won't have to look at your face every day, I can even feel cozy.
Onee-chan...
Hmm... Even though these are holidays I'll still be meeting with our teacher almost every day...
Eh? Why is that? Do you have to report on something?
I'm in the same party with her in a netoge...
And what's that?
Netoge?
The teacher's a WIZ and I'm a tank, so when I pull as a pair we get quite a bit of experience...
Well, I'm the only one busy there, teacher can just click background spells.
The other day when I was aggroed by a mass of mobs, she was sleeping somewhere...
It took me a day to recover from the death penalty...
Eehh... Wouldn't you at the very least speak in Japanese...?
Good morning...
Today it's really hot from the morning...
Morning, your morning hair's pretty amazing.
Hey, Onee-chan, wouldn't you put the cooler on?
Oh, it's that again. Try not to depend on it so fast and bear it with a fan or something.
There you go.
Uwaaah... It gets pretty cool with just the fan, doesn't it...
I did say you?
It's hot...
You get tired when you flap that around...
and when you stop, doesn't it just feel additionally hot?
Yeah, I knew that. But let's try a bit.
We are all matching with yukata, I see.
Un-un!
Well, it's just that our obi is a ready-one, though.
The one that can be put on fast.
To wear something properly is hard even with yukata...
Miyuki's is a really tied one, should I just said as expected...
No, I had this one put on by a person in a shop...
Tying an obi was indeed hard...
Ah, it was like that.
Even Konata is properly dressed, a bit unexpected...
Yeah.
Did you, too, get it put on in a shop?
Ah, no, I had my father tie it properly...
Is that so...
Come now, let's go!
"I wonder why her father can tie such a thing..."
Hey! Konata-chan!
Ah...
Someone from the police?
Is she acquaintance of yours?
She's my relative, Yui-neesan.
Hello there!
Ah, Hello...
I'm pleased to meet you...
Listen to these big girls here and try to go home early without making a racket out of it.
"Big girls"
No, no, no... We're all classmates...
Don't take Konata as the standard...
We're all classmates!
Was that so?!
Oh, sorry, sorry. Big sister's surprised!
There was such a difference in your figure, so...
Hmm...
Ah, no problem at all...
Ahh, but even so there's a lot of girls with good growth nowadays...
"No, just like I said, don't take Konata as the standard... because we are the general majority..."
Ah, a shooting booth!
Yui-neesan, aren't you good at shooting and stuff?
Huh?
Hah-hah-ha...! What is there to hide...
I've got enough skill that at the station I'm known as the 'Sharpshooter Yui'.
A straight 10 with five bullets in three seconds...
I can put a peace mark into the face of a man-target!
Uhaa....
Well, then try away. Here...
Huh? Huuuuh?
Is sharpshooting with a rifle? I'm surprised.
Huh?
The one I'm using is a pistol, too...
Waku-waku, waku-waku...
Huuu-pah!
Ngh...!
Shh..goh...ku!
Gh...
Narumi! What are doing so enthusiasticly while on duty?!
Let meee!
Yeh, now patrolling, patrolling!
To bring up the mood...
Onii-san, if I hit any of those lined up over there, do I get it?
Which ever is OK.
Really which ever?
Yes, which ever.
Hmmmm...
Whum!
Oh, little lady, I'm not a prize, so...
When you mention summer festivals a shaved ice with syrup is a must...
It's hot, too. Let's eat?
By the way, I had thought like this from before...
I do understand strawberry, lemon and melon tastes, but...
what fruit, what flavour is 'Blue Hawaii'?
The flavour of Blue Hawaii, I think...
"That is so, it turns out like that..."
And so, Miyuki-san, do you know what 'Blue Hawaii' is?
Eh, 'Blue Hawaii'?
Ah, eetto... eetto... wa...
Could it be a song? 'Blue...', no, that's not it... 'Blue...', uwah...
I do not really understand... I'm sorry about not being able to be of any help.
I will look about it next time...
Yeah, thanks.
I think that there are such juices and sweets,so...
No, that's not something Miyuki should look at, but the person who wants to know himself.
Well, about that 'Blue Hawaii'...
Hn?
The origin of the name comes from the fact that it has the same colour as a cocktail with the same name.
And the cocktail was named so after the feelings gotten from the movie 'Blue Hawaii'.
Ah, so, that was it. I will use it for future reference.
Ehhe-he...
"When I learn something from Tsukasa I really feel like I lost in something..."
Aww...!
When I notice there's not much money left...
The costs at the stalls are not cheap, so you should always think when you use money, really...
But at a festival you really get into the feeling and use some cash...
Oh, well...
It's the same feeling as when that doujinshi don't feel expensive at the Komike hall...
after noticing later there's a crazy price tag on the goods...
As I said, we can't understand the talk from that side...
You get exhausted while you wait in line from the morning and the East Hall and the West Hall are really far from each other...
I don't know what you're talking about.
Huh?
I just love cotton candy because it's soft and sweet!
Ah...
You're no longer a child, so eat calmly already...
Ehhehehe...
Something like that is not really interesting if you do it girl-to-girl...
Don't even drag it there...
Ohhh, why there is no romance for us here...
Yukata in a festival in summer!
If this would be a gyaruge, at least one scene flag could be gotten.
'Flag'?
And some event scenes and stuff! It's outside, there's yukata involved!
Yes, yes. Just stop it there!
Kagami-san doesn't really play around, now do you?
Hmm... Well it's the rare occasion, so should I do something like goldfish dipping?
Huh!
Uwah!
Ah...
Ugh!
Why do they run away even if I'm not reaching at them?!
Aren't they just running away because they feel in their instincts that you're a violent person?
A-huh?!
Oh, did the proof get out already?
Yes, yes.
Uhhhh...
Oh, look! There's one over there!
Ah, there really is!
Let's go...
It's a GET!
I did it! I could get one!
It's great, great! ufufufu!
Let's pet you right...
Let's really pet this one...
Gyopi-chan...
Ah!
Yo! Everyone's together, it seems!
I was told there was a festival around here...
It's not so often, so I came around.
And I like festivals, too.
Did you come together with a boyfriend or someone else?
Hah-hah-haa, there's no way something like that...!
"After all there's not a single piece of romance around us..."
"Just like expected..."
Met with you again!
It seems you're enjoying yourself with even bigger numbers!
Hello there!
Hm?
Hmm...
This time it's a well-grown girl, too.
'Girl'?
It's our homeroom teacher!
Excuse me, making a hasty judgement that you were a classmate...
No, it's not such a problem.
She's Yui-neesan, a relative of mine. A policewoman.
As you can see.
Ihhaa, it's the Summer Festival today, so I have to work on patrol.
Ihhaa, even though it's so hot...
"Work?! It seems more like she's having the fun of her life!"
Are you too, on duty, sensei? Something like patrolling around?
No, no. I had some free time, so I just came around.
That's so good!
If I would've had a night free, I could've come here alone and play around...
"No, you're just having enough fun I think..."
Hm?! Are you alone, too?
Yes, I am.
Ah, was that so...
Just Single
Ah?
Husband's out at a new position
Ah-hah-hah-hah-hah...
Lucky Star!
"In the summer balsamic vinegar is what I recommend, but if you don't have it you can use rice vinegar or any other thing you can find in your house..."
Balsamic vinegar...
This was a place to laugh...
Ehehe! Balsamic Vinegar!
Isn't summer vacation usually pretty boring and there's nothing to do, right?
You just end up living lazily...
Hihihi... If you say as much, you won't say 'Show me your homework', or something like that, at a later time, right?
Ah?!
Was that so?
Yeah, yeah, it's really cute, isn't it?
Just a little dumpy and rolling around.
That frog-like appearance, right?
Yes, that exactly.
Yeah.
Hee, depleted uranium, now is it? That's great!
Eh-hehehe...
Ah, If I make too long calls my parents get angry at me.
Yeah!
And so...
While I was talking with Kona-chan I asked her about how summer vacation can be boring...
Hm?
She's playing all the games she had been storing one after another, so she's not really free.
After all, depending on the person they more or less spend a full summer vacation.
Should I do something, too?
"No, that's good 'as it is'..."
"That's why I'm always saying that you should do your homework properly!"
"Oh, with her... Every given time..."
I'll get one
0k
ohLOL
I'll get one
0k
ohLOL
I'll get one
0k
ohLOL
debuff plz
0k
ohLOL
debuff plz
Debuff please.
0k
ohLOL
debuff plz
Friend nanakon
logged in
ohLOL
debuff plz
Friend nanakon
logged in
Ah! Sensei came in!
Hello
Yo (^з^)/
It could be the summer vacation, but you've got a good logon rate there
Oh well... *laugh*
We have time, so what about some hunting? I'm in the cave near Chopron
Oh yeah, I'm in in! >w<b It's the time for my wiz to get in!
Well, I'll be waiting near the gate then
Well, I'll be waiting near the gate then.
Oh yeah, I'm in in! >w<b It's the time for my wiz to get in!
Well, I'll be waiting near the gate then
Hey, that's all good, but did you do your homework? (-_-)
Huh?
Well, I'll be waiting near the gate then
Hey, that's all good, but did you do your homework? (-_-)
Huh?
You're not in your room all the time, now are you?
Just don't forget the day when school begins
And then, keep a limit with your sitting up late and with your oversleeping habit, even if we're on holidays
Oh...
Sensei, let's not bring up real-life subjects in the world of netoge every day...
Ahh, it's like getting yelled at by Kagami every day...
Good day!
It's hot today, too.
Ah, welcome!
Come on in!
Hello.
Hm...
Haa!
You took out the electric fan!
Yeah, because it's pretty hot now.
Sit over there and keep yourself cool.
Hmm...
Aaaaaaaahhhhh...
I thought you'd do that, I was sure you'd do that...
Good morning...
Ah, Kona-chan's around!
Ossu!
It's no longer 'Morning'!
What hour do you think it is already!?
Ehhe-he...
Even so it's really hot...
Aaahhhh...
You, too - is it?
No, usually you do it...
No I don't!
But Kagami, too, did it this morning?
Lookie!
Ugh...
I got caught...
The Comp Matsuri seems to have a good reputation.
What's that?
If you send out all the application tickets from these magazine books, you'll get a limited edition QUO card.
Hee...
Even I take a book behind a counter or something in order to take them out...
I remember you saying something like that before about QUO cards...
We the Japanese are really weak for presents or 'limited edition' things...
That's why after all the ground rule is to buy for preservation, for experiencing and for propagation.
Wait a sec! Yours is without any doubt a special case!
Such people can't possibly be around.
And then there are times when I buy something again as I forget to whom I lent it...
Don't you forget...
And then I'd like to ask the regular one...
Ah! Homework!
Again?!
I will explain you the things you don't understand,...
so try to solve it by yourself sometimes.
Hmmm...
Balsamic Vinegar...
Kagami, explain me this...
Hm? Oh, this is...
Hmm...
Kagami...
I just can't understand from here to here...
Uah...
Hmmm...
Uh, that was close...
Kagami...
Here's...
You just don't have any intention to think, now don't you?
But I am thinking...
I don't really know...
And then I can't understand anything after this point...
SO YOU'RE NOT THINKING AT ALL AFTER ALL!
So I couldn't get these explained after all...
Yahoo! I came to play!
Oh, Yui-neesan, you came in a good time...
I'd like you to explain this to me.
Ou, mathematics homework now is it?
Which one? Leave it to me!
Aghhh...
Oh well...
As a policewoman keeping an eye on a good girl...
I must say that you shouldn't only depend on others for your own good!
Uhe?!
Uwaaa... Aargh...
It's so bothersome, full of things I can't understand...
Ha-ha-ha!
Even if you don't understand, you can just write something that seems close to the subject!
Hm...
After all, you just have to give the homework back!
Oh, now I understand - that's very clever of you!
"But that line you said earlier just became harder to swallow...
and this clearly won't do any good to me..."
Oh, I did do that in my time, too...
I'm tired...
Let's play netoge a bit for a change...
Ohhh, 30 minutes of solo hunting is enough, right?
If only for 30 minutes...
Hm...
Solo Hunt now ain't it ain't it...
in a world wh...
we become stronger...
Not... somebody else...
Huh?
Ha... Rare drop!
Gotten ahold of Magical Sword Lævatein
Something Like This
The Lævatein!
I haven't seen anyone holding it...
It's super rare, ain't it?!
Got the Læva sword!!!!
Got the Læva sword!
RLY!?
Got the Læva sword!!!!
lolz congrats lol
RLY!?
Im gonna go there now, showmeshowme!
lolz congrats lol
Lets party. Lets gather all clan members
Lets party. Lets and try it out o(^^)o
Im gonna go there now, showmeshowme!
Lets party. Lets gather all clan members
Lets party. Lets and try it out o(^^)o
All-nighter decided lulz
ROFLCOPTER BBQ!
OK! Come, come!
All-nighter decided lulz
ROFLCOPTER BBQ!
0k. camcam
And where should I go to try it out...
Oh, everyone's on full drive!
Ah, yes, I gave everyone the task to write a high quality speech for the times of misfortune.
After I've gone back to the town once...
It's going to be busy time!
Lucky Star!
LUCKY CHANNEL!
Good lucky!
I'm your navigator Kogami Akira!
As a fast thing Lucky Channel is already in its fift time!
I'm putting in all my spirit and trying my best!
The one who's going to be sleeping forever is...
the one who's gotten more and more time on the main story and getting on full swing...
Oh no, not like that...
Getting better all the time, Shiraishi Minoru-san!
Clap clap clap
Oh, I had no intension on going to full swing...
Ah, the assistant Shiraishi Minoru -dessuu, greetings-suu.
And so, we do get a lot of postcards every time,...
but today we have a letter from USS Gatou-san, residing in Tokyo prefecture.
Occupation: NEET - he's sent 50 pieces all by himself...
Surely he's a pitiful person, right?
But now on to the letter.
Akira-san, Minoru-san, good day.
In the main story Konata-chan seems to be fond of netoge,...
but do you, Akira-sama, play such games?
By the way, I am having a solid life pretending to be a woman on the internet...
Wah! Ai-da-da-da-da-daa!
Netoge... network games, aren't they?
Unfortunately I haven't played them, but...
Yeah, but it'd be better if you wouldn't...
"Completely chopped me off again..."
I... is that so?
Because there are many people who sink and fall into them and leave their lives somewhere...
I was pretty bad at one time, too...
If only I had time I would just up my IN, hunt forever and be busy with PKK and stuff...
While I was young, you know...
While you were young... Or should I say that many words that I cannot understand keep popping up...
It's OK for you not to understand...
Well, I think that the reaction of the audience will be split in half, too...
In... in any case you have played them, right?
Well, do you have any memories from such games?
Ah, yes! There are memories!
When I was a beginner, I didn't really understand it all...
and if I got into trouble many veteran guys helped me out.
They gave me a lot of really pricey armors, rare items and stuff!
Akira got inspired!
Is that so...
It's really fun, so everyone, please try to play, too!
Ah, it's already time!
Bye-nii!
And so, let's meet next time.
Or should I say, you really are popular at such games.
Huh? Akira-sama?
What happened?
Page 38, 12th cut...
Yes...
Don't you doubt me all the time!?
Do you get angry here this time?
I'm telling you that I'm Akira!
Well, now that you say so...
Jyaakiisa come out!
Director! Director!
Aah, no! Producer's better, producer's better!
Hey, Akira-san, please calm down!
I ask you!
Anyways, the name of Shiraishi Minoru...
Should we make it something else...
For example Suu.!
Kagami'n, you're cool!
Oh, you don't have to...
And, Tsukasa, Miyuki - who will go first?
I will!
Again?! When did you enter a song?
Isn't it just a waste as Tsukasa and the others don't really enter anything?
Sorry, we're still choosing, so wait a bit more.
Excuse me...
Ahh, it's OK, OK. Konata's songs can work for killing time.
Ah....
Ah, I know this one!
Now you did something rare. The song selection is major.
Gaagi's the best!
Dakiii!
光る雲を突き抜け Fly Away!
Hikaru kumo wo tsukinuke Fly Away!
Pierce those shining clouds, fly away!
からだじゅうに広がるパノラマー！
Karada jyuu ni hirogaru panoramaー！
The panorama that is spreading throughout my body!
顔を蹴られた地球が怒って・・・
Kao wo kerareta chikyuu ga okotte・・・
The earth, after getting a kick in the face gets angry...
火山を爆発させるー！
kazan wo bakuhatsu saseruー！
makes the volcanoes blow their flow!
溶けた北極の中に・・・
Toketa hokkyoku no naka ni・・・
If there would be dinosaurs...
恐竜がいたら玉乗り仕込みたいねー！
Kyouryuu ga itara tamanori shikomitai neー！
on the melted North Pole, I'd like to teach them how to stand on a ball!
CHA-LA HEAD-CHA-LA
CHA-LA, HEAD CHA-LA!
何が起きても気分はへのへのカッパー！
Nani ga okitemo kibun wa henoheno kappaー！
Whatever should happen I'm always on a good mood!
CHA-LA HEAD-CHA-LA!
And so, the next Lucky Star is?
It's Konata.
When I started 'Monster Hunter 2', the condition for upping my weapon usage stats was Gyanos Five-head, so I went back to the village, got the quest from the Elder...
and when I couldn't go back to the village even after killing Gyanos Five-head or completing the snow mountain level, or even after taking all those Popotans I first understood that I didn't put them into my bag...
And there I understood that the reason for my decreased rewards was me myself, who hadn't read the manual and thought some things would go closer to reality, don't you do so, too?!
Next Time: The Standard for Summer
Look forward to it!