Yoshimizu Kagami
Theatre
Ah, the B class of third year?
Kuroi-sensei!
Yeah, yeah...
曖昧3センチ
Aimai 3 senchi
Unclear 3 centimeters...
そりゃぷにってことかい？ちょっ!
Sorya punitte koto kai? cho!
Is that a puni? Waitasec!
らっぴんぐが制服…
Rappingu ga seifuku…
The uniform's the wrapping…
だぁぁ不利ってことない　ぷ。
Daa furitte koto nai　Pu.
Hey, there's no disadvantage in that, yeah.
がんばっちゃ♥やっちゃっちゃ
Ganbaccha♥yacchaccha
Try your best♥do your thing-cha,
そんときゃーっち&Releaseぎョッ
son tokyaacchi & ririisu gyo
at that time, well, catch & release, gyo!
汗っ、々っ
A-se, a-se!
In the sweaty, sweaty...
の谷間にDarlin'darlin'F R E E Z E!!
No taniai ni daarin daarin furiiーzu!
cleavage darlin' darlin' FREEZE!!
Fan        subs
E
J
B
E
なんかダるー、なんかデるー
NankaDAruuー, nankaDEruー
Somewhat lazy..., something's coming out...
あいしテるー
AishiTEruuー
I love you...
あれ一個が違ってるんるー
Are ikko ga chigatterunruー
One of those is different, ruー.
なやみン坊ー 高鉄棒 おいしん簿ー
NayamiNbouー Koutetsubou oishinboー
A worrywart, high horizontal bar - an ever-lengthening list...
いーかげんにシナサイ
Iikagen ni SHINASAI
Now get reasonable!
飛んでったアイツの火照るカラダって
Tondetta AITSU no hoteru KARADAtte
The burning body of who flied away right now is...
所謂ふつーのおにゃのコ
Iwayuru futsuu no onya no KO
what is called a "usual girl".
驚いた、
Odoroita,
I'm surprised,
あたしだけ? 豚骨ハリガネおかわりダー!!!!
atashi dake? tonkotsu harigane okawari daaー!!!!
Only me? I get an extra portion of tonkotsu with super hard noodlesー!!!!
BON-BONおーえん団
BON-BON oーendan
Bon-bon cheering team.
Let's get! Cherry pie
Let's get! Cherry pie.
RAN-RAN　かんげー会
Ranraan　kangeーikai
RAN-RAN, welcoming party.
Look up! せんせーしょん
Look up! Senseーshon
Look up! Sensation.
はい！　存在感・・小惑星
Haai　Sonzaikan　tenten　shouwakusei
Yes, feeling of being here・・meteor!
ぶつかって溶けました　呆然　大いに歌ってシレンジャー
Butsukatte tokemashita　bouzen　ooi ni utatte shirenjaー
Got melted by the collision, dumbfounded and singing a lot, "Shiranger!"
もっていけ!
Motte ike!
Take and go!
最後に笑っちゃうのはあたしのはず
Saigo ni waracchau no wa atashi no hazu
The last one laughing should be me,
セーラーふくだからです
Seeraa fuku dakara desu
because it's a sailor fuku.
←結論
←Ketsuron
←Conclusion.
月曜日なのに！
Getsuyoubi nanoni!
Even if it's monday!
機嫌悪いのどうするよ？
Kigen warui no dou suru yo？
What will you do with that bad mood?
夏服がいいのです←キャ？ワ！イイｖ
Natsufuku ga ii no desu←KYA?WA!IIv
I want my summer uniform←It?Is!Cute!
接近3ピクト するまでってちゅーちょだ　やん☆
Sekkin san pikuto, suru madette chuーcho da　yan☆
Getting closer's in three paces, I'll hesitate until you do 'it' Oh☆
頑張って　張り切って
Ganbatte,　harikitte
Try your best, be on high,
my darlin' darlin' please!
My Darlin'darlin' P L E A S E!!
Mai daarin daarin puriizu
Hey, Kagami, do you like chocolate wafers?
I do, but...
Is that so... Well, then please help yourself.
Oh, thank you.
Itadakimasu!
There's still more!
There's still lots and lots of them, so please...
Now wait up, why do you have so many of them?
Well, there's a toy that comes with them, you know, but I just didn't get the one I wanted, so I carelessly bought a lot of them...
Yes, there are such people, whose eyes are only fixated on the premiums and disregard the actual sweets.
Many men,
Many minds
Hmm... Fox.
Err... Squirrel.
Dog.
Huh?
What are you saying, all of a sudden!?
Well, I just wondered what it would be like if I likened everyone to some animal...
I like to cause mischief, so I'm a fox!
Tsukasa is a dog by her image.
Yuu-chan is small-animal-like, so she's a squirrel.
I see...
In the end you want to say that I'm something like a tigress or a wolf, right?
Huh?
Oh, Kagami gets lonely easily, so you might really be a bunny...
The twin things are like ears, too.
I feel kind of embarrassed by it a bit, so stop it..
That's interesting, I wonder what other people would be?
Yui-neesan has an image of moving around energetically, so she could be a leopard!?
Iwasaki-san is cool and graceful, so a hawk?
Yuki-chan feels like soft, and is somewhat fluffy, too, so...
she could be lamb?
Fumoffu!
Hmm...
Well, all things considered, Miyuki-san is a dairy cow, isn't she?
Around here and all...
That's an old-man-expression!
Yesterday at Konata's place I looked at the collection of compositions from elementary school and all.
Oh, is that so?
But, you know, Konata looks negligent, but surprisingly she has kept stuff like that in good order.
Since my dad said I should properly keep stuff.
But even more surprising were her dreams about the future.
There were usual jobs like "veterinarian" or "lawyer", too, you know...
Was that so?
Well, changing her dreams every year is Konata-like, though...
When you look at those, you understand which games I liked at that time...
Ahh... I see, so that was it after all, huh...
But there are people who write "housewife" into the "wished occupation"- field, too, you know...
It's not even an occupation, too...
That's cute, isn't it?
Well... Or should I say it's about you, though, Tsukasa...
Eh!?
Ah... W-w-was that so...
This is why natural people are...
Within natural people there are many of those who have no consciousness, aren't there?
That just might be so...
I'll just caution you, but Miyuki, you're like that as well...
Yes? Did something happen?
Miyuki-san, how good is your eyesight with the naked eye?
I don't even have 0.1.
tn: 0.1 on Japanese scale is 20/200 in US & 6/60 in metric
Ah, was that so...
I heard somewhere that it's good for the eyes if you eat blueberries and stuff.
Yes, that is right...
In addition there are carrots, that contain vitamin A,
the greenish-yellow vegetables such as spinach,
tn: Vegetables that have more than 600milligrams of carotin in 100 grams of them.
pork that contains vitamins from the B group.
Such foodstuff as sesame seeds and liver, that contain even more protein, are said to be good for eyes as well.
Also, laser treatment is becoming a topic...
Ohh...
Just as expected, I have no courage to receive such...
Additionally you see eyesight training and such on the television, too.
Ah, so you know a lot about it...
Well, these are just some of many...
But as you know as much, why is it that your vision doesn't recover?
Eh?
Even if I know, I don't really use them, so...
Why don't you not use them?
That is...
I wonder why?
Try something for me! What about eyesight training?
Right now?
Well, let's see...
At first, you close your eyes... and open them wide.
After that... you keep your face as-is...
and move only your eyes, like this... to left-right-up-down...
Miyuki-san! Your face! Your face is moving as well!
O-o-oh, my... Oh my...
T-this is weird, isn't it...
It's enough already, so please...
Despite your intentions, it seems like my eyes got tired...
Wouldn't your eyes get even worse like this...
Hey, Kona-chan - what's this thing called "moe"?
Hmm...
If you ask so formally...
It's unmistakably an expression of the feeling "I love",
but even I don't know it more detailed...
What's that? So you're using it so often without really knowing what it means?
For now, my opinion is that I think that people who take this word up naturally are otakus, I guess.
It's really an indifferent thing, but I feel like I understand what you said...
It's the "Doggies of the World" feature!
Daffunda!
Puppies are really cute, aren't they?
Daddy, let's have a dog here, too!
Hm?
Hey, hey! Tsukasa!
Even if you naively say it so lightly,
Discipline, walking, feeding, et cetera... can you properly take care of all that?
The image of a puppy and the one of an adult dog could be different.
Do you have the sense of raising something that is alive, not a thing?
Y-yeah, that's right... We have to think about it thoroughly, right?
B-but even so, oneechan, you're familiar with this all...
That's, well... Just that I'm naive as well, after all...
That's why I checked a lot, too...
Look! Konata!
You like this artist, right?
Try to read it!
Oww, got it... You're so annoying...
Your face's too close!
Ehh...
Ji...
Uh...
Err... Is there something..?
I just wondered until where did you read...
Did a person called Osano come out already?
No, I haven't reached that stage yet, so...
Come on, let's read it fast...
This year there were a lot of elections, weren't there?
I'm really in trouble...
Is that so?
Ohh, why are you looking so down?
Exam students should go home fast and study!
Ah, sensei - we're talking about how unpleasant it is that there are all those elections...
Why such an abrupt thing?
By all those election programs, the broadcast time of the usual ones changes, doesn't it?
The other day a certain first broadcast got off time by 4 hours suddenly, too!
tn: Chiba TV - the first episode of L☆S was that one.
Furthermore, they run the election reports during the show!
Also what's with the screen becoming smaller because of the L-shaped graphs!?
Well, but you know...
The election programs become a study on the current news topics, as well.
It's not the time to say "Anime! Anime!", is it?
Mm...
Additionally the broadcast times sometimes change even without the election programs, as well.
K-1 and such do take off the regular and take timeframes, right?
Izumi, didn't you like martial arts?
Even if I'm an experienced one, I don't really like them!
That anime you like gets into special positions sometimes as well, right?
My honey!
But as they do not cause trouble to the later programs by getting extended and what not, there's no problem at all!
Hey! Exam students shouldn't think about that,
but study-!!
So in the end it's the force skill after all!
Sorry for keeping you waiting!
Kona-chan, you know, said that she doesn't have an umbrella.
Just look at the weather report, you know...
Well, I was thinking I should just go home already like the guys who don't care about getting wet...
But I really wonder why guys don't mind getting wet?
Isn't it because they have no fear of their bra and all becoming see-through?
I see.
I guess you have a point there, but don't say it out with such a big voice so stately!
Have some decency!
So, one of you - lend me an umbrella.
Well, we are going to the same place, so it's somehow OK with just one...
Thanks-a-lot.
Uh, don't you keep an umbrella in school?
Even if you leave the books...
Ohh, until some time ago I did have one...
but, you know, I always forgot to bring it after I used it once...
Since I usually don't have it..
So it means you can't learn as long as you are indolent, huh?
Hey, Suzume - wait!
That reminds me, you know... when we put on rubber boots and a raincoat...
there's an image of being unstylish, right?
Yeah, that's right.
It feels somewhat childish, doesn't it?
Although I wonder why we all 'moe' as much, when they're seen in pictures...
Like I care...
This is a free softsub.Not for sale, rent, auction or hardsub.
Not for sale, rent, auction or hardsub.This is a free softsub.
or hardsub.This is a free softsub. Not for sale, rent, auction
Wiis! Konata!
Good morning...
but what happened, Tsukasa?
This month's mobile phone charges were high, and I got yelled at...
I'm always on the basic charge, as I seldom use something like a mobile phone.
Just the basic charge
Is that so?
Economical, isn't it?
You do call that "economical" though...
but I think that, if you nearly always don't use it, the basic charge itself is a waste...
Such small things can live without comments, Kagami...
Ah, a mail.
"Please buy eggs when you go home", huh...
"Un-der-stood...
When I go back...
I will go...
with neechan..."
Hey... You are answering to your parent, right?
Doesn't it somehow turn into polite language when we communicate by mail?
Well, but I can understand that somehow...
As you get used to it the words'll change...
Hmm...
Ah!
How long've you used this?
Probably, about a year.
How often do you usually change models?
Isn't the best time to change it about every two years?{around two years... only works with fixed dates)
The time for the battery to die is around that, isn't it?
If that is so...
I can show you that I can keep it twice... No! Three times longer!
By any means!
I don't understand the meaning of that will...
I treasure the things I have.
I care for my possesions...
You're just leaving stuff, right?
Oh, yes there are...
those people who spend any amount on hobbies,
and are stingy about anything else...
Oneechan, I'm sorry...
but lend me your World History textbook.
Again?
Oh, it can't be helped, can it...
Here.
Be more careful from the next time, will you?
Y-yeah...
I'll come and give it back to you later.
Hiiragi, your younger sister's quite careless, too, isn't she?
Yeah, that's right.
That's why if I won't be firm...
Hm...
But isn't this that thing?
Since she has someone to depend on, she slacks more easily.
In short, Hiiragi - your existence is allowing that.
Wah...
Somehow you are amazingly persuasive...
Hiiragi, what time is it now?
There's an alarm clock in front of you, right?
Ah, that's true.
The legend of Hiiragi's wakeup violence!
I'll tell you that it just fell and broke off, you know...
Tsukasa,
manga isn't bad either, but try to read a newspaper or something sometimes...
and learn what happens in the world, as well.
Y-yeah...
Hmh!
Err...
Huh?
The newspaper's hard to read, isn't it..?
It's got all these indentions, and I don't know where to go...
I did think that it was something like that, though...
Ah! You over there!
Ah, what is it?
I wonder if you could call the Kobayakawa-san from this class?
Tell her that Izumi from the third year has come.
Y-yes!
Kobayakawa! Izumi-senpai from the third year has come!
What is it, oneechan?
Ohh... Isn't it funny that when they understand I'm senior, it changes to honorifics?
They're really cute, aren't they?
Eh-he-he-he...
Iwasaki-san, it's so good that you're tall...
Eh?
I wonder why there's such a gap...
I don't really know, but it could be because I often drink milk...
I see! So it's the fruit produced by the daily efforts, isn't it?
No...
Humans just get it that easy...
Compared to height, I would've wanted a certain other place to become bigger...
Huh?
I heard that, as it's raining, today's PE will be dodge ball in the gym!
Iwasaki-san, you have an image to stay until the end in games like this, right?
As you seem strong.
I, too, when on field, somehow stay there until the end...
I wonder if I'm hard to aim at as I'm small...
Even if they both remain, the reason for it is very different, isn't it...
Even though moving my body isn't something I am good at, though...
and Kobayakawa-san, she looks like she'd break somehow if she's hit by something...
How unlucky, we ended up in different teams, didn't we?
Yeah...
We're together, aren't we?
Yeah.
Iwasaki-san seems to be good at sports and merciless, so she's someone to be feared, right?
Ah...
Head... Out of question
Upper body... It'd be terrible if she'd
be hit hard and get sick
Lower body... If she'd slip and hurt
herself it'd be terrible
But still, I don't know how it would end
if I'd leave it to others
I got myself rotated to the outfield, so it's alright, you know.
Oh, that's a relief...
So Iwasaki-san is a good person after all...
So, Kobayakawa-san's on offence...
Yeah!
And, Iwasaki-san, you're on the field?
Yeah...
So, you're the receiving si...
Ah!
Not that... a defender, huh?
Huh?
Got attacked by the helper of the nurse's office...
Are you alright?
Even so, Iwasaki-san, you're amazing...
It hits right into the personality, doesn't it...
I wonder if that's so...
Both your kinetic vision and motoric nerves are good, aren't they?
Not really...
Ah!
Oh...
I wonder if she got angry because I fussed over it?
Not that! That's her being embarrassed, you know!
Is that so?
If that'd be so it's alright,
but as I don't fully understand...
Ah...
So people who get misunderstood are like this, huh...
If we do not know the personality well, the impression we get is different, as well...
Have you gone on a trip somewhere or something like that after you've come here?
Yes. I did pilgrimage to the holy places.
Holy places?
Yes!
For now, I have pilgrimaged to the three greatest holy places of Japan!
Something like Kamakura and Kyoto or Nara?
No!
The Akiba in Tokyo, Nipponbashi in Oosaka and Oosu in Nagoya!
Huh?
And then I went around seeing the sights around here, too.
Something like the Tokyo Tower or Asakusa?
That's not it!
Something like Nakano or Kichijouji!
Err...
Aw...
What happened?
Oh...
It seems like some dirt got into my eye...
Are you alright?
Yeah...
Tell me if you aren't be able to endure it...
Yeah, I'm alright...
It's a good situation now! Right?
Eh! This is no good! I mustn't look at my friends with such rotten eyes!
Good day!
Yes, come on up!
I'll bring some drinks and stuff now.
Hmm...
Ah...
Hm?
Hm...
Ah! She's got a lot of books!
There was nothing else than something like this...
So for Hiyori there was a time like this as well...
Pleassee kill her...
Please just kill her off at once...
And this is her "now", isn't it?
So she did get there...
Remarkable, isn't it?
Really! Skillful, isn't it?
Yeah...
This drawing somehow resembles Iwasaki-san, doesn't it?
Ohh, Takarazuka, isn't it?
tn: Takarazuka - a revue where all members are women
Ah, is this me?
Is this a fairy tale or something?
Yeah...
Eh...
Show it after it's done, right?
This is no good! You mustn't draw your friends with such rotten eyes...
Tamura-san, do you go to the "Maiden Street"?
Yes, I'm going with that intention.
What kind of place is the "Maiden Street"?
Don't you know!?
Yeah...
Me neither...
Ah... Good grief...
"Maiden Street", is it..?
The word "Maiden Street" means the road to the west of the Tokyo Ikebukuro Sunshine 60.
Here there are many dedicated anime and manga and character goods shops, you know...
It is viewed as a place where maniacs gather on the same level as in Akiba.
Namely because of the differentiating factor from Akiba, that there are many female customers, it came into being that this road is called "Maiden Street".
In other words, it's about a road where "fujoshi" go...
"Fujoshi"?
Written "rotten" plus "girl", read as "fujoshi".
tn: "fujoshi" - a girl/woman with interest to homoerotic manga/anime
Are they rotten!?
Well, it's true if you put it that way...
Ah, look!
The rule of 3 seconds! 3 seconds!
They do say that the germs don't get onto it if it's only 5 seconds, you know!
What is it? We haven't said anything, right?
Ah!
Wah!
The best thing of them all - the meat ball did...
Aww...
What about the 3-second-rule?
No... I'd be glad if you'd pass that on the view of "it differs by case"...
Please visit us at
http://jeeb.fiveforty.jp/
#jeeb@irc.rizon.net
Lucky Channel!
Good lucky!
Yes, I'd like to get at this cheerfully this time as well!
Some way or another Lucky Channel turned into it's 18th time this time!
Yes! Your navigator is, already become quite familiar, Kogami Akira!
And then...
Yes! I'm working as Akira-sama's assistant today as well!
I am Shiraishi Minoru!
And so, today's theme is...
I'd really like to introduce the new characters besides the regular people!
Down!
There's too many of them!
First of all, Konata-san's cousin, who came over to the Izumi household - Kobayakawa Yutaka-san.
And her classmates - Iwasaki Minami-san and Tamura Hiyori-san.
Patricia Martin-san!
What's even more!
Kagami-san's classmates Kusakabe Misao-san and Minegishi Ayano-san...
Whatever you say, it has gotten quite lively!
Although I think that you all have noticed already,
Could this not be an obstacle!?
these new members, to tell you the truth, have already come out in the opening!...
Hey! Can't you see that it blocks!?..
Wah! it flew!
How much stuff do you have to put in front of me to become satisfied!?
It's the 18th time already, right? What's happening to my debut!?
Ahh, that reminds me, Akira-sama,
didn't you get out this time?
With those rubber boots to a raincoat, in such an adorable appearance...
Huh!?
Ah. Well.. How should I explain..
Last week I got to talk with our guest Anizawa-san...
He said that for an actor...
Attraction! The fact that you cannot be easily ignored!
Certainly...
Today's Akira-sama's way of appearance was just for a moment,
but to my eyes it was like "Kogami Akira is here!"...
Umh!..
Hey!
Ah, yes?
Ah, no-no! It isn't that!
Oh! How unfortunate!
So it's the time for us to part, isn't it?
And so, from now as well, we are really waiting for your impressions, cheers and opinions on the program!
Hey.
Where..?
We're taking them on the homepage, radio and at other places!
Well, bye-nii!
Shut it off!
Well, thanks for your hard work...
Was it a mail?
N-no, that's different.
That's not it... There's no way...
Where did you send the mail?
No, just a bit from the family, so...
For what!?
Well, they say that I should soon go back to my parent's house...
What are you writing!?
No, because, that's...
Try and say it.
Well, in essen!..
ずっと探してたんだ
Zutto sagashitetanda
I was always searching...
Translation: JEEB
Translation Checking: Senoby
運命の人ってやつを
Unmei no hitotte yatsu wo
for that person called my partner in fate...
Encoding: Heedly
Editing: Ro, Ilaggoodly
Izumi Soujirou, DarkJug
Typesetting: Kei Striker
それはきっと君さ
Sore wa kitto kimi sa
That's probably you, you know...
根拠なんかはないけれど
Konkyo nanka wa nai keredo
Even though if there's no ground for it,
君の笑顔を見れば
Kimi no egao wo mireba
should I look at your smile,
ありふれた日常だって
Arifureta nichijou datte
even the ordinary daily life...
輝くから不思議さ
Kagayaku kara fushigi sa
shines, that's mysterious, you know...
まるで魔法かけたみたい
Maru de mahou kaketa mitai
It's just like I'd be bewitched...
愛しさも切なさも
Itoshisa mo setsunasa mo
Belovedness and sadness,
君が教えてくれたね
Kimi ga oshiete kureta ne
they both were told me by you...
どんな長い道のりも
Donna nagai michinori mo
However long the distance is,
二人なら怖くない
Futari nara kowaku nai
As long as we're together, there's nothing to fear...
今日という特別な日が
Kyou to iu tokubetsu na hi ga
This special day, called "today"...
君と一緒でよかった
Kimi to issho de yokatta
I'm happy I could spend it with you...
この僕の全てで君を
Kono boku no subete de kimi wo
With all this I have,
永遠に守るよ
Eien ni mamoru yo
I'll protect you forever...
I promise you
I promise you...
The End
Yes!
Although I failed a bit on the falsetto.
Excuse me, excuse me...
I was touched.
Ah.
I was touched!
Thanks.
Thank you very much!
It's old, old.
And so, the next Lucky Star is?
It's me, Hiyori.
It's me, Patricia!
Pattie, did you get used to your part-time job already?
Yes, perfectly.
I guess if Pattie's the partner, even a person who'd be coming for the first time would be able to enjoy it without being nervous.
No, I don't serve first-timers.
Eh, is that so?
I will not serve others than those who come many times and spend a lot of money.
That is our cafe's policy, so...
U-unexpectedly severe, isn't it...
"
Th
Next time: "There is essence in 2-D".
ere
is
essence
in
2-D
"
Please look forward to it!