Yoshimizu
Kagami
Theatre
Ah, the B class of third year?
Kuroi-sensei!
Yeah, yeah...
曖昧3センチ
Aimai 3 senchi
Unclear 3 centimeters...
そりゃぷにってことかい？ちょっ!
Sorya punitte koto kai? cho!
Is that a puni? Waitasec!
らっぴんぐが制服…
Rappingu ga seifuku…
The uniform's the wrapping…
だぁぁ不利ってことない　ぷ。
Daa furitte koto nai　Pu.
Hey, there's no disadvantage in that, yeah.
がんばっちゃ♥やっちゃっちゃ
Ganbaccha♥yacchaccha
Try your best♥do your thing-cha,
そんときゃーっち&Releaseぎョッ
son tokyaacchi & ririisu gyo
at that time, well, catch & release, gyo!
汗っ、々っ
A-se, a-se!
In the sweaty, sweaty...
の谷間にDarlin'darlin'F R E E Z E!!
No taniai ni daarin daarin furiiーzu!
cleavage darlin' darlin' FREEZE!!
Fan          subs
E
J
B
E
なんかダるー、なんかデるー
NankaDAruuー, nankaDEruー
Somewhat lazy..., something's coming out...
あいしテるー
AishiTEruuー
I love you...
あれ一個が違ってるんるー
Are ikko ga chigatterunruー
One of those is different, ruー.
なやみン坊ー 高鉄棒 おいしん簿ー
NayamiNbouー Koutetsubou oishinboー
A worrywart, high horizontal bar - an ever-lengthening list...
いーかげんにシナサイ
Iikagen ni SHINASAI
Now get reasonable!
飛んでったアイツの火照るカラダって
Tondetta AITSU no hoteru KARADAtte
The burning body of who flied away right now is...
所謂ふつーのおにゃのコ
Iwayuru futsuu no onya no KO
what is called a "usual girl".
驚いた、
Odoroita,
I'm surprised,
あたしだけ? 豚骨ハリガネおかわりダー!!!!
atashi dake? tonkotsu harigane okawari daaー!!!!
Only me? I get an extra portion of tonkotsu with super hard noodlesー!!!!
BON-BONおーえん団
BON-BON oーendan
Bon-bon cheering team.
Let's get! Cherry pie
Let's get! Cherry pie.
RAN-RAN　かんげー会
Ranraan　kangeーikai
RAN-RAN, welcoming party.
Look up! せんせーしょん
Look up! Senseーshon
Look up! Sensation.
はい！　存在感・・小惑星
Haai　Sonzaikan　tenten　shouwakusei
Yes, feeling of being here・・meteor!
ぶつかって溶けました　呆然　大いに歌ってシレンジャー
Butsukatte tokemashita　bouzen　ooi ni utatte shirenjaー
Got melted by the collision, dumbfounded and singing a lot, "Shiranger!"
もっていけ!
Motte ike!
Take and go!
最後に笑っちゃうのはあたしのはず
Saigo ni waracchau no wa atashi no hazu
The last one laughing should be me,
セーラーふくだからです
Seeraa fuku dakara desu
because it's a sailor fuku.
←結論
←Ketsuron
←Conclusion.
月曜日なのに！
Getsuyoubi nanoni!
Even if it's monday!
機嫌悪いのどうするよ？
Kigen warui no dou suru yo？
What will you do with that bad mood?
夏服がいいのです←キャ？ワ！イイｖ
Natsufuku ga ii no desu←KYA?WA!IIv
I want my summer uniform←It?Is!Cute!
接近3ピクト するまでってちゅーちょだ　やん☆
Sekkin san pikuto, suru madette chuーcho da　yan☆
Getting closer's in three paces, I'll hesitate until you do 'it' Oh☆
頑張って　張り切って
Ganbatte,　harikitte
Try your best, be on high,
My Darlin'darlin' P L E A S E!!
Mai daarin daarin puriizu
my darlin' darlin' please!
Both of you, good morning!
Ossu!
Good morning.
So you properly put on your winter uniform, didn't you?
Well... As I'm not Tsukasa...
What!?
But as there still are many hot days,
I'd think it's still OK with the summer uniform...
To the contary, it's sometimes cold when you change to the summer uniform,
it'd be good if they would let us be free with the outfit...
Yeah...
If anything, you're for altering the mindeset altogether, right?
And I think that people that have no variance will probably increase, too...
Pandora's
Box
We don't have such, but there seem to be parents...
who check the mail on the daughter's cell phone or PC, right?
Yes, you do hear of that sometimes...
Is there nothing like that at your place?
Hmm...
I think I could say that its not like that at our place, too...
Your father seems to be very fond of you...
So he, as expected, won't do anything to displease his daughter, huh?
Hmm... Well, there's that, but...
as my father uses computers as well...
I wonder if its because he knows...
the shame of having someone look into his D drive?
D... What?
Waah...
This year's summer I've only had writing courses and the like,
the playing was just the fireworks display and Ariake, right?
So you're going to the Comike after all...
Comike!..
That's, you know...
Because of that I'm low on cash...
How much did you spend?
Since you don't care how much everything costs...
Two copies averaging at about 1000 yen...
The total being around 4-50,000 yen, I wonder...
Wait a sec! You...
There's the thing called going crazy with your sense of money...
Even if you say so, Kagami...
There's the thing called "market" in the world...
And self-published books are pretty expensive, you know...
It's not that!
It's the sense of using all that amount!
Ahh...
Even if they say that its already September,
it's still hot, isn't it?
Yeah, that's right...
It seems to be especially hot this year.
They do talk about the global warming, too...
As Yuu-chan is easily affected by heat,
she almost always rests with the air conditioner on.
Tsukasa, as well, is in her room always, with the air conditioner on.
Although she's just slacking off...
Ah..!
Well, my dad and I partake by forming the "Shou" symbol and lying around.
tn: 小 - "shou", small
川 - "kawa", river
"Shou"?
If you say it so, isn't it "kawa"?
No...
As my father always lays down in the middle...
Your place is as always...
Or should I say that Yutaka-chan got used to it, too...
Yahhai!
Yutaka, are you feeling well?
I came to play!
Ah, oneechan!
Uh, this person here is...
My friend, Iwasaki Minami-chan.
Ah...
Aah, so this is the Minami-chan you always talk about...
Oneechan!
To have hope in the most close place possible...
I'm a bit envious...
Huh?
Well... I although i have heard about you,
but you really are a beauty, aren't you?
Big sister's surprised!
Would you like something to drink?
Well then, beer!
Huh!? Aren't you driving?
I'm kidding!
Barley tea it is!
Ah...
I see...
So the other one absorbs...
Absorption, huh...
Oh, it was Yassai-Mossai, huh?
During the night I somehow end up wanting to sleep,
I wonder if there's no better way?
Isn't it better to go to sleep and wake up early than to force yourself to stay awake?
Emotionally speaking ,too.
Is that so? Ah, so it is!
Let's wake up early and try for the best~tto...
Huh!? I wonder why it's the same time as always...
Now that I think of it, it felt like I stopped something halfway through...
Out of habit, even if I do wake up early,
I just take it too easy, and end up falling asleep again!
Your determination is weak, isn't it?
I wonder if it's better for me to try my best and continue till late night...
Even if you do it, rubbing your sleepy eyes,
I can't think that your performance will improve...
If that's the case, wouldn't it be good to be woken up?
Mom and all wake up early, too
Isn't that right, mom?
Yes, yes... I will wake you up on time.
If this works out, its guaranteed, isn't it?
Oneechan, as expected!
Mommy, even though I told you to wake me up!
I did, and you even answered, didn't you?
Eh, I don't know what you mean...
Don't you remember?
Ah...
Ah!
Oneechan forgot her o-bentou!
Thank you.
The hallway of another grade feels somehow strange, doesn't it?
A bit like I'm getting attention...
Ah, I know what you mean...
I bet Yuu-chan caught people's attention, didn't she...
She's that size, too...
Huh?
Usually it's the imagination of the person at hand,
but regardless of whether you go where seniors or juniors are,
you do feel the foreign atmosphere of having attention, don't you?
Since, I'm small in the first place, I stand out...
But when you think that it's the seniors...
I feel a little nervous...
Although I do appreciate such attention, you know...
Hee, is that so?
But even if I go to the place where freshmen are, I don't really get attention...
As I don't seem like a senior...
Pressure  as  a
Senior:  none .
Ah, Patty-chan!
Hi! Hello it is!
Are you going to work now?
Indeed, I put too many shifts in this week.
You're still doing it, too, right?
That's right!
We are quite popular, you know.
A-boys, are all moe-moe too!
Wah... "A-boy"..?
tn: "obviously otaku" is what she means.
That's what you call obvious boys whom visit Akiba often.
But, Narimiya-kun was a bit different...
She has gotten used to Japan well, hasn't she?
That's too limited though!?
Ah! I thought of a good idea!
Let's draw it after I get out of the bath...~tto
Ah...
A...
E-er...
I can't remember...
If I don't quickly write it down... this is what happens...
Even if... even if it'd be interesting for sure...
Ahh...
I got tired today as well~tto...
Eh-he...
This idea could be interesting!
Let's draw it after I wake up tomorrow~tto...
Huh..?
How strange, what was it?
Although it was a good idea for sure...
I should've taken notes without being lazy...
Ah!
Ahh, again...
Even though I woke up so fast, I wonder why you forget dreams quickly...
Even though this right now would've been interesting for sure!
This is a free softsub.Not for sale, rent, auction or hardsub.
Not for sale, rent, auction or hardsub.This is a free softsub.
or hardsub.This is a free softsub. Not for sale, rent, auction
Lucky Star!
☆
Things
to be
decided
School
field
trip
Kyoto
Nara
Assignment
of
hotel
rooms
And so, everyone's going to talk and decide everything!
School Excursion
Kyoto
Nara
As we're especially going to Kyoto and Nara,
research every possible sightseeing spot!
School
field
trip
☆
Things
to be
decided
Groups
for
Free
activities
Assignment
of
hotel
rooms
Train
seating
Garbage
duty :
Shiraishi
Minoru
Will we not visit all of the sightseeing spots by bus together?
Ha-ha-ha!
Going together is all about planned places, so it's not interesting...
Should she say it like that, nothing good will come of this...
Wahh...
So this is where Irys got in...
Huh?
From here we shall guide you through the ancient city of Nara.
About 1300 years from the Heijoukyou relocation of the capital in year 710,
please enjoy the historical romance of Nara indeed only in Nara.
Bwahahahaha! Ha!
"Of Nara"!
Is this the place to laugh?
Sorry for making you wait!
Hmm...
This here is the main part...
And the small ones around it are an option, aren't they!?
You'll be smitten, you know...
Ah...
It's sticky...
It's smelly...
I became smelly...
Here, here, here...
It really is smelly, isn't it...
What are you trying!?
Please please...
Eh? Eh!?
It's probably "Please take a picture", I think.
Err.. Err...
Pop-pop, OK?
During times like these the amount of everyday studies really shows up, doesn't it?
You're one to talk!
Shala-uhu!
Oneechan, I wonder how "Cheese!" is said in Indian?
Ah, it's Hindu, isn't it...
Well, you know...
Err...
Yes-yes... Our bright girl Kagami is defeated at first round as well...
Isn't it so that in India English is understood as well?
Yes, that's right, isn't it?
Isn't it enough with "Say cheese!?"
I see.
"Say Cheese!"
You know, when the school excursion begins,
there are such couples that suddenly cling to each other, aren't there?
You just can't take away the school excursion events, now can you?
Oh...
After all, couldn't it be that the circuimstance of...
being out of the school makes people feel more free?
It's the feeling of "Were here!", isn't it?
Even though it is embarrassing,
I just can't relax and fall asleep with a different pillow...
I just can't relax and fall asleep if I don't have this next to me...
Even though it is embarrassing,
I just can't relax and fall asleep if I cannot turn this on once in a day...
Ah...
Everyone, in a moment the bus will come to the Kiyomizu-dera temple.
The hill that leads to the Kiyomizu-dera is called Sannenzaka,
There is a legend that if you slip here, you die in three years.
The slope of three years ends up becoming the slope of unluckyness.
Is stumbling from laughter in that as well?
You hear me? You'll be free to move about on your own from now on!
Go around while watching out for cars.
As the assembly is in 12:30 before the Chiyoin,
you mustn't be late!
Those who are late are going to welcome writing 20 pages of reports!
I wonder if this works...
Should we try?
The dragon killing was done with something like this, I wonder...
It is high, isn't it?
They do say "With the intention of falling from the Kiyomizu platform",
but if you really did fall from here you'd die, right?
Is it about not caring what happens next?
Kagami has no dreams, has she?
Hey, hey! There're love knots there!
This place seems to be famous by its god of knotting love.
The Stone
of love
Fortune
telling
Easy to understand, isn't it?
The Stone
of love
Fortune
telling
Fulfillment of Romance
Fortune slips of love
Ah, look! There are fortune slips of love!
Let's all try!
Prayers for a good match
Oh! Let's do it, yes!
Indeed, this I cannot tell...
Isn't that normal?
Ah! This is!
Fortune slips of love
Special on Love knots
Ah, "great luck"!
Ah, Kona-chan, you're lucky.
Oh my, I got a "luck".
Isn't that good enough?
Well, and I get~tto...
"Half-luck" - what's this?
It seems to be half luck...
In other words, it's half bad luck, you know.
Not like I really care, romance fortune slips or something like that.
This is cute!
Ah, this is good isn't it?
No, Kagami's getting this one, right?
What're you implying!?
I'll buy this one.
Ah, Kagami, Kagami! You've forgotten something!
I'm not buying it!
Well, this one is?
Like I'd buy it!
You, be careful, you know.
Votive pictures of love knots
Ah, there's "Konata's my wife!" written here...
Eh?
Alright! Everyone's gathered, right?
We'll first check into the hotel, and then have dinner.
So we'll be off now.
And so, please...
You know, there was "IZAM-style" written in the Koizumi's character song...
Woah!
Huh?
Sensei! There's someone pursuing us from the rear!
What!?
Isn't this just repetition of the same mistake on the location in Hokkaido!?
You must say "Maetel"!
That idiot...
50 pages of report for you!
Driver, excuse me, please stop!
Hotel Honnoudera
Again?
Ah...
To Hiiragi
Ah!
I would like to talk to you,
so please meet me in
front of the hotel
at 9 o'clock tonight.
From :
a certain boy
Hey!
That doesn't work at all!
Ah, that's bad!
Even though the Kinkaku-ji is golden...
the Ginkaku-ji isn't silvery, is it?
As it was built as something to pair with the Golden Temple,
it seems like it was named "Silver" per to the "Golden".
It seems like it wasn't silver-coloured from the beginning.
I wonder if there's Sapphire, or Ruby or something, like in Pokemon?
Ah, won't you interject a comment?
Oh...
Our shrine was in the news, you know...
What's left has become another day, hasn't it?
The plan for the free activities is right on the mark, isn't it?
Tomorrow indeed is our real "school excursion"!
Now, let us go! To the place where we were born!
Is that... so?
Ah...
Ah..!
"In front of the hotel"... Was this alright?
Yeah, did you wait for long?
And, the thing you wanted to talk about...
Hmm...
I couldn't say something like this to anyone other than you, Hiiragi...
Please give that doll to me!
Huh? "Doll"?
Ah, look!
You bought one at that souvenir shop at Kiyomizu-dera, right?
The Yatsuhashi-character!
Yatsuhashi-kun?
Yes, that one!
I really liked it and wanted it no matter what,
but if someone were to see someone like me buying it,
I'd get picked on by everyone, so I beg you!
Ah, alright...
Thanks! I owe you one!
Yeah!
You won't tell anyone about this, right!?
I wonder how that talk about Yui and Toudai was called?
Souryuuden?
I can't take this off...
Yes! That one!
The steam inside has cooled down, and it has become a vacuum, hasn't it?
Should you slide the ends a bit,
air will be able to enter, and I think it should become easier to open...
Hee...
I wonder if it was until around the fourth book of the original...
OK then...
Wah!
Oh?
I'm sorry, I'm sorry...
So she shows us it until the end...
I've researched the place right on, so...
Is it really alright to go there?
As we'll just be looking from outside of the building, it's alright!
Just because we came to Kyoto, isn't it alright not to do stuff like that?
No-no-no...
tn: romance - roman (jp.) - marron as a joke (play with syllables)
You seem not to understand the marron of otakus...
I don't even want to understand!
It's a place where there's nothing, isn't it?
To be able to concentrate on the work around this is the best.
An unexpectedly usual building, isn't it?
As they're narrowing the number of their works, around this is good.
Is there any meaning to specifically buy them in Kyoto?
Eh!? That's embarrassing, you know!
Isn't it alright? As a memory of this day, you know!
Oneechan, let's take it together!
As it's a commemoration.
As we came all the way to Kyoto!
What in this is Kyoto-like!?
Yeah, I and Tsukasa already came home safe.
Although Tsukasa fell asleep already.
Hmm...
And I thought that Kagami, you went to bed in a huff.
Why must I go to bed in a huff!?
Have you stuck that purikura somewhere, as you should?
There's no way I'd stick such an embarrassing thing somewhere!
This is embarrassing...
This week there was the school field trip, too...
I worked hard...
Well now...
I'll treat myself to a weekend on an internet game since its been a while...
Maintenance Information:
Message of Emergency Maintenance
Due to server difficulties of unknown origin, we are now carrying out
Emergency Maintenance.
Content of the maintenance
Maintenance of our company's servers
As soon as the maintenance is over, we will inform you of it at the forums here.
Our sincerest apologies for the trouble we have caused to all of our users.
Please visit us at
http://jeeb.fiveforty.jp/
#jeeb@irc.rizon.net
Lucky Star!
Lucky Channel!
Good lucky!
This time coming out at once again, Lucky Channel!
I'm your navigator - Kogami Akira~depikko!
I'm your navigator - Ono Daisuke.
How quickly the time flies! It's already the 21st time!
Yes, that is right... It has finally become the finale...
Now, let us go to this corner right away...
This week's
Maggaare
This week's maggaare.
Eh!? Who's that...
What... Eh?
I scooped it.
What's this!?
Lukewarm!
Like I could drink something like this!
If it's like this, I'd prefer the one in the vending machines...
Waaargh!!!
Stop the bullshit!
You know, you know...
How long do you think I've put up with this!?
Always, always saying just selfish stuff!
Mi-minoru?
I'll let my feelings out on this day!
Have you got any idea with what kind of feelings I've done this corner!?
Every, every day working at Cocoa's!
Compared to what my earnings from voice acting are, I get more from the part-time one!
Thanks to you I'm an old-timer now!
Before I lifted you up,
I always lowered my face to the ground!
So you like being that way, is that so?
How annoying! Why is Onobo sitting there!?
That is my stage seat!
You were abandoned, you know... By the producer and director.
What'd you say!?
Those people are too fast with their habit of abandonment!
I'm a late bloomer, you know!
I happen to change into a Stargazer all of a sudden!
Is that possible... For you..?
Making a fool of me...
Like I could keep going with some Hinemosu or with some Love&Berry!
I'll quit this...
I'll quit this program, whatever you do!
You're annoying!
What's a Lucky Channel!?
Get the hell of out of my way, idiot!
What were you about to say!?
What's "Misoji Misaki" then!?
If you'd become a veteran with such...
I'm soon thirty, too - you know!
And about you, too... I'm gonna say it!
Welcome to Idaho!
His belt isn't long enough, so she's holding it from the back.
Hello! I am Shiraishi Minoru!
Indeed...
Translation : JEEB
Encode : Heedly
Now, I'll leave you to listen!
I don't want to hear it.
The song of Shikaider!
What is this!?
宇宙に響け
Uchuu ni hibike...
Make the sound of drills echo throughout space!
You're really into this...
ドリル音
doriru on!
Yeah-yeah...
TLC : Senoby
No matter what kind of enemy it is, he'll finish it with a single blow!
どんな相手も
Donna aite mo...
Hey, no moving!
一撃だ！
ichigeki da!
Yeah, yeah... Don't you move!!
皆の願い
Minna no negai...
To protect everyone's wish,
Ah, stop it!
守るため
mamoru tame...
己を捨てて
Onore wo sutete...
he stands up, sacrificing himself.
Typesetting : Ilaggoodly
Editing : ro, Ilaggoodly
立ち向かう
Tachimukau...
Justasec! Akira-sama!
敵は地獄のムシバモス
Teki wa jigoku no mushibamosu!
His enemy is the Mushibamosu from hell!
QC : DarkJug, Kylaran
Got it!
正義のドリルを見せてやれ！
Seigi no doriru wo misete yare!
Show your Drill of Justice!
Yeah, yeah - yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Ah, it h-h-hurts!
今だ！
Ima da!
Do it now!
削れ！
Kezure!
Chip it off!
ツインドリル！
Tsuin doriru!
Twin Drills!
Don't move, hey!
砕け！
Kudake!
Smash it!
Yeah-yeah-yeah-yeah...
Chip it off!
削れ！
Kezure!
俺は、俺は・・・
Ore wa, ore wa...
I am, I am...
俺はシカイダー！
Ore wa Shikaidaa!
I am Shikaider!
Isn't this enough?
Shikaider is..!
No biting!
He is a cyborg.
He will...
In order to defeat the Mushibaa of Evil,
You can't become a hero!
he will continue to fight, day and night!
You can't fight, if you're like that!
How was it?
No good, it's going to be retaken.
This video was brought to you by JEEB
Understood.
And so, the next Lucky Star is?
I'm Kogami Akira!
Pika...
I'm Ono Daisuke.
Hn?
Peko?
Pekkoo...
Peko peko pekkoo!
Hnn... Hm?
Peko?
Hn-hn!
Pekko!
Hhhn-h!
All right, an end to the animal talk already!
So we were animals...
Next time: "The Yonder Here"
It's alright to make a goal already...
Pekkoo!
Raamen set!