Now, let'ssu begin yoo!
It's gonna come now...
Fungaa!
Now start out already!
I My Something
"I my something"
そりゃぷにってことかい、ちょっ
Sorya punitte koto kai, cho
That's about a puni, is it, cho?
ら、ぐーんぐーんが制服
Ra, guun-guun ga seifuku
Ra, guun guun goes the seifuku,
なぁふりってことない？　うん
Naa furitte koto nai？　Un
Hey, there's no irrationality in this? Yeah.
頑張っちゃ、やっちゃっちゃ、
Ganbaccha, yacchaccha,
Try your best, do the thing-cha,
そんときゃ　じゃリリース料
son tokya　jya ririisu ryou
at that time, well the things for release!
あせっ、あせっ
A-se, a-se!
"A-se, a-se!"
の谷間にダーリンダーリンフリー
No taniai ni daarin daarin furiiー
In the cleavage darling darling free!
なんかたるー、なんかてるー
Nankataruuー, nankateruー
How to cheat, how to win,
あいしてるー
Aishiteruuー
I love you.
あれ一個が違ってる
Are ikko ga chigatteru
One of those is different.
むん　むやみに暴行鉄棒おいしん棒
Mun muyami ni boukou tetsubou oishinbou
Stuffy, violence with recklessness - steel rod is a sweet rod.
いいかげんにしなさい!
Iikagen ni shinasai!
Now get reasonable!
飛んでったあいつの火照る体って
Tondetta aitsu no hoteru karadatte
The burning body of who flied away right now is...
いわゆる普通の女の子
Iwayuru futsuu no onna no ko
what is called a "usual girl".
驚いた、
Odoroita,
I'm surprised,
あたしだけ豚骨針金おかわりダー!!!!
atashi dake tonkotsu harigane okawari daaー!!!!
Only I get an extra portion of tonkotsu with a needle insideー!!!!
ボンボン応援団
Bon-bon ouendan
Bon-bon cheering team.
Let's get cherry pie
Let's get cherry pie.
らんらーん　関係感
Ranraan　kankeikan
Blazing, relationship feeling,
you have センセーション
you have senseeshon
you have sensation.
ハーイ　存在感　点々　小惑星
Haai　Sonzaikan　tenten　shouwakusei
Yes, feeling of being here, here and there meteors.
ぶつかって溶けました　呆然　大いに歌ってシリンダー
Butsukatte tokemashita　bouzen　ooi ni utatte shirindaa
Got melt from the collision, dumbfounded singing a lot, "Cilinder!"
もっていけ、
Motte ike,
Take and go,
最後に笑っちゃうのはあたしのはず
Saigo ni waracchau no wa atashi no hazu
The last one laughing should be me,
セーラー服だからです
Seeraa fuku dakara desu
because it's a seeraa fuku.
結論
Ketsuron
Conclusion.
月曜日なのに
Getsuyoubi nanoni
Even if it's monday,
機嫌悪いのどうするよ
Kigen warui no dou suru yo
What will you do with that bad mood?
夏服がいいのです、かわいい
Natsufuku ga ii no desu, kawaii
The summer uniform is better, cute.
接近賛否それまでって躊躇だ　やーん
Sekkin sanbi, sore madette choucho da　yaーn
Yes and no for getting closer, until that it's undecided, yaan.
頑張って　張り切って
Ganbatte,　harikitte
Try your best, be on high,
ま、ダーリンダーリンプリーズ
Ma, daarin daarin puriizu
well darling darling please!
To your positions!
Ready!
Oh! As expected, Kona-chan. Just awesome.
As you're so good with sports, why won't you enter a sports club?
But if you enter a club, you know...
you can't watch golden time anime, can you?
Speedy Lady
Hey, Tsukasa. Where do you start eating a choco cornet?
Hmm... From the head, I suppose.
Ah, so...
By the way, which one of them is the head. The fat side or the thin side?
I think that the thinner side here is the head.
Ah so, well I thought that the fatter side was the head.
But why the thin side is the head?
Well, it looks like a shell, doesn't it?
Hmm...
Why did Kona-chan pick the fatter side?
Well, you know, it looks like caterpillar, doesn't it?
Caterpillar...?
Well... but if you think about it that way, shell sounds better, doesn't it.
E... excuse me...
There is a way to eat it by holding the thinner head and pushing out the remaining chocolate...
Oh, I see that.
Phew... Miyuki-san, as expected, you've got a good brain...
Oh it's not that... As everyone is free to have his or her own way of eating...
How do you eat a cream-filled pastry?
Eh, a chou a la creme?
Well, let's see...
I split the pastry in half first...
...and eat the cream by picking it up with the upper half...
...and... Well, after that I eat the pot side.
If you do it like that, the cream won't just out...
and the cream with the chou can be eaten in a balance, can they not?
Well there's the one with both custard and cream, isn't there?
How do you eat that one?
Do you mix it, too?
Oh no, I can't dare to mix like that.
But how can you mix it?
Oh, I just asked you.
When do you eat things like the strawberry on the top of a strawberry short or the chestnut on a Mont Blanc?
Yes, let's see...
It all differs with the quantity of strawberry between the sponge cakes, too.
I eat it by the proportions of strawberry, cream and sponge cake distribution.
Because of that the time I eat the strawberry always differs.
Hmm... you're all hands aren't you...
I always keep it to the end...
...but sometimes my stomach gets full...
...and I cannot eat it or it gets eaten by my family.
Yeah, if you don't eat the things you like most first...
If you mention it, I haven't seen my sister having her strawberry taken.
Kagami as usual, no blunders there.
Can you eat the last bite of stick ice without dropping it?
Do you drop it?
If you don't eat it skillfully...
...it drops, right?
Un...
How does Kona-chan do it?
I lick it and cut it.
What about eating it by spinning it like this?
That might be good.
Actually I don't like soft ice that much.
Eh, why is that so?
You just hate it when only the cone gets left, don't you...
Un, un. It always ends up with only the cone.
I'm always eating it with pushing the ice cream down the cone all the time.
How do you push it?
Like this "gui-gui" while I'm eating.
"Gui gui", now is it?
Yuki-chan is particular about balance, right?
Yup, that's it.
Well, then how do you eat curry rice?
Do you eat it mixing the curry and the rice?
No, I don't mix anything, but I put it all in a balance.
I just go for the mixing.
How's Kona-chan?
It all depends on the curry...
I just might mix it when I add sauce or a fresh egg.
Sauce to curry?
It's pretty good.
Do you add sauce to sunny-side-up eggs, too?
Nope, soy sauce is for sunny-side-up eggs.
Hee, I add mayonnaise on it.
Not onto a boiled egg, but onto fried eggs?
Un! You know, mayonnaise pretty much fits egg dishes.
Do you add it to curry, too?
Un!
tn. Gyuudon - a dish with a bowl of rice topped with cooked beef and sometimes vegetables
It's an "Off course!" to white rice, but to gyuudon*, too.
It fits with well with sweet sauce.
Oyako-don is delicious with it, too.
The egg and and the chicken are the parent-and-child, right?
So, when I put the egg-based mayonnaise on it...
...I'm calling it the shinseki-don*.
tn. Shinseki-don = "Relatives-don"
And then...
...the nattou* I couldn't handle well went pretty good with mayonnaise!
tn. nattou - a traditional Japanese food made from fermented soybeans, sticky and has a strong smell.
Ugh! I cannot imagine it!
Huwa! But adding mayonnaise to half-boiled egg could be the tastiest!
At our place even fried eggs are half-boiled.
It's my father's preference...
...and he likes to suck the yellow of an egg.
And so he says if you frie them over he can't do the chuu-chuu.
How do you eat yakitori?
tn. yakitori - "grilled chicken", in a way
What do you mean by "how"?
Do you eat them from the stick...
...or do you first take them off with chopsticks?
Oh, yes...
When I eat one by myself, I eat them from the stick...
...but when eating with others I take them off.
Oh yeah, isn't it awkward when just one is left?
Oh yes, it is so hard to eat the last one, isn't it?
Time goes on as no-one eats it...
...somehow dried, really changed into unappetising shape,...
...and no-one lies a hand on it,...
...but when a staff member comes to take it, saying something like "Hey, we will still eat that!"...
...and in the end like leaving without eating it...
That's a bit wasteful, isn't it...
Somehow I feel pity...
Ah! In yakiniku, you know...
tn. yakiniku - Korean barbequed beef
The black burnt meat stuck in the net is a pity too, right?
Yakiniku should be eaten with frying and dealing, so it's a pretty busy thing, isn't it?
The meat with green onion is particulary fast to burn, so it's even more hurried, isn't it?
Oh yes, even if you turn it over even once it's already burnt.
"Turn it over"?
Negitanshi?
Yeah.
You shouldn't turn over Negitanshi.
Eh? Is that so?
But if you turn it over the green onion on the top will fall, will it not?
Ah, that way...
If you fry it with one side as-is, it will naturally get fryed on the other side.
Ah, so it was... I will do so from now on-tto.
'Cause you never should turn that over...
Is that so...
Yeah.
Ah!
By the way, the fat side or the thin side - which is the head of a choco cornet?
He?!
A bit insulting...
Nowadays there's a lot confinement incidents around.
Telling girls to call them "My master" and the likes of that...
Isn't that just...
from playing too much eroge than from the progress of moralities?
A common pattern in games, too.
Isn't that just about you, ain't it?...
...but wait a sec...
Why do you know details about adult games, second-grade high-schooler!?
Lucky Star!
Always up in the charts, that's amazing.
Eh?
Miyuki-san, do you have any weaknesses?
Even though it's embarrasing...
...I sometimes fall into thoughts,
or should I say just "faze out"...
Something like cutting a finger while using a slicer...
...or tripping on my own feet while in haste...
...or having the end of my bag end up between the doors of a train...
Huwaa!
Miyuki-san, that's not a 'weakness', but a moe element.
Eh... 'moe'?
For those who're weak for clumsiness.
What kind of image was made in Kona-chan's head?
Why's Miyuki-san wearing glasses although you're a classy looker?
Only a particular group of people goes after that.
"Go after"...
If we leave the popularity aside, don't you try contacts?
Glasses seem to make vision worse, too...
Well, it's a bit embarassing as I'm a high-schooler already...
...that, I...
...am scared!
Of contact lenses...
Or should I say putting something in eyes...
I can't even open eyes in water...
Shit! Disarmingly cute, this person. Is she a natural-type?
Huh? Isn't that Miyuki-san?
Hm?
Could she be coming for an examination? For the contacts.
Miyuki-san could always be better like that.
It looked like it hurt...
She's a natural memento, ain't she.
Hm? Kagami's resting today because of cold?
Un, but at least it doesn't look like influenza.
I'm a stupid one so I don't have to be worried of influenza and stuff, though.
He-he, you get well fast from cold, but even influenza is OK?
He? Cold and influenza are different?
And I was sure that it was a bad version of cold...
I-I think it's not that but...
...when you say it like that I'm beginning to lose my confidence in it...
Eh? The difference of cold and influenza?
Un-un.
Let's see... Influenza is a virus-based one, but...
...there's a high fever, a lot of muscular pain and bodily symptoms...
...with the possibility of complications, too.
Meanwhile cold consists of heavy throat irritation and dripping nose.
Fever doesn't rise that high.
Additionally the detailed symptoms differ, too.
Hmm...
Because of that these two are different diseases.
Got it...
But... well, there are many similar parts in them, so...
...it's not impossible to call it a scaled-up version of cold...
Oh, I understood!
Kona-chan, what happened - why such a difficult face?
No, nothing in particular, but...
...there was something in the conversation this morning that stayed in my mind.
Eh? About cold and influenza?
The thing that you didn't really point at the fact that I'm stupid...
You're mistaken! It's not like that!
"Konata-chan, welcome!"
"Did you come to see onee-chan?"
"Ahh, thank you for coming!"
"It's my pleasure. Excuse me..."
Hee, Kagami's got a surprisingly cute face while sleeping...
What the!? What did you come to do?!
Hee, woke up woke up...
He!? Came to see me?
You did... especially for me...
That's right.
B-but it would be bad if you'd get it too. I'd even be thankful for the idea.
Chi, what's this... I'm a bit happy, aren't I...
She might be worried because there's a new virus around and stuff...
I always thought she thought only about anime and games, but...
...I am a bit touched, aren't I?
Hmph?
You know, I wanted to see the homework we got earlier...
...and I got to see a good sleeping face, so you don't have to worry.
Huh?! Go home!!
Kagamii! Miyuki-chan came to see you!
Unh... Yes.
Excuse me for entering...
Oh, I'm sorry for it being a holiday.
Are you OK with being up?
This is for getting better.
Thanks!
Mostly OK. The fever got lower after I took the medicine, too.
Here.
Oh, I'm so happy to get flowers and fruits!
Ah, take a seat.
Thank you very much.
I wanted to come as soon as possible with Izumi-san and all...
...but yesterday the circuimstances got a bit worse...
Oh it's OK, OK.
Ah, the documents from the school comittee's meetings...
I picked them all up for you.
Oh, thank you!
If only I could meet you without touching your health...
Yeah.
And, these are the budgetary estimates for the other clubs...
...and, after that... what was it...
Let me s...
Ah, if it would seem like I'd touch your health I will be going back...
"Going to see someone is like this after all, isn't it?"
Did something happen?
Actually yesterday Konata came over and...
It was just like I thought...
It could perhaps be consideration, Izumi-san- style.
Fooling around with the homework,
she could've been trying to get you more energetic.
The 'sleeping face' could be consideration without being too noisy,
an additional strenght-giver, it could be.
"Is this woman a saint?! I just can't visualize it like that..."
And now when I think about it...
Isn't Tsukasa-san here today?
Good morning...
Onee-chan, did you get into better condition today?
Just like that, living a life even more loose than the patient here.
You know, it's not always like this, but...
...today my going to bed was about how good the red rising sun is...
Ah! It's a bit late, but 'welcome'.
Ah, I understand that. I, too, have had problems getting up lately.
Y-yes, isn't that so? Lately everyone's sleepy, aren't they?
Yes it is, today it is especially warm, too.
Yes, just that - just that.
There's nothing you can do about it.
The last vacation was warm too, wasn't it?
Yes.
When I opened my eyes it was already evening!
I pretty much spent that day sleeping.
You should take rest when you can.
Eventually I was in a pajama all that day.
Ah, now, too? E-he-he-he...
Eh? What you're wearing now is a pajama?
Ah? Yes, it is.
It's really cute, doesn't even look like a pajama.
Really?
Yes.
Could it be OK if I would just stay like this?
Yes. It looks like you could even go outside like that.
Could I even go to a conbini?
np. conbini (konbini) - Convenience Store (like 7/11 or Lawson's)
Somehow the half-asleep follow seems endless...
"Strange gain..."
"No... that's not it..."
"Today's bra has more padding in it than usually, so it's got as much more weight in it."
"Oh yes... how many grams was it? If I could minus that off..."
"Ah... It ended..."
"A failure. I forgot about the examination and...
...put on character panties..."
"Embarassing!"
"Not getting any longer!"
Oh god damn it with you! One-of-a-kind going out with a happy face!
Ossu!
I came!
Onee-chan!
I thought of unfarity, but...
Kagami comes here to play pretty often...
..., don't you have any friends at your class?
Don't drag me to the same pool with you!
Are you trying to start a fight?
Damn. And I thought you were left out for certain.
Try to worry more about sociability-zero yourself than about others.
If it's about that there's no problem.
Even if I look like this I have almost 100 friends...
...and my Social transaction skills are pretty high...
...and I attend parties every night.
Huh?!
Bringing back the shininess of a crystal with friends in order to protect the world from being destroyed...
or saving abducted princ...
Te, that's game talk, right?!
That person really didn't look at the dungeon, now did he...
Who?
In-game friend talk, isn't it?
Yeah. Anyways, a fighter character, but...
"I want to pump my combat skills, so I'll go to a monster-infested place to train." were his parting words.
Hmm...
When I asked another person,...
...I was told that he was sitting around on the savanna of relaxation.
Wonder if he's OK.
Secluded by himself, everyone's worried 'bout him.
Secluding himself in a game?
I don't know for sure...
..., but if you look at the login stat you can see that he's always online playing, too.
Secluding yourself both in reality and virtually?!
Well, it is the same person doing...
By the way, Tsukasa. How did you get into friends with Konata?
Tsukasa was about to be dragged along by a big, suspicious foreigner...
...but I stepped in alone...
...with my pridal aquatic bird style...
...and releasing the whirlwind devotion on him I saved her.
Why does it always turn into game talk in the middle?
Well, actually I only moved my hand-to-hand- combateer arm.
I don't know about sudden violence, but you do have good points, don't you.
Actually I was being asked way by a foreigner...
...and in a gibberish non-understanding situation Kona-chan...
You're completely minus!
What's with that winner face?!
"Now this time has come again..."
Is there something?
Nope. Just that the pro baseball league has started...
Kona-chan, don't you like watching sports?
You look like good at sports and that way it feels like you could like such things.
Still if it gets extended the later programs will be late...
...and the recordings of new anime will get messy...
...except for amateurs, a whole program can get smashed.
You just hate it when you lose something you like, don't you?
When does Kagami eat the strawberry on a strawberry cake?
Eh, why?
I just thought you were the type to leave most liked things to the end.
Surely I eat the favourites at the end...
...but it depends on the strawberry...
Do you fry both sides of negi tanshi?
Negi tanshi?!
Hmm... It gets fried fast by itself but if you do both it's much faster ain't it?
That's bad! The green onion will fall, won't it?
Don't you add the green onion after you fry?
But that way it doesn't get fried, does it?
But isn't it a condiment from the beginning?
She doesn't understand, does she...
Well, they're both ways, right?
Ah!
Which side of the choco cornet is head to you: the thin side or the fat side?
The fat one?
U, the same with me.
He, really?
Well from which do you eat?
Don't you hold the thin side and eat the remaining chocolate?
Heee...
Un.
Have you made any other real friends besides us?
Well I did have a very close friend while in junior high...
Hee, so you did have...
I haven't been in contact with him in a while, I wonder how's he doing...
But he did write 'magician' into the 'What is your dream?' field in the graduation paper.
A partner in type, after all?!
Lucky Star!
Lucky Channel!
Good luckyy!
Well, started at last, Lucky Channel!
The first time on television!
Gyaa!
The first 'good day' on television!
I'm your navigator Kogami Akira!
Se!
Ah, Shiraishi-ssu
Who?
First lie!
This person is the one who's going to help Akira,
...Shiraishi Minoru!
Bonkopoboon!
Aah, howd'd...
I am working under Akira-sama. Shiraishi Minoru.
Thanks.
Shiraishi-san, you're really tense.
As we're already on TV come out with more power!
Try it!
Excuse me for not getting used...
And so, it's pretty immediate, but congradulation mails from viewers have already come!
Un, yes...
Well, a message from Berrykou Daisukikko-san from Oosaka Prefecture...
"Congratulations on getting on TV, Lucky Channel!"
A thank you!
But there's a question for Akira-san.
"Akira-san is an idol phamed by many and me,
...but the fee of idols is about how much?"
"Please tell me."
The fee?
Yes...
A very direct question this is, isn't it?
You know, what the hell will you do with just knowing 'bout it?
Akira-sama!..
Well, if you want to know as much I'll tell you.
To tell you the truth it's high to the ten.
There can be some low fees in itself, but the kick-back at the office...
I'm still living with my parents, so it's not like I really know how many %s I'm taking home.
On top of that I'm doing this from 3-years-old...
...so it's all in my parent's account, right.
It's not like they give me something else than pocket money.
And that's with the worst sums, too.
Ah. And as I remember my mom just bought some damn brand bag...
...that was from the TV money, was it...
IT'S NOT ANY JOKE!
And she speaks like I'm some Cinderella!
Just a bit...
Just a bit ago papa was working his ass off 'for living expenses'!!! Couldn't it be that I'm getting more in the end, huh!?
Oh, this is troublesome...
It's already the time to part.
Akira is lonely...
And so...
On this part of the programme we answer questions, words and programme-related comments from the viewers...
Send a lot of 'em, PLEASE!
A word from Shiraishi-san, too, PLEASE!
And I ask for your love and patience on the next time.
SEE YOU AGAIN!
And are you serious 'bout getting on the show itself?
E? Where did that talk come from?
Karaoke by the four of us is pretty rare, isn't it?
I rarely even come to such places, so...
Hey hey! We've only got two hours so sing, sing all!
Even if you don't hurry as much there's some time!
Somehow my heart is beating...
It's really fun, you feel refreshed after singing, too!
Hey, where's the catalogue?
Catalogue?
Yeah, the catalogue!
A catalogue?
Hey, the one with the numbers of songs.
Ah! This?
Here.
And so I'll start!
Huwa! Fast! Already three songs in...
It's wasteful if you don't add a lot, ain't it?
A-a-a, ya kisu kisu kisu...
What's up with this song?!
宇宙鉄人キョーダイン!
Space Ironman Kyo-dain!
The first one HAS to be this, right?
I don't know it at all...
ダ ダ ダダダダ ダダ星の地球強奪ロボット軍
Da da dadadada dada, The Earth Pillaging Force of the stars...
Kona-chan, try your best!
Hey! The volume's loud!
Lower the damn volume!
と飛べ 兄貴 スカイゼル
...and fly my brother Skyzel!
Why does she know a song like this?!
走れ 弟 グランゼル
Run, my little brother - Granzel!
スクラム 鉄の腕と腕
Scrum, the hands of steel!
バチッと火花の大銀河
And that Great Milky Way, full of sparkles!
GO GO ジェット! GO GO カー!
Go-go jet! Go-go car!
宇宙（ヤァ！）鉄人（オゥ！）キョーダイン! ヨ～！
The Space (yaa!) Ironman (ou!) Kyo-dain!　yo～!
And, what's about the next Lucky Star?
I'm Konata.
I'm sleepy...
Why am I so sleepy even though I slept well the earlier night?
There's no meaning in sleeping more, is there?
Next Time: The Effort and The Result.
Look forward to it!