Yoshimizu Kagami
Theatre
Now, let'ssu begin yoo!
It's gonna come now...
Fungaa!
Now start out already!
曖昧3センチ
Aimai 3 senchi
Unclear 3 centimeters...
そりゃぷにってことかい？ちょっ!
Sorya punitte koto kai? cho!
Is that a puni? Waitasec!
らっぴんぐが制服…
Rappingu ga seifuku…
The uniform's the wrapping…
だぁぁ不利ってことない　ぷ。
Daa furitte koto nai　Pu.
Hey, there's no disadvantage in that, yeah.
がんばっちゃ♥やっちゃっちゃ
Ganbaccha♥yacchaccha
Try your best♥do your thing-cha,
そんときゃーっち&Releaseぎョッ
son tokyaacchi & ririisu gyo
at that time, well, catch & release, gyo!
汗っ、々っ
A-se, a-se!
In the sweaty, sweaty...
の谷間にDarlin'darlin'F R E E Z E!!
No taniai ni daarin daarin furiiーzu!
cleavage darlin' darlin' FREEZE!!
なんかダるー、なんかデるー
NankaDAruuー, nankaDEruー
Somewhat lazy..., something's coming out...
あいしテるー
AishiTEruuー
I love you...
あれ一個が違ってるんるー
Are ikko ga chigatterunruー
One of those is different, ruー.
なやみン坊ー 高鉄棒 おいしん簿ー
NayamiNbouー Koutetsubou oishinboー
A worrywart, high horizontal bar - an ever-lengthening list...
いーかげんにシナサイ
Iikagen ni SHINASAI
Now get reasonable!
飛んでったアイツの火照るカラダって
Tondetta AITSU no hoteru KARADAtte
The burning body of who flied away right now is...
所謂ふつーのおにゃのコ
Iwayuru futsuu no onya no KO
what is called a "usual girl".
驚いた、
Odoroita,
I'm surprised,
あたしだけ? 豚骨ハリガネおかわりダー!!!!
atashi dake? tonkotsu harigane okawari daaー!!!!
Only me? I get an extra portion of tonkotsu with super hard noodlesー!!!!
BON-BONおーえん団
BON-BON oーendan
Bon-bon cheering team.
Let's get! Cherry pie
Let's get! Cherry pie.
RAN-RAN　かんげー会
Ranraan　kangeーikai
RAN-RAN, welcoming party.
Look up! せんせーしょん
Look up! Senseーshon
Look up! Sensation.
はい！　存在感・・小惑星
Haai　Sonzaikan　tenten　shouwakusei
Yes, feeling of being here・・meteor!
ぶつかって溶けました　呆然　大いに歌ってシレンジャー
Butsukatte tokemashita　bouzen　ooi ni utatte shirenjaー
Got melt from the collision, dumbfounded and singing a lot, "Shiranger!"
もっていけ!
Motte ike!
Take and go!
最後に笑っちゃうのはあたしのはず
Saigo ni waracchau no wa atashi no hazu
The last one laughing should be me,
セーラーふくだからです
Seeraa fuku dakara desu
because it's a sailor fuku.
←結論
←Ketsuron
←Conclusion.
月曜日なのに！
Getsuyoubi nanoni!
Even if it's monday!
機嫌悪いのどうするよ？
Kigen warui no dou suru yo？
What will you do with that bad mood?
夏服がいいのです←キャ？ワ！イイｖ
Natsufuku ga ii no desu←KYA?WA!IIv
I want my summer uniform←It!Is!Cute!
接近3ピクト するまでってちゅーちょだ　やん☆
Sekkin san pikuto, suru madette chuーcho da　yan☆
Getting closer's in three paces, I'll hesitate until you do 'it' Oh☆
頑張って　張り切って
Ganbatte,　harikitte
Try your best, be on high,
My Darlin'darlin' P L E A S E!!
Mai daarin daarin puriizu
my darlin' darlin' please!
~Fifteenth Concert~
Symphony No. 9
in D minor, Op. 125
~Fifteenth Concert~
Symphony No. 9
in D minor, Op. 125
~Fifteenth Concert~
Symphony No. 9
in D minor, Op. 125
Miyuki-san...
Do you have anything to do at the end of the year?
Ah, Izumi-san...
There is a festival, and I thought how you would think about such...
A year-end festival?
Seems fun...
Yeah, it's very fun!
Could it be something like the snow festival?
But I will go to our countryside house...
If I remember correctly,
you used the same pretext to invite me in summer, as well...
Kagami-san...
If you translate what Konata says,
it's "Participation in the Comic Market as shopping personnel"
When I went there in summer I was really surprised...
I didn't lie!
A festival's a festival!
It's difficult alone, boring as well...
Let's Go To
The Festival
Hey! It's me, Izumi.
Ah, Konata?
I'm writing New Year's Cards right now, but were you still mourning?
We didn't get a Nengashitsurei, though...
tn: Nengashitsurei - A card, sent out to inform others that a person in family has died, so impolite New Year's cards are not sent...
Mm... No, but why do you suddenly ask?
Well, you know...
Weren't you absent from school because of mourning once this year?
Well...
Ahh, yes! But it's OK!
Don't tell me that you used such a manga-like way again..!
Sparkly-sparkl...
I was in the middle of house-cleaning right now.
I see...
Well, long calls are bad as well, so I'll hang up now.
Yeah.
Bye then!
Yeah...
I wonder why...
Even though you really want to clean up if there're other inconvenient things to do,
why does it suddenly become so troublesome once you decide to start, I wonder.
Konata, keep your breaks moderate as well...
Was it called Comike?
first timer
I did hear it's a big festival, but they sure start early in the morning.
I'm really looking forward to it!
second time
So she hasn't been informed at all, right...
Pitiful her...
regular customer
Oh no, she'll get used to it soon.
Tsukasa, just so you know: That event is really tiresome...
in many ways...
Are you OK with that?
Yeah, well I'll try my best then!
I wonder if you really understand...
However the typical people are gradually beginning to increase...
Alright! This line will soon change to green light!
Oneechan, it's kind of scary here...
That's why I told you...
Normal Participants
Corporative exhibitors
Authorized personnel
Circle Members
Ah yes... I must explain you your parts while we're here...
"Parts"?
Here, take this.
It's the shopping list.
After you've gotten in,
separate once and go around the circles according to this map.
You two go around 1 to 3 of the East Hall...
as I will go around 4 to 6.
However, be aware...
If you don't follow this red-marked route...
You might get caught into the lines of the doujinshi circles next to the wall...
and become unable to move.
Especially here and here!
If you get caught up in the crowd in this area, more than 30 minutes will be lost.
Why do we have to get so desperate?
Don't mind such trivial things...
The circles marked green are OK to pass by even during afternoon.
They ensured to put enough armament aside,
so there is almost no danger of "sold out".
During morning only think about patrolling the red-marked circles!
S means a new publication, K means a quarterly publication!
When you're not sure,
a quarterly one is OK, too - just gather and buy them all!
Here! This is the live ammo!
It's no good if you get confused when counting, so take them.
That Cafe au lait is as the supply for the time being...
remember to drink it once per half an hour.
The final rendezvous place is here, exactly at 1300 hours.
I will wait for 15 minutes, but beware -
if you don't show up I'll search at the sick bay.
That's all! Any questions?
You... you only show fierce intellect and passion at times like this...
Please do not run!
Get over there, you idiot!
We would like to limit the purchases of the new publication to four books per customer!
Please co-operate!
Ahh, excuse me, but this is A-92, right?
Yes, it is.
Ah, the new publications one piece each?
That'll be 1000 yen!
Yes, and?
Well, I wonder which of these are your new publications?
Yes, the newest ones are this and this...
Both of them cost 500 yen.
Oh, thanks for your hard work!
Were the sweets I gave you tasty?
Oh, that's nice.
Well... Three pieces of each, please.
Here, we appreciate your support!
"Nuru-nuru Brigade Leader" and "Naughty Captain", right?
That'll be 3000 yen.
Only these please!
Yes, that'll be 4500 yen.
Here.
Thank you very much!
TomDon...
I will head for the next point...
Well... This is the East Hall...
and the north side should be here, so...
Jus...
Excuse me, I am heading over ther–
I have pretty much visited the bigger places, right...
Well, the next circle is...
Curse
Just a bit...
Gauron is... Sousuke...
This is...
How do you like it...
That'll be 500 yen...
Well... That's no stimulus for me...!
She came! It's her! The "Legendary Girl A"!
Tsk! Calm down! If you fidget, you'll be suspicious!
Yes...
But there's a weird jinx...
that most places that girl buys a book from grow rapidly into major circles!
"Don't fidget." you say? That's impossible you know!
Yeah, I understand.
That's why we made a book with such effort!
So that she would buy it!
Yeah, that was so...
Even it was the end of the year,
we tried our best even by taking a leave from the store...
Surely this year... this year...
May I?
Ah, please!
Well, how do you like it..?
That live scene, for example, I drew it with rather great effort!
Hmm... Not really...
Thankyourullymuch!
Don't cry! Surely next summer...
Err, excuse me...
Yes, what happened?
Where would the place called "P-61" be?
P? Wasn't B around the East Hall?
Where is that East Hall?
This is the West Hall.
If you'd like to go to the East Hall,
line up in the queue over there and get to the upper level.
And how long would that take?
Oh, well, right now it could take about one hour.
"Please wait for a moment"
Ohh, no more...
I'm sorry, Kona-chan.
I just finally came back from the place called West Hall...
Once you get flushed with the crowd, you really get lost at this event...
As I was lined up for the restroom an hour passed...
Well, as I thought the menu was too hard for first-timers...
so let's go around together merrily during the afternoon.
So you still think about going around..?
But, you know...
Since the hall was changed to this Ariake Hall everything became so comfortable...
Back then, during the time of Harumi Hall...
there were only two convenience stores in the vicinity, as well...
The Harumi Hall?
Yeah, the last time it was held there was about twelve years ago, now was it?
Wait! How old were you then?!
I was about five-year-old,
had my father take me there.
We always stayed at Hotel Urashima for two nights.
It was during the first Summer-Comike,
the 2nd level of the annex was unbelievable...
the mass of sweat vaporized...
Huh?!
and formed a cloud that wafted...
It's enough already, I don't want to listen to it...
But as the hall was changed to Ariake many things got more convenient, as well.
Maybe it's because of the event getting large-scale, but...
it's really sad that many young attendees think of themselves as customers...
Even though it used to be an event that we all made...
I'm sorry, but even though you're telling very efficiently,
I can't understand it at all...
Kogami Akira
Apology
Kogami Akira is
absent due to
sudden illness.
I didn't come during summer, but they did have places like this, too...
Yeah, but I think the best goods are already sold out.
Hmm...
Ah! It's Nagato, Nagato!
Huh?
The person who did Nagato is selling!
Here. Thank you very much for your purchase.
So what is it?
No, thank you very...
What's this with Haruhi goods selling out?!
Coming here has no meaning if there are no Nagato telephone cards!
Uwah... The worst...
"Please calm down! We have a lot of other things as..."
Like I just said... such people are increasing...
"Like I know! I'd like to swing this at you!"
My apologies, dear customer!
It is really regrettable, but we have already stopped the sales of the limited edition goods!
Eh... Is that true?
Yes it is!
Well, even if you come at a time like this...
It's a pity, but if you don't wait from morn  -
You idiot!
W-what do you...
"To satisfy an unlucky customer with all our strength!"...
What are you doing, forgetting about that motto?
How-however... at this store there are but leftovers!
Did you say "leftovers"..!?
There is a fortune in left things!
Something that can't be made even with the selling works or moe like that!
This Comike is a revolt that brings out the genuine value of things!
Isn't it especially now,
with all limited goods slaughtered, the time for the real battle between the display booths?!
U-understandan...
Well then, try to suggest something to this customer!
Something you think is a true treasure!
Aren't there any weapons...
Wh-What about this one!?
Not! It's going to be this!
Well, you know...
Even though Nagato and all are on hyper-sales, this must be it, right?
Seeing that Koizumi is selling, too...
You're annoying! This is left from three years ago!
Although the Ma'am Captain was sold out the same day!
And thus, please check this Kyon!
No! This Sousuke is our recommendation!
No, I just wanted to get the Saikou Hikkoko-chan one...
You idiots!
You... you're... Director Takahashi!
Direc-
I, indeed, am director Takahashi!
tor
I've listened to your talk!
To present customers a new valuable is widely enough for today!
Hmm... They're always on high tension there...
Ah, so it's like that...
But I cannot overlook such selfish manner of trying to...
So it was like that...
knowingly sell unpopular characters!
No, both of them are leads...
This is a free fansub
Not for sale, rent, or auction
Oneechan, I'm sleepy...
I am sleepy too, you know...
Helping at home right after we got away from Ariake...
I wonder why they're having such an event on New Year's Eve...
Kagami, Tsukasa! Newyear!
Oah...
Kona-chan, happy new year!
You're really energetic, even though you were on such an uproar since morning.
It's cold and I thought you had something else to do...
Ohh, well - that is true,
but New Year's Day is like a map for the year,
so going for the first shrine-visit
in order to keep the spirits for the new year would be nice...
Hee, isn't that admirable...
No, said dad...
Hello~
I feel that suddenly something's not right...
The divinity of Shrine Maidens!
Things like this... and things like that...
We said our prayers!
Yes, welcome back.
Did you two do something like prayers?
Now that you mention it oneesan was just praying for something eagerly.
St... You say unneeded things again!
I'm not doing it so eagerly...
I only thought that it'd be nice...
to be in the same class as Miyuki and Tsukasa at least this year...
Hmmm...
Oneechan, what about Kona-chan?
Kagami, you know, you really are quite cute like that...
You're annoying!
And I didn't want to say it because you'd make fun of me like that!
And that resistance is something as well...
Got a problem with that?!
Only oneechan was always in another class, right..
I wonder if I'm hated by Kuroi-sensei...
I will pray to be in the same class with oneechan, too!
Tsukasa...
Oh no, no - we must have Kagami put into another class...
W-Why is that!?
Well, you know,
I can borrow things when I forget some,
and even if I copy your homework I don't get caught.
If Kagami came too, my grades level would fall.
If that's so, go into a different class by yourself!
The other day...
The other day, you know, Sebastian invited me to try those clothes on...
Schoolgirls... are so good...
How to use the water
for washing hands
First wash
the left hand.
Next, wash
the right hand.
Last, take some water
into the left hand and
rinse the mouth.
Wouldn't you get fortune slips this year, as well?
Oh, yes... if I'm here already...
Bad luck
Very good luck
So early in the new year, that's a very good omen...
Ohh, yes...
This year I've already seen good things, it seems like it'll become a good year.
It's OK... If now is the worst, the luck will only raise from now on...
There are good things.
Yeah, what should I say... things are as you say they are, thanks...
If it's a burden, would you like to tie it to a tree branch to divert the evil?
Yeah, I'll do so...
Ah! They're all full!
Ah, here as well!
Ah, found one found one...
I wonder if this is the thing called bad luck...
I guess you're right...
Whether good things will happen is just a matter of...
the persons effort after all.
Fortune slips are just for trying out your luck, in the end.
That might be so, but that's not a line for someone who is doing it...
Should I try to collect them all from "very good luck" to "very bad luck"?
Are they some kind of trading cards for you, huh?!
With even some secrets in the mix...
Just what kind of a fortune would a secret in fortune slips be?!
Something like super-bad luck!
Huh?! To the minus side of things?!
I'd rather not get that!
That's where, you know,
you give special goods to people who bought them all and it'll be OK!
No, as we don't have such in the first place...
Which reminds me, I just thought about it as I saw a big 'kagamimochi'...
tn: kagamimochi - round rice cakes offered to the gods at New Year
Like this.
Might Kagami's name come from that?
Oh, well that's not wrong.
The circle of a kagamimochi symbolizes a mirror,...
and since ancient times it's said that gods dwelve in mirrors.
So, it seems that I was named Kagami to become a child...
that would be able to experience the blessings of god.
Also there is the meaning of household harmony in the circular form.
Even though the origins and all are mysterious,
she ended up grown pretty realistic, didn't she...
tn: These three sentences make up the meaning "Squid is... g.. ood" ("Ikaga? U~ Mai."; "Ika ga umai.")
How do you like them..?
Hmm...
Here.
There're really a lot of people who came to worship...
Well, it is New Year, so...
Although this is not one of the famous places...
I wonder how many of these people here came for the shrine maidens like my father...
Does she think so?!
Such people are almost inexistent!
Probably...
Afresh, congratulations upon the New Year.
Please treat me well this year, too.
Hoy, regards.
Happy New Year!
This is Duuda!
Just look at this beautiful scenery, it is just great, fantastic, now isn't it?
Now, look here,
there are many, so many, so pretty flowers blooming here..!
DOOOOH!
Daddy, would you like tea?
Oh, yes, sure...
Here.
Thank you for that.
Daddy, would you like to play a game?
Daddy, would you like New Year dishes?
Daddy..!
And like that...
he seems to like how I fidgety come to him until I get my New Year's Money...
I got tired...
Was it so... Your place has really good relationships, doesn't it?
And, since I just safely got my New Year's money,
I'm thinking about going to GAMERS right now.
Is that... so...
The fact that there are no such stores on the countryside is the drawback, isn't it?
To make matters worse my money is limited,
and then there's the train fee and all that...
I would like one store at our place, too.
But aren't many shops offering internet order nowadays as well?
So isn't there such a place doing that as well?
Oh, you don't understand, do you...
Well, you do get the points even by internet order,
but to go to the shop yourself and walk around...
looking for unexpected finds is the fun part, isn't it?
What's that!? Aren't you fully ready to use a lot of cash!?
About now the radish has taken all of it into itself, and you'll have to cut it all - all...
I wonder why this is called a Pochibukuro?
Aah, it seems that it comes from the words pochitto and koreppochi,
meaning a bag where you put your change.
Pochitto is from Kansai, and koreppochi is a word used around Kantou.
Congradulations on the New Year, Takara speaking.
Ah, Miyuki-san? NewYear!
And so, I'd like to ask about the origin of the word "pochibukuro"...
Konata, let's believe daddy sometimes...
"Pochibukuro", now is it?
Yeah.
If I remember right, it originates from the words pochitto and koreppochi...
Couldn't you at least ask in a place that I can't see...
and has the meaning of a pouch into which you put...
Well, let's do the first greeting of the New Year to my friends in the game!
And so it was terrible.  In the end, I even missed the chance to buy those Haruhi goods...
gatongo: Don't you cry!
A friend konakona has logged in.
gotongo: Oh?
konakona: NewYear!
yamanka: Ou, NewYear!
gatongo: Happy lololol
At last I got in. I was so busy from the end of the year, uknow
Your friend nanakon has logged in.
Ah! It's sensei!
Sensei, congradulations on the new year.
Yo, NewYear!
Please treat me well this year, too.
Yahyah, treat me well
Should I ask...
Sensei seems to somehow always be on,
I wonder if she doesn't have anything else to do?
It means that she surely has no boyfriend...
Please visit us at
http://www.wing2.jp/~jeeb
#jeeb@irc.rizon.net
LUCKY CHANNEL!
G-Good lucky!
It's me, the assistant of Akira-sama, Shiraishi Minoru!
As a fast thing, Lucky Channel is already in its 12th time today!
Ah... This sea is the hell...
Err...
Well... as you can see,
Akira-sama was supposed to be on the main program this time,
but just before it her physical condition fell...
Eh?
Yes, it seems to be a cold,
but I put up a life-size pop of Akira-sama,
so if you would carefully review it...
Eh? Ah?! Hey! Akira-sama!
Aah! And so, since this time Akira-sama seems to be very tired as well...
I'd like to end it around here!
And so, everybody - bye-nii!
Argh... I shouldn't get on high spirits? There's no way I'd be...!
Eh?! "I'll let you hear the real "Motteke! Sailor-fuku""?
"So look forward to it!"?
"If you don't watch the next time as well, in the name of the Mars, I will scold you!"?
Fumof!
Main Translation: JEEB
Translation Checking: xbe
That was pretty exciting, wasn't it?
It was fun.
Indeed...
Ah, no-one's put in a song!
Isn't it your turn if we go by them?
Especially at these times you should put some in!
Timing: JEEB
Snoopy007
Typesetting: Snoopy007
Al79
Encoder: heedly
QC: ansonyyp
I hadn't decided...
I wonder which one I should take...
Should I search as well?
Opening Karaoke: JEEB
Ending Karaoke: Snoopy007
Ah, there's a menu as well!
Yeah.
So you can even eat here, am I right?
Yeah, that's right.
As I just sang that old song, the flow's bad...
I should've taken it later...
What's that "flow"?
How should I say...
Well, aren't there? Those ways to up the feelings to sing.
I don't really understand...
I wonder if I could sing this?
おーい、ゴッドマン！
Ooi, goddoman！
Hey, Godman!
聞こえるかーい？
Kikoeru kaai？
Can you hear me?
They even have a tamborin and stuff here.
おーい、ゴッドマン！
Ooi, Goddoman！
Hey, Godman!
You can shake this to up the mood.
飛んでこい！
Tonde koi！
Fly over here!
Ah, Yuki-chan, let's try this out.
Ah, this is good...
Yes! It's this!
An anime song is OK too now, so just input it!
For the time being I tried to put in a song that'll up the mood!
Aah!
You'll be able to sing if it's this, right?
Yes!
I somewhat know it...
負けな・・・
Makena・・・
Don't lo...
Ah, got it wrong...
This video was brought to you by JEEB
With Q/C from STAR
ふとした瞬間に・・・
Futoshita shunkan ni・・・
On the whim of the moment...
And so, the next Lucky Star is?
It's me, Miyuki.
When describing something being in the front...
with an overwhelming lead,
there are some times when the word "dantotsu" is used.
This seems to be an abbreviation of "the absolute top",
and, it seems that, the first who actually used this word in an article was,
indeed, the person who had, literally,
won the previous mayoral elections in Tokyo with a "dantotsu".
"
Next Time: A Delicious Day
Look forward to it!