Yoshimizu
Kagami
Theatre
Ah, the B class of third year?
Kuroi-sensei!
Yeah, yeah...
曖昧3センチ
Aimai 3 senchi
Unclear 3 centimeters...
そりゃぷにってことかい？ちょっ!
Sorya punitte koto kai? cho!
Is that a puni? Waitasec!
らっぴんぐが制服…
Rappingu ga seifuku…
The uniform's the wrapping…
だぁぁ不利ってことない　ぷ。
Daa furitte koto nai　Pu.
Hey, there's no disadvantage in that, yeah.
がんばっちゃ♥やっちゃっちゃ
Ganbaccha♥yacchaccha
Try your best♥do your thing-cha,
そんときゃーっち&Releaseぎョッ
son tokyaacchi & ririisu gyo
at that time, well, catch & release, gyo!
汗っ、々っ
A-se, a-se!
In the sweaty, sweaty...
の谷間にDarlin'darlin'F R E E Z E!!
No tanima ni daarin daarin furiiーzu!
cleavage darlin' darlin' FREEZE!!
なんかダるー、なんかデるー
NankaDAruuー, nankaDEruー
Somewhat lazy..., something's coming out...
あいしテるー
AishiTEruuー
I love you...
あれ一個が違ってるんるー
Are ikko ga chigatterunruー
One of those is different, ruー.
なやみン坊ー 高鉄棒 おいしん簿ー
NayamiNbouー Koutetsubou oishinboー
A worrywart, high horizontal bar - an ever-lengthening list...
いーかげんにシナサイ
Iikagen ni SHINASAI
Now get reasonable!
飛んでったアイツの火照るカラダって
Tondetta AITSU no hoteru KARADAtte
The burning body of who flew away right now is...
所謂ふつーのおにゃのコ
Iwayuru futsuu no onya no KO
what is called a "usual girl".
驚いた、
Odoroita,
I'm surprised,
あたしだけ? 豚骨ハリガネおかわりダー!!!!
atashi dake? tonkotsu harigane okawari daaー!!!!
Only me? I get an extra portion of tonkotsu with super hard noodlesー!!!!
BON-BONおーえん団
BON-BON oーendan
Bon-bon cheering team.
Let's get! Cherry pie
Let's get! Cherry pie.
RAN-RAN　かんげー会
Ranraan　kangeーikai
RAN-RAN, welcoming party.
Look up! せんせーしょん
Look up! Senseーshon
Look up! Sensation.
はい！　存在感・・小惑星
Haai　Sonzaikan　tenten　shouwakusei
Yes, feeling of being here・・meteor!
ぶつかって溶けました　呆然　大いに歌ってシレンジャー
Butsukatte tokemashita　bouzen　ooi ni utatte shirenjaー
Got melted by the collision, dumbfounded and singing a lot, "Shiranger!"
もっていけ!
Motte ike!
Take and go!
最後に笑っちゃうのはあたしのはず
Saigo ni waracchau no wa atashi no hazu
The last one laughing should be me,
セーラーふくだからです
Seeraa fuku dakara desu
because it's a sailor fuku.
←結論
←Ketsuron
←Conclusion.
月曜日なのに！
Getsuyoubi nanoni!
Even if it's monday!
機嫌悪いのどうするよ？
Kigen warui no dou suru yo？
What will you do with that bad mood?
夏服がいいのです←キャ？ワ！イイｖ
Natsufuku ga ii no desu←KYA?WA!IIv
I want my summer uniform←It?Is!Cute!
接近3ピクト するまでってちゅーちょだ　やん☆
Sekkin san pikuto, suru madette chuーcho da　yan☆
Getting closer's in three paces, I'll hesitate until you do 'it' Oh☆
頑張って　張り切って
Ganbatte,　harikitte
Try your best, be on high,
My Darlin'darlin' P L E A S E!!
Mai daarin daarin puriizu
my darlin' darlin' please!
Ah, Konata - Would you let me use your computer?
There was something I wanted to write down for the committee next week.
Alright...
Err...
"Even though lately there has been a bit of disorder..."
Although I've lately been a bit of a head nurse,
"...it seems like it'd be done in time,..."
I'm in the middle of mania transfer,
"...so we should pick up more speed..."
so I should dress more as a woman,
"...and, not only treasuring momentum, but also the mood of the committee..."
And, not only treasuring momentum,  but also
the mood of the committee,
tn: She has written fun'iki as fuinki, which the IME usually cannot change into the usual kanji. Here Konata has a joke on it inputted into the IME: "fuinki <- somehow cannot be converted"
"I would like to discuss the matter even further..."
I would like to discuss it frthr so that there would be no matters
Hey, wouldn't you tell me a bit about this PC?
Ha-ha-ha...
Another person's computer is something that's hard to use, Kagami...
A Subtle Line
After not checking it for two or three days, mail has megas piled up!
Ah, Konata, so, despite of your appearance, you do get a lot of mail?
Neesan, you put such awkward comments so bluntly...
They come, as you say...
It could be that I was deserving of the comment,
but more than 90% of it is  either nuisance or spam mail.
I'm troubled how I should react to that,
so stop confessing such things to a police officer.
However, I've always thought that...
mailers of this type can really think of interesting topics...
It's me, Mi☆noru
I Are you free today?
Are you free tomorrow?
Are you free on the day after tommorow?
Are you free in three days time?
When will you be free?
Am I annoying?
Uncalled?
I've deposited the money!
What're you saying...
Are you free tomorrow?
Acknowledge me!
Ah, I want to go to Panama
Congratulations! You have won!
You have won 5,000,000 bags of rice!
You can eat as much rice as you'd like!
Congratulations! You have won!
Jagged 10 yen coins, 100! You have won!
I am Yoshiko.
Please listen to my wish.
fistandilus!, It's me! Dondakee~
Yes, indeed...
Ahoge
Elf
Sister
Maid
Yandere
nekomimi
miko
Music
Twin Tail
Tsundere
Pony Tails
Pictures
Games
Video
Various
Copying from "Tsundere" to "Pictures"
It seems like it's going pretty fast...
I wonder if it ends faster than I thought...
Copying from "Tsundere" to "Pictures"
Hmm...
Ah!
It's always like this...
But the time just keeps on going up and down, missing its mark...
I wonder if I should eat some cup noodles or something as a midnight snack~tto...
Got played by fate...
Hello...
Welcome.
I heard that Konata and Yutaka got a cold. Am I right?
Oh my...
Are you alright, Yutaka?
I ended up getting it after a while...
Ossu! Konata, are you alrig..?
Ah, neesan - welcome!
Hmph...
So you have no energy to attend class, but you have plenty to play games, huh...
Well, you know...
Neesan, you should understand...
Good Day!
Ah, Minami-chan and all! So you came to visit!
Thank you...
She ended up staying in bed this time,
but this is the first time Yutaka is so energetic...
I'm really grateful to you, Minami-chan...
No, I haven't done anything...
Though she did have a girl with whom she was friendly in junior high...
I wonder if its called "good chemistry", since she often talks about you...
I guess it can't be helped, school being enjoyable and all...
Look! They do say that "The illness comes from the heart," right?
It seems that when you're having fun, you'll forget about the illness, too.
Good Day!
Ah, Minami-chan and all! So you came to visit!
Thank you...
She ended up staying in bed this time,
but since this is the first time Yutaka is so energetic...
I'm really grateful to you, Minami-chan...
No, I haven't done anything...
Though she did have a girl with whom she was friendly in junior high...
I wonder if its called "good chemistry", since she often talks about you...
I guess it can't be helped, school being enjoyable and all...
Ah...
Minami-chan with Tamura-san and Patty-chan... Welcome.
Are you all right?
Get well soon!
Yeah...
But I wonder why my body is so weak...
People get worried about me as well, I dont like it...
No, no - that's why there are so many people who will want to protect you!
No... Even if people see you being well,
it might be tough for the person himself most of the time...
Hmm...
So to say, it's the same thing as with people...
who actually have little sisters hardly having a "little sister" moe...
Ah, that's it!
Oh, it came!
The attack of contempt from the normal people!
This is the path which they cannot follow, isn't it!
There's nothing to do about it, we are outlaws, senpai!
Talking about people minding their weak spots...
Minami-chan was minding the fact that she has no breasts, right?
Was that so?
No... no such...
They do say that breasts become larger if you massage them, don't they?
Ah, I've heard about that!
I-Is it really alright, Minami-chan..?
As I... don't have... anyone else... to ask such a thing...
I...I'll touch it then...
Y-ye...
Ahh... Restrain myself, restrain myself - I!
Ah, so Tamura-san was a member of that circle...
Yes, I attended the previous Summer-Comi as well...
I have some of the books, you know.
Ah, it's an honour...
Was that so...
I'd like to see manga drawn by Tamura-san...
Oneechan, please let me read some...
Hm? It's alright, bu...
Hmm..?
Please... somehow don't do th...
No, no - Hiyorin...
Doujins are things that exist in order to be seen by people, you know...
tn: bushi - samurai, warrior
Please, show some bushi compassion...
At the very least, only the ones for normal people...
I see you are a bad loser, Hiyorin...
Ah, awesome, isn't it...
Then, let us go over it...
In gum that has xylitol...
Yes, it has an effect to extinct the bacteria of bad teeth.
This is...
as the xylitol gets absorbed by the bacteria...
and at the same time as the ATP of the bacteria gets wasted...
it breaks into parts inside the bacteria of the bad teeth...
If it's so good for the teeth... I should try it out as well...
As I was chewing gum for my teeth, the filling in my tooth came out...
It turned into going to the dentist's...
"Admirable-but-ran-out-of-luck" Miyuki-san, moe~
And so, you know - Miyuki-san was crying today...
Ehh...
I moe'd!
I-is that so...
...oneechan said it like that...
So that was why Miyuki-san was so dark...
I'm sorry for the person called Miyuki-san...
But I get that story!
Well, as a story just wouldn't come out...
How do you think of the stories in manga?
Hmm... I cannot tell for everyone,
but I think I use real experinces and such quite much...
R-Real experiences...
So you read it..!
Err, those...
Even if I told her as much not to show them...
Sorry...
As the "experience" in it is not that...
B-but there were many good stories, it was really interesting.
Thanks...
I wonder if it's called 'deja vu'?
There also were stuff that I felt I had experienced somewhere...
I, as well, would like to read it later on...
Sorry, I'm really sorry...
That must be the one to which you two were the models...
Hm?
Sensei, good morning...
What is it, Izumi?
Games all-nighter again?
Or would it be midnight anime?
Oh, lately midnight anime has really gotten big, hasn't it...
It's a good age...
Could'nt you have just said you were studying, even if it was a lie...
I really think about treating myself a bit, like buying a DVD recorder...
Ha-ha-ha, that's no good, leave it be...
As anyways, even if you do record them, it'll turn into not watching them...
The same as with the piling games, I see...
Huh!? What are you saying?
Hey, you! Cut it out!
It's not a joke!
I'll say it to you, but I don't know, you know!
Ahh...
Ah, hello?
You didn't hang up just now, did you?
No, even though there were three bars, it somehow cut off...
Ah, yeah...
Well, I was being immature just now...
Sorry...
Ah, just so you know, I didn't snap and hang up.
So it once again turned into visiting this place, didn't it?
And so, please show me where it came off...
Aah..!
Ah, if that's it, it'll be fine if I just glue it in there...
This'll end quickly.
Ah...
But, there is one turning into a cavity at the back,
I might start treating that one as well...
This is a free softsub.Not for sale, rent, auction or hardsub.
Not for sale, rent, auction or hardsub.This is a free softsub.
or hardsub.This is a free softsub. Not for sale, rent, auction
Lucky Star!
Hm? What is it?
I just suddenly realized...
that strawberries have the smell of short cakes...
Ah...
But isn't that that because there's a strawberry smell coming from short cakes?
From the strawberries inside.
Wah...
Well, err...
Well, there sometimes are such illusions, aren't there...
Uncle, oneechan - good morning...
Yuu-chan, morning!
Morning!
Today's doggies!
Ah, many animals!
They were doing a pet feature!
The first to be introduced is a Welsh Corgie - Kuu-chan!
Ah, a corgie - it's cute...
This owner girl is pretty good as well...
The over-knee gets high points, doesn't it...
The "absolute territory" is in a nice balance!
It seems like a gothic maid uniform would look good on her, doesn't it?
The next coming out was a Siberian husky - Sylviana-chan...
Ah, it's a Husky!
Lately you don't really see them, don't you?
Even though I like them...
This girl is definitely a tsundere, isn't she!?
Oh you moe...
When girls wear twin tails, they will always look like a tsundere, don't they?
So even you, Kusakabe, play games...
I'm a liking no-good- person, though...
Would you like to try a bit?
Hiiragi, you're good!
Amazing!
What's this!? I just can't believe it!
Look, look! Hiiragi is amazing, isn't she!
Really, isn't she...
As I look at her having as much fun,
I kind of feel that this me, dwelling upon victory and loss, is losing...
It's a masterpiece for sure, isn't it?
Smelly moe, isn't it.
Ah, Patricia-san.
Hello there.
You often come here lately, don't you...
Patty is an exchange student who is very eager to research, you know.
That is why I try to instruct her...
in the essence of Japan's culture like this every day...
But isn't what you can teach only a small portion of Japanese culture?
'Otaku' are the pride of Japan's culture!
To absorb all kinds of these things...
and to take them back to America is my critical mission!
I do admire you just for that spirit,
but Patricia-san, you know...
What kind of songs are you listening to here right now?
Hmm... Let's see...
Orange Range, Chemistry...
SUNEOHAIR, Porno Graffitti, L'Arc~en~Ciel,
Jinn, Nightmare et cetera, I listen to various Japanese artists!
Hee, unexpected, isn't it.
But that's, you know...
All of those are people who have sung anime songs, right?
Ooh, Konata - you really are sharp, aren't you?
Besides, Patty, you haven't listened to any others than those that became anime songs, right?
Ah... I'd like a maid as well...
Eh?
A maid.
Ah, "a maid" is it...
So, Patricia-san, you were living by yourself, instead of a dorm or something?
Yes. I am really busy with cooking, laundry, manga and anime.
And to make matters worse, you're not used to it...
so I guess you could begin wanting to employ a housekeeper.
Non-non! Not a housekeeper, but a 'maid'!
Aren't they like the same thing...?
Oh, they're completely different!
What were you studying in this country!?
No, I wonder if you're not mistaking Japan?
I can't give you this...
As it contains oil...
Ah, since it knows that you are a softy, Minami, it won't leave you alone.
It seems like there's nothing to be done. Come here, I'll give you this...
Calm down and eat...
But... This as it is is somehow lonely...
Although she's thought as quiet and scary in the class,
she really is nice, as well as cool and stylish, isn't she?
She is really adored by Kobayakawa-san in the Izumi residence.
Oh my, is that really so?
Minami-chan, the circular notice!
Minami-chan is cool and stylish, isn't she..?
Ah, now that you mention it, Izumi-san said as well...
She has the image of being really cool and always being on guard,
but when you look at her when she's with Yuu-chan,
you know that she's a good person, right?
...like that...
Hm?
Excuse me, this is a bargain item, and is limited to one per customer...
Ah!
Oh my...
Minami-chan is cool and always on guard...
Additionally, Kagami-san as well as Tsukasa-san,...
Minami-chan seems like she can do everything quick and perfectly, right?
It seems like there's nothing she can't do.
She's so cool, I look up to her...
Minami-san is looked at as an aspiring one...
by Kagami-san as well as Tsukasa-san.
Ah, mom?
The item you asked for was a limited to one...
Eh? Ah... Yeah...
Oh my?
Oh-oh my...
Oh-oh-oh my...
Oh-oh-oh-oh my...
"Minami-chan does everything quick and perfectly..."
Ossu!
Mesu!
Welcome!
What are you watching?
A mecha anime I borrowed.
Hee, cool, isn't it...
Haah...
So you still like those, don't you?
Hmm...
Not like I'm that particularly interested in mecha.
Huh?
"Not particularly interested in mecha?"...
Well what are you looking at then?
For the broad range of the audience,
the mecha ones lately almost certainly...
have cute girls and guys, you know...
Is it alright to call that mecha!?
OK, Hiiragi, got it!?
Absolutely, you know!
Really, tomorrow! I'll be counting on you!
Yeah, yeah... I'll deal with it good and proper.
Look, Misa-chan... As Hiiragi-chan's saying so as well...
I think it'd be better not to push it as much...
But, based on my previous experience...
the line "I'll deal with it good and proper" is one
of a person that has no motivation from the beginning, isn't it...
Tsk...
She's only sharp on weird things, isn't she?...
Kagami-sama!
Let's drop by Gamer's when we go home!
As I have nothing to buy and something to do today, I'll pass.
It's alright, isn't it... let's go around for a bit...
I don't want to!
Hey! Hey!
Don't you play!
All in all, there's at least a bookstore around your place, right?
Hmm...
After you have once gone to such a store,
don't you feel a bit dissatisfied if its a usual bookstore?
Not being able to gather the things you wanted and all...
Isn't that because the stuff you want is too special?
And, what'll you be buying today?
Today...
it'll be this!
So you're watching a lot of stuff...
No, I haven't watched the anime.
But, from the moment I saw this jacket I just couldn't leave it alone...
I had it on my mind from long long ago...
Don't really understand you...
But, you know...
Only lately have I begun to understand the psychology of buying by the jackets...
Look! You do happen to select light novels by the cover as well, right?
Well, although I can't deny that...
When such things hit the nail, you really feel like you gained something,
and should it, to the contrary, be a miss,
as you bought it in a whim, you don't really regret it as well...
In other words...
Once-in-a-lifetime thing!
You might've intended it to be a clever punchline,
but that hurts somewhere deep inside...
"Let's just take it easy..."
So should this be a once-in-a-lifetime one, or something...
Magnificent, as usual...
Try to at least put your hand there...
Well, as you really can't control sneezing, right?
This is the first time I've ever seen...
someone really saying "hakushuu", just like it's drawn in pictures...
Somehow you know...
Even if you take the same sneeze, this difference of individuals...
It's not fair, is it...
It's somehow not fair with a cute one, is it...
Don't you twine...
After making a lap, it ends up being a nice scent to the contrary, doesn't it?
But I heard that she already gave up on that...
You two go well together, don't you?
Have you fought or done something like that?
Yeah, we have!
Even if she looks so, Ayano is scary when she gets mad.
Ah! There are such people, aren't there? Indeed...
Hmm... So even Hiiragi-chan...
In other words,
Hiiragi is scary even usually, though...
So, after all, I'm at a such rank, huh?
Minami-chan has the same time as oneechan in the 100m dash, you know!
Eh, was that so?
But...
should we really compete, I would win by the size of my bust!
...like such!
Tsuru----n
Peta----n
Munepettan-Girls
tn: Tsurupettan, anyone? Tsuru - smooth (down) Pettan - flat(-chested)
B-but wouldn't Minami-chan come out first because of the height difference?
Flatty...
I was brilliantly passed...
You think so too, right - Hiiragi?
Yeah...
It's interesting, isn't it - Hiiragi?
Hiiragi, what do you think about it?
"Don't you answer 'Oh well..."- Misa-chan's,
and the "Don't ask all kinds of stuff while I'm reading."-Hiiragi's voltage is...
going all up, isn't it?
Ohh, so after all there is moe...
in Japan's anime and games characters, isn't there?
So it is...
Huh? Doesn't this image have a bug?
Ahh... This is alright, as this is the way it's done...
Hmm... This has a feeling of immoral conduct as it is...
Wah-ha!
Ahh, what'cha game are you playing, dear high-schoolers?
What are you doing all together?
Yuu-chan, you don't need to!
Ah, got it done...
Today I wrote a long journal entry in a long time...
Yeah, let's send it~tto.
The page cannot be displayed.
The page you are looking for might have been removed, had its name
Eeh!?
Come back! Come back!
Warning:
Page has Expired
The page you requested was created using information you submitted
To resubmit your information and view this Web page, click the ref
Please visit us at
http://jeeb.fiveforty.jp/
#jeeb@irc.rizon.net
Lucky Star!
Ahh...
You know!
I, too, do not intend to lecture you like a mother-in-law...
"Dull..."
Yes...
No matter what the details were...
Together, you know, that...
Didn't you exchange sake cups and make this corner from scratch?
And that's you know...
with a last stage like this, having everything broken to pieces is not it, right?
I sink down...
Yeah...
I as well did a lot of stuff after being told "you're dark",
but this is the first time I'm arbitrating such a damn boring fight!
Do you understand?
You know, should this relationship not improve with this...
It'll become into plastering my face with dirt, you know...
Uh, Shiraishi...
I have no excuses, Gotuuza-sama...
Ah?
Uh...
And what is Akira thinking?
I'm sorry, Gotuu...
HUH!?
I'm sorry, Gotuuza-sama!
Well, you know... Let's strike a bargain here then.
You know...
How about trying to carry out the original intention,
and pulling off the last Lucky Channel?
How does that sound?
Understood...
Put out more voice!
Understood!
Well then, the personal affairs are settled!
The rest I have...
left to you.
Firmly persevere in the anime world from now on!
Well, I'll be off for a moment then.
I'll inform the producer on my side as well...
Should something happen again, call me.
If you'd like, I'll send you some of my followers, as well.
Wrum, wrum-wrum...
Wuf-wuf...
Oh my, oh my...
Translation: JEEB
Encode: Heedly
TLC: Senoby, Piglet315
Typesetting: Ilaggoodly
Editing: Ilaggoodly, Evilitschi
QC: DarkJug
And so, the next Lucky Star is?
This month, you know - it's hard isn't it?
You're loud already!
Hey, everyone - try to do at least the end or so properly, please!
Are you listening to me!?
Hey!
Ah, it's enough already! As I can do it even by myself!
Next time: "Pending"
Huh!? It isn't decided!?