Yoshimizu Kagami
Theatre
Ah, the B class of third year?
Kuroi-sensei!
Yeah, yeah...
曖昧3センチ
Aimai 3 senchi
Unclear 3 centimeters...
そりゃぷにってことかい？ちょっ!
Sorya punitte koto kai? cho!
Is that a puni? Waitasec!
らっぴんぐが制服…
Rappingu ga seifuku…
The uniform's the wrapping…
だぁぁ不利ってことない　ぷ。
Daa furitte koto nai　Pu.
Hey, there's no disadvantage in that, yeah.
がんばっちゃ♥やっちゃっちゃ
Ganbaccha♥yacchaccha
Try your best♥do your thing-cha,
そんときゃーっち&Releaseぎョッ
son tokyaacchi & ririisu gyo
at that time, well, catch & release, gyo!
汗っ、々っ
A-se, a-se!
In the sweaty, sweaty...
の谷間にDarlin'darlin'F R E E Z E!!
No taniai ni daarin daarin furiiーzu!
cleavage darlin' darlin' FREEZE!!
なんかダるー、なんかデるー
NankaDAruuー, nankaDEruー
Somewhat lazy..., something's coming out...
あいしテるー
AishiTEruuー
I love you...
あれ一個が違ってるんるー
Are ikko ga chigatterunruー
One of those is different, ruー.
なやみン坊ー 高鉄棒 おいしん簿ー
NayamiNbouー Koutetsubou oishinboー
A worrywart, high horizontal bar - an ever-lengthening list...
いーかげんにシナサイ
Iikagen ni SHINASAI
Now get reasonable!
飛んでったアイツの火照るカラダって
Tondetta AITSU no hoteru KARADAtte
The burning body of who flied away right now is...
所謂ふつーのおにゃのコ
Iwayuru futsuu no onya no KO
what is called a "usual girl".
驚いた、
Odoroita,
I'm surprised,
あたしだけ? 豚骨ハリガネおかわりダー!!!!
atashi dake? tonkotsu harigane okawari daaー!!!!
Only me? I get an extra portion of tonkotsu with super hard noodlesー!!!!
BON-BONおーえん団
BON-BON oーendan
Bon-bon cheering team.
Let's get! Cherry pie
Let's get! Cherry pie.
RAN-RAN　かんげー会
Ranraan　kangeーikai
RAN-RAN, welcoming party.
Look up! せんせーしょん
Look up! Senseーshon
Look up! Sensation.
はい！　存在感・・小惑星
Haai　Sonzaikan　tenten　shouwakusei
Yes, feeling of being here・・meteor!
ぶつかって溶けました　呆然　大いに歌ってシレンジャー
Butsukatte tokemashita　bouzen　ooi ni utatte shirenjaー
Got melt from the collision, dumbfounded and singing a lot, "Shiranger!"
もっていけ!
Motte ike!
Take and go!
最後に笑っちゃうのはあたしのはず
Saigo ni waracchau no wa atashi no hazu
The last one laughing should be me,
セーラーふくだからです
Seeraa fuku dakara desu
because it's a sailor fuku.
←結論
←Ketsuron
←Conclusion.
月曜日なのに！
Getsuyoubi nanoni!
Even if it's monday!
機嫌悪いのどうするよ？
Kigen warui no dou suru yo？
What will you do with that bad mood?
夏服がいいのです←キャ？ワ！イイｖ
Natsufuku ga ii no desu←KYA?WA!IIv
I want my summer uniform←It!Is!Cute!
接近3ピクト するまでってちゅーちょだ　やん☆
Sekkin san pikuto, suru madette chuーcho da　yan☆
Getting closer's in three paces, I'll hesitate until you do 'it' Oh☆
頑張って　張り切って
Ganbatte,　harikitte
Try your best, be on high,
My Darlin'darlin' P L E A S E!!
Mai daarin daarin puriizu
my darlin' darlin' please!
Hey, what on earth is this line for?
Yuki-chan, do you know?
I wonder...
Now, now...
Blank
tn: A coupon for the entry to pre-sales for "Suzumiya Haruhi no Gekisou"
So it was like this.
How regrettable, I got a blank, too.
Ah!
Uh, but I won.
I did as well!
My kind friends..!
And I am?
Club member, you're a big one...
Look.
It was breathtaking, wasn't it?
I was impressed!
The first person to step on the stage was cool, right?
Eh, was he?
Eh, no good?
So there is demand...
Konata, you haven't spoken at all since just now, have you?
Ah? Yeah...
Like the feeling of lassitude after a festival, right?
I was impressed as well, though.
Yeah. I wonder what this is...
This feeling...
Can't change
suddenly
What are you doing?
Look, we'll be going!
Kagami, you're active in weird places, aren't you?
After all, if we don't go to look at the cherry blossoms today,
we'll miss the full bloom.
If you think something like...
"Should I go tomorrow, or rather the day after?",
it just starts raining or the blossoms wither.
That reminds me, what did you do with the goldfish from the summer festival?
Uh, to tell you the truth...
Somehow I gave out too much feed... It turned out like this...
Huge! "Shogun"!
Happened to pet it a bit too much...
Just wait a sec! Isn't that the wrong training objective?
That's not a goldfish!
There's only to pray that it'll at least be happily fat...
Possibly you were thinking about eating it?
Like I would!?
There's an anime where the pets you fondled reincarnate as humans...
and greet you with "Welcome back, my master.", right?
You bring out only hardcore things again.
Maybe I should put it on a bit of a diet?
Kagami...
Dipping for Goldfish
You're not thinking about changing to a substitute or something?
It has gotten pretty cold, hasn't it?
Should we go back soon?
If you carelessly come to watch the cherries at night with daytime clothing,
you grow cold, don't you?
And, if you sit, your bottom grows cold.
I heard once that the average temperature of March...
about equals to the one of December,
and that April equals November.
Ah, if it was November or December,
I'd wear warmer clothes for sure!
During March and April you just somehow end up scantily clothed.
Aren't you just bored because you wear winter cloth all the time?
Isn't that an expression of the feeling of...
wanting the spring to come fast, after all?
Kagami, you're cheerful, aren't you?
Could it be... wool..?
Blocks far infrared rays
Full preparation!
I'm not wearing them!
Let's keep it around this, shall we, Gyoppi.
Huh!?
If he appeared, grown into a lover,
it'd be troublesome if he was a domestic-violence-guy...
But well...
I wonder what happened with oneechan...
Ahh, it stings...
My skin is pretty delicate, you know...
During this time it's so bothersome, it beats me.
Troublesome, isn't it.
Even though I'm mostly in the house...
Nowadays there seem to be different pollen countermeasure goods, so..
why not buy such for a try?
Transformation!
I see, this is good!
Pollen exposure cut by 99%!
Now he's not only suspicious on the inside, but the outside turned so as well...
Eh!?
Just don't become a police case...
I'll go shopping for a bit.
Have a nice day.
Would you come along?
No, I won't.
Well, daddy - are you going shopping looking like that!?
Yeah, sure. If I went without this equipment, it'd have no meaning, right?
The next news.
A woman broke into a convenience store
Last night, at 11 PM a woman broke into a convenience store...
and tried to rob the sales.
Hey, Yuu-chan.
But as the clerk shouted out loud, she ran away.
What is it?
I wonder if in this season convenience store robberies...
with people pretending they have pollen allergy increase..?
Might even be...
Freeze!
Why does it turn out like that?
Eh, tomorrow? It's alright, I guess I should play after a while.
Yeah. As I finished my homework as well!
Huh? What did you say now!?
"Finished my homework"!? Really? Can't believe it!
Sorry, it was a lie.
Well, don't you think that you just have to lie on April fools'?
Good that I remembered.
No, you know... Or should I say, your will to work is zero, right?
A person of leisure, aren't you...
You're the only person who'd bother to call at such a time for a lie...
For now, see you tomorrow.
Yes, Izumi speaking.
I'm Kuroi, is this the Izumi residence?
Ah, sensei!
Hey, Izumi! It's me!
Sorry! I mistook the game I borrowed and overwrote your saves.
It's a lie, it's a lie! You fell for it! Today's April fools'!
So there was... another person of leisure...
Sensei...
Oh, what is it?
The other day Miyuki-san said:
As even a person like Kuroi-sensei can continue doing it,
teaching must be really easy as a profession.
...like that.
Ahh, that brat... So she was playing a nice one, huh...
Err, sensei - that was a lie...
That darn Konata called me in order to make a lie, really...
Did Tsukasa lie to someone or something like that?
Eh!? Yeah...
Eh, that's rare. What kind of?
That right now... about lying, was a lie...
Hard to understand!
Or should I say that you don't have to lie forcibly!
W-what kind of lie did Kona-chan tell?
Huh? Something like doing her homework on her own...
and if I think about, I'm something, too, allowing myself to be tricked like that.
Impossible.
The lie is that she hasn't done her homework yet, right?
Well, as it's about her, she hasn't done it for sure.
I see.
You just thought that it is nice that there's another one, right?
Eh!? No...
Konata, is it OK for a while?
Is that... interesting?
Yeah, unique...
Is that so...
Konata!
To tell you the truth daddy is thinking about remarrying!
Oh really...
No, it is natural of you to be against it.
Indeed, Kanata is the only mother for you...
Huh!?
"Oh really..."!? Are you alright with it!?
Even if daddy would remarry?
Wouldn't it be good?
B-but, look!
That means there'll be a new mommy for you!
What kind of a person is she, new mommy?
Eh?
No, well...
No... Well...
Even if you take me that seriously...
And so, the next question:
What would be the humble version of "iku" (~to go)?
That's "ukagau" (~to visit), easy!
Ah, yes, that's right.
It's "ukagau", isn't it?
Yes, that'd be the correct answer.
Yeah, if I remember right it was that.
The correct answer was "mairu" (~to stride).
Now as they say so, it's right...
Ah, yeah, indeed...
Mommy got lured into that as well...
I wonder what this subtle atmosphere is...
Yeah, me too...
As everyone's off base with full assurance...
The first problem of the three-choice-quiz:
Within the following, which is a prefecture that doesn't face the sea?
A - Ibaragi-ken, B - Tochigi-ken, C - Kyoto-fu.
It's B, isn't it?
It's B, right?
B, it is.
This is easy, isn't it?
The right answer was "B".
The next question:
Waged as a difficult problem in the mathematical world,
the famous theorem proven by professor Wiles...
in Prinston University in 1994 is:
A - Pythagoras' theorem, B - Taylor's theorem, C - Fermat's theorem?
I wonder why do they close their mouths simultaneously when it's a question...
in which they have no confidence, but answer fast when it's easy...
As it's the spring vacation,
let's go and play at Miyuki-san's place!
Ah, that's a good idea. The place is far, so I've never been there.
Hmm... Miyuki-san's place is rich, right?
I wonder what it's like!
Having a pool in the garden...
No, no - people like guards being around the house...
No, it's going to be more normal.
Ah! They sound like having pets and something!
By the image something like a ferret! A white one!
No, no - it's a dog.
A big, white dog!
A white parasol in a big garden!
They might have something like a dog!
The talk is going on like that, so...
I welcome you, but please, honestly, do not expect as much.
Excuse us for not even having pets...
But, even if we do not have a large, white dog or parasol,
there is such a household in our neighborhood.
Hee...
And it seems that a girl from that family is going to enter Ryouou this year!
Will you go with us if she'd call that girl around?
My friend's younger cousin seems to be entering Ryouou.
The world's small, don't you think?
This is a free softsub.Not for sale, rent, auction or hardsub.
Not for sale, rent, auction or hardsub.This is a free softsub.
or hardsub.This is a free softsub. Not for sale, rent, auction
Hm... I'm sleepy...
Really... That's because you habitually sleep during noon...
Ah, Konata! Ossu.
What? You're a habitual sleeper as well?
This...this is after playing through three all-nighters...
I'm about to die...
These two only look like each other on the slovenly side of things!
Izumi Konata
Takara Miyuki
Hiiragi Tsukasa
Shiraishi Minoru
Ah, we're in the same class again!
Ah, really. How nice!
Good morning!
Ah, Yuki-chan, morning!
Morning! Miyuki-san, you're in the same class as well.
Oh, true.
How nice.
Treat me well for another year.
Here too.
Iwasaki Minami
Kobayakawa Yutaka
It seems like we're in the same class!
Yeah...
Ah, please treat me well for this year!
Here too.
Ah...
Only Kagami is in another class again.
To add to it all, we already meet on many occasions,
so if we're not at least in different classes, I'll get tired.
Oneechan...
How unfortunate...
Not really. It's what always happens, right?
Besides, per Konata, she will come to borrow notes and textbooks, anyways.
She's calling me, isn't she?
Well, as it's like this, go on ahead.
Yeah, see you later...
See you...
Ossu!, Hiiragi!
How's the class placement?
Oh, aren't we in the same class again?
If you include Junior High as well, it's the fifth year in a row?
Treat us well again.
Eh?
Huh?
There are, aren't there...
Such cold-hearted people who don't see anything else than their foremost goal.
Now, now...
We are just like the background.
I wonder how the criteria for classes are decided.
They are doing it so that the grades do not get biased,
trying to put relatives in different classes...
and dividing students who have problems as well as possible...
That's what I've heard.
Although I think there are differences depending on the school.
In dramas, and all, the troublemakers usually pack up in one class, don't they?
As that's more interesting.
But high school is supposed to gather people of the same level,
so there're probably no special problem children.
Yes, that's right.
Miyuki... Here it's OK for you to intervene with...
"Get conscious that you're the problem child yourself."
Miyuki, you don't want to be put on the same level as well, right?
No, it's not like that...
Even though the chime sounded, sensei's late, isn't she?
Now that you mention it, you're right...
Everyone, get to your seats!
Dangerous! I'm barely safe on time!
You're out.
Aah, I'm your classroom teacher - Kuroi.
As you've all risen a grade, don't be on holiday mood -
- try to change your attitude completely towards working hard..!
Not persuasive at all!
First period staff
-Class representative
-Library helper
Well, I won't nag like "Study!",
but it's the last year of high school, so spend it usefully.
So, let's divide the roles at once...
Takara, can I ask you to be the class representative for the first half?
First period staff
-Class representative
-Library helper
Yes.
If you're class representative or something once,
your image gets fixated and you'll do it again...
Yes, that's right.
Although it's OK as I don't hate it.
In the first term the teacher often decides.
As there are many unknown people, it is hard to nominate, as well.
In Kuroi-sensei's case...
isn't it because it's easier for her if she puts you in duty?
I can hear you.
The teacher's hair was all a mop, wasn't it?
But it looks like it'll become another nice class with Kuroi-sensei.
Oh, well - as she's upbeat.
Because it's usual that the colour of the class...
gets decided by the homeroom teacher.
I see... Got it.
So the untidy part of you two resembled your homeroom teacher.
I can hear you.
I'm Iwasaki, greetings.
That girl, isn't she pretty cute?
I was in the same junior high as she was,
but she never talked, was dark and always read books - she's weird.
Even though she really is awfully kindhearted...
So I'm the only one to know, makes me feel a bit special.
Next.
Ah, y-yes!
With things like this the beginning is essential, isn't it...
I must act cheerfully.
I'm Kobayakawa Yutaka.
I appear like this,
but I'm not something like a grade-skipping elementary school student.
Like that.
A grade-skipper? Is she? But if that's so... Yeah, you're right.
I wonder if I'm getting influenced by oneechan and turning maniac-like...
And so, I'm thinking about determining all of the leaders of the class...
Are there any volunteers for class representative..? Looks like none...
Iwasaki, you did it during junior high, so do it.
Is that so, can I ask you that, Iwasaki?
I'm sorry... There is another job I'd like to do...
Even though someone experienced would be better...
What do you want to do? Something like the library helper?
The helper of the nurse's office.
Sensei! I will be the class representative!
She's a really good person!
The spring's, you know...
it has a premonition that...
something will begin...
New encounters...
Izumi Konata
New living...
A new... love...
Izumi Konata
With that person, my childhood friend...
With the upperclassman of my dreams...
Or with the unknown transfer student?
A little worry and huge expectations,
the five seconds before seriously falling in love. MK5!
...there's such a refreshing image,
but as you have to start from the beginning with a stranger in reality,
it's depressing.
Although I've gotten used to it already.
You're better off, right?
Oneechan!
Ah, Yuu-chan, saw you again after the morning.
Yeah, that's right. hello after morning.
And then...
This person is the one I talked about, who helped me.
Ah! So you did meet her!
I'm glad to meet you.
I'm glad to meet you...
See, it went like I said -
- that she'd pass for sure!
Yes, yes. But Yuu-chan, you know,
you're missing the possibility of not coming despite passing.
The result counts, so it's OK!
By the way, what were you doing?
We thought about checking the nurse's office,
since I'll probably depend on it.
I see.
Ah, oneechan. Guide us!
Good, good... Leave it to oneesan!
Now where was the nurse's office...
Uh?
The nurse's office
As I haven't ever used it, I don't know...
Hey, hey -
- to come here for even two years,
and not to know where the nurse's office is?
Well, doesn't that mean I've spent the last two years in good health?
No, you've gone to the physical examination, right?
As you mention that, I think I've never been to the art class.
If you have selected music, you don't really have occasions to go there.
I have not set my foot into the judo room and such.
Until recently I didn't even know that we had a tea room.
Even if you go to the same school for three years...
It's like one doesn't go anywhere...
except the places one has business at.
I don't really go to the study hall, either...
I go to the study hall!
Oh, that's unexpected.
That quietness, it is just proper for sleeping, isn't it... Yeah.
I wonder...
Ah, Yuu-chan, you know...
She went to see the nurse's room with...
the girl who helped her on the day of the exam.
They're in the same class she said,
isn't it a miracle?
Now that I think of it, it could be a miracle...
that I met and became friends with you all in this school, Kona-chan, Yuki-chan.
Oh, well...
It's only one more year that we can pass time together like this, isn't it?
Only Kagami was always in a different class though, wasn't she...
Just don't say that...
The correct answer is B - poisonous carrot!
I will put this on the test, so try to remember it!
Look! Izumi, wake up!
Ah, Potemkin!
What kinda dreams do you have?
Ah, excuse me...
Even like this I'm trying my best not to doze and concentrate...
But, sensei! They are coming! The sandmen!
It's sudden! Impossible to defend yourself from!
It's the ultimate fate!
Even if you insist so majestically to an educator...
I guess you got a bit awake with this.
Miyuki-san, you don't doze off, right?
Do you have a trick or something...
It's not something I'd call a trick,
but as I'm one of those people who just cannot be without sleep,
I end up sleeping at 11 o'clock...
By the way, until the second year of high school...
I was already sleeping at 10 o'clock.
It's no good! I can't imitate that, as it feels like losing a lifetime!
I remember the fact that I memo'ed the things that...
I thought were important during the last lesson,
but as I slept the other half of it I can't understand what I wrote...
I don't understand it...
But looking at it...
makes me feel I'm really praiseworthy.
It's a sign that I want to study! Yeah.
But I really wonder what I wrote...
Aren't those formulas?
Kuroi-sensei...
It's incredible, sensei - you can read this mysterious document?!
Oh well, but I mean to say it ends up so that you, Izumi,
didn't have any World History class in your dreams...
And so...
Oneechan, are you still awake?
Hmm... So it was smelly after all...
Ah, I did it again! Is it already so late?
I wonder if someone'll be here gradually...
You really don't know when to stop, do you...
Tomorrow'll be something to look forward to.
Please visit us at
http://jeeb.fiveforty.jp/
#jeeb@irc.rizon.net
LUCKY CHANNEL!
Good lucky!
The program of gossip, which brings world peace - Lucky Channel!
I'm your navigator - Kogami "Pretty" Akira!
Similarly I'm the assistant - Shiraishi Minoru.
As a fast thing, Lucky Channel's already in it's fifteenth time!
Oh, is it the 15th time today?
Yes, it is so...
So you're done for today?
Well... We-ll...
Goodbye...
Didn't you hear?
I was told by the producer:
"From the 16th time on you, Kogami Akira, will be on your own, so I'm counting on you."
Ahh, but that is..!
Yes, got him fooled! It's April fools!
Ahh... What, so it was so...
Goodbye... Come to think of it, didn't you considerably come to life?
At Haruhi's Geki...
Nyoro~n
was it? I just felt like someone like you was MC'ing.
Ah, was that so? That couldn't...
So! When is my live event!?
I wonder...
If you don't tell me early on,
you know, my schedule will be filled up far ahead!
Ah, I will check it immediately!
Watch! The East is burning red!
Faster, faster, faster!
Circle...
Eh, circle?
Producer - "OK"?
The next time?
Understood!
Next time, at this time, a Kogami Akira live event will be held!
Ah, huh!? N-next time!?
S-s-sseriously!? Have they booked a hall?
Yes! It seems like they went off their ways to get it!
Maggaare.
Unbelievable! I did it! So you can do things, Itou!
Ohh, I'm looking forward to Akira-sama singing.
It's a lie! No it's real, real!
Ah, you can leave the MC'ing to me!
Even if I look like this, I have a reputation as an MC!
Everyone! Let's keep the feelings higher and higher next time!
And so, until the next time - Bye-nii!
And so, I wonder if Shiraishi Minoru will really be here next week as well?
I am a member!
Huh?
And so, please listen!
What will he sing first?
The first one isn't Hare Hare, right?
The Minoru's Legend of Love!
1-2-3-4, Mi-mi-miracle, Minorun-run!
This isn't Hare Hare for sure.
Mi-mi-miracle, Minorun-run!
He somehow already started (by himself)
Mi-mi-miracle...
Huh?
No HareHare!
There's immense audience waving!
What'll be the first one?
Ah, Well...
General Busybody / Translation: JEEB
Bastard TC from Hell: xbe★
Let's call it Minoru's Legend of Love!
For the time being.
For the time being?
Encoding: Heedly
Editing/QC: ShiroiYuki, ro
OK. Do it.
And so, well, already in your own pace...
In your own pace
Huh?
Is it
Do it in your own pace.
In your own pace!
And so, please listen!
Minoru's Legend of Love!
1-2-3-4!
Mi-mi-miracle, Mi~norun-run!
This video was brought to you by JEEB
And so, the next Lucky Star is?
I'm Inori.
I'm Matsuri.
I'm Miki.
I'm Tadao.
Next time: "Ring"
Look forward to it!