Yoshimizu Kagami
Theatre
Ah, the B class of third year?
Kuroi-sensei!
Yeah, yeah...
曖昧3センチ
Aimai 3 senchi
Unclear 3 centimeters...
そりゃぷにってことかい？ちょっ!
Sorya punitte koto kai? cho!
Is that a puni? Waitasec!
らっぴんぐが制服…
Rappingu ga seifuku…
The uniform's the wrapping…
だぁぁ不利ってことない　ぷ。
Daa furitte koto nai　Pu.
Hey, there's no disadvantage in that, yeah.
がんばっちゃ♥やっちゃっちゃ
Ganbaccha♥yacchaccha
Try your best♥do your thing-cha,
そんときゃーっち&Releaseぎョッ
son tokyaacchi & ririisu gyo
at that time, well, catch & release, gyo!
汗っ、々っ
A-se, a-se!
In the sweaty, sweaty...
の谷間にDarlin'darlin'F R E E Z E!!
No taniai ni daarin daarin furiiーzu!
cleavage darlin' darlin' FREEZE!!
Fan        subs
E
J
B
E
なんかダるー、なんかデるー
NankaDAruuー, nankaDEruー
Somewhat lazy..., something's coming out...
あいしテるー
AishiTEruuー
I love you...
あれ一個が違ってるんるー
Are ikko ga chigatterunruー
One of those is different, ruー.
なやみン坊ー 高鉄棒 おいしん簿ー
NayamiNbouー Koutetsubou oishinboー
A worrywart, high horizontal bar - an ever-lengthening list...
いーかげんにシナサイ
Iikagen ni SHINASAI
Now get reasonable!
飛んでったアイツの火照るカラダって
Tondetta AITSU no hoteru KARADAtte
The burning body of who flied away right now is...
所謂ふつーのおにゃのコ
Iwayuru futsuu no onya no KO
what is called a "usual girl".
驚いた、
Odoroita,
I'm surprised,
あたしだけ? 豚骨ハリガネおかわりダー!!!!
atashi dake? tonkotsu harigane okawari daaー!!!!
Only me? I get an extra portion of tonkotsu with super hard noodlesー!!!!
BON-BONおーえん団
BON-BON oーendan
Bon-bon cheering team.
Let's get! Cherry pie
Let's get! Cherry pie.
RAN-RAN　かんげー会
Ranraan　kangeーikai
RAN-RAN, welcoming party.
Look up! せんせーしょん
Look up! Senseーshon
Look up! Sensation.
はい！　存在感・・小惑星
Haai　Sonzaikan　tenten　shouwakusei
Yes, feeling of being here・・meteor!
ぶつかって溶けました　呆然　大いに歌ってシレンジャー
Butsukatte tokemashita　bouzen　ooi ni utatte shirenjaー
Got melted by the collision, dumbfounded and singing a lot, "Shiranger!"
もっていけ!
Motte ike!
Take and go!
最後に笑っちゃうのはあたしのはず
Saigo ni waracchau no wa atashi no hazu
The last one laughing should be me,
セーラーふくだからです
Seeraa fuku dakara desu
because it's a sailor fuku.
←結論
←Ketsuron
←Conclusion.
月曜日なのに！
Getsuyoubi nanoni!
Even if it's monday!
機嫌悪いのどうするよ？
Kigen warui no dou suru yo？
What will you do with that bad mood?
夏服がいいのです←キャ？ワ！イイｖ
Natsufuku ga ii no desu←KYA?WA!IIv
I want my summer uniform←It?Is!Cute!
接近3ピクト するまでってちゅーちょだ　やん☆
Sekkin san pikuto, suru madette chuーcho da　yan☆
Getting closer's in three paces, I'll hesitate until you do 'it' Oh☆
頑張って　張り切って
Ganbatte,　harikitte
Try your best, be on high,
my darlin' darlin' please!
My Darlin'darlin' P L E A S E!!
Mai daarin daarin puriizu
Ossu!
Ah, oneechan!
How were they? The tests.
Like always...
Shabby as usual...
You know, even though there's more time than usual during the test period...
Before you realize it, you've spent all your time like always...
and in the end you have to cram, right?
I think it'd be better if you had some consciousness of being an examinee...
Under The Sun
Manga and games were confiscated...
from the suspect's room in large numbers...
Through that, the opinion that...
the criminal is the same as before is growing stronger...
This report again...
Unbelievable..!
Once again a person like Konata appeared, right?
You know... Everytime I think that it's unfair...
Even though they immediately criticize such manga...
Even though there're lots of good manga, they don't bring them up at all...
Ah...
Yeah, you're right... My bad I guess...
Kagami, you're a pretty good person after all, aren't you!?
If I appeal to others like that, normally they just...
make fun of me as a "A desperate otaku!".
If you look at those around you,
sisters are usually attached to each other, right?
Like you, Yuu-chan, and Yui-neesan or Tsukasa and Kagami.
Ah! Yeah, yeah!
...I had a talk like that with oneechan this morning!
Minami is really attached to you, Miyuki-chan...
You two get along well, like sisters, don't you two?
I see... Attachment...
Kona-chan, happy birthday!
Oh!
I'd have forgotten if Tsukasa hadn't told me though...
Congratulations!
Thank you, everyone!
You get delighted to be celebrated like this, but,
around our age, it's no longer so pleasing to become older, right?
No, I'm really happy though...
Eh, why is that?
Do you want to get your driver's license or the likes?
Because with this, I can play eroge and stuff, can't I?
Haven't you... been playing a lot of them before now anyway?
It's alright...
Even though you've gotten older,
you haven't changed inside or outside at all now, have you...
Let me go...
Miyuki's mistaken as older after all, right?
Yuki-chan's adult-like, too...
Yes, when I go out in plain clothes,
I am sometimes mistaken for an office lady...
Hmm... So you surpass university students, huh?
In your case, when you go out in plain clothes,
you have the opposite effect of being an elementary school student.
Fufu, no matter what you call me, I'm an adult as of today!
What're you talking about...
If you effectively became a good adult,
you shouldn't get excited over games or manga, should you?
A childish heart filled with dreams and passion is needed, you know!
Which one are you?
This?
Yeah...
While oneechan is at her part-time job,
we'll secretly prepare her birthday party.
I came late!
OK! Let's start the preparations right away!
Yes!
Oneechan,
Happy Birthday
Happy
Birthday
Konata
Cellphone
Ah, Konata's right on time!
I wonder if she'll be coming back soon...
Konata?
I'm sorry! I forgot to say this, but as it seems that everyone...
at work is throwing a party for me, I don't need dinner today!
I'll also be coming home late, as well!
Yutaka, this is tasty, isn't it..?
Yeah, I tried my best...
Yui-chan, you can take that off...
Future hopes, huh...
You do have dreams and stuff,
but when you actually think of it, it's hard, isn't it?
Indeed...
If you go to college, the faculty you choose affects your future, as well...
First choice is the dietetics faculty, second is clothing design...
and third is marketing...
Yeah, since I like to sew and make food...
So Tsukasa wrote down her dreams, didn't she?
And Miyuki-san's are?
Since I want to become a doctor, the university is different,
but I wrote "medicine faculty" for first to third hope...
Miyuki-san, as expected, your goal is clear isn't it?
And what about Kagami, then?
Me? My...
first choice is law, second is economics and third is literature...
Oh, that's not very interesting, is it..?
Is it bad if it's not interesting!?
What about you then!?
First Choice
Brigade Leader
Second Choice
The Master of The Divine Fizt of the South Star
Third Choice
Storyboard Conte Man
There really are such people who aim at jokes like these...
In other words, don't you have any skills...
apart from being good at the staring game?
Special skillls...
Huh?
Ah! I can name all Poke**n!
T-that's quite amazing, although it has nothing to do with the future...
There it is..!
I'll go and buy this.
You... always take from the bottom...
when you buy magazines or manga, don't you?
You know, it feels like everyone has taken it into their hands from the top...
Wouldn't you rather have a cleaner one if possible?
Ah, I understand that!
It's the same as going to a conveyor belt sushi and ordering...
all the time instead of taking the ones going around.
You know, since the topping of the ones going around often dries out.
Uwa! Kagami, you do such things!?
What an unpleasant customer...
No way! You don't!?
Sounds small-minded...
I've always wondered, Kagami,
how you can read books with only letters...?
Don't you get sleepy?
But that's because this is a light novel.
It's the same as a manga, on the feeling side of things.
Hee, I wonder if that's so...
There're lots of illustrations, and the expressions aren't difficult either...
Why don't you try reading it, too?
Oh... Well, but that's... you know...
It became animated as well, so I have it covered...
Should it be a manga...
you'd say there're "the good points of the original" and all...
and check both...
I'm telling you to try to read it.
I humbly refrain...
But you know, you read a fair of books independent of...
whether they're light novels or not...
I wonder what it's called... Doesn't it feel like...
your heart gets wealthier when you treasure education?
Well, perhaps it's like nutrition for the heart...
Ha-ha... I see...
What?
On that note, ingesting sweets makes the body wealthier as well...
Ah! Shut up!
Aren't there serial novels and all in those magazines you read, as well?
Not only comics...
Although I only look at the illustrations,...
Ahh... Even though you usually say all kinds of things,
your affection isn't such a big deal after all.
Skimming through, are you?
Alright! I got it! I'll read them!
Oh, no! It's alright. You don't have to push yourself so hard.
I'm only skimming through because there are many other things to read!
As I said, it's alright. I haven't said a thing...
Oh, no! I forgot the World History textbook!
I left it on the desk after reviewing it...
Konata, lend me your World History textbook,
you keep it in your table, right?
OK. Did you forget yours?
Yeah...
Unusual, isn't it..?
Here!
Uwah!
Ohh, Hiiragi, this is another considerably delightful textbook, now isn't it?
Eh... No... This is... That...
I can't progress well...
For the time being, something to drink...
Ah, darn...
Huh? I thought that the one I bought the other day still had some left...
Just right for a mood change, huh?
Eh!? It's closed!
So this is a challenge aimed at me, isn't it!?
That's 320 yen.
Huh?
What's the matter, oneechan?
No... You know, somehow when you're annoyed,
you make many small mistakes and get even more annoyed, don't you?
Ah... I do, I do. Anything you do or make doesn't go well, right?
The thing called minus spiral?
Oh, right! You know, I baked a cake!
Want some?
Wai!
Studying for the exams is hard, so you have to change moods once in a while.
Ah, so! Tomorrow I'll bake some cookies!
Ohh, they'll dissolve stress, won't they!?
I'm counting on you!
After that...
So it's stress over here now, huh...
Isn't it, isn't it? Iwasaki-san, you think so as well?
Yeah, that's right. As, after all, those two are too busy...
and end up missing with each other all the time, you know...
Yeah!
I understand that, I do!
Ah, that's right.
Oneechan's an examinee, so I have to do...
this in a way that doesn't interfere with her studies.
Ah, I'm sorry, I need to talk in a small voice a bit.
Oh!
Yuu-chan, after you're done with the call, let's compete in games, compete!
Huh?!
This is a free softsub.Not for sale, rent, auction or hardsub.
Not for sale, rent, auction or hardsub.This is a free softsub.
or hardsub.This is a free softsub. Not for sale, rent, auction
So this uniform is at its end after this year, too, huh...
After thinking about it, it seems a little thoughtful...
Ah!
There's something inside.
My favourite handkerchief that I thought I had lost...
had been in my summer uniform's pocket, huh...
Huh, wasn't there octopus wasabi?
Ah!
I wonder what this is...
I wonder what this was... It has changed so utterly that I can't tell...
For just the rainy season there's plenty of rain, isn't there..?
Oh, that's right...
When you think it's awfully hot and you've just changed your clothes,
it's troublesome when it suddenly cools down at times, isn't it?
Oh, so you guys are still here?
It must be really nice for you, sensei, since you can change clothes freely.
What're you saying!?
Isn't it better to have a uniform,
and not have to think what to put on every day?
Sensei really is... that, you know...
Yahoo!
It's the rainy season, isn't it? Humid, isn't it?
Yui-neesan!
Oneechan!
The constant rain gets you down, doesn't it?
Would you like to drink some tea?
Yeah, please.
Well, to move to a positive subject...
oneesan, it's almost the anniversary for your first year of marriage, right?
Yeah, that's right... Fast, isn't it?
Weather condition of the rainy season.. And?
Yui-neesan's heart, whose husband's away at a new position...
by himself although the wedding anniversary is soon.
The similarity is...?
Sorry. It was my bad...
It's alright... I've become used to emotional wounds of this size...
Here. Try to drink this warm drink.
But I'm still feeling hollow...
Ah! This is delicious!
I'm glad...
Ah... At this rate, my love will rust, too!
Ahh... It seems like it'd get better in 45 minutes...
if she'd go to a garage, doesn't it..?
Please comfort me a little at least...
Sorry, sorry... I carelessly...
Ah, yes...
Eh?
So you can come back!
It didn't even take 45 minutes,
It was instant.
Right!
Eh? Tsukasa, you still haven't gotten that outfit...
back from Matsuri-oneechan?
Yeah...
That's no good!
If you don't tell her to give it back soon,
she'll make it her own before you know it.
Eh!? That'd be bad. I really like that one!
Ah...
It's so enviable that Kagami-san and Tsukasa-san even have two older sisters.
Oh well...
Uh? Is that so?
For me, I think that I'm more jealous...
of only children like Konata and Miyuki.
Isn't that so?
Yeah, it's like that at times, but...
You know, with that big of a cast, you can do a lot of things, right?
Like that story about America's past,
in which a mother and four sisters expectantly await the return...
of their father, who was sent to the front, you know?
Or maybe something like the story of mysterious female art thieves?
Huh?
Ah, there's one too many!
Really, if you get commented by her it's all put into anime or games...
Hey, Kagami!
Did you buy the groceries for dinner?
Eh?
Ah!
Tsukasa, did you forget to tell her?
I'm sorry...
What, what? What is it?
Oh no, did you forget? Tonight mom and dad aren't home.
Oh, was the trip today?
Yeah... And so, I was asked to buy the groceries...
I forgot completely...
I even called Kagami's cell phone and left a message.
tn: Messages: One
Wah...
Matsuri, let's make do with what's in the fridge.
Huh? Even though it's such a rare occasion I thought I could make something!
Isn't it fine with the next time?
Eh?
Ohh, it's because of Kagami and Tsukasa!
I'm sorry...
It's alright, I'll go right now.
Jeeze, Matsuri, it's because you put it that way...
But...
Anyways, I wonder if that girl knows what to buy?
Ah!
Really, what was that? She doesn't even like cooking that much...
What's up with that hard-working attitude...
Oneechan!
Huh?
Tsukasa...
Oneechan, you don't have a shopping list, right?
Uh...
They sure are late...
If you're worrying, wouldn't it have been better if you had gone?
Oh...
You're late.
Ah...
What happened?
Matsuri was really worried about you.
As there was no saffron at the usual shop...
I suggested substituting it with curry powder...
As oneechan said "It's a rare occasion, so let's look for it",
and we went to a supermarket further away...
Jeeze, even if it's unnecessary to go that far...
Oh, sorry about that!
Hmph!
C'mon, c'mon! Let's cook.
Oh, I'm hungry!
Here! Sorry for making you wait!
Now just Matsuri's special one is missing.
I'm done!
Looks delicious!
Yes, isn't it pretty well baked?
Hey, Matsuri-oneechan, when did you learn to cook something like this?
Ah... You know, the other day,
at the place where I went with the girls from the seminar, they served this...
And it was so delicious, I thought about making it for everyone...
and asked for the recipe.
Hee, I'm amazed they told that to you.
Look! Let's just eat!
Yeah!
Huh..?
What happened?
Well, your dad had the wrong dates!
Huh?
What does that mean?
The reserved time seems to be next week...
Like in a comic skit...
...Now?
You guys haven't eaten?
Yeah...
Ehh, a paella?
Matsuri-oneechan made it!
Oh my, isn't that great?
Yeah.
But Kagami gathered all ingredients, you know.
She went out of her way to get to a far away supermarket you know...
Should we dine here then?
Yes, we should.
Quite tasty, isn't it?
Huh? Who took all the blue mussels?
Blue mussels?
Eh, should I not have?
I can't believe it! I thought I could eat them last!
Write your name on them, then!
Oh, don't quarrel!
Ossu! I'll be walking with you on the way from school today.
Do you want to buy something?
The newest publication of Yamada Shin**, you know.
Lately, I've had a lot to do though, so I haven't had much time to read.
Ah, I accumulated many unread manga on the bedside, too.
You just end up carelessly reaching for the new things, you know?
I understand that a bit!
Read the ones you have without buying new ones!
Ohh... But if you buy them right away there's this feeling of relief,
or rather something like the feeling of something missing...
Right?
Don't you ask for approval!
Please visit us at
http://jeeb.fiveforty.jp/
#jeeb@irc.rizon.net
Lucky Channel!
Good lucky!
Yes! I'll be delivering this once again with high spirits!
As a quick part, Lucky Channel is on its 17th time on air already!
Yes! Your navigator is: "There are thorns to red roses" -
- the monotreme of the idol world - Kogami Akira!
And so we've invited a really important guest today!
Hello!
Err...
How long do you plan to make me wait?!
Oh, no... Sorry, Sorry!
So he really came out again...
So he came out...
Err... Today's guest is the "Anime Tenchou" - Anizawa Meito-san!
tn: "Anime Tenchou" -- Anime store manager
Special Guest
Anizawa  Meito
Yes...
This program's motivation is too low!
But, err.. since Lucky Star is an anime about...
the daily lives of normal high school students anywhere,
that is drawn leisurely in a relaxed mood...
Therefore... The Lucky Channel is as well...
If I could name it, it'd be "The Relaxed...
That's no good!
Where'd he go!?
Here I am!
He's fast!
Listen! Do you know the three elements that make an anime successful?
Three elements?
Err, could they be the voice actors, the drawings and the scenarios?
THAT'S NOT IT!
Wah! My back is burning red!
Those are...
"Those are"?
the affection given to a production by the staff and cast,
the time and the size of the budget!
Although this is not something we can do anything about.
Do you hear me!? However good the original is, if the scenario's no good there's no meaning behind it!
However much the voice actor tries - without color, it won't go well!
Ah, Shiraishi, you're lineart.
tn: Pun; His name translates to "White Stone"
Shi-Shiroishi!
Each part makes a desperate effort!
The passion and affection given to a piece while working assiduously...
are what produce superb works!..
Ah... I wonder if that is so...
You! You were Kogami Akira-san this time, right?
"This time"? Akira is Akira now and has always been Akira.
Were you abundantly passionate when you did...
Rou**n, Gao**nger, **teto, Mai**i, huh!?
Huh? What's that?
Ohh!
Ohh! If you regret that,
Nope, no...
burn yourself out as Kogami Akira!
Oh, I told you...
Yes! I will burn myself out as Shiraishi Minoru!
You said that well, Shiraishi!
Well! First of all, for starters... the grip for events!
The end?
You did MC at this one large event the other day, right?
Bye-nii...
So you were watching!?
Of course, as it's my work!
Thanks for the hard work... I'll be going first...
I was given an important task, so I was all tense inside!
Ah! There's still things to do! First of all, you're weak at ad lib!
Ah! With that, Shiraishi, I'm counting on you...
Yes!
You musn't lose to some Sugita!
Shiraishi Minoru
Theatre
Ma'am! Are you unsatisfied with your husband?
Hello! I am Shiraishi Minoru!
Usual Busybody: JEEB
Encoder: Heedly
Now, let's hear it!
Unclear sunshine! Is that a handicap, huh? Chu!
Translation Checking: Senoby, xbe
Editing / QC: ro, Kylaran, Ilaggoodly
It's wrapping, a sale! There's no disadvantage in that, right?
Like these those, those these - at that time, catch n' release!
Assei! Assei! Funny, funny darling darling peace!
Lucky         Star
ra
Shi
shi
I
Somewhat lazy, something's coming out, I love you...
One of those is different-runrun.
A worrywart, high horizontal bar - go-in...
Now get reasonable!
The burning body of who flied away right now is...
what is called a "usual girl"!
I'm surprised, only me!? Take and go, wire-hard noodles extra portion!
He's fast!?
So this is Shiraishi!?
Just a sec!? Isn't he here?
Like that? No way!
He's so easily trickable...
Bon-bon cheering team. Denden, Denniina!
A sloppy one with indifference, you know - how's the heritage?
Yes! The feeling of being there!
Let's say south side up!
haran haran furun furun horon horon  hiren haren horon turou
Take and go! The last one laughing should be me,
because it's a sailor fuku.←Conclusion.
WA WA WAWAWAWA
Even if it's sunday, what will you do with that bad mood?
Due to circuimstances we send this sped-up.
The summer air is nice, cute!
Yes, make it succeed! WTF!?
Try your best, be on high, my darlin' darlin' please!
And so, the ne...
That's boring, Shiraishi!
Stop the conventional previews and such!
Yalttseblakkin, Tenchou!
Alright! Then listen!
Hints on how to become a big voice actor, Number 1:
The first hint!
"Be rolled around long things!"
T-that's small!
Next time, "Many men, Many minds"!
"
Many
men,
minds
"
This is the last for Anizawa, too - so Goodbye.
Finger!