The Day Before the
School Closing Ceremony
My name is Misuzu, Misuzu Kamio.
I have to give you a name, too.
Isn't that the guy who was on the bank?
That we met on our way home from school?
Nobody's interested in a puppet show
like that these days.
Boy, am I hungry!
I've got it! Sky!
I'll call you Sky.
That's where I always stand to look at the sky...
Kieru hikouki gumo bokutachi wa miokutta
Mabushikute nigeta
Kuyashikute yubi wo hanasu
Todokanai basho ga mada touku ni aru
Negai dake himete mitsumeteru
Kodomotachi wa natsu no senro aruku
Ryoute ni wa tobitasu kibou wo
Kieru hikouki gumo oikakete oikakete
Kono oka wo koeta ano hi kara kawarazu
Itsumademo
Massugu ni bokutachi wa aru you ni
Watatsumi no youna tsuyosa wo mamoreruyo
Kitto
Hello.
It doesn't look like he's sick...
Sitting like this, it's almost like we're friends.
It's a beautiful sunset, isn't it?
I wish I could play with someone like that...
Oh! Bye-bye!
Episode 10
What's that black thing?!
He followed me.
It looks like he's too little to fly yet.
I'm surprised he's so friendly.
I gave him a name: Sky.
And we're going to live together.
No way!
Oh, that was quick.
If it's a pet you want, get a cat or dog.
Having something like this around
would be depressing.
That's not true.
He's cute. Here, say hello to Mom.
MY EYE!
Mom was really mad, wasn't she?
I'll sneak you into my room tonight.
Let's apologize to her tomorrow, okay?
Summer vacation starts tomorrow.
I think I'm going to try and invite some
of my classmates over.
But, I wonder if they'd want to play with me...
I think I'll practice what to say.
Uh... I'd love it if you'd
play with me this summer.
Oh, I have remedial classes,
so it'll have to be in the afternoons.
We could go swimming,
or play card games, play with fireworks...
and we could do homework together.
I'd just copy yours, so I'd have it easy...
I'm just joking.
I'd do my best too.
I feel braver now.
I'll be back at noon,
so just play by yourself.
Don't go too far, now.
Piko?
Piko, piko, piko, piko...
Piko piko piko piko piko piko.
Pikori.
Piko?
Piko!
Piko! Piko piko!
Oh! Look, a crow!
Oh, it's true! He's pitch black!
No! He's creepy!
What? He's cute.
Oh, no! He's coming this way!
Oh, he ran away!
Wait!
What's this? A crow!
Where did you come from?
Don't worry.
I won't be mean to you.
No, don't! I can't take that off yet.
If I take it off when I'm grown up,
I'll have magic powers, you see.
There are cars on the roads,
so you'd better be careful.
So long!
Hey, hey, how about going to the beach?
Okay, sure! My bathing suit this year
is super daring.
What?!
I mustn't cry. Hold it in.
Sky...
I'm going to be all alone again
this summer, after all.
I couldn't get anyone to play with me.
They all know about it...
that I'm not a normal girl.
But, I'll do something really fun by myself.
For my independent research I'll do a picture
diary and write about all the fun things I did.
So... So I'll be fine.
It's that person from yesterday.
I really don't want to be all alone.
Such a long vacation...
I don't want to be the only one all alone!
So I'm going to try talking to that guy.
If he seems like a nice person,
I'll ask him to play with me.
Keep smiling, now, and try to act natural.
A-a ramen set!
Hello. Are you alone?
What's going on here?
Why is there another one?
And another one! And another one!
Why, I said it three times!
Just shows ya what a shock it was for me.
But Mom...
Absolutely not!
It's nothing like you said.
Well, you do seem to have pluck.
I like that about ya.
That's right. Yukito is a really nice guy.
All right. He can stay.
You're serious?
Serious? Why, I'm dead serious.
So his name's Yukito Kunisaki, huh?
He seems to get along well with Misuzu,
but she hasn't had another one of
those episodes, ya know?
So he just might be able to
become Misuzu's friend.
Because of that illness of hers,
she hasn't been able to make a single friend.
Besides, he doesn't seem to be a bad guy.
I want to take a chance on him.
Don't you have a different one?
All of the other ones are small.
It smells nice.
Sky...
Yukito and Mom are going to work.
I have to go to school.
You watch the house, okay?
I wonder if they're out...
I bought this for them,
but what should I do with it?
What in the world are ya doing out here?
You should be at home!
But I'm glad I ran into you here.
Why don't ya come with me?
There's going to be a festival here soon.
It's the tenth Summer Festival
since that summer.
I remember it as if it were yesterday.
She sat in front of the chick stand
for a long time, talking to them.
She kept saying "Gao! Gao!"
Ya know, that girl thought that chicks
grow up to be dinosaurs!
But the chicks ya buy at the fairs
don't last long, ya know.
I took her hand and tried to drag her home.
Then, ya know...
That child, who always seemed to believe
that she mustn't cause anyone any trouble...
Well, she stared at me and said,
"I wish I could have one..."
She sounded so apologetic.
Misuzu wasn't a wanted child.
She was born to an unwed couple
who were always bickering.
Then my big sister died,
leaving the father and her daughter.
Then the father forced me to take his child.
I tell ya, I had a rough time of it.
I lived from day to day, believing that
that man would come for his child any day soon.
But, after spending so much time
with that child...
She's always hasty and so clumsy,
but she forgets those things
and is always laughing...
I can't help laughing along with her.
Still, I'm not her mother.
That guy might come to take her away any day.
Then... like it or not,
I'll have to return to living alone.
I didn't want to seem so pitiful
when that happens,
so all I could do was try to protect
my own way of life.
That's why I've never given her
a birthday present.
Every year, I'd make believe I forgot.
I've been debating all this time
about what to do this year.
I won't give it to her, after all!
It's too late for us to become a real family.
That person... and this view...
I'm sure I've seen them somewhere before.
But when? Where?
I just can't remember...
Oh! A cicada flew in through the vent again!
Oh! The soy sauce bottle fell over!
Oh! The salad oil spilled!
Oh! I messed up Yukito's bacon and eggs!
Yukito, is it good?
Yeah.
Really?
It doesn't taste like cicada?
What do you mean by that?!
Nothing. Nothing.
G-gao.
Hey, where are you going?
What a weird crow.
Please make my big sister Saika all better.
Mommy... Are there really gods?
Of course there are.
The gods are watching over you and Saika.
I'm sure your wish will come true.
Oh!
Mommy! This is a god.
It was walking all by itself.
It looks new.
Let's leave it here, because
this is the house of the gods.
Okay.
Oh, my... Are you all by yourself?
You don't fly away, do you? How clever.
If you don't have a home, won't you come
with me to the station?
I think you would make
a good friend for Michiru.
And you'll have all the food you can eat.
You'll be ultra-happy...
I see... You have a home to return to.
I hope you'll keep trying,
so that you'll be able to fly one day.
Just think about how I feel, being called out to
your school each time you have an episode.
I'm sorry.
Yer fine when yer with that
freeloader, aren't ya?
I thought you'd gotten over them.
Well, I'm going back to work.
I'm sorry to trouble you.
Mom was angry, wasn't she?
But you know... She came to school
so quickly. She always does.
Yukito must be waiting.
I wonder if he's worried.
I have to do the best I can
to act as if nothing happened.
I'll just tell him it slipped my mind
that he was waiting.
I want Yukito to think I'm just an ordinary girl.
Misuzu, I'm home.
I'm home!
All of a sudden, Misuzu...
I know.
Sky...
Mom says Yukito has gone away.
I wanted to be with him longer.
But he says he'll walk me to and from
school like before.
So I have to be patient.
I'll still be able to see him every day.
Ouch...
I wonder what's wrong...
Sometimes I get a pain in my back.
Why did you take Misuzu in?
That's why she can't lean on you.
Think about it! For her, you are her only parent!
What a mean thing to say.
He didn't have to tell me. I've always known that.
How long do I have to live like this, I wonder...
Never giving her a birthday gift,
always scared that she'll be gone one day.
I've made up my mind.
I'm making her my daughter.
I'll march into the Tachibana house
and negotiate with them.
Yeah, I thought I'd get away by myself,
visit some hot springs.
What are you thinking? What about Misuzu?
Misuzu, I'll be back.
If I stay with you any longer,
neither one of us will survive.
So, I've decided to run away from you.
Well, then, I guess that's how it has to be.
We have no choice, do we?
I had a fun summer vacation...
a summer vacation with you.
I had fun, too.
Really?
Yeah.
Well, I'd better go.
Bye-bye, Yukito.
He's gone...
I'm going to be all alone. Really alone...
If I'm all alone, I won't be able to keep strong.
What should I do?
I just had a good idea.
I should go on the trip, too.
Then Yukito and I won't have to be separated.
That's a good idea...
It's not that I want to leave this house.
I just have to stay away from you.
Stay strong.
Stay strong, even if you're alone.
Yes, I'll stay strong even if I'm alone.
I'm a tough kid.
That's my girl. Bye, now.
I'm all alone now...
Really, all alone...
Yukito...
Mom...
Ow...
It hurts so much!
I've been alone until today.
And I'll be alone from now on, too.
Even if I do my best, I just cause
trouble for other people.
There's not a single good thing about me.
I should've just continued to resign myself,
like I've always done.
I should've never learned to love anyone.
I'll go to sleep.
I don't have to wake up again.
Why didn't I realize it sooner?
All I needed to do to be happy was
to be here with you, and watch you laugh.
Why?
I thought I wouldn't be able to get up anymore...
Yukito! Where are you?
You came back, didn't you?
Oh, yeah... I remember now.
I was once a human.
I was a human named Yukito Kunisaki.
And I was near Misuzu.
Hey, I got better. I think I'll be okay.
Hey, Yukito?
Misuzu...
I'm here... I'm here.
Yukito!
Misuzu...
Yukito...
Yukito... Yukito!
Misuzu...
I'm going to do my best.
I'll show you.
So, so please don't go anywhere.
Stay by my side.
Yukito...
You'll be all right.
You're a strong girl, so I'm sure
you'll be able to reach it...
that goal that no one else
has been able to reach.
I'm sure you'll make it.
I don't want you to go away. Don't go!
I'll always be near you.
I'll never forget you.
I'll be with you.
Yukito?
Yukito?!
Oh... My mind is getting hazy again.
But Misuzu, I'll be with you.
I'll be with you forever.
Yukito! Wait! Don't go...
Let's stay strong, Misuzu.
Stay strong until you reach the goal, Misuzu.
Okay. I'll stay strong.
Let's stay strong, Yukito.
Shiroku togireta
Yume no kirehashi wo tsukamaete
Shounen wa hashiru
Te wo hanashitara
Doko mademo touku kaze no ne ni
Kiete yuku
Itsuka mieta yasashisa wa mou nai
Hitori fumidasu ashi dake miteru
Asa ni wa kieta ano utagoe wo
Itsumademo kiiteta
Bokura ga nokoshita ano ashiato wo
Itsumademo otteta
Next Episode
How short should I cut it?
I'll let you decide, Mom.
Mommy?
That's right. That's me.
Mommy went far away.
Misuzu...
I'm your father.
No!
If she says she doesn't want to stay with me...
Then it's okay. You can take Misuzu away.
Gao...
Episode 11