Good morning.
What?
Hm?
Oh, I remember. You've been staying here since last night, haven't you.
Breakfast is ready.
Did you bring all these from the house?
Yes.
You might be more suited to travel than I am.
Minagi!
Welcome home!
Michiru.
I was worried about you since you didn't come yesterday.
I'm glad I made that wish.
Wish?
Yeah, I made a wish on the star sand, that you would come back.
I see.
Okay, let's have breakfast, breakfast!
Yay! I'm gonna eat, too.
Hey, restrain yourself a little.
What? Don't be so stingy!
I'm not stingy!
We watched as the vapor trails disappeared
Kieru hikoukigumo bokutachi wa miokutta
We ran away because it was so bright
Mabushikute nigeta
I was so bitter that I released your finger
Kuyashikute yubi wo hanasu
There are still unreachable places in the distance
Todokanai basho ga mada tooku ni aru
That she gazes at with her wishes tucked away
Negai hi dake himete mitsumeteru
The children walk along the summer railways
Kodomotachi wa natsu no senro aruku
Holding in both hands their wishes to take flight
ryoute ni wa tobidatsu kibou wo
We've been chasing and chasing after the disappearing vapor trails
Kieru hikoukigumo oikakete oikakete
Unchanging ever since that day we cleared this hill
Kono oka wo koeta ano hi kara kawarazu
And we'll chase forever
Itsumademo
And just as we are now, standing tall
Massugu ni bokutachi wa aru youni
We will be able to maintain that sea god-like strength
watatsumi no youna tsuyosa wo mamoreru yo
Surely
kitto
Why didn't you wait for me this morning?
I came to get you.
Oh, I had something to do.
I'm sorry.
Well, that's okay.
Are you still having those dreams?
Yeah. Last night's dream was set in a forest at night.
I was talking with someone in the forest.
In a forest? With whom?
I don't know, but there was someone beside me.
I asked that person what an ocean was.
Then, she told me many things about the ocean.
It was a lot of fun just talking to her.
So much that I wanted to wrap her words up and keep them forever.
If you had that much fun, then you should keep sleeping forever.
G-Gao...
Ouch!
episode six
A fan, a fan!
Kunisaki-san.
Welcome home!
I'm home.
How was your day? Did your puppet shows go well?
Well, uh, no.
What are you doing? You're not good for anything, Kunisaki Yukito!
What did you do that for?
Oh, shut up! Who do you think you are, freeloader?
What?!
Why you!
Playing, eating, sleeping.
It's a truly enviable life.
I dreamt of my father last night.
Your father?
A long time ago, we would often watch the night sky here.
My dream was about those days.
Minagi, a god lives on each of those stars and protects us,
and purifies the hearts of those who observe them.
Some time after that, he left home.
After we lost my sister, my parents couldn't get along anymore.
Where is he now?
I heard that he remarried in a town far away.
He gave me this right before he left.
Hey, don't you have to work?
I'm taking a break for now.
Hey, Minagi ran away from home, right?
You can't hide it from me. I'm her best friend, after all.
Things mustn't stay the way they are.
Minagi has to wake up from her dream.
What do you mean by that?
I'm gonna go ahead and go home.
See you. Piko.
Hey.
See you later!
I am sorry to have bothered you.
Not at all. If you have any other questions, don't hesitate to stop by.
All right.
She's started to remember?
She said that she had lost something important.
So that's why she came to visit you.
I just told her that she would remember when she found it.
The rest is up to Minagi-san's feelings.
Welcome home.
Is something wrong?
I've decided to leave this town.
I've stayed too long. It's about time.
I... see...
Why don't you come with me, Tohno?
What?
I want to show you the world -- the real world, not a dream world.
The world...
Let's go together to discover the world.
I'm ready.
Okay. Here we go.
Umm, Kunisaki-san...
May I say something to Michiru, before we leave town?
Don't worry; just follow me.
Okay, we're finally here.
Why?
Michiru said that she didn't want to see you being sad.
Michiru said that?
You must decide for yourself what you are going to do.
If you want, you can really come with me.
I'll take you along, wherever it is I end up...
It's your choice.
You, Tohno Minagi, must decide of your own will.
Mother.
Minagi...
Mother!
There are so many stars out again tonight.
Yeah.
I wonder if Minagi is looking at the stars, too.
Yeah, probably with her mom.
I have to go back now.
Yeah, it's getting late. If you want, I'll walk you home.
Where's your house?
I have a place to go back to.
Michiru?
There is a very lonely girl in the sky.
A girl? In the sky?
That girl only has sad dreams, and has nothing else to look forward to.
Since she can't be happy, she can't help but have sad dreams.
She has battered wings on her back.
Those wings have a very mysterious power.
They are packed with many memories of many people.
She granted me one of those plumes, because there was someone I wanted to find and comfort.
And I thought if she became happy,
then the girl in the sky would become happy too.
I see.
People can't live without memories.
But, you know, you can't live with only memories either.
You have to wake up from dreams sometime.
A dream that you don't wake from will eventually bring sadness.
So, I'm gonna go return the plume.
I don't want to say goodbye to everyone, but I am just a dream.
Stars must disappear at sunrise.
Michiru, are you...
I'm a piece of a dream; I was here just as part of a dream.
But you know, it was a really exciting dream.
I was really happy.
Michiru...
The real Michiru...
wasn't allowed to be born in this world, but...
The first time I met Michiru, it was at the station.
Even after my dad left us, I went to the station every day to get him.
He had already quit his job there,
but I didn't have anything else I could do.
Was it then that your mother started calling you Michiru?
Yes, but as long as I was Michiru, Mother kept smiling.
Hijiri told me it was around that time that you stopped laughing much.
It was one summer afternoon after a rain storm...
I felt like I had seen her somewhere before.
No... like she was always with me.
I'm called Michiru.
I am... I am Minagi.
All of this developed out of my sin.
Your sin?
If I hadn't wished for a little sister...
...nobody would have had to dream.
I might even end up hurting Michiru.
But, I still want her to meet someone, someone important.
Hey, wait up!
Nee-chan, hurry up, or we won't be able to get a spot at the fireworks.
I know, but wait!
Oh, I'd fallen asleep.
You played hard all day, you must've been tired.
You must be hungry.
Shall we have supper at my house?
At your house, Minagi?
It's unusual for my daughter to bring friends home,
so I made a special dinner.
Oh, excuse me. I hadn't even asked your name yet.
Ummm... name...
Yes, your name. Could you tell me your name?
Please tell her.
Are you sure?
Um... um...
My name... my name is Michiru!
Michiru?
Ah, so your name is Michiru, is it?
Ah, umm... I'm actually... I'm actually...
I'm actually...
Michiru.
That's a wonderful name.
Hamburger steak has always been my daughter's favorite, too.
She always used to say that when she got a little sister, she wanted her to have my hamburger steak.
Isn't that right, Minagi?
Yes.
Here, Michiru-chan.
Eat the hamburger steak before it gets cold.
It's your favorite too, right?
Yeah. Thank you!
How is it? Is it good?
Yes. It's really good!
This is my original recipe.
Here you go. I taught Minagi how to make it.
I can eat this?
Yes. It makes me happy if you eat a lot.
Thank you.
Good-bye...
Mom.
Then, I will keep it for you.
Please take good care of it, Minagi.
Sure.
Michiru?
Michiru? Michiru?!
She didn't even say good-bye.
It's too early... We should still have time.
The stars aren't out yet.
She must be over there.
Michiru.
Michiru, it's not safe.
It's not safe over there, so come over here.
No, I have to go now.
I had so much fun until now.. . So I have to go now.
Don't look like that. You have to keep smiling.
Otherwise, I'll be sad.
Michiru...
I was able to be me because of you.
If you go away, I'm sure I won't be able to laugh anymore.
You'll be okay.
You've learned to laugh with other people, not just me.
Hey, Minagi, Kunisaki Yukito. Let's make a promise.
A promise?
The girl with wings continues to have sad dreams in the sky.
I'm going to return to her first.
I'll return to her with lots of good memories from the two of you.
So, if you find her, please tell her many happy things.
And set her free from her sad dreams.
Okay.
Minagi, please keep smiling, always.
Tell me "bye-bye" with a smile.
I can't...
I can't say good-bye with a smile!
Minagi...
But we won't be able to see each other anymore!
It's okay.
Even after you wake up from a dream,
the memories will still be with you.
So, please laugh, and make the memories of me happy ones.
Only you can do that.
Minagi, it's a promise.
Yes...
Are you smiling now?
Yes.
Really?
Then, keep smiling. Say bye-bye while smiling for me.
Are you smiling, Michiru?
Yeah.
Our parting isn't hard on you?
No, it's not hard on me. I'm smiling, after all.
Wouldn't it be wonderful if we kept smiling and the world filled with smiles,
and everybody got to live happily?
Yes.
Minagi?
Michiru, bye-bye.
Thank you, Michiru...
Hey, what's up?
You're not running away from home again, are you?
Is that a rice coupon?
It's a letter from my father.
He is inviting me to come see him during my summer break.
Evidently, I have a little sister.
He and his current wife had a baby girl.
That baby's name...!
To be honest with you, I hesitated a little.
But I've decided to meet her.
Mother encouraged me to go, too.
I see.
Tohno!
Wings that cannot fly have a purpose too!
They're precious memories of the days that you spent flying.
Isn't that right, Michiru?
Do you like bubbles?
Yeah, I love them!
But, but you know, I can't blow them very well.
Shall I teach you how to do it?
Really?
Yes. Let's be friends.
I am Minagi. What is your name?
It's, it's...
Misuzu! I'm here!
Hey, Misuzu! Misuzu!
Snap out of it!
Misuzu!
Open your eyes! Misuzu!
Shiroku togireta yume no kirehashi wo tsukamaete
Catching hold of the scrap of a dream that fades to white
Shounen wa hashiru
The young boy runs
Te wo hanashitara dokomademo tooku kaze no ne ni kieteyuku
When he lets go, it goes on forever, vanishing into the cry of the wind
Itsuka mieta yasashisa wa mou nai
The kindness I could once see is now gone
Hitori fumidasu ashidake miteru
All I see now are the steps my feet take
Asa ni wa kieta ano utagoe wo itsumademo kiiteta
I listened forever to the singer's voice that had disappeared by morning
Bokura ga nokoshita ano ashiato wo itsumademo otteta
Always following the footprints we left behind
Next Episode
Yukito-san, it's not a coincidence that I started having those dreams, is it?
I thought this summer was special.
I wanted to try making friends.
Then, I met you and started having those dreams.
I think they're all connected.
So, I want to work hard to make this summer my happiest.
Because it's the summer that I got to meet you, Yukito-san.
episode seven