Sir Ryuya...
What is it?
I have a favor to ask of you.
I am a little embarrassed, but...
would you look?
Kieru hikouki gumo bokutachi wa miokutta
Mabushikute nigeta
Kuyashikute yubi wo hanasu
Todokanai basho ga mada touku ni aru
Negai dake himete mitsumeteru
Kodomotachi wa natsu no senro aruku
Ryoute ni wa tobitasu kibou wo
Kieru hikouki gumo oikakete oikakete
Kono oka wo koeta ano hi kara kawarazu
Itsumademo
Massugu ni bokutachi wa aru you ni
Watatsumi no youna tsuyosa wo mamoreruyo
Kitto
Now then, here I go...
Just a minute!
What are those?
Can you not see? They are beanbags.
What are you going to do now?
I told you, these are beanbags!
I was able to throw three earlier!
Part 2
Your eyes say that you do not believe me.
It is true! It is true that I was able
to throw three beautifully!
Good night.
Do not go back to sleep!
Go back to bed. I'm on watch here.
Your Mistress is offering to show you
her hard-acquired skills!
It is the duty of a retainer to
respectfully observe!
Don't be so unreasonable!
Then, I will order you!
Wait, wait, wait!
It's not fair to use your authority as a
superior in a time like this!
I can't stand to take any more pointless oaths!
Ouch! Ouch, ouch!
Stop biting me all the time!
That is because you were so rough!
Fine then. I'll watch you, but make it quick.
I do not like the way you said that!
Okay, okay! I want to see it!
I would love to see it,
so please do it right away!
As usual, your words are not sincere.
Well, it is okay.
When you see my skill,
you will change your attitude.
I finally got the trick.
Now that I have mastered it,
it is not anything difficult.
Now I am as skilled a
beanbag thrower as Uraha.
Uh-huh...
I now understand the importance of
striving toward something.
Uh-huh...
Behold!
That was a mistake.
I am not lying. I really did do it.
Nobody said you lied.
I'm watching. Do it as many times as you want.
This time for sure...
Relax your shoulders.
Even a master can't do it well if she's not calm.
Y-you are right.
Here I go.
See, see? I am doing it!
That was impressive!
I do not need consolation.
It's not consolation.
You reached this level because
you made the effort.
It's amazing when a person
doesn't know when to give up.
I am not sure whether that is
a compliment or not...
It's a compliment.
Either way, good work, Kanna.
I want to get even better.
If you keep practicing every day,
I'm sure you'll become a master.
You exaggerate...
It's true.
Will you watch me again, sometime?
Yes, if I may.
Get a little sleep now while you can.
We have a long walk ahead of us again today.
Yeah.
We're going to have to go over
these mountains...
Going through the mountains is the
surest way to evade our pursuers.
I will go fetch some water for us.
What is wrong, Kanna?
Ow!
Forgive me...
I can't, I can't take any more...
I can't... Not anymore...
I can't eat any more...
Hey, you're gonna catch a cold,
sleeping like that!
Hey, don't go back to sleep!
Don't go back to sleep
for the third time either!
Sir Ryuya, you are too easy on her.
That hurt. What do you think you are doing?
Lady Kanna, I trust you are feeling well today.
Do I look like I am feeling well?
Can you not wake me up a little more gently?
Then, the next time, I will adjust my force.
I am telling you not to
pull my pillow out from under me!
You have strange ears.
Do they not get caught in branches
when you run?
With those long ears, you must be able
to hear sounds from pretty far.
You! Are you teasing me?
Wait up! Wait, I tell you!
Hey, wait up! Wait, wait, wait!
Be quiet!
Settle down a minute!
What have you been looking at?
It's a map I found at the market earlier.
It's a lucky find!
What are these wriggly marks like worms?
They're the names of rivers.
Kanna, you can't read?
Nobody taught me.
How is it possible that I can read?
I can't believe Uraha neglected you.
I did not neglect her.
Lady Kanna told me that she would
never learn to read, not from ME.
That was your fault.
I will not let you pretend that you do not
remember those poetry books.
I was only trying to enrich your mind.
How do you expect to enrich my mind
with that teaching method?
What are you talking about?
I was teaching her poems.
You know how there is a bit of hardship
in learning anything...
But Lady Kanna was...
Memorizing one hundred poems in one day
is hardly a BIT of hardship!
You could not take too much time,
as the books contained 4,500 poems in all.
I have not slept in five days.
You must endure until you've memorized
two hundred more.
I'm surprised that you didn't die.
Yes, exactly.
I thought I would end up being killed
if I didn't do something.
So, I threw all my poetry books
into the furnace.
With that, the six precious volumes
of our ancient poetry collection
became fuel for our breakfast.
Breakfast that morning was poetically tasty.
Is it this mouth that speaks such crude words?!
S-Stop it, Uraha.
A mouth that cannot recite a single poem
is a useless possession!
Do not he so irrational!
Shall we sew it shut?!
What are you doing? Help her quickly!
But, even I'm afraid of Uraha, too.
You! How useless you are!
I am so sorry. I lost control of myself!
Oh, no. Don't worry about it.
Why are you forgetting her?
You still sound funny.
Enough!
I am going to go over there and
practice my beanbag throwing.
Staying here any longer will make me irritable.
Then, I will come with you.
There is no need for that!
Why are you hitting ME?
I am taking it out on you!
Kanna! What happened?
A monk... is he not?
He doesn't have any external wounds.
He must've collapsed here.
Sir Ryuya.
May I interrupt?
What? Beanbags again?
No, it is not.
You have something on your mind, do you not?
Something on my mind?
Yes. If you want to say something,
don't keep it inside. Speak up.
Something I want to say...
Then let me say one thing.
Yes, what is it?
There's a worm on top of your head.
You must be the type
beasts and worms are fond of.
Don't just sit there calmly! Help me!
I sensed that something
might be wrong with you.
I, your Mistress, was worried about you,
her retainer, and this is what comes of it?
I'm sorry. I'll tell you the truth, so stay.
You are not going to tease me again, are you?
It's a silly story. Do you really want to hear it?
Tell me anything.
I don't know my parents' faces.
Why ever not?
I think I was abandoned.
Unsui picked me up when
I was crying on the roadside.
Unsui was a traveling monk.
"Traveling monk" sounds nice and all,
but in actuality, he was a homeless monk
who survived on handouts.
The two of us traveled to
many places together.
We went north, south, east and west.
Was he your foster parent, Sir Ryuya?
I wouldn't call him that.
He was very strict.
Unless he was chanting prayers,
he didn't waste his breath.
He never even told me his priesthood name.
It was the summer when
I was about five years old.
We were attacked by villains
while going over a mountain pass.
Unsui was killed with one swing of a sword.
Seeing that monk earlier
brought back that memory.
You had no mother either, Sir Ryuya?
Huh?
Then, it does not seem fair that
only I will meet my mother.
Don't worry about that.
I want you to meet her, too.
Unsui was still chanting a prayer
even after he was slashed,
praying that the killer would be saved
and enter the Pure Land...
even while he was dying,
covered in his own blood.
They didn't kill me.
They told me I wasn't worth
soiling their swords.
Then, I was alone on the roadside once again.
After that, I was alone for a long time.
I did anything necessary to survive.
I stole swords and spears,
and took part in battles.
I even killed people.
Survival was the only thing on my mind.
Until recently, that is.
Recently? Did something happen?
It's called a change of heart.
Humans can change, if given the chance.
I imagine the villains regret what they did.
Huh?
It is natural to feel regret
after killing an admirable priest.
I really doubt he was an admirable priest.
Why do you doubt it?
Because his prayer was heard, the villains
did not kill you. Is that not so?
I see.
True enough, it might have been Unsui
who saved me back then.
I wish I'd realized that sooner.
Then I definitely would've taken a different path.
That is not good.
If you had, I would not have met you.
That's true. I'm glad that I met you, too.
Sir Ryuya.
Sir Ryuya... Uh...
Uh, well...
What is it?
I am not sure where we go from here.
So, I will leave the rest up to you.
H-Hey!
I am embarrassed. Hurry up!
Um, do you really understand
what's going to happen to you?
D-do not make a fool of me.
I know everything.
Uraha told me.
I knew it was Uraha's doing.
Well... you are... To me...
I do not know how to say it, but... it's like...
Uraha told me this.
When the time comes that Ryuya starts to tell
you about his past, do not miss the opportunity.
A man inevitably tells the woman
he loves about his past.
She said so.
She read my actions...
"When Sir Ryuya finishes his story,
loosen your clothing casually."
"It is important, though, not to expose
your breasts completely..."
It came with acting lessons, too?
Did I miss something?
Sir Ryuya, do you, by any chance, prefer men?
Hold it right there.
Oh, I understand now!
Even among straight men,
there are a few useless ones...
Don't go around smearing my good name!
Maybe I got undressed too far?
Alright, I got it.
I will show you that I am a man.
Prepare yourself.
Sir Ryuya, you have
a strange look in your eye!
You're the one who seduced me.
Now be a good girl and take my venom.
You have venom?
All men have venom. We have a lot of
things you don't even know about.
I'll take you by the hand and
teach you EVERYTHING.
Hey! Stop! Stop it!
Stop it!
Uraha! I know you're hiding
around here somewhere! Come out!
As usual, your intuition is good.
Lady Kanna, are you all right?
I am not sure, but it seems it did not go well.
Sir Ryuya!
Did I anger you?
No, I'm not angry.
Uraha, you knew I would
never touch her, didn't you?
I know it was not a very good bet, but...
You'll never find a more harmless man than me.
That is also called being useless.
Oh shut up!
She's sleeping well.
Because she worked hard again today
on her beanbag juggling.
She looks pretty cute when she's sleeping.
We must teach her about men,
before a no-good worm gets to her.
What am I, training material for her?
She's still a child. She hasn't even
played with dolls or beanbags.
Mother...
Are you awake?
I was dreaming.
It was not here. It was somewhere else.
I was wearing something strange,
and I looked different.
Was it really me?
What did you look like?
I do not remember so well.
But Mother and other kind people
were around me.
I was very happy.
It was a good dream, then.
You can turn it into reality.
You'll meet your mother soon.
Then, your dream won't be a dream anymore.
Yes, you are right.
If I pray, I am sure that my wish
will reach the heavens.
Look, look! I am doing it! It's going!
It's still going!
It looks like you need a little more training.
But that was wonderfully done, Lady Kanna.
If you keep training like this,
you will become even better.
Really? Will I become good enough
to show Mother?
Of course!
It's about time to get going, Kanna.
What is wrong? Do you not want
to come with us?
Is that your mother?
I am happy for you.
I wish you a long, happy life.
Shiroku togireta
Yume no kirehashi wo tsukamaete
Shounen wa hashiru
Te wo hanashitara
Doko mademo touku kaze no ne ni
Kiete yuku
Itsuka mieta yasashisa wa mou nai
Hitori fumidasu ashi dake miteru
Asa ni wa kieta ano utagoe wo
Itsumademo kiiteta
Bokura ga nokoshita ano ashiato wo
Itsumademo otteta