What's going on?
Kano!
Wake up!
Hey, Kano!
Don't be so rough with her!
It hurts... It really hurts...
Big Sis...
Wha? Yukito-kun?
Where am I?
What... happened to me?
We watched as the vapor trails disappeared
Kieru hikoukigumo bokutachi wa miokutta
We ran away because it was so bright
Mabushikute nigeta
I was so bitter that I released your finger
Kuyashikute yubi wo hanasu
There are still unreachable places in the distance
Todokanai basho ga mada tooku ni aru
That she gazes at with her wishes tucked away
Negai hi dake himete mitsumeteru
The children walk along the summer railways
Kodomotachi wa natsu no senro aruku
Holding in both hands their wishes to take flight
ryoute ni wa tobidatsu kibou wo
We've been chasing and chasing after the disappearing vapor trails
Kieru hikoukigumo oikakete oikakete
Unchanging ever since that day we cleared this hill
Kono oka wo koeta ano hi kara kawarazu
And we'll chase forever
Itsumademo
And just as we are now, standing tall
Massugu ni bokutachi wa aru youni
We will be able to maintain that sea god-like strength
watatsumi no youna tsuyosa wo mamoreru yo
Surely
kitto
Can you stand?
Yes.
Thank you.
Don't worry about it. But you don't remember anything?
No. I'm sorry.
You don't need to apologize, but...
What happened in that pampas grass field?
You saw it too?
Kano!
What is the meaning of this?!
Okay, listen carefully.
Yes, I am holding her, but this is not what you think it is.
It's not like I gave an innocent girl alcohol and took her into some isolated place-
That's enough!
Wait, wait a minute!
Big Sis?
episode three
I can't say it enough, but I am very sorry.
I wasn't aware of the situation and I got a little upset.
You call that "a little" upset? You old maid.
Did you say something?
Oh no, nothing.
I have to apologize too. I am sorry, Yukito-kun, and uh...
I'm Kamio, Kamio Misuzu.
Oh, yes. I've seen you around, but...
I don't leave a very strong impression on people.
She and I know each other. She's come here for examinations a few times
Anyway, your birthday turned out weird in the end.
Yeah, but I get the feeling it will get even more memorable.
Why don't you become friends with Kano, instead of spending all this time with me?
You might get along pretty well.
You are both a little different...
Yeah, I guess you're right.
What's the matter?
I forgot to get paid for today.
You go ahead and go on home.
Can't you wait till tomorrow?
They may screw it up if I wait till tomorrow.
Hey, where is my pa-
Gone to sleep already?
This place isn't secure at all.
Jeez! I asked you not to turn on the light so suddenly!
Oh, sorry, but without light, I can't examine you well.
Oh, you've grown so much.
Stop it, Big Sis!
Don't touch me there!
It's called palpation and is a legitimate medical examination.
Palpation isn't the same as massaging.
Did you hear that?
What?
Oh, it's a cat.
But we don't have a cat here.
Oh yeah. Then I guess it was just my imagination.
Yes, it must've been.
Then, Kano, let's continue.
Kano?
Hey, What's going on? Kano?
I see, you're back again.
It's been a while.
Again? Stop it already!
Always saying the same words...
This child is my life! My only treasure!
No! Kano is mine!
My precious little sister!
What?
What, what, what?
Why are you hugging me, Big Sis?
You were half asleep.
You started to hug me, so I embraced you in return.
I don't remember that at all.
That's why I've been telling you to go to bed earlier.
Yeah, but can we stay like this just a little while longer?
You held me like this when Dad passed away.
Yeah, that's right.
Big Sis, you smell good.
Oh! A cicada flew in through the vent again!
Oh! The soy sauce bottle fell over!
Oh! The salad oil spilled!
Oh! Yukito-san's bacon and eggs just had a horrible accident!
Hey, Misuzu!
I won!
Yukito-san?
Is something wrong?
Something happened to this, didn't it?
Nothing, nothing.
Why are you looking at me like that, as though you're shocked that I'm actually eating it.
I'm not looking like that. No, no.
Yukito-san, is it good?
Yeah.
Really?
It doesn't taste like cicada?
What do you mean by that?!
Nothing, nothing.
Yukito-san?
We're here.
Oh, sorry.
What's wrong? Is something bothering you?
Kind of.
Is it about last night?
Well, this and that.
See you later, then!
Okay.
G-gao!
Hey.
At least do enough to earn your wages.
I've done everything.
Then, I have more. Come over here.
Why are you looking at me like that?
If you want to say something, say it.
A pay raise is out of the question, by the way.
It's nothing like that.
Then, what is it?
Actually, it's about last night-
- Hey...
Have you seen Potato?
Potato?
Now that you mention it, I haven't seen him.
Yeah, I've been looking for him, but I can't find him!
Potato!
Potato, come on out!
I wonder where Potato went off to?
It's almost sunset.
What's wrong?
No, nothing. Let's keep looking.
I guess he's not here either
I can't think of anywhere else to look.
Can't you use your magic to find him?
What?!
I don't think my magic works like that.
Is that so?
When I was given this bandana,
I was told to keep it on until I'm grown, and not to ever take it off till then.
Then I'll grow up to be able to use my magic.
Who gave it to you?
I was so little, I don't remember,
but I've been wearing it ever since.
It was really difficult at times like swim meets and health checks,
and I was teased sometimes too.
I see.
But you see, Big Sis always saved me!
That's how I was able to make it this far.
We've come all the way to school.
I don't think he could possibly be here...
Huh? What is it? Wait up!
Hey, Yukito-kun, what's going on all of the sudden?
I know where Potato is.
Really?
He is right over there.
Right over there? You mean at school?
Yeah, he should be in here.
What? In this bush?
Are you sure?
Potato!
We finally found you!
Jeez, don't frighten me like this.
But what are you doing here?
And Yukito-kun, how did you know that he was here?
That is... well... uh...
Well, it's like a sort of magic.
Right?!
Now listen, Potato.
Don't ever wander off without telling me, okay?
If only your actions lived up to your response.
But what a relief!
Kano.
Yes?
You really don't remember anything about last night?
No. I'm sorry, really...
No. Don't worry about it.
Yukito-kun. Would you listen to something?
Yeah, you can tell me anything.
I remember almost nothing about my mother.
I've been told that she was never very healthy.
She fell ill right after she gave birth to me.
And she passed away when I was about three.
Dad told me that Mom was a lot like me.
But I have a hard time picturing that.
Oh, but, but, I wasn't that lonely.
Big Sis was like a Mom, and I had Dad.
But Big Sis didn't have a Mom that whole time.
I realized recently how unfair that was.
Dad was always busy with his clinic, and then he got sick himself.
The only thing I could do was to watch.
Even now, Big Sis works and takes care of me,
but I can't really help.
I'm not of much help either.
That's not true, not at all!
If... if I can ever use my magic,
I... would like to see Mom.
I want to apologize to her in person, for many things.
Rather than apologizing, you should thank her.
You are here because of her.
If someone said to me, "I'm sorry that you gave birth to me,"
I would be furious.
Oh, I see.
I guess so!
What is your Mom like?
She's not here either.
A long time ago, she went to the same place your Mom is.
I see.
My mother was looking for a girl in the sky.
A girl?
Yeah. "Beyond this sky, there is a girl with wings."
She used to say that a lot.
I'm looking for the girl, too.
Then when I can fly someday, I'll look for her.
I'm home.
You're sure late.
Are you alone?
She's in her room.
She's not feeling too good, so she's in bed.
Don't you have to be there for her?
If I'm there, she won't rest well.
You're her mother. It shouldn't bother her.
We may be mother and daughter, but we do have issues.
Misuzu, I'm coming in.
Oh, Yukito-san.
You're not feeling well?
No, but it's not that bad.
Sorry, I couldn't go get you today.
Don't worry. You're busy, too.
Well, okay...
But you must really like dinosaurs.
Why does she like dinosaurs so much?
Who knows? She's always liked them, ever since she was a little girl.
You don't know your daughter very well, do you?
Didn't you forget that it was her birthday yesterday?
Hey, is there anything weird about her during the day?
She's always a little weird, isn't she?
That's not what I mean.
Oh, if there's nothing, it's all right.
What are you talking about?
Enough with the gloomy talk!
Let's get started on the main event of the day.
An erotic confessions corner!
- So we're doing that after all?!
Oh, no, no. Just saying the title turns me on!
- What are you, a nymphomaniac?
Romantic?
Yeah, romantic.
Because, dinosaurs thrived for eons, but they went extinct.
They came to an end.
Somehow, that tears me up and makes me emotional.
Are you still having the dreams?
Yeah, I still do.
I'm traveling backwards through my dreams.
What do you mean by that?
I can't explain it well, but I can tell...
The scent of the breeze and its sensation on my skin...
The way the air flows and the seasons change...
They all show me that I'm going back in time.
I've never heard of dreams like that.
Yukito-san.
Where do you think my dreams are taking me?
Okay, are you ready?
Potato, don't you get hit by mistake.
So it's watermelon splitting today, huh?
Yeah, Kano wanted to do it.
Don't you think you're spoiling her a little?
Here I go!
See you tomorrow!
It's deserted.
It'll be impossible to make money here-
Kunisaki Yukito!
Yukito-san!
Don't crash into me every single time!
Why didn't you come yesterday?
Yesterday?
We were waiting for you... Minagi missed you.
I didn't mind
You're putting up a strong front again!
I'm sorry. I got too busy yesterday.
To make up for it, you will live here starting today!
Don't be silly.
You wanted me to leave the town to start with anyway.
That has nothing to do with this!
Wow! He got up!
I can't figure it out.
Looks like I win.
It's really a wonder.
You have such a wonderful talent, Kunisaki-san.
I applaud you.
I have just a touch of telekinetic ability.
Telekinetic ability...
There are so many wonders in this world...
I have a special thank you gift for you.
Ta-da!
Kunisaki-san?
A girl with wings?
Yeah, I'm looking for the same girl my mother was trying to find.
Do you think I'm silly?
I had a picture book like that when I was a little girl.
A picture book?
In that book, there was a girl with pure white wings on her back.
As a little girl,
I dreamt of flying through the sky with her one day.
It's not silly at all,
even if you're journeying in search of that girl.
Because surely everyone has somewhere they want to reach.
I can tell the stars are going to be beautiful again tonight.
Minagi!
Help me out! I can't do it right at all!
I'm coming, Michiru.
Somewhere I want to reach?
I'm done with today's homework!
Yukito-san!
Let's play cards. Cards.
Why, all of a sudden?
I've always wanted to play cards with you.
Play by yourself.
We have come from a faraway planet-
I wanna play cards.
I wanna play cards!
I wanna play cards-
Misuzu! Are you here?
Kano disappeared again. Is she here?
How about the shrine?
I've already looked there. I'll try the school.
Can you two go that way?
Yeah.
Yukito-san, do you have any idea?
We just have to look anywhere we can think of.
Kano!
- Kirishima-san!
Potato?
I think he's telling us to follow him.
The shrine again?
But she said she'd already looked there.
Kano!
Hey, are you all right?
Sacrifice her... My only treasure...
Kano!
Then I would rather... with my own hands...
Hey, Kano!
Shiroku togireta yume no kirehashi wo tsukamaete
Catching hold of the scrap of a dream that fades to white
Shounen wa hashiru
The young boy runs
Te wo hanashitara dokomademo tooku kaze no ne ni kieteyuku
When he lets go, it goes on forever, vanishing into the cry of the wind
Itsuka mieta yasashisa wa mou nai
The kindness I could once see is now gone
Hitori fumidasu ashidake miteru
All I see now are the steps my feet take
Asa ni wa kieta ano utagoe wo itsumademo kiiteta
I listened forever to the singer's voice that had disappeared by morning
Bokura ga nokoshita ano ashiato wo itsumademo otteta
Always following the footprints we left behind
Next Episode
Yukito-kun, I am writing this to you because I think you will believe me.
I've decided to go to the skies after all.
I feel that this will allow everyone to be happy.
I have a feeling that I will be able to meet the person you are looking for too.
I don't know how long it will take, but I will bring her back with me.
It would make me happy if you helped out Big Sis until then.
episode four