How long has it been since you came here?
I imagine you have gotten used to the shrine.
My robes are splendid, as you can see,
but in reality, I am as good as imprisoned here.
A winged person is a messenger of the gods.
In times of famine or disease, you are able to
communicate directly with the gods
through your spiritual powers and prayers.
I assumed that your living conditions
would be better.
Just because I have wings, that does not mean
I am a messenger of the gods.
Where are your wings?
I am hiding them. Normally,
I look just like a human.
What do you think you are doing?!
Well, since it was shaped so well...
Do you touch everything that is well shaped?
How rude you are!
What is so funny, Uraha?
The way you were so embarrassed,
Lady Kanna...
Whatever. But must you always
approach so stealthily?
You called Sir Ryuya over again today.
You must have grown quite fond of him.
N-No way!
I am just trying to teach some manners to this
rude, impolite, despicable and shameless one.
Truly, there has never been anyone
quite like Sir Ryuya.
Kieru hikouki gumo bokutachi wa miokutta
Mabushikute nigeta
Kuyashikute yubi wo hanasu
Todokanai basho ga mada touku ni aru
Negai dake himete mitsumeteru
Kodomotachi wa natsu no senro aruku
Ryoute ni wa tobitasu kibou wo
Kieru hikouki gumo oikakete oikakete
Kono oka wo koeta ano hi kara kawarazu
Itsumademo
Massugu ni bokutachi wa aru you ni
Watatsumi no youna tsuyosa wo mamoreruyo
Kitto
Episode 8
Lady Kanna, this is for you.
I found this earlier in a back vault
of the wine cellar.
It is highly unusual to find ice
in the height of the summer.
I felt that I should inform you,
so I brought this for you.
Oh, that is strange.
That shed is an ice cellar.
It is a serious crime
to enter without permission.
Oh my, my.
Dangerous, dangerous.
I knew you two were in this together...
How cold!
Sir Ryuya, you should try it too.
Eating offerings to Lady Kannabi
is also a serious crime.
You're eating it yourself
as you speak, aren't you?
The three of us together, eating ice. It is as if...
...as if we are a desperate family with no
savings, surviving on snow under the eaves.
That is such a pleasant metaphor!
What is a family like?
Yes, well, if I were to describe it...
Hey, do not come so close. It is too hot!
Wait, wait. Do not be so sulky. Come closer.
I told you not to come so close!
You do not need to go that far.
Why are you here too?
Uh, I just felt like it.
Both of you! Get away from me!
Are you teasing me?
Being a family means you can
lean on one another.
How long has Kanna been living like this?
Since you took your position here,
her life has become so much brighter.
That isn't what I mean.
How long has she been living in this shrine?
I do not know. I have not been here
quite six months yet.
I've only heard that she has been held captive
like this with no one to talk to
and has been moved around from
place to place since she was a toddler.
Sir Ryuya.
It is time for the changing of the guards.
Oh...
Why are you so nervous?
Well, since we came here, I have been uneasy...
I feel that, if we get too close to Lady Kannabi,
we may receive divine punishment.
As far as I can see, there is no sign
of such a thing.
I hear that many people loathe and fear
the winged people.
I wish to return to regular duty
as soon as possible.
Is anything wrong, Kanna?
Sir Ryuya, do you have dreams?
Sometimes.
What is it? Did you have a scary dream
and cannot sleep?
It was a dream about long ago.
I, as a small child, am sitting
in the dark, just like now.
I cannot see anything.
I cannot even tell if my own body exists.
I am so scared and so lonely, yet I cannot cry.
Every day is like that.
I sometimes see a warm light.
It is the figure of a person.
However, if I try to catch up with it,
it disappears.
I see the same dream not just once,
but over and over.
Do you know who it is, Sir Ryuya?
It must be your mother.
I do not remember anything about my mother.
A dream is a memory of scenes from the past.
So, even if you do not remember,
you sometimes see it in your dreams.
That means that my body remembers?
Then, it does not necessarily
mean it is a bad dream.
I want to see her...
I never thought being alone
would be as difficult as this.
It has been decided that Kannabi-no-Mikoto
shall be transferred to the north shrine
in order to say prayers for an abundant harvest.
Silence!
Her departure shall be on
the midsummer Day of the Ox.
Are we to follow Kannabi-no-Mikoto
to her new residence as well?
No. We are to remain and follow the orders
to cultivate the land.
I heard. It happens at
this time of year, every year.
I didn't know until this morning.
I will have to part with you and Uraha soon.
We do not have many more days.
Are you all right with that?
With what?
I am asking if you can accept being
separated from Uraha and me.
I am sure there will be interesting people there.
They won't be Uraha or me.
Do not be arrogant!
Do I look so spineless?
I will be fine without you.
I have been living alone like this all along.
Weren't you lonely?
Don't you want to see your mother?
I am saying that there are some things that
will not come true no matter how hard I wish.
Is your mother dead?
She is not dead.
No, she is not dead.
I am certain Mother is
thinking of me somewhere...
Uraha, Kanna is...
I am busy!
What are you doing?
Can you not see? I am preparing for a journey!
The only one being transferred is Kanna.
We're supposed to stay here.
That is why I am taking her away before then.
It is so inhumane for Lady Kanna
to keep living like this.
Can I ask why you're
so concerned about Kanna?
I would like to ask the
same question of you, Sir Ryuya.
Hmm... If I have to come up with an answer...
I don't know anyone else who's so fun to tease.
Yes, that is true, is it not?
Hey, Kanna. Wake up.
Good morning.
Intruder!
Shh! Don't make noise. I have to talk to you.
Don't you want to see your mother?
In my duties, I must never disobey
Kannabi-no-Mikoto's orders.
Therefore, if you order me to find your mother,
I will risk my life to do it.
Will you give me the order as my mistress?
Are you agreeable with that?
It's your choice.
In that case, I order you to
guide me to my mother.
Senior Assistant Lieutenant of the
Outer Palace Guard, Ryuya,
humbly swear to fulfill
Kannabi-no-Mikoto's command.
Lady Kanna!
Hurry!
Sir Ryuya! Can we please take a short break?
It does not seem that they have noticed.
It's only a matter of time.
There's going to be a commotion soon.
It is a bit late to realize this now, but
we have acted very rashly, have we not?
Don't start having second thoughts now.
Look there!
What is happening at the shrine?
I don't know,
but it looks like we should move away
from here as soon as possible.
What is it?
Apparently we're surrounded.
Kanna, Uraha, run as fast as you can!
Run!
Throw down your sword.
Answer me honestly.
You're from Edo, right?
Why are you pursuing Kannabi-no-Mikoto?
I don't know. We were ordered to.
What were your intentions with
Kannabi-no-Mikoto?
Whose orders are you following?
I don't know! We were just ordered
by our superior!
I see.
Stop it!
You! Did you intend to kill him?
If I don't kill him, he'll kill me.
Shame on you! How despicable!
Do you kill people without any thought?
Lady Kanna...
I do not wish to be protected by such a villain!
I hereby order you.
As long as I am your Mistress,
I will not allow you to kill anyone from now on.
Understood?
Yes. I understand.
But do you really think we'll be able to
make it through without killing anyone?
I trust it will be an easy task for you, Sir Ryuya.
Don't make it sound so easy.
Where did you find a kimono like this?
I borrowed it from a clothesline by the river.
Of course, I left some money.
You look good in it, Kanna.
D-Do you think so?
You have strange tastes...
Lady Kanna is so funny!
While she was changing,
she said that she did not wish you to see her
if the kimono was unbecoming on her.
Silly! Do not mention that!
This is not so tasty, is it?
When the three of us eat dried food
like this, it is as if...
As if we're court nobles being demoted
to some back country,
moistening our food with tears of frustration.
Such an elegant metaphor, is it not?!
Those are beanbags. They were in the kimono.
But, beanbags made with cloth inside
are rather unusual.
Normally, they would be made
with stones inside,
but I imagine they were made out of
consideration for the safety of children.
Do you think I can do it, too?
I am sure you will be good at it
with a little practice.
You cannot be expected
to do something well at first.
Patience is important for everything.
M-My hands were not steady, that is all.
You must not be so forceful.
Just at your eye level...
I know!
I never knew she was this clumsy.
Oh, Lady Kanna, poor thing...
Do not be so dramatic!
I heard that your mother is confined
on a sacred mountain in Kishu.
Where is Kishu? Is it far from here?
Yes, it is... especially if we walk
along the mountains.
Let us proceed carefully, without rushing,
so that we will not be caught by the pursuers.
Ouch!
Let me...
It's been a whole month, but you haven't
gotten any better at all.
Sometimes I can do it well.
I did it three times in a row, three days ago.
Oh, that is impressive.
You are insulting me, are you not?
When we sit around a fire
in the mountains like this...
...it's like I'm some lady's man
who kidnapped a princess,
and is regretting it because
he realizes how naive she is.
That is such a free-spirited metaphor, is it not?
It is not really a metaphor. It is almost a reality.
We are practically in Kishu.
We will not have this kind of life
for much longer.
Why are they so joyous?
When they dance like that,
they can forget about their problems.
That is not all.
They all believe that their wishes
will reach the heavens.
Who will deliver them to the heavens?
Well...
I have wings, but I cannot fly.
I have tried it many times since I was a little girl.
Flying to the heavens is out of the question,
for I cannot float even to tree branches.
They are useless wings.
Still, I wonder if I pray,
if my wish will reach the heavens.
It will.
It's enough just to hold your wish in your heart.
Your wish is sure to come true.
Isn't that right, Uraha?
It certainly is!
Hey, Uraha, you're tickling me.
Hey!
It is so quiet.
Don't drop your guard.
We should be within the bounds
of the sacred mountain.
It seems that a joining boundary is in place.
Please be quiet.
I feel it is this way.
You sense it?
Yes, it is just an intuition.
Don't utter a sound.
Warrior Priests, huh?
Women are banned here!
You look like a country soldier.
What business do you have on this
sacred mountain?!
I was wandering through the night merrily.
It seems that I was tricked by a wild fox!
Or was it a wild tanuki?
We cannot let you go.
If you cross the boundary,
we can no longer touch you.
Sir Ryuya, behind you!
I will not allow you to kill anyone from now on.
Sir Ryuya!
Stay away!
You, what are you scheming?
I will not let you see Yaobikuni.
Yaobikuni...
Sir Ryuya!
You came through!
I am so glad! It seems the worst is over!
How long have I been sleeping?
For a full day.
Do not worry!
We have crossed the joining boundary.
The monks will not be able to reach us.
I see.
I will go fetch some water.
Sir Ryuya.
Are you hurt, Kanna?
I said to you not to kill anyone,
but that was... I realize now, I...
I am loyal to you.
I will follow your orders
no matter what they are.
For example, if you order me not to die,
I will never die.
Then, I will order you.
No, this is not an order. It is my plea.
Sir Ryuya, please do not die.
I won't. I promise.
Is this it?
Yes. I feel something.
Is Mother here?
Most likely.
Out of the way.
Stop.
If you are trying to drag me into a war,
know that you will not leave here alive.
I am Kannabi-no-Mikoto's attendant, Ryuya.
Forgive me, but I assume you are
Kannabi-no-Mikoto's mother.
Kanna!
Are you my mother?
My wings. They cannot flutter or fly.
But, if you have the same wings...
Kanna!
Mother!
You there, Ryuya!
Take Kanna off this mountain right away.
Shiroku togireta
Yume no kirehashi wo tsukamaete
Shounen wa hashiru
Te wo hanashitara
Doko mademo touku kaze no ne ni
Kiete yuku
Itsuka mieta yasashisa wa mou nai
Hitori fumidasu ashi dake miteru
Asa ni wa kieta ano utagoe wo
Itsumademo kiiteta
Bokura ga nokoshita ano ashiato wo
Itsumademo otteta
Next Episode
What are your intentions with me?
We will take you away from here.
Then you will live happily ever after
with Lady Kanna.
Mother...
Let us set up a small residence
somewhere quiet.
Dreams are not all sad.
I have enjoyed myself.
Kanna!
Why?
Why does everyone... leave me?
Episode 9