What in the heck happened?
I was shocked when I found you on the floor.
I got dizzy all of a sudden
and my feet got tangled.
I'm sorry that I made you worry.
Maybe you're slightly anemic.
What do you want to do?
Do you want to go see a doctor?
No, I'll be all right. I think I just need some rest.
The remedial classes have started.
Missing one day isn't going to
make any difference.
You should rest today.
Okay.
What about your job today?
I'll take the day off.
July 21 (Thur)
Weather: Clear
I went to school with Yukito.
It was really fun.
July 21 (Thur)
Weather: Clear
I went to school with Yukito.
It was really fun.
I played with Yukito.
A cicada flew into Yukito's breakfast.
I went to the train station with Yukito.
I went to the shrine with Yukito.
You shouldn't look in someone else's diary.
Don't you have anything else to write about?
I think I'm doing a good job, though...
Well, to be blunt, you don't have
any talent for diary-writing.
So from now on, instead of writing about
what you did, write about what you want to do.
But then, it's not a diary.
Yes it is,
because I'll make all of those things come true.
I want to go to the ocean... with you, Yukito.
We've never gone down to the beach together.
I want to dig in the sand and
pick up pretty seashells.
You can see the ocean anytime, can't you?
Gao!
Ouch!
Fine.
I'll go to the beach with you.
Yeah!
We watched the vapor trails
As they disappeared
We ran from the blinding light
In vexation we let go
There are still places she cannot reach
She gazes with wistful eyes
Children walk along the tracks in summer
In both hands, their wish to take wing
We chased and chased vanishing vapor trails
Since the day we climbed over that hill
Unfailingly
And just like we have always
Stood straight and tall
We will stay as strong as the god of the sea
Surely
The girl said she wanted to see the ocean.
But I couldn't take her.
Episode 7
Misuzu fainted?
Yeah, she hasn't been feeling well all day.
She's resting in her room.
Could you go check on her?
If she sees my drunken face,
she'll feel even worse.
Hey, I brought some sushi.
Let's enjoy it together.
That really hurt, you know.
Why did you take Misuzu in?
Huh?
Oh, so she told you about that...
I didn't choose to take her in. I was forced into it.
I said I didn't want her.
That's why she can't lean on you.
Think about it! For her, you're her only parent!
She has an episode whenever
she gets friendly with someone.
She and I never got emotionally close.
That's why this is working.
What is a family, I wonder...
I don't know because I'm not her real mom.
Ugh... This one isn't good.
The girl dreams. The first one is about the sky.
The dreams keep going back in time.
The dreams plague her.
She starts to feel pain for no reason.
Eventually, she starts to lose her memories.
She will even forget the one she loves most.
Extra Thick
Peach Nectar
She will even forget the one she loves most.
And in the morning after the final dream,
she will die.
She is always alone.
If she becomes attached to anyone,
both will fall ill.
Neither will survive.
So the girl told me, "Stay away from me."
She was a kind and strong girl.
That's why I survived.
But she...
There is a girl with wings in the sky.
She is always alone.
She perishes, never having a chance to grow up,
repeating such sad dreams over and over again.
You're going on a trip?!
Yeah, I thought I'd get away by myself,
visit some hot springs.
What are you thinking? What about Misuzu?
She's all yours!
If you don't get too close to her,
she should be all right.
Wait!
She's having dreams.
The dreams are doing this to her.
Huh?!
I remembered a story my mother told me.
My mother met a girl with the same
sickness a long time ago.
Misuzu will start to forget:
About me and about you.
And when she has her last dream,
she's probably going to die.
Now, listen...
There are jokes you can make,
and those you shouldn't.
It's not a joke! Misuzu is...
Move!
Hey!
I'm coming in.
Oh, you're up?
Yeah, I just woke up.
I heard Mom's voice.
Yeah, she's going away for a while.
Oh, I see...
I love my mom.
Let's go to the ocean.
We're not in any hurry, so take it easy.
Yeah.
Oh, a crow.
Misuzu!
Hey, are you all right?
Yeah...
I'm okay.
V.
I take this road all the time,
but I don't remember the ocean being so far.
What's wrong?
I'm sorry.
I... again...
You're having another attack?
I'm sorry...
I'll be all right soon.
We'll try the ocean tomorrow.
Are you all right now?
Yeah.
You know...
I had another dream last night.
This one was a happy one.
The night sky was really bright.
I think it was a festival.
I was watching it from afar.
I see.
Hey, Yukito...
What is it?
There's a connection between the person
you're looking for and my dreams, isn't there?
I don't know... Probably not.
I thought about this a lot, and
I think I know the answer.
Would you listen to me?
It's another me in my dreams.
And she's suffering now.
I'm going to try to see more dreams.
Because they might help me understand.
Then, maybe I can help her.
Yukito, it's not a coincidence that
I started having dreams, is it?
I thought this summer was special.
I wanted to try to make friends.
Then, I met you and started having the dreams.
I think they're all connected, don't you think?
So, I want to do my best,
because I want to make
this summer the best one.
Because it's the summer I met you.
Hey.
I'm okay now. I feel much better.
Misuzu!
Huh? I wonder what's wrong?
My legs won't move.
Maybe we should call Hijiri.
Or should I take you to a hospital?
No, I don't think a doctor can fix me.
You know it, right?
That my dreams are making me this way.
Well...
I had another dream last night.
It was about a journey.
A journey?
I was looking for something.
I was walking through a forest
for days and days.
It was hard but I kept going.
I had someone special with me.
Someone special?
I know it. Every time I have a dream,
I get weaker.
And then, in the end I will be just like
the girl in the sky...
Stop it! That's not going to happen!
I got scolded.
Don't think about your other self.
First, you have to get better.
Yep. I'm a tough kid!
Yukito!
Yukito, Yukito!
What happened?
Nothing...
If nothing happened, your face
wouldn't look like that.
My face has always looked like this.
Misuzu, go back to bed.
I can't leave you here.
I'll be okay, really. Don't give me a hard time.
Okay...
What's with this scar?
It hurts!
Misuzu! Hang on!
Misuzu!
I'll be all right.
I'll be better soon.
Please stay here with me.
But if I'm close to you...
I'll be okay. Please stay here...
Why does everyone leave me?
How are you feeling?
I'm okay now. How about you, Yukito?
I'm fine.
What do you think?
Should I call Hijiri? Or Kano?
Minagi is out of town, so maybe
someone from your school...
No, that's okay. I don't want to bother anyone.
Don't lie. Don't you want friends?
You don't like being alone, do you?
I want you. As long as you're here,
I don't need anything.
Do you not like that?
Don't be silly.
I want to go to the ocean with you.
I want to play on the beach, run and
splash water at each other...
And then, in the end, tell each other,
"See you tomorrow..."
But I have to be patient now.
Then, it'll be even better when we
finally do get to go.
Hang in there, Misuzu!
Misuzu...
What?
I think I should leave soon.
If I stay with you any longer,
neither one of us will survive.
So, I've decided to run away from you.
I'll leave this town and go somewhere
where I won't see you again.
By yourself?
Yeah, we got too close to each other.
Well, then, I guess that's how it has to be.
We have no choice, do we?
I should've played by myself like this all along.
Maybe...
I had a fun summer vacation...
a summer vacation with you.
I had fun, too.
Really?
Yeah.
There aren't any more buses today?
Yukito.
Um, my dream this morning.
I was locked up in a room alone.
I was sad.
I was waiting for someone to come
and take me out.
I... I want to go with you.
Can't I please go with you?
It's not that I want to leave this house.
I just have to stay away from you.
If I'm away from you, you'll heal.
So, that's why I can't be with you.
Yeah, I see. I understand.
I'm sorry I said such stupid things.
No...
Then, bye-bye. Take care.
You, too. Stay strong.
Stay strong, even if you're alone.
Yes, I'll stay strong even if I'm alone.
I'm a tough kid.
That's my girl. Bye, now.
Misuzu...
What are you thinking now, Yukito?
Do you want your audience to laugh?
Otherwise, they won't move.
Ocean Taxi Ferry Depot
Just wishing for them to move isn't enough;
you have to reach further.
Then, and only then,
will the puppet move for you.
You did it!
The girl said she wanted to see the ocean.
But I couldn't take her.
Yukito, I want you to save her this time for sure.
There is a wish that was never granted,
here in this puppet.
My mother, and her mother before her,
managed to put their power into this puppet
before they perished.
For the day someone is ready
to release her wish...
So, I want to become one of the wishes.
How you use it is up to you.
You can forget about the girl in the sky.
But Yukito, you are sure
to meet a girl somewhere.
If you really feel that you want to help her,
then, put your heart and soul into the puppet.
Because I will be with you.
Put my heart and soul into the puppet?
There's something wrong with this guy.
Maybe he got sick in this heat.
Let me go!
Please, help me.
What?
I want you to watch the show and tell me what
I can do to make it fun, make people laugh.
Wow, cool!
Strange!
But it's not all that funny, is it?
You should do more instead of
just making it walk.
Make it like a story.
Like, make it dance.
D-Dance?
It has to be more original.
Wow!
Extra Thick
Peach Nectar
That was funny!
It was funny and cute!
Okay. Thanks a lot for staying this long.
Then good luck, Mister!
Bye now!
Misuzu, I'm back.
I won't go anywhere.
I'll stay with you and I'll make you laugh.
Yukito...
I learned the trick. It'll be really funny for sure.
So, pay close attention.
Misuzu!
Watch this! Please laugh!
Why didn't I realize it sooner?
All I needed to do to be happy was
to be here with you, and watch you laugh.
If I'd done that, I would've been happy.
I'll never go anywhere.
Stay with me and keep smiling.
Okay? Misuzu?
Yukito, remember now what it is
that you need to do.
I... I want to be with Misuzu.
I want to do it all over, if I can,
from back when I first met her.
Then, this time, I'll stay with her...
Why?
I thought I wouldn't be able to get up anymore...
Yukito? Where are you?
You came back for me, didn't you?
Hey, I got better. I think I'll be okay.
Hey, Yukito?
Shoryaku 5
Ouch...
You, what are you doing in such a place?
If you have time to talk, get off of me!
You are not from here, are you?
I am Ryuya, Senior Assistant Lieutenant
of the Outer Palace Guard.
What about you? Where in the world
did you come from?
You don't know my name?
No. We just met.
I see. I guess I'm not that well-known.
I am Kanna.
That's a strange coincidence.
The winged person who ordered me to
become a guard... her name is Kanna, too.
Oh... It certainly is a strange coincidence.
That's for sure.
How rude!
Catching hold of the remnant
Of a dream that fades to white
The young boy runs
When he lets go
It vanishes forever with
The cry of the wind
A gentleness, once so apparent, is now gone
My eyes remain on the steps my feet take
Hearing forever the sounds of singing
That had faded away by morning
Always following in the footsteps we left behind
Next Episode
A winged person is a messenger of the gods.
In times of famine or disease, you are able to
communicate directly with the gods
through your spiritual powers and prayers.
Being a family means you can lean
on one another.
I want to see her.
I never thought being alone
would be as difficult as this.
Episode 8