My child, heed my words.
The story I'm about to tell is a very important one.
It is the story of a long, long journey, a story that will be passed on from parent to child forever.
Boy, am I starved!
Boy, am I hungry!
That's all you've been saying.
You walk too slowly. Hurry up, will you?
Hey, you guys!
Do you know what a ramen set is?
I'm absolutely starving right now!
I desperately want to eat a ramen set!
But...
Unfortunately, I'm broke. So...
Hey! It's time for a fun puppet show.
You can pay me afterwards.
What do you think? Isn't it great? Isn't it interesting? Isn't it fun?
What a filthy doll!
How ugly...
Can't it do anything else?
Take that! And that!
Kids are best when they're honest
You can pay me as much as you want.
That's why we're honestly saying it's ugly.
Why should we pay money for something like this?
Are you crazy?
Hey! You brats!
Run!
You brats, hold on!
It's hot...
We watched as the vapor trails disappeared
Kieru hikoukigumo bokutachi wa miokutta
We ran away because it was so bright
Mabushikute nigeta
I was so bitter that I released your finger
Kuyashikute yubi wo hanasu
There are still unreachable places in the distance
Todokanai basho ga mada tooku ni aru
That she gazes at with her wishes tucked away
Negai hi dake himete mitsumeteru
The children walk along the summer railways
Kodomotachi wa natsu no senro aruku
Holding in both hands their wishes to take flight
ryoute ni wa tobidatsu kibou wo
We've been chasing and chasing after the disappearing vapor trails
Kieru hikoukigumo oikakete oikakete
Unchanging ever since that day we cleared this hill
Kono oka wo koeta ano hi kara kawarazu
And we'll chase forever
Itsumademo
And just as we are now, standing tall
Massugu ni bokutachi wa aru youni
We will be able to maintain that sea god-like strength
watatsumi no youna tsuyosa wo mamoreru yo
Surely
kitto
A-A ramen set!
－episode one－
Hello!
What's with this girl?
Are you alone?
It's hot, isn't it?
What? What is she after? Money? I don't have any money.
Aren't you thirsty?
I'll go and buy something!
Here!
Had a little trouble there, huh?
Gao!
"Gooey and Thick - Peach Flavor"?
Why did you do that?
You're making fun of me, aren't you?!
Not at all.
This tastes really good.
Would you like to go to the beach?
Why?
Because I want to play.
What?!
Yesterday, the kids were playing on the beach.
I thought, "It looks like they're having fun. I want to play too"...
...the whole time you were asleep next to me
You were watching me?
You've been asleep since yesterday, haven't you?
I poked you to try to wake you up, but you didn't look like you were going to.
I was so hungry I couldn't move.
Where are you going?
To work.
Work? What do you do?
A puppet sho-
Huh?
It's gone!
Is it really that important?
I need it to work.
It's hot, right? Go on and head home.
There it is!
Crow! Crow!
You're going after the wrong one!
Weren't we lucky we found it?
Yeah, we were. It's all thanks to you.
Now you can play with me, right?
What are you after?
Why have you been hanging around me?
Like I said, I want to play on the beach.
We can play tag, and splash water on each other.
And, at the end, we'll say, "See you tomorrow!" and part ways.
That sounds like something that friends would do.
Yeah. Friends...
You and I are friends.
So...
I want to play!
We don't even know each other's names.
My name is Kamio Misuzu. What's yours?
Kunisaki Yukito...
But listen! I have work to do.
I'm hungry, so I have to earn some money.
Oh! If that's the case...
I ended up following her home, lured by the thought of food.
It's nice to eat with someone else, isn't it?
Do you usually eat alone?
My Mom gets home late. And I don't have a Dad.
After you finish eating, let's go play, okay?
No. If it gets late, I'll have trouble finding a place to stay.
You haven't found a place to stay yet?
No. I'll probably end up sleeping outside.
You can stay here!
Now, listen. We just met today.
And you have no idea who the heck I am.
I'm a stranger.
Who in their right mind would let someone like that stay the night?
Your mother probably wouldn't allow it anyway.
My Mom's really lax, so I don't think it will be a problem.
Although I guess I shouldn't talk about my mother like that.
But really, it's okay for you to stay here.
I'm tired. I don't have the energy to play with you.
Then we can play tomorrow.
It's summer vacation, so I have lots of time.
No.
G-gao...
Say... What kind of use do you think math has?
Do you think stuff like quadratic
functions will be useful in my future?
How should I know?
Anyway, why am I helping you with your homework?!
Hey, your eyes are too close.
You sound just like my Mom, Yukito-san.
Do I?
My Mom's home.
Hey!
She ran into the shed with her motorcycle.
Don't worry. It happens all the time.
Are you really sure it's okay for me to be here?
Sure! I'll smooth it over with her-
Absolutely not!
This isn't going the way you said it would.
It doesn't matter what you say!
There's no way we can let a young man like him stay here!
G-gao!
Ouch!
How many times do I have to tell ya to stop saying that?!
What's your relation to Misuzu?
Uh... Classmate.
What? Aren't you a bit old for that?
Don't fall for me.
As if I would?!
Well, you do seem to have pluck. I like that about you.
That's right. Yukito-san is a really nice guy.
All right. He can stay.
You're serious?
Serious? Of course! I'm dead serious.
But there are TWO conditions.
First, you sleep in the shed.
And second...
You will be my drinking partner.
And then in the end, this is what the guy said...
"Maybe I was the one who fell in love."
Whaddya think? I win, right?
And so I told him...
"The fish you let escape was a mermaid, you know..."
How was that? Pretty good, huh?
Why does it end up like this?
Mom's in top form.
Hey, Freeloader. Why're you looking so glum? Why don't ya join in?
MY EYES!
Yukito-san!
Do something? What do you want me to do?
Anything will do. A tale of an erotic confession or a hidden talent...
I see... In that case...
Oh, that puppet from earlier.
Wow! That's impressive!
This is how I earn my living.
My mother used to travel with this as her trade.
When do we get to the punchline?
No good. You got no sense at all.
But it's amazing that he can do that without using any tricks.
Who cares?
As long as the show's funny, it's better, even if the strings are easily visible.
I'm going to bed.
Oh! He's going off to the shed on his own!
Hey, there's nothing wrong with having no talent!
Let's drink up and forget about it, huh?
My name's Haruko. Kamio Haruko.
One more drink, ma'am.
I told you my name so you wouldn't call me that!
You're a really thoughtless guy!
So... You a runaway?
I'm on a journey.
You chasing a goal or a dream?
Maybe.
You're so young...
Well, compared to you...
You're a funny guy, aren't you?
Am I?
I may not look like it, but I have a pretty good eye for men.
I wouldn't mind if you stayed on for a while.
But I have a favor to ask.
Would you look after her?
Huh?
She's a little bit prone to getting into trouble, right?
She's careless, and once something catches her eye, she goes off like a bullet.
What am I, a babysitter?
Also, I'd like you to fix that strange habit she has.
You've heard her say "Gao", haven't you?
When she's frustrated or about to cry?
Yeah...
That's supposed to sound like a dinosaur.
She loves dinosaurs. She's been saying that ever since she was little.
She's still just a child...
What's up? Isn't it summer vacation?
To be honest, I have to take remedial classes.
Has Haruko already left?
Yeah. She leaves early every morning.
It's been a while since I've had company for breakfast.
What are you going to do today, Yukito-san?
First, I'm going to walk you to school. Haruko asked me to do it.
She wanted me to watch over you to
make sure you didn't do anything stupid.
She doesn't trust me at all.
Gao!
I'm done drawing a map of this town!
That was fast.
Now you'll know where to find people gathering together.
This should help with your work, right?
Yeah, thanks.
Oh, I'm going to be late.
I'm in a pinch!
I'll come to pick you up after school. We'll meet right here.
Okay!
Here.
Delicious!
It's the ocean!
Munch Munch.
I'm
studying.
Japanese
use
these,
right?
W-What in the world is this?
Here.
Delicious!
It's the ocean!
Munch Munch.
I'm
studying.
Japanese
use
these,
right?
Here.
Delicious!
It's the ocean!
Munch Munch.
I'm
studying.
Japanese
use
these,
right?
Is this how she sees the world?
What do you want?
Are you this town's local legendary creature?
If that's the case, if I do it a favor, like in those fairytales,
maybe it'll give me something in return.
Okay. Come here. I'll show you something good.
What do you think?
Isn't it such a wonderful act that it makes you feel like giving me something in return?
Hey!
Wait!
Give up, you evil extraterrestrial!
You won't get away!
What are you doing?
A strange extraterrestrial being ran away with my puppet.
You mean this?
Potato isn't an extraterrestrial.
He's a neighborhood stray dog.
You mean, that's really a dog?
I see...
Huh?
I'm sorry he caused you so much trouble.
Why are you apologizing?
Well, Potato said that he brought your puppet here.
It seems he wanted to play with you.
You mean you can understand what he's saying?
Yes! We're best friends.
Right, Potato?
It seems that there are still worlds here on Earth that I know nothing about.
Thanks.
Are you hurt or something?
Oh, this?
Well, uh...
Nope! I have to keep it a secret.
My name is Kirishima Kano. What's your name?
I'm Kunisaki Yukito.
Do you have some free time, by any chance?
I guess...
Okay! Then you will be Citizen Number 2 of Planet Dilly-Dally.
Who's Number 1?
Me! And Potato is Number 3.
And what do the citizens of Planet Dilly-Dally do?
They just have time on their hands.
That is the fate of those from Planet Dilly-Dally.
Right? We have nothing to do, do we, Potato?
I have to go to school, so I'll say good-bye for now.
I thought you were from Planet Dilly-Dally?
You believed that? You're such a kid!
So long!
Are all the girls who wear that uniform weird?
Hey!
What is it?
Have you ever wished you could do magic?
What?
You're stunned! So long!
Magic?
Oh, Yukito-san!
How did your work go?
I made a mint.
Really?
I'm sorry. I lied.
I have to find someplace where there are more people or I won't be able to make a living.
Why is this place so quiet when people should be returning from work?
Well, this station is closed down.
You should have told me that earlier.
G-gao!
Ouch!
Why'd you hit me?
Haruko told me to scold you whenever you say that.
Oh! How cute!
It's Tohno-san...
You know her?
Yeah.
Why are you getting so anxious?
H-hello!
Hello. This is unexpected.
Y-yes. Quite a coincidence.
I'm astonished.
What were you doing?
Getting some sun.
Just kidding. It's evening right now.
Hey, who the heck is this girl?
It's Tohno Minagi-san. She's my classmate.
She's smart. She's at the top of our grade, and she's president of the Astronomy Club.
Please just call me Tohno.
Hey! Minagi!
Oh, Yukito-san is flying like a leaf!
Hey, hey! Let's hurry up and go back to blowing bubbles!
I'm doing really good now, you know!
Please!
Is this girl your little sister?
No, I'm not. I'm Michiru, Minagi's best friend.
And who could you be?
I'm Tohno-san's classmate.
That hurt, you know.
What?! Are you another one of Minagi's classmates?
I'm an innocent passerby who got bowled over by you.
I've got it! Minagi, this is a perverted kidnapper who's after us!
I'm on this side too?
Who are you calling a kidnapper?!
Yikes! He's mad!
We young girls are in trouble!
Wow, did you hear that sound?
Kamio-san, who is this?
Kunisaki Yukito-san. He's a traveler who's staying with us now.
A traveler?
A homeless, perverted kidnapper? He's a lost cause, right?
Kamio-san, I think we'd better be going.
What? But I was doing really well blowing bubbles.
Let's do it some more. Kami-Kami can join us, too.
Kami-Kami? Is that me?
It's getting dark, so let's do it again tomorrow.
I'll pack a lunch for us.
So long, Kamio!
Kunisaki Yukito!
Yeah?
Get lost, will you?!
What was that?!
Hey, hey, will you make me hamburger patties for lunch tomorrow?
All right.
Really? Hurray!
Did I do something to that kid?
Hmm, I don't know.
I didn't make a single yen today.
You were standing there like that when we met yesterday, too.
Ever since I was little, I've had this longing for the sky.
Why?
I don't know.
It's just...
I just have a feeling like... there's another me out there...
That's a romantic thought, isn't it? That the real you is in the sky...
I bet it would feel really nice.
You'd be able to see far into the distance,
and everything that happens in this world would seem so insignificant.
You'd really be able to feel at ease, I'm sure.
Misuzu... You're...
That was the start of a summer that seemed to me as
evanescent as the twinkling of a star, yet as long as eternity.
Shiroku togireta yume no kirehashi wo tsukamaete
Catching hold of the scrap of a dream that fades to white
Shounen wa hashiru
The young boy runs
Te wo hanashitara dokomademo tooku kaze no ne ni kieteyuku
When he lets go, it goes on forever, vanishing into the cry of the wind
Itsuka mieta yasashisa wa mou nai
The kindness I could once see is now gone
Hitori fumidasu ashidake miteru
All I see now are the steps my feet take
Asa ni wa kieta ano utagoe wo itsumademo kiiteta
I listened forever to the singer's voice that had disappeared by morning
Bokura ga nokoshita ano ashiato wo itsumademo otteta
Always following the footprints we left behind
Next Episode
It might be the other you whom I've been looking for.
I'm not cut out to be a parent. I should have stayed alone.
I had a dream. A strange dream. A dream about the sky.
I was in the sky.
It was a world I'd never seen before.
Everything went on into infinity.
Hey, did you have wings in your dream?
－episode two－