Then I would rather... with my own hands...
Hey, Kano!
Misuzu! Kano!
We watched as the vapor trails disappeared
Kieru hikoukigumo bokutachi wa miokutta
We ran away because it was so bright
Mabushikute nigeta
I was so bitter that I released your finger
Kuyashikute yubi wo hanasu
There are still unreachable places in the distance
Todokanai basho ga mada tooku ni aru
That she gazes at with her wishes tucked away
Negai hi dake himete mitsumeteru
The children walk along the summer railways
Kodomotachi wa natsu no senro aruku
Holding in both hands their wishes to take flight
ryoute ni wa tobidatsu kibou wo
We've been chasing and chasing after the disappearing vapor trails
Kieru hikoukigumo oikakete oikakete
Unchanging ever since that day we cleared this hill
Kono oka wo koeta ano hi kara kawarazu
And we'll chase forever
Itsumademo
And just as we are now, standing tall
Massugu ni bokutachi wa aru youni
We will be able to maintain that sea god-like strength
watatsumi no youna tsuyosa wo mamoreru yo
Surely
kitto
Looks like you might have this bruise for a while.
I apologize for the trouble.
I'm sorry, Kunisaki-kun, Kamio-san.
Oh, not at all.
It's not really us I'm worried about.
It goes back to when Kano was still a little girl.
episode four
It was the first summer after our mother died.
Look, Onee-chan! Balloons!
BALLOONS
Over there! If we bought one, do you think we could fly?
If one balloon could lift up a person,
the shop would've flown away by now.
I see.
Onee-chan, you are so smart!
But then, that means we can fly if we have many balloons, right?
Well, maybe you could fly if you had a lot.
But I can only buy you one.
We just have to blow it up really big!
Then, it can lift up something a lot heavier.
We won't be able to buy anything else.
Okay!
There.
Oh, thank you, Onee-chan!
Kano had wanted to fly.
She thought she could see our mother that way.
I taught her that our mother was in the sky and watching us.
Neither our father nor I could tell her,
that her mother was no longer around anywhere.
Kano!
Then, what happened?
Nothing. Nothing happened.
Who's playing over there?
We put the plume back and went home.
I guess we can't go to where Mom is anymore.
The following morning, Kano started acting strangely.
She became afraid of bright lights,
and she started wandering around in a daze and talking to herself,
saying things that didn't make any sense.
One evening, I noticed that she was gone.
I rushed to find her, and when I did, she was in this examination room, with a scalpel to her wrist.
I caught her in time,
so I was able to stop her before things got too serious,
but I realized then that she wasn't Kano.
Someone else was pretending to be her.
Is it multiple personality?
It could be.
This is a magical bandana.
If you wear it until you grow up, you will be given magical powers; so don't ever take it off.
I see. You were the one who gave her the bandana.
If she tried to cut her wrist again unconsciously,
I had thought that the bandana would snap her back into reality.
I doubt that Kano remembers much about it.
There never was any such thing as magic.
I decided to follow in my father's footsteps.
I thought if I became a doctor, I'd be able to heal Kano's illness one day.
What kind of thing was that plume that Kano touched?
I don't know.
Seems like it's been there at the shrine since the olden days.
I heard that even the shrine keeper doesn't know the details.
Maybe it's the plume's curse.
As a doctor, I can't accept that kind of reasoning.
It's possible that it acted as a psychological trigger for her illness.
Kano was suffering severe stress after losing her mother.
I believe that is the root cause of her illness.
Will you visit Kirishima-san again today?
Yeah, I have work there anyway.
Maybe I will go visit Kano later too.
You should. I am glad that you made a new friend.
I had a dream again last night.
A dream about flying.
I've been going further and further back in time in my dreams.
Last night, I was mourning in the sky.
Mourning?
As usual, my body was flying through the sky.
And I was mourning there.
I wonder why I was feeling so sad, in the middle of such beautiful and comfortable breezes.
It was only a dream. It has nothing to do with you personally.
Right.
When you're not smiling, I also feel...
Huh?
Anyway, keep smiling.
There's nothing here...
I found it!
What are you doing?
Kunisaki Yukito! What are you doing here?
That's my line!
Picking up stuff like that... What are you, a garbage collector?
How bothersome!
It's my hobby to find interesting things at places like this.
That's the shabbiest hobby in the world!
Leave me alone!
Anyway, you play day in day out. I envy you.
Kunisaki Yukito, you're doing almost the same thing, aren't you?
I work like a decent person.
In fact, I'm on my way to work diligently at my job as we speak.
You need a pit stop?
No. Look over there.
That's...
By any chance, is that Minagi's mom?
What's wrong?
Umm, nothing.
Minagi looks sad.
Hey, call Minagi over.
I bet she's lonely all by herself.
You're right. I'll give it a shot.
Tohno!
Kunisaki-san. What are you doing here?
Oh, I was just taking a walk with Michiru.
Sakuma Cycling Shop
Where did she go?
Were you with Michiru?
Sakuma Cycling Shop
Yeah, I was with her, but...
Did she say anything about the person who was just with me?
Sakuma Cycling Shop
No, she didn't say anything in particular.
I see. Then, that's okay.
Sakuma Cycling Shop
That woman... she's your mother, right?
I once helped her with a big load.
Now that I think about it, you two do give off a similar aura.
I am a fragment of her dream.
Huh?
Don't run away, Potato.
This will cool you off!
You're looking well.
Oh, Yukito-kun. Good morning.
I'm sorry for causing you trouble again last night.
Not a big deal. Don't worry.
Oh, there you are, Kunisaki-kun. As usual, I have a lot for you to do today.
Is Kano-san taking a nap?
Yeah, I told her to rest. Especially because of last night.
She should be waking up soon.
I'll go check on her.
Kano?
Huh?
Yukito-kun, I am writing this to you because I think you will believe me.
I've decided to go to the skies after all.
I feel that this will allow everyone to be happy.
I have a feeling that I will be able to meet the person you are looking for too.
I don't know how long it will take, but I will bring her back with me.
It would make me happy if you helped out Big Sis until then.
She may not look it, but she's been under a lot of stress.
P.S. I am really sorry about the bruise on your neck.
Kano!
Wake up! Kano!
There are no external wounds.
Then, this blood is...
There's no sign of blood loss.
It doesn't seem to be life threatening.
What in the world happened?
I wonder if she tried to go up to the sky from here.
What's this?
Is something wrong, Yukito-san?
I feel a chill... sort of nostalgic, and sort of melancholic.
Lay Kano down.
Kunisaki-kun...
My name is Shiraho.
Please listen to my story.
I remember it was a beautiful autumn.
My husband and I had our first child.
She had a birthmark on her right wrist.
The villagers said it was bad karma, but we didn't worry about it.
When Yakumo cried, I would sing a lullaby that I learned from my mother.
Usually, she'd stop crying, but that day, she didn't.
I was sure that the plume was a god-sent charm for her.
Take them away!
A war broke out and my husband never returned.
Is there anyone in this village who picked up a shining plume?
It is cursed! Anyone who touched it should step forward!
I ran away from the village that night.
And finally, I arrived at this village.
The priest was very kind to us outsiders.
I was sure that Yakumo and I would be able to start a new life in this peaceful village.
But...
That summer, a contagion spread through the village,
and many people died.
How is she, sir?
She is over the worst. The fever should break soon.
However, the villagers believe that the two of you brought the plague to this village.
Oh no!
It was my mistake to take you in.
The villagers worship an idol at this shrine.
The idol marks the one who brings bad fortune.
If they discover her birthmark,
they will demand her for a sacrificial offering.
Are you telling me to offer her for a living sacrifice?!
In this land,
we have always contained natural disasters by doing so.
She is my life!
She is the only treasure my husband left for me!
Give her up!
Otherwise, you will be killed as well.
Then I would rather do it with my own hands...
I can't do it. I can't do it!
What mother could kill her own child?
Even if that child might destroy the world, what mother could kill her own child?
I will sacrifice myself.
Please save her, please save my child.
Don't do it!
Mom?
Where are you, Mom?
I am right here.
Mom!
Is there anything you want to eat?
Nope, I'm full!
Is there anything you want?
Uh-uh.
Umm, I'm going home now.
Onee-chan is waiting for me. And Potato as well.
And my new friend.
I see.
He's looking for a girl in the sky.
I kind of wished that I was her.
If things are too hard for you, you can come with me.
Umm, Mom,
Thank you.
I don't remember very much about you, and...
It was probably because of me that you died so young.
But!
Thank you for giving birth to me!
I just wanted to say that.
Kano, you don't have wings, so live happily there.
Limitless are the ways this child is dear
Kono ko no kawaisa kagirinaya
Kano, you don't have wings, so live happily there.
Limitless are the ways this child is dear
The number of stars in the heavens
Ten ni tatoeba hoshi no kazu
The number of trees in the mountains and the eulalia grasses
Yama dewa ki no kazu, kaya no kazu
Flowering eulalia, bush clover, and bellflowers
Obana karukaya, hagi, kikyou
More precious than all the flowers of autumn
Nana kusa, chigusa no kazu yorimo
Is my sleeping child
Daijina kono ko ga nenne suru
What was that?
You saw it too, Kamio-san?
Yes.
Are you awake?
Kano!
Yukito-kun...
Onee-chan...
Kano!
What was that plume, anyway?
I don't know.
Onee-chan, I saw Mom.
Yeah, I was watching.
I couldn't go with her, but I was able to say thank you to her, just like Yukito-kun told me.
I have to thank you, Yukito-kun.
No, don't thank me.
That was your magic.
Yeah.
Let's let it float up to her in the sky.
Yeah!
Shiroku togireta yume no kirehashi wo tsukamaete
Catching hold of the scrap of a dream that fades to white
Shounen wa hashiru
The young boy runs
Te wo hanashitara dokomademo tooku kaze no ne ni kieteyuku
When he lets go, it goes on forever, vanishing into the cry of the wind
Itsuka mieta yasashisa wa mou nai
The kindness I could once see is now gone
Hitori fumidasu ashidake miteru
All I see now are the steps my feet take
Asa ni wa kieta ano utagoe wo itsumademo kiiteta
I listened forever to the singer's voice that had disappeared by morning
Bokura ga nokoshita ano ashiato wo itsumademo otteta
Always following the footprints we left behind
Next Episode
Bubbles are so pretty.
They're empty and just like the sky.
I'm a real burden on her, so I have fun by myself.
Maybe I did something wrong...
Mother's hopes lost their destination,
so she chose to live in her dreams.
Is there a purpose to wings that cannot fly?
episode five