It might be the other you whom I've been looking for.
Somewhere beyond this sky is a girl with wings.
She's been there forever, and is still there even now.
Somewhere in the same atmosphere,
she continues to spread her wings to catch the wind.
My mother died before she could give me any more details.
Ever since then, my only companions have been that story of the girl in the sky and this puppet.
Are you also trying to find that girl your mother was searching for?
Of course, there's no way you're that girl.
A lot of people dream about flying through the sky.
That girl can fly too, right?
Yeah. She has wings.
Wow... I wish I had wings too.
We watched as the vapor trails disappeared
Kieru hikoukigumo bokutachi wa miokutta
We ran away because it was so bright
Mabushikute nigeta
I was so bitter that I released your finger
Kuyashikute yubi wo hanasu
There are still unreachable places in the distance
Todokanai basho ga mada tooku ni aru
That she gazes at with her wishes tucked away
Negai hi dake himete mitsumeteru
The children walk along the summer railways
Kodomotachi wa natsu no senro aruku
Holding in both hands their wishes to take flight
ryoute ni wa tobidatsu kibou wo
We've been chasing and chasing after the disappearing vapor trails
Kieru hikoukigumo oikakete oikakete
Unchanging ever since that day we cleared this hill
Kono oka wo koeta ano hi kara kawarazu
And we'll chase forever
Itsumademo
And just as we are now, standing tall
Massugu ni bokutachi wa aru youni
We will be able to maintain that sea god-like strength
watatsumi no youna tsuyosa wo mamoreru yo
Surely
kitto
I'm home!
Hey, Freeloader! A present for ya!
A sloth.
Isn't this one cuter than that dirty puppet of yours?
We need to have you make some money and get out of here soon.
He's cute.
episode two
There's nothing like a drink after work!
It's like, "This is the reason I'm alive!"
Okay, Freeloader, tonight our subject will be "Touching memories that bring a tear to the eye"!
Go ahead and entertain yourself.
What, are you sleepy, Misuzu?
Yeah, I guess.
Come over here. You can use my lap as a pillow.
What?! T-that's okay, I'm not a kid.
I'm going to bed.
Good night.
Oh, dear. She ran away.
Do you have her lay her head on your lap a lot?
Are ya crazy? That was a joke.
Do you think she would cuddle up to someone as incompetent as me?
Was that girl saying 'Gao' today too?"
Yeah. I whacked her each time she said it.
That girl...
When she was little, for some reason, she thought chicks were dinosaur babies.
And so, when she saw the chicks at the summer fair, she begged for one.
But we were so poor then, I couldn't buy one for her.
And ever since, she learned to say "Gao" for every little thing.
I'm not cut out to be a parent.
I should have stayed alone.
Besides, that child is a little weird.
Weird?
But, she seems to cheer up when she's with you,
...so I hope you stay friends with her.
There's nothing more I can do for her.
Okay, it's time for a fun puppet show!
What is this?
It's kinda creepy.
It's like something you might see in a dream... I mean a nightmare.
Come on. Let's go.
Hey! Leave some coins!
You didn't help business at all!
You again. Your name was Potato, was it?
What are you doing?
- Is your daughter well?
Yes. She says white rice tastes so good, and asks for seconds and thirds,
So I enjoy cooking for her.
Please tell her to be careful of an upset stomach.
I will. Well, good-bye.
Now...
What have you been doing in front of my place?
Well, shall we go home, Bubbles-
- Hey now, don't ignore me like that!
Hey, it's Potato. What's he doing?
You know him?
Oh, Yukito-kun?
Yukito-kun is talking to Big Sis!
Kirishima Clinic
Wow, that's amazing! He's good, isn't he?
It looks like Potato's become a fan of Yukito.
You say your name's Kunisaki Yukito-kun, right?
Your technique is admirable,
but I doubt you'll be able to make much money with that trick.
You say that, but I've been using just this trick in all the cities I've passed through.
Oh! That must mean you've made a lot of money in this town, too!
Huh? You haven't?
Would you be interested in working at this clinic?
My name is Kirishima Hijiri.
Since our parents died, I've been the only doctor in this town.
I've been looking for someone to do odd jobs.
Why bamboo?
How nice! I've always wanted to try this.
Why are you eating soumen for lunch?
In this household, if Kano asks for soumen, that's what we eat.
No matter how you look at it, I'm in an unfair position here.
Why? You seem to be quite hungry.
All right. Then, come at around the same time tomorrow.
You're going to pay me well, I hope.
Then, as an added benefit,
I will allow you to put on your puppet show in front of my clinic.
Don't worry. I'll at least feed you lunch.
It was fun! Let's play again tomorrow, Yukito-kun!
So long!
Did I make a mistake taking that job?
Man, there sure aren't many people walking around this town.
There must not be many traffic accidents-
Oh... I'm so sorry!
No... I'm sorry.
I really appreciate your doing this.
D-Don't mention it.
I bear some responsibility for running into you.
But, this sure is a lot...
My daughter loves rice and eats so much of it, that I just...
Thank you very much.
It's not much, but to thank you...
N-no. No thanks. That's not why I did it...
You must take it. It isn't much but, here.
Doesn't anyone use currency in this town?
And by the way, what kind of girl would eat up all that rice?
Misuzu's sure late
Oh, it's a sloth!
He's so cute!
She's like a mini version of Misuzu.
Hey you, where are your parents?
Huh?
Don't tell me you're lost.
You want to eat this?
It's yummy and cute...
Yummy or cute. Choose one or the other.
Cute and yummy.
Oh, Yukito-san.
Where'd that little girl come from?
I think she's lost.
What's your name?
Six years old.
What a name!
Keep quiet, Yukito-san.
What's your name? It's what you say before your age, right?
Shino Saika. I'm six.
Oh, Shino-san.
I heard that girl has to be admitted to the hospital.
She's sick? Is it serious?
No. It doesn't seem too serious.
And besides, she said the sloth has become her friend, so she'll be all right.
I see.
I had a dream.
That's nothing unusual. I have them too.
A strange dream. A dream about the sky.
I was in the sky. It was a world I'd never seen before.
See, when you sit like this, the clouds are above you.
But in my dream, the clouds were packed below me.
I could see the blue of the sea between the clouds.
But I couldn't tell how far it was to there.
Everything went on into infinity.
Hey.
Did you have wings in your dream?
Huh? I don't know... I didn't notice.
You shouldn't go around telling people about such dreams.
Don't worry. You're the only one I've told.
Oh, it looks surprisingly good on you.
Don't you have a different one?
All of the other ones are small.
Yup, it smells nice.
What is this?
Lunch. I put all my effort into it so it's very delicious.
Lunch?!
You made it especially for-
Deliver it to Kano, will you?
Anything wrong?
Nothing...
Kano is at school taking care of the animals today.
Let me make this clear. If you dare to eat it on the way...
I will deliver it swiftly and safely!
There are quite a few students.
I guess they're here for remedial classes, club activities or school committees.
This might be a good place for my business.
Everyone, I want to hear you laugh out loud over my puppet show!
Kunisaki's the greatest!
Everybody, say it!
Love and Peace!
Kunisaki's the greatest!
As if that'll ever happen.
If I took this weird creature in there,
the whole high school might be thrown into a panic.
Don't move from here until I tell you it's okay.
I have a question for you.
Yes?
I'm here to deliver lunch to Kirishima Kano,
do you know where she is?
To Kanorin?
Maybe Kanorin's still in the nurse's office.
The nurse's office?
No, no. She said she wanted to get some fresh air so she was going up to the roof.
She mumbled something, and then suddenly collapsed.
I think she just got a little light-headed.
I see... So you worried about me.
Are you sure you're okay?
You're overreacting. I just got a little dizzy.
I see.
The sky is so clear, isn't it?
Yukito-kun, can't you fly?
Of course not.
But you can move your puppet.
That has absolutely nothing to do with anything.
By the way, you were talking about my wishing I could use magic or something.
Oh, that? I asked because I can use magic.
That's not completely true. I can't use my powers until I grow up.
But, I've already decided what I'm going to do the first time I use my magic.
What are you going to do?
It's a secret.
But I can tell you what I'll do second.
I don't really want to hear about it.
What? You've got to listen.
If you don't listen, it'll claw its way out of my belly,
and it'll turn into something no human can counter!
And Earth, Earth will be in a big jam! Right?
Yes! You've got to protect the Earth!
So what's the second thing you want to do?
Well...
I want to fly through the sky.
Magic to fly through the sky...
Hey! Kunisaki Yukito!
Quit attacking me, will you?!
Why are you mad?
And after I went through all the trouble of calling to you, too!
Shut up, will you?!
My brains are sloshing.
Oh! What a dirty doll!
Oh, that's mine.
It's all tattered. Poor thing.
You're suffering under your stupid master, aren't you?
Don't say it so soulfully!
- All right, I will save you!
What?!
See you 'round!
- Hey! Wait a minute!
Come and get me!
Are you from the planet Butt Sway?
Hey! Where are you going?!
Catch me if you can!
Enough is... enough, I tell you!
Oh! Minagi!
You're lucky! You get to have Minagi fix it.
So, where's your "thank you"?
Who are you to act so high and mighty?!
Ta-da. I'm done.
Oh, it's nice now!
- Whoa. Not bad...
Ahem.
It must be a very precious doll for you to always be carrying it.
Yeah, I guess.
It's the physical form of a precious memory...
Am I wrong?
I don't know...
Yeah, I guess you're right.
That ruined the mood!
- Shut up!
I present you with a coupon for rice.
You're hungry, are you not?
Tohno-san is amazing, isn't she?
Not only is she good at her studies, but she's good at sewing, too.
So, where are we headed?
A place where lots of people gather.
If you put on your puppet show there, lots of people should gather.
It's Mom.
What sort of work does Haruko do?
It's a secret.
I wonder if she went to say a prayer at the shrine.
The shrine?
Yeah. Where we're headed now.
Hey, there's no one here!
It's almost time for the Summer Festival.
It'll be full of people then. Lots of kids from town will come.
The kids in this town are all smart-mouths though.
Oh! Wait!
What is it?
Well, uhh... Since we're here, I thought we could play some more.
Let's play hide-and-seek!
What?!
I want to play hide-and-seek with you, Yukito-san.
How old are we, anyway?
Then... Then let's catch bugs.
Gao!
Oh, fish!
I want to catch fish.
You don't care what it is, do you?
It's summer vacation, so I want to play as much as I can.
Hey, Misuzu!
Listen, I'm leaving! Understand?!
Huh?
Gotcha!
By the way, do you still believe that chicks grow into dinosaurs?
Gosh, I know now that chicks grow up to be chickens.
Actually, what I really wanted wasn't a chick or a baby dinosaur.
I heard that you cried all day long.
If my Mom had bought me something,
I would've been happy with it no matter what it was.
That was fun!
Was it? That's good.
I've never had so much fun on my birthday before, so it was great.
It's your birthday today?
Yeah.
Why didn't you tell me such an important thing?
Huh? But...
If I'd known, I would've bought you a present.
Yukito-san?
Go on home.
No one would watch a puppet show so late in the day.
Oh, are you done for the day?
Can you show me something quick?
That's amazing. Hmm...
But I don't suppose kids would be interested.
It's none of your business.
That was rude of me.
What is this?
I went to visit an acquaintance, but no one was home.
I'll give it to you for showing me something so unusual.
It's really good.
It was lucky that what I got just happened to be a cake.
And there were just the number of candles I would need.
I wonder if he was planning to celebrate someone's birthday.
Doesn't Haruko remember that today is your birthday?
Mom's busy.
How pretty...
Now are you satisfied?
Yup. I'm happy.
Then, shall we go home?
Kano...
H-hey, Kano!
The shrine again?
I thought she went in.
Like the number of stars in the heavens,
the number of trees in the mountains,
the number of grasses in the field.
Kano!
Shiroku togireta yume no kirehashi wo tsukamaete
Catching hold of the scrap of a dream that fades to white
Shounen wa hashiru
The young boy runs
Te wo hanashitara dokomademo tooku kaze no ne ni kieteyuku
When he lets go, it goes on forever, vanishing into the cry of the wind
Itsuka mieta yasashisa wa mou nai
The kindness I could once see is now gone
Hitori fumidasu ashidake miteru
All I see now are the steps my feet take
Asa ni wa kieta ano utagoe wo itsumademo kiiteta
I listened forever to the singer's voice that had disappeared by morning
Bokura ga nokoshita ano ashiato wo itsumademo otteta
Always following the footprints we left behind
Next Episode
At least do enough to earn your wages.
Potato!
Next Episode
Pikopiko!
Potato!
Telekinetic ability... There are so many wonders in this world...
She's always a little weird, isn't she?
That's not what I mean.
Oh... if there's nothing, it's all right.
What are you talking about?
I won!
Help me out! I can't do it right at all!
episode three