When did you make the hidden door
in the fence?
I got it ready a while back,
so that we could escape at any time.
You are certainly my guard.
You are quite earnest in your job.
This is no time to be sarcastic!
I know that.
Until I meet Mother,
I will endure any hardship.
Starting here, there isn't going to be a path
for a while. Watch your step.
This is no big deal...
Like I just said...
Lady Kanna! Are you all right?
Do I look all right to you?
I cannot see in the dark.
I hope your clothing did not get soiled...
My clothing is more important to you than I?!
Both of you, pull your kimonos up.
Oh, that is naughty of you
to ask us both at once!
Yeah, you are no better than a wild beast.
Would you listen to yourselves?
I'm only suggesting you lift your kimono
to make it easier to walk.
I think our pursuers are near.
Sir Ryuya.
We watched the vapor trails
As they disappeared
We ran from the blinding light
In vexation we let go
There are still places she cannot reach
She gazes with wistful eyes
Children walk along the tracks in summer
In both hands, their wish to take wing
We chased and chased vanishing vapor trails
Since the day we climbed over that hill
Unfailingly
And just like we have always
Stood straight and tall
We will stay as strong as the god of the sea
Surely
Don't go far from me.
Run!
Part 1
You can move now.
What a bother...
You did a good job of keeping quiet.
Do not underestimate me!
I am not so spineless.
Hurry up! I will leave you behind.
That's the way we came.
Looks like there's a lot of them out there.
Uraha, you have a change of clothes
for Kanna, right?
The two of you just sit around here and relax.
Don't move from here.
Sir Ryuya?!
Don't worry.
Over there! It's a woman!
She is surprisingly fast!
Don't lose her! Hurry!
The woman fell into the river!
Seems that she fell into the river!
The sound came from directly below here.
Look! Her garment!
Get everyone here! Hurry!
Downstream! Search downstream!
Throw down your sword.
Answer me honestly.
If you do, I will spare your life.
You're from Edo, right?
Why are you pursuing Kannabi-no-Mikoto?
I don't know. We were ordered to.
What were your intentions with
Kannabi-no-Mikoto?
Whose orders are you following?
I don't know! We were just
ordered by our superior!
I see.
Stop it!
You! Did you intend to kill him?
If I don't kill him, he'll kill me.
Shame on you! How despicable!
You had just said that you would
spare his life, did you not?
Do you lie with no shame?
Do you break your promises without shame?
Depending on the situation...
Are you telling me that,
depending upon the situation,
you will break your promise to me, as well?
Do you kill people without any thought?
Lady Kanna...
I do not wish to be protected by such a villain!
I hereby order you.
As long as I am your Mistress,
I will not allow you to kill anyone from now on.
Understood?
I understand.
As long as you understand...
But do you really think we'll be able to
make it through without killing anyone?
I trust it will be an easy task for you, Sir Ryuya.
Don't make it sound so easy.
Relax. I don't see any pursuers.
Thank goodness...
Uraha, sorry to trouble you,
but can you fetch some water for us?
I think there is a stream down below.
Certainly.
Kanna, are you all right?
Do not speak to me. I have a headache.
It's the heat. Here...
What do you think you are doing?!
Just trying to cool you down.
Say something before
you do something like that.
Okay, I'm going to pour water on you.
I mean, can you not do it a little more gently?
Don't be such a brat!
Y-you shameless fool!
Oh, my, my, Lady Kanna.
I see you are feeling much better now.
Yeah, children recover quickly.
I am not feeling better! I am angry!
But we have a problem.
Summer is coming and it will get hotter.
If she stays in that garment,
the heat will get to her soon.
Do not worry. I have prepared this for her.
Okay, Lady Kanna. Please come here.
I-I am comfortable like this.
My, my... Just like a spoiled child.
Oh, my, my. You are drenched in sweat!
Hey, do not touch my private places...
As I thought! You are wet all the way through!
S-Stop! You are tickling me!
I am telling you to stop it!
What's wrong?!
Lady Kanna's kimono was taken
by that monkey...
Give it back, you insolent beast!
Step back.
Well done, Sir Ryuya!
Indeed, that is as my loyal servant should be.
Stop, silly, stop!
No, I will not stop.
To jump into your Mistress's dressing room,
that is the most disloyal act of all!
You just said that I was loyal, didn't you?!
Stop the irrational talking back!
Who's being irrational here?!
Thank you for waiting.
Where did you find a kimono like this?
I borrowed it from a clothesline by the river.
Of course, I left some money.
You look good in it, Kanna.
D-do you think so?
You have strange tastes...
No matter how you look at it,
you're a veritable country girl.
You might even be a little too cute.
You are a tiny bit bony, though.
That "bony" remark was unnecessary!
You don't seem to be getting any better.
When learning something new,
the beginning is the most important.
If you have a good foundation,
you will progress in no time.
You are telling me to practice with these?
Beanbags are supposed to be
made with stones.
If I make a mistake and they hit me, it will hurt.
If you sense there is a danger,
then you will try harder.
No, throwing beanbags isn't supposed
to be so dangerous.
Go on now, Lady Kanna!
They're ignoring me...
Lady Kanna!
Hey, are you all right, Kanna?
She's sleeping well.
Being active is the best way to sleep well.
All these years, she was confined in the shrine.
You are right...
You go ahead and sleep too, Uraha.
We'll have to hike mountains again tomorrow.
You must be tired too, are you not, Sir Ryuya?
I'm all right. I'm used to stuff like this.
You mean battle?
Yeah.
Please rest, if even for a little bit.
I will keep watch over us.
Then, I guess I'll take you up on that.
I have some good ones.
This seems to be a big market.
What is a market?
It is a place where merchandise is traded.
Don't make a lot of noise.
We're being pursued, you know.
I know. I am not that stupid.
Uraha! What are these?
They are called Ubai.
It is a medicine for stomachaches.
Oh, that really, really sour stuff.
Oh, here is some mochi.
Once, you tried to eat too many at once
and almost choked on it.
They were so good, I could not resist.
What is this, then?
I think it is sweet rice wine.
Once, you drank too much and
you became violent and...
There is no need to speak about
such unimportant incidents!
Hey, did you forget I just told you
not to make noise?
Do not worry. Any noise will be drowned
in this much commotion.
Who would be able to identify me
in this crowd to begin with?
I am, after all, just a bony country girl.
Holding a stupid grudge...
All right, I was wrong. You're cute, very lovely.
You stand out so much because you are
so lovely, so please be quiet.
As usual, your compliments
do not sound sincere.
You there. What are these striped balls called?
They're melons.
Melons are softer and juicier, are they not?
You cannot bite into it if it is so hard.
You must be high-class. Where are you from?
If you walk for about ten days from here
over the mountains...
Yeah, we have trouble with this girl.
She has a bit of a mental problem.
I'm sorry to hear that.
Who are you saying has a mental problem?
Who else can there be besides you?
Talk to her, Uraha!
Wait, she's gone...
Uraha!
Where are you, Uraha?
Ouch! Don't bite, don't bite!
That is because you are so rough!
I ended up spending half the day
baby-sitting Kanna, after all.
Where did Uraha go?
I have never seen an ugly bird like you before.
No wonder you're still sitting here unsold,
clucking so fussily like that.
Cuckoo birds and buppousou birds
chirp more merrily.
Ouch, ouch, ouch!
You dare to laugh at me even though
you are a mere bird! How insulting!
Those silly tail feathers!
I am going to yank them right out
from your very skin!
P-please stop it. That is my best Onaga!
What are we going to see next?
First we're going to look for Uraha.
Excuse me, sir!
Excuse me, sir. Please have mercy on me.
I was chased out of my village three days ago,
and I fled with nothing other than what I wear.
A war?
I do not know.
A group of ferocious armored warriors
simply ordered me to leave
and took over my home and fields.
Oh, you didn't deserve that.
Oh...
By any chance, is that young lady
there of noble blood?
Oh, you can tell?
Oh, no. You are mistaken completely.
I am only a cute village girl,
with nothing to hide.
Just a little bony, is all.
She's still holding a grudge.
Why are you just standing like that?
Give him something.
What do I have to give him, though?
This isn't worth much, but it might be useful.
Thank you so much. I will never
forget your kindness.
Take care of yourself.
We did a good deed, did we not?
Not necessarily.
Why do you say that?
He could be pretending.
If I was starving, I would lie or use flattery.
You're a fool if you believe that kind of story.
You really are dumb.
Nothing changes the fact that
he was extremely thin.
Oh, yeah, I see.
But, I am hungry.
The second I get impressed with her,
she says something like that...
That is because these are
Lady Kanna's growing years.
If you're growing, instead of padding your butt,
why don't you try putting some on your chest?
Be quiet.
You're quiet, Uraha, what's on your mind?
You are not surprised...
Whoa! Uraha, when did you get back?
I never noticed at all.
You disappear and reappear
like a stealthy ghost.
I do truly appreciate your
sarcastic compliments.
Where have you been?
I will tell you that later.
I almost forgot, I have something for you,
Lady Kanna.
A walnut, huh? That's rare in this season.
It is good luck, as it comes from a branch
at a shrine that got walnuts unusually early.
It is Lady Kanna's favorite,
and it is nutritious, too.
Seriously, though. I had a hard time
while you were gone.
Oh, Lady Kanna!
S-stop!
Uraha, you weren't thinking about dumping
Kanna on me, were you?
Only you would think such
disrespectful thoughts, Sir Ryuya.
Why does it not break for me?!
Stop, stop. You'll break your teeth.
Let me do something to help.
I do not feel good about making
the two of you work all the time.
Then, go collect some firewood.
And leave the walnut here. I'll break it for you.
Thank you.
Now then, I will go collect some firewood.
All right.
Don't go too far!
I will not.
They have set up a checkpoint
past the market we were at earlier.
They were picking out young girls
and checking their backs.
I believe they were checking to see
if any of them had wings.
I guess we'll have to avoid the main
roads from now on.
But how did you notice that?
That is somewhat a strange location
for a market.
I felt suspicious, so just in case...
You sure are wise about the world.
That was a big help.
Where did you learn such a skill?
I just do this for fun.
But I also do it because it's not good
for me to be out of practice.
Don't tell Kanna.
I'm afraid she might say a walnut
is a living being, too.
"I will not allow you to kill anyone
from now on," was it?
Do you think I'll really keep my word?
Kanna ordered me to never say this, but...
Do you remember the night
we left the shrine?
After that, when she heard the
pursuer's whistle, Lady Kanna said...
Sir Ryuya is being pursued.
We must go immediately!
If I do not go, Sir Ryuya will be killed!
If Sir Ryuya dies, then I, I...
I told her that it was a scheme,
but she would not believe me.
I see.
With all due respect, I believe you will
keep your promise not to kill.
Why do you think so?
If Lady Kanna had ordered the pursuer killed,
what would you have done?
I probably would've gotten angry.
I would've said not to take human life lightly.
Adults have to set good examples for children.
I agree completely.
I got them!
Did I do good?
Lady Kanna!
I told you to be careful, didn't I?
Be quiet. I only lost sight of where I was going.
Sir Ryuya...
What is it?
I have a favor to ask of you.
I am a little embarrassed, but...
would you look?
Catching hold of the remnant
Of a dream that fades to white
The young boy runs
When he lets go
It vanishes forever with
The cry of the wind
A gentleness, once so apparent, is now gone
My eyes remain on the steps my feet take
Hearing forever the sounds of singing
That had faded away by morning
Always following in the footsteps we left behind
Next Episode
Ow!
I don't know my parents' faces.
Why ever not?
I think I was abandoned.
Unsui picked me up when
I was crying on the roadside.
Part 2