She said she wanted to see the ocean.
But I couldn't take her.
There were so many things I wanted to do for her.
But I couldn't do anything for her.
Even though the summer had just begun...
Yukito-san.
Yukito-san, it's morning.
Yeah...
We watched as the vapor trails disappeared
Kieru hikoukigumo bokutachi wa miokutta
We ran away because it was so bright
Mabushikute nigeta
I was so bitter that I released your finger
Kuyashikute yubi wo hanasu
There are still unreachable places in the distance
Todokanai basho ga mada tooku ni aru
That she gazes at with her wishes tucked away
Negai hi dake himete mitsumeteru
The children walk along the summer railways
Kodomotachi wa natsu no senro aruku
Holding in both hands their wishes to take flight
ryoute ni wa tobidatsu kibou wo
We've been chasing and chasing after the disappearing vapor trails
Kieru hikoukigumo oikakete oikakete
Unchanging ever since that day we cleared this hill
Kono oka wo koeta ano hi kara kawarazu
And we'll chase forever
Itsumademo
And just as we are now, standing tall
Massugu ni bokutachi wa aru youni
We will be able to maintain that sea god-like strength
watatsumi no youna tsuyosa wo mamoreru yo
Surely
kitto
episode five
I'm glad that Kirishima-san got better.
Yeah.
I felt strange too, when I saw the plume.
Yukito-san.
What? Did you say something?
You've been spaced out ever since you got up this morning.
Yeah, well, I had a dream of when I was a kid.
A dream?
It's no big deal.
More importantly, what about you? Are you still having those dreams?
Yes.
Last night's dream was completely different from the ones I had before.
The moon was in the sky, and it was very bright.
I was trying to fly up to the sky.
I was sore all over, but I kept going higher and higher...
Then, I heard voices.
Voices?
I heard many people's voices. They were trying to confine me.
The noise became a whirr in my ears and I couldn't go on anymore.
Okay, I'll see you later.
Yeah.
I'll be going.
Hey, watch ou-
Luna's Bar
Wow! Isn't it great, Onee-chan?
I wonder how he walks without strings.
Oh? He fell down.
He got up!
That's the way kids should be.
But you...
Shouldn't you be with Kano?
Oh, she went to school to take care of the animals?
Wait, why are we having a normal conversation?
Well, we should go now.
Okay.
Mr. Puppet, see you later.
Shake hands, shake hands!
Let's go.
That's what you call being "really close."
I didn't make any money again.
I wonder what's taking Misuzu so long.
Tohno.
Oh, Kunisaki-san. Good afternoon.
If you are going to talk, swallow first.
Thank you for lunch.
You are welcome.
Have you seen Misuzu?
Kamio-san? No.
I see.
Hey, will you make me hamburger again tomorrow?
Okay.
Yay!
What a little pig!
Let go!
You let go first!
Ouch, ouch...
Michiru?
Did the shower work all right?
Yeah. Why do you have the key to this place though?
My father was the stationmaster here.
He is no longer working here, though.
Is he working somewhere else?
I know what, I'll give you this as an apology.
And I will give you this too today.
Hey, it's the vial I found yesterday!
These are grains of star sand.
They are sand grains shaped like baby stars...
Wow, that's cool!
Here.
Wow!
They're smooth!
Kunisaki-san, here's one for you as well.
For me, too?
Yes. This way, the three of us match.
This sand was given to me by my father, when I was a little girl.
Then it means a lot to you, doesn't it?
Are you sure about this?
Yes. For you and Michiru, it's okay.
Looks like Kamio-san has already left.
I see.
I wonder if she stayed for a while after school?
Maybe...
Oh, do you have any plans after this, Kunisaki-san?
Welcome to the Astronomy Club.
Wow! The stars are already out!
Where are the other club members?
There are no other club members.
I am the only member.
You're the only one?
That's why I am the club president.
It's a very select group...
I see.
Does she come here a lot?
No. This is the first time I've brought her here.
Umm, I didn't inconvenience you by inviting you here, did I?
No.
Is that so?
I wanted the three of us to observe the night sky tonight.
Because she seems to like you, Kunisaki-san.
I don't think that's possible.
It's true. All she talks about when she is with me is you.
She really loves you.
I can't believe that at all.
I can tell,
because she is my other half.
Other half?
Michiru and I have spent all of our time together like this.
She is so precious... Blush.
What about you, Kunisaki-san?
Me?
You have been traveling alone for a long time, haven't you?
Have you ever spent time like this?
The happiness of sharing time with someone else...
The joy of living for someone else's sake...
I'm sure I have.
Though it was long, long ago.
So long! I have to go now!
Okay, see you tomorrow.
Okay, okay! Michiru-dash!
Thank you for going through the trouble of walking me home.
Not at all.
You're pretty tall.
Do you not like tall women?
Oh, no. A good figure is an advantage.
Blush.
To tell you the truth, I am rather proud of it myself.
You are, rather, huh?
Yes, rather...
I figure the taller you are, the closer you are to the sky.
Thank you for walking me home.
Don't mention it.
Please be careful on your way home then.
Yeah.
Welcome home.
Oh, whom are you with?
A new astronomy club member.
Am I?
Oh, I remember you.
Thank you for the other day.
What?
I told you, didn't I? I helped her with some heavy stuff.
Thank you for walking my daughter home.
Now come on inside...
Michiru.
What's wrong, Michiru? Dinner is ready.
Yes.
Hey, Tohno...
Good-bye.
I'm home.
Misuzu, I'm coming in.
Hey, wake up. You'll catch a cold.
Oh, Yukito-san. Good morning.
It's still night.
Why didn't you tell me you had to stay late?
Sorry. I forgot.
Good grief... Huh?
Are you keeping a picture diary?
Yeah. It was a summer assignment option.
M-maestro! Why did you betray me?
You fool!
You think you can conduct this orchestra?!
That's a laugh!
Never
't conduct, who will?
Give the baton to me!
The only way you'll get it is over my dead body!
Damn it!
Appas
.. God... Fingers-
Appassionato... God... Fingers-
Hey, that was the best part!
Let's play cards.
You never give up, do you?
I just want to play cards with you.
You mean it?
Yeah. I mean it.
No matter what?
Yeah, no matter what.
Okay, I will play cards with you.
Yay!
Okay, what do you wanna play? Old Maid? Poker?
Make it an easy, mindless one.
Okay then, let's play "Concentration."
Oh!
Huh? What's wrong?
Oh, nothing...
I messed up.
Are you crying?
No, I'm not crying.
I can play.
I have to try.
What's going on? Do you feel sick or something?
I'm okay! I'm okay!
Misuzu! What's going on? Hey!
Get a hold of yourself!
Misuzu...
All of a sudden, Misuzu...
I know.
Do you mind leaving for a moment?
Misuzu... Settle down, Misuzu!
She's been like that ever since she was a little girl.
It happens whenever it seems like she's about to make a friend.
When she's about to make a friend?
I took her to a clinic, even to a big hospital,
but it was no use.
They all say it's only in her head and she'll grow out of it.
To tell you the truth, she had an episode at school today.
They called me at work,
so I went to get her on my motorcycle, and brought her straight home.
I see.
I thought she might be all right with you. I was so hopeful...
She's all right when she's with me.
Are you really leaving?
Misuzu suffers attacks when I'm here, right?
I should keep my distance for a little while.
Okay, I see.
Tell her that I'll still keep walking her to and from school.
Come over for dinner every now and then.
It's my fault that you had to move out.
Aren't you lonely by yourself?
Even though I'm living alone, I've made quite a few friends somehow.
You have friends too, don't you?
Oh, no. I don't have any friends. I've always been alone.
I start crying whenever I'm about to make a friend, so everyone stays away.
But you have Haruko. You're not alone.
My mom, well, she's not my real mom.
Really?
Haruko-san is actually my aunt.
She had to take me in because I'm so strange.
She didn't want me, but I ended up living here.
But, I don't want to be any trouble,
so we live our separate lives under the same roof.
That's why I don't ask for much.
I'm a real burden on her, and I don't want to cause any more trouble.
So, I have fun by myself, finding weird juices or playing cards.
Misuzu.
Just keep smiling.
V!
See you later then.
Be careful.
What's wrong?
Minagi hasn't come.
She's at school. She'll be here soon.
It's not her day to go to school.
Maybe I did something wrong.
Let me see that.
Give it back!
Just watch.
Stop! It's an indirect kiss! How dirty! Oh, no!
Don't be precocious.
Wow!
Cool! Do it again!
Wow! Wow!
Bubbles are so pretty.
They're empty and just like the sky.
She didn't come.
No, she didn't.
I wonder if something happened.
Why don't we go to her house then?
Go to Minagi's house?
Yeah. If she doesn't come, then you should go visit her.
What's wrong?
I don't want to go to her house.
Aren't you her friend? You've never been to her house?
Then, I'll go alone. I have to go pick up Misuzu, too.
Thank you for walking me home.
Sorry but I have to run today.
You're not going to have dinner with us?
I have to go somewhere. See you tomorrow.
Who are you?
I met you last night. I'm the new member of the astronomy club.
Yes?
May I see your daughter? I need to talk to her.
My daughter?
Isn't she at home?
I don't have a daughter.
What?
Maybe you have the wrong address.
Hey, are you kidding me? Hey!
What are you doing here, skipping work?
Tohno's mother has been suffering from a psychological disorder.
I've been checking on her every time I get a chance.
She believed that her older daughter, Minagi, was her second daughter, the one who died.
She's believed that for a long time.
But it seems her condition suddenly changed.
When she accepted the fact that her second daughter was dead,
she erased Minagi-san from her mind as well.
In her mind, she never had either one of her daughters.
I was supposed to have a little sister, named Michiru.
A precious little sister.
I was a daddy's girl, so Mother was lonely.
The baby she was expecting was supposed to fill her void.
If you could have just one dream come true, what would it be?
Umm... Ummm...
I want a little sister!
Mother's hopes lost their destination, so she chose to live in her dreams.
And I became a fragment of that dream.
But last night, she dreamt about the time she miscarried Michiru.
According to Kirishima-sensei, that made her accept reality.
This morning, my mother looked at me and said, "Who are you?"
She can't go back?
This is the end of my dream.
My own dream of a life as Michiru has ended.
My wings have forgotten how to fly.
For I have only been pretending to flap them.
Is there a purpose to wings that cannot fly?
Shiroku togireta yume no kirehashi wo tsukamaete
Catching hold of the scrap of a dream that fades to white
Shounen wa hashiru
The young boy runs
Te wo hanashitara dokomademo tooku kaze no ne ni kieteyuku
When he lets go, it goes on forever, vanishing into the cry of the wind
Itsuka mieta yasashisa wa mou nai
The kindness I could once see is now gone
Hitori fumidasu ashidake miteru
All I see now are the steps my feet take
Asa ni wa kieta ano utagoe wo itsumademo kiiteta
I listened forever to the singer's voice that had disappeared by morning
Bokura ga nokoshita ano ashiato wo itsumademo otteta
Always following the footprints we left behind
Welcome home!
Next Episode
You might be more suited to travel than I am.
Why don't you come with me, Tohno?
What?
Things mustn't stay the way they are.
I want to show you the world,
the real world, not a dream world.
All of this developed out of my sin.
episode six