Sky...
I had a dream about my favorite person.
Yukito came back to me in the end
after all, didn't he?
He gave me something precious, you know...
That's why...
I can't just give up over this, can I?
I can do it.
I'll do my best, even if I'm alone.
We watched the vapor trails
As they disappeared
We ran from the blinding light
In vexation we let go
There are still places she cannot reach
She gazes with wistful eyes
Children walk along the tracks in summer
In both hands, their wish to take wing
We chased and chased vanishing vapor trails
Since the day we climbed over that hill
Unfailingly
And just like we have always
Stood straight and tall
We will stay as strong as the god of the sea
Surely
I think I'll try going outside today...
Even though it hurts to walk.
I'll go as far as I can.
TAKEDA SHOP
Let's rest for a bit.
I guess I'll have my usual; the weird juice.
TAKEDA SHOP
Ice Cream
It's that person... the one who lived
with us until the other day.
Who could it be?
I seem to vaguely remember her...
Episode 10
So, that freeloader left, did he?
Well, if he finds he has nowhere to go,
he'll probably come back.
I had a tough time, too.
I worked very hard to keep ya here with me.
Yer not my kid.
One day, you'll be taken
by the Tachibana family.
That's why I couldn't get too involved with ya,
even though we lived together.
If I started to love ya, it'd make it
that much harder to say goodbye.
I kept myself ready for the day
someone would come for ya.
But it was all for nothing. I love you.
I can't lie to myself anymore.
So I made up my mind to make you
my own child.
I did a "sit-in" in front of the Tachibana house.
They finally gave in.
You didn't have to do that.
What?
I decided to do my best on my own,
and to not be a burden on anybody.
Misuzu!
What's wrong? Misuzu!
You were feeling that bad?
I thought it was just a cold.
Your legs won't move?
Let's go to the doctor. I'm sure you'll get better.
Ya know, that female doctor at the clinic.
I'm sure she'll help.
No hospital can cure me.
Huh?
Yukito and I figured out
the cause of this problem.
There's another me up in the sky
and she's burdened by something.
That's the reason why my body won't move.
Sounds like something from a dream.
Listen, Mom...
Let's keep on living like before,
without worrying about each other.
What?
Let's live our separate lives.
I'll do my best on my own.
W... Why would you say something like that?
Are you angry because
I left you alone all this time?
Okay. If you don't want to see a doctor,
you don't have to.
I'll take good care of you.
But two are better than one!
Let's stay strong together!
Okay, Misuzu?
How is it? Isn't it good?
Oh, really?
Sorry. I'll get it right the next time.
I don't want any. The food
you cook never tastes good.
Even if it doesn't taste good,
children grow up eating their parents' cooking.
I'm sorry. Is it so bad that it made you cry?
That's not it.
If we become too close, you'll get sick too.
Was that in your dream too?
Listen to me, Misuzu.
I'm not the least bit scared of getting sick.
If I get sick, I... I'll be happy.
It'd be a sign that we've grown close.
Isn't that right?
Here, eat something.
It's delicious...
Mom...
What is it?
How short should I cut it?
I'll let you decide, Mom.
Okay, then I'll cut it to a length
that's most flattering for you.
Okay.
Mom, you have more wrinkles now.
Shall I give you a crew cut?
Just kidding.
You look young, Mom.
When you came to our open house at school,
everyone else's mothers were older,
so I was really happy.
You answered a question wrong
and started crying.
Yeah... I felt like I had to
show off for you,
so I raised my hand even though
I didn't know the answer.
You came and gave me a whack
in front of everyone.
That's because you said "gao" again.
That's called disciplining.
Thanks to you, I've grown into a fine young lady.
That's right. You've grown quite a bit.
You hardly ever say that word anymore.
Misuzu?
Well, it's easier this way.
I'll just have to even it all out.
Oh, no! Now the other side is shorter!
Oh, no...
I managed to even out the left and right, but...
It's gotten really short!
I'm sorry!
It's like I'm back to being a little girl again.
Your little girl.
That's right.
Let's start all over from here.
The two of us, okay?
Yeah. We'll start from here, right?
V!
Hey, isn't the summer festival soon?
Oh, yeah... That's right. I forgot all about it.
I'd like to go with you, Mom.
Of course! I'll take you.
And then, I want to go to the beach, too.
I've never been there with you.
You have a lot of places you want to go.
Don't you, Misuzu-chin?
Yeah. I want to do a lot of fun
things with you, Mom.
Yes! Let's do all sorts of fun things.
Picture
Diary
Yes! Let's do all sorts of fun things.
Picture
Diary
We'll fill your picture diary with fun things.
You know, Mom...
I'll remember... your smile.
I swear I'll remember it. Mom...
I don't know what you're talking about.
What do you mean, Misuzu?
Oh, you're up, Misuzu?
What's wrong? Are you still sleepy?
Who?
Who are you, lady?
Have you forgotten?
Didn't you agree to be strong
with your mother?
Mommy?
That's right! That's me!
My mommy went far away.
You don't have to remember that.
I'm taking the place of your mother.
Never mind... I'll win you back starting today.
Until the day you accept me as your mother,
you can call me Aunt Haruko.
Misuzu, see what I've borrowed for you.
Look! Now you can go outdoors.
It hurts too much to walk!
That's why I got you a wheelchair.
Come. I'll give you a push.
It's more fun playing cards by myself.
Come on. Let's play together.
It'll feel good in the sun.
And there are lots of other fun things to do.
The wind is blowing.
Yes, it is.
The sun is sizzling.
The cicadas are calling.
Yes. Noisy, aren't they?
It feels good.
Does it? I'm glad.
TAKEDA SHOP
What is the meaning of this?!
Keisuke...
Who is that?
Misuzu, I'm your father.
As you know, this child cannot live
surrounded by too many people.
You live in this quiet town;
that's why I let you have her.
But it was a mistake.
Haven't you heard? This child is mine now.
I got your parents' approval.
She is MY child. Mine and Ikuko's.
You give her to me when she gets in the way,
then come to get her when you
remember about her.
Do you think this home exists
for your convenience?!
How can I leave her here
when I see her wasting away?
Quit talking without your accent!
It creeps me out hearing you talk like that.
Aunty... scary...
Oh, I'm sorry for yelling.
"Aunty"?
N-No... that's not...
Until just a little while ago, she called me "Mom."
Come. Let's go, Misuzu.
Now, say "thank you" to your aunty.
Come on. Where's your "thank you"?
Thank you.
No!
No! No! Don't take Misuzu away from me!
Misuzu has been alone all this time.
And whose fault is that? It's ours!
That's why I've decided to stay with her.
Yet, you want to manipulate her
because of the trouble between us?
Haruko...
I'm not too smart, so I don't know
how to put it nicely...
But one thing's certain.
I want, so much more than you do,
to stay with her!
That's the absolute truth!
Then let's ask her.
Misuzu, do you want to stay with Aunty Haruko?
Aunty?
Yes. Do you want to keep living with Aunty?
Keisuke! Wait, Keisuke!
Three days. Please wait three days.
Lf, at that time, she says she doesn't
want to stay with me...
Then it's okay. You can take Misuzu away.
I'm begging you, Keisuke!
Three days...
Can I regain our mother-child
relationship in that time?
Misuzu, you really love dinosaurs, don't you?
This is a Maiasaura.
It means "good mother lizard."
Really? It sounds like me.
This is a Velociraptor. It means "swift thief."
That sounds like Keisuke!
I wonder which one of us is the thief...
It's hot...
It is, isn't it? Just hang on for a bit.
It should be cooler at the beach.
Let's have our lunch there:
The lunch that I made.
I want to go home.
Don't say that. Our lunch will go to waste.
I want to go home!
There are sweet egg rolls, too.
I made them because you asked for them.
Let's make this a fun day.
No.
You really want to go home?
Yes...
But what about the lunch that I made?
I don't know.
I see... Then just do whatever you want!
If you want so much to play by yourself,
find your own way home!
You little fool!
It's hot. I'm getting dizzy.
Gao...
Let's go...
Let's go home, Misuzu.
I've known it all along.
I'm not cut out to be a mother.
That's all there is to it.
What a thing for me to do!
Misuzu! What's wrong?
Catch it!
Catch that cicada.
Okay. I'll catch it for you!
I'm the Old Cicada Catcher!
The Old Cicada Catcher?
That's right. Scaredy-cats
like you need me, right?
There it is!
Got it!
Now you can play without worrying, right?
Yes...
Okay. I guess I'll be going, then.
Is it okay for Aunty to stay here?
Yes.
I'm not going to ask for much anymore.
I'll be happy if I can just spend one day with you.
That's all I wish for.
This is the day I promised Keisuke.
That fool. He'll ask you once more.
Then you'll probably say
you want to go with him.
You'll probably say you don't want to
stay with me anymore.
Summer vacation is a long way from ending,
but our summer vacation ends today.
Are you sure?
TAKEDA SHOP
Yeah. I'm sure.
I see.
TAKEDA SHOP
Listen, Keisuke.
There's one final place I want to go with her.
TAKEDA SHOP
Do you have time?
Misuzu. This is the sea.
It's the sea.
Isn't it beautiful?
It was so far. How many years
did it take us to get here, I wonder?
We could have enjoyed this beautiful view
any time we wanted.
What in the world were we doing?
Have you had enough time?
She's heavy. It's been a long time
since you carried her.
It's thanks to you that she's grown
this big. Thank you.
Oh, yeah... Let her hold on to this.
She loves this doll.
She should be able to sleep comfortably
if she's holding this.
If she's still fussy, give her this to drink.
It's her favorite juice.
Got it. Well...
Shouldn't you go, too?
Your princess is going away.
That fool! What is he doing?!
Misuzu!
Mommy!
Mommy! Mommy!
That's right, I'm your mother.
Mommy...
After that, the two of them talked
for a long time in the sunset.
I'll bring a reliable doctor,
so please let him check her.
I finally realized that...
this person who'd been
with Misuzu all this time...
was her mother.
Catching hold of the remnant
Of a dream that fades to white
The young boy runs
When he lets go
It vanishes forever with
The cry of the wind
A gentleness, once so apparent, is now gone
My eyes remain on the steps my feet take
Hearing forever the sounds of singing
That had faded away by morning
Always following in the footsteps we left behind
Next Episode
I had wings.
I was flying through the sky
with pure white wings.
Is that so? What a nice dream.
No, it was a sad dream.
The world's saddest dream.
But you know, that was my last dream.
From now on I will stay with you.
Forever and always...
Final Episode