When I think about it,
I think everything that's happened has been
a trial for me to become your real mother.
The paralysis in your legs and
your memory loss...
They happened to prepare me to start
over from the day we met.
Mommy...
Misuzu! Misuzu, hang on!
Where does it hurt?
I'll rub it for you.
Ow... It hurts, Mommy.
Is it here? Does it hurt here?
No.
Is it your leg? Your arm?
My wings...
What?!
My wings... hurt...
Misuzu will start to forget:
About me and about you.
And when she has her last dream,
she's probably going to die.
It can't be true.
If she falls asleep...
If she has a dream, she'll...
Misuzu, you're going to the summer
festival, aren't you?
You're going to the summer festival
with Mom, aren't you?
I want to go to the festival.
I want a baby dinosaur.
You mean a chick, right?
I'm sure there will be a stand there.
Can I buy a dinosaur?
Sure! We'll have some good things to eat, too.
Let's make tomorrow the best day ever!
So please get better, Misuzu!
Kieru hikouki gumo bokutachi wa miokutta
Mabushikute nigeta
Kuyashikute yubi wo hanasu
Todokanai basho ga mada touku ni aru
Negai dake himete mitsumeteru
Kodomotachi wa natsu no senro aruku
Ryoute ni wa tobitasu kibou wo
Kieru hikouki gumo oikakete oikakete
Kono oka wo koeta ano hi kara kawarazu
Itsumademo
Massugu ni bokutachi wa aru you ni
Watatsumi no youna tsuyosa wo mamoreruyo
Kitto
Misuzu, it's morning.
The summer festival is today.
Yeah...
The festival...
Final Episode
Please, gods. Please do something. Sis!
I'm such a fool. There's no way
they'll be holding it.
There'll never be a miracle.
The gods don't really exist.
What did this child do wrong, anyway?!
She waited like a very good little girl!
She was so looking forward
to the summer festival!
Why can't she be rewarded?!
It's just like that time.
I can't give you anything this time, either.
Mommy, where's the baby dinosaur?
Why?
Why is it here?
I threw it away.
So, it's been waiting all this time.
Misuzu! Misuzu, wake up.
What is it, Mommy?
There's a dinosaur here. Right over there!
Let's go and get it together. Okay?
Come on, a little more...
Mom will help you.
This will be a happy memory for the two of us.
Let's take good care of it together.
I'm tired. I'm sleepy...
No, no! Do your best. I'll help you!
Your friend is here too.
We're all in this together.
Let's all find happiness together.
Okay.
A little further...
A little more, and you'll reach our happiness.
There! You got it!
I did it!
It's my birthday present to you.
I haven't been able to give you one
since the day we met,
but will you accept one now?
Yes. I'm so happy.
You are? Isn't it nice, Misuzu?
It's so cute.
He says, "Gao!"
Gao...
Dear gods, I offer my thanks.
Mom...
She hasn't slept... because of me.
Oh, dear. I was asleep, wasn't I?
I'm sorry.
It's okay. Let's go to sleep.
I want to sleep with you, Mom.
What should I do?
If you go to sleep and dream,
your pains will get worse, won't they?
No. There's no pain now.
What?
There's been no pain for a while now.
I wonder why...
Really? You really don't feel any pain?
That's why I want to sleep.
I want to sleep lots and get better.
Really?
I'm so glad! It's really great, isn't it, Misuzu?
You were trying so hard, weren't you?
You were rewarded, Misuzu!
Misuzu... no... That's not candy...
You mustn't eat it...
I'm sorry for lying, Mom.
If I didn't, you wouldn't have rested.
Yukito...
Picture Diary
I think I'll write in my diary.
Misuzu!
I was asleep!
Isn't your body sore?
Do you remember who I am?
Mom! Good morning!
It's cleared up nicely,
now that the storm's passed.
Mom, I had another dream last night.
A dream?
You always get worse after a dream.
I'm fine. I have no pains anywhere.
Besides, that was my last dream.
Really? You're really all right?
You don't feel any pain anywhere?
I'm fine.
V!
Really?
That freeloader said something about
after your last dream...
But I guess he was wrong.
I was so worried.
It was like living a long nightmare.
But it's finally over, isn't it?
Mom...
I can't tell you not to cry; I'm a crybaby myself.
Ya mustn't cry, now.
That's right. There's nothing sad,
so I shouldn't cry, should I?
My dream last night was about
a dinosaur with wings.
He was flying like he really
enjoyed it, saying, "Gao!"
Is that right?
And I was flying above him.
I was looking back over my shoulder.
I had wings. I was flying with pure white wings.
Is that so? What a nice dream.
No, it was a sad dream.
The world's saddest dream.
But you know, that was my last dream.
From now on I will stay with you.
Forever and always...
It sure feels good, doesn't it?
Yeah. It sure feels good, doesn't it?
It smells like summer.
Yeah. It does.
What does it smell like?
The sea.
That's right. It does.
It smells like the sun.
That's right. It does, at that.
It smells like you, Mom.
Yes. It does, doesn't it?
Yuck! It would be awful if it smelled like me!
It smells a lot like you, Mom.
Are you sure?
Yes. This summer smelled a lot like you, Mom.
The smell of my favorite Mother.
It would be awful if I was smelly.
It would be awful!
But, it smelled good.
Did it? That's nice.
Uh-huh. It was.
It's hot, isn't it?
Yes, it's very hot.
Say, Misuzu, shall I tell you what
you're thinking now?
Yeah.
I wish I could have some juice.
You're right! That's amazing!
Anybody could guess that.
Very Very Very Very
Thick Thick Thick Thick
Milk Peach Gerurun Bitter
Flavor Flavor Melon
Anybody could guess that.
Very Very Very Very
Thick Thick Thick Thick
Milk Peach Gerurun Bitter
Flavor Flavor Melon
I want this one.
Very Very Very Very
Thick Thick Thick Thick
Milk Peach Gerurun Bitter
Flavor Flavor Melon
This again?
You sure like this, don't you?
And what shall I have?
You should have that Gerurun juice.
Really?
Very Thick
Gerurun
It's not just thick, it's hard!
Who wants juice like this?!
Don't throw it away!
You're supposed to squeeze it while you drink.
Like this?
Well, it's not all that bad...
It's summer vacation, isn't it?
Summer vacation for just you and me.
But that's okay. We can play together.
Listen, Mom. I want you to go ahead a little.
Why? Is there a reason?
Yes. Take Sky with you.
Is this far enough?
Yeah. Wait there.
Don't push yourself!
Stand there, Mom!
Huh?
Don't come, no matter what happens.
I'm going to do it myself.
I'm going to do my best to walk up to you.
You'll be my goal, Mom.
I see. So I'm the goal?
Yes. You and Sky are my goal.
Just take it slowly. I'll wait as long as you need.
Okay.
Are you all right?
Yeah! V!
V...
Over here, Misuzu. I'm over here.
That's right. Just take it slowly.
If you try really hard, I'm sure you'll get well.
We'll do our best together. Right, Misuzu?
It's all right, isn't it?
Huh? What is?
I've done my best, haven't I?
It's okay to cross the goal line, isn't it?
Are you tired already?
Okay, when you reach your goal,
we'll go home and play cards.
No...
My goal... The goal I've been trying
to reach all this time...
Huh?
I did my best, so it's okay, isn't it?
I can rest now, can't I?
Don't tell me you're in pain?
Have you been in pain?
Don't move!
It's not true. Tell me it's not true!
You're going to get better, aren't you?
The bad dreams are supposed to be over, right?
I'm sorry, Mom.
But I was able to do all that I needed to.
That's why, I'm going to cross the goal line.
No, Misuzu. You mustn't come here.
You mustn't cross the goal line!
We just started! Why, we just started yesterday!
We're going to get it all back.
The happy life that we should have started
ten years ago.
We're going to get that all back together!
Our happiness just started!
No, we did everything.
Almost more than enough.
This summer was filled with enough
happiness for a lifetime.
No! You're wrong! There are lots
of things I want to do!
I love you, Misuzu. There are lots
of things I want to do with you!
Everything is just beginning!
This summer, I decided I would try
one more time.
My summer started on the day I met Yukito.
All sorts of things happened;
painful things, difficult things...
But I'm glad I tried so hard.
My goal was the same as my happiness.
I wasn't all alone.
That's why... That's why
I'm going to cross the goal line.
No! We've only started!
We've only started, I tell you!
Goal!
Ano umi doko made mo aokatta tooku made
The sea was blue into the far distance
Ano michi doko made mo tsuzuiteta massugu ni
The seaway continued on forever, straight ahead
I finally reached the place I've
searched so long for.
Ano michi doko made mo tsuzuiteta massugu ni
The seaway continued on forever, straight ahead
A happy place.
Ano michi doko made mo tsuzuiteta massugu ni
The seaway continued on forever, straight ahead
Forever... A happy place.
Ano michi doko made mo tsuzuiteta massugu ni
The seaway continued on forever, straight ahead
Forever... A happy place.
Ichiban hayaku sunao ni waratta mono gachi
The one who truly laughs first wins
No! This can't be!
Ichiban hayaku sunao ni waratta mono gachi
The one who truly laughs first wins
Mom... Thank you...
Ichiban hayaku sunao ni waratta mono gachi
The one who truly laughs first wins
Mom... Thank you...
Ichiban suki na ano hito waratteru
The one I love best is laughing
Misuzu!
Ichiban suki na ano hito waratteru
The one I love best is laughing
You taught me so much!
Ichiban suki na ano hito waratteru
The one I love best is laughing
You taught me so much!
How not to live alone...
Dare yori mo tooku ni itte mo koko kara mata waratte kureru?
If I go farther away than anyone?
Don't leave me! Don't leave me alone!
Dare yori mo tooku ni itte mo koko kara mata waratte kureru?
If I go farther away than anyone?
I don't need anything else.
Dare yori mo tooku ni itte mo koko kara mata waratte kureru?
If I go farther away than anyone?
I don't need anything else.
Dare yori mo tooku ni itte mo koko kara mata waratte kureru?
Will you still smile at me from here again?
No friends, no new clothes;
I don't need anything extravagant!
Dare yori mo tooku ni itte mo koko kara mata waratte kureru?
Will you still smile at me from here again?
I'll be happy if I can just live with you!
Dare yori mo tooku ni itte mo koko kara mata waratte kureru?
Will you still smile at me from here again?
I'll be happy if I can just live with you!
Hitomi wo tojireba futto natsu no hi no nioi
If I close my eyes, I catch the scent of a summer day
First Grade
Class 4
Haruko
Kamio
I'll be happy if I can just live with you!
Hitomi wo tojireba futto natsu no hi no nioi
If I close my eyes, I catch the scent of a summer day
I'll be happy if I can just live with you!
Hitomi wo tojireba futto natsu no hi no nioi
If I close my eyes, I catch the scent of a summer day
Let's live together in the Kamio house.
Hitomi wo tojireba futto natsu no hi no nioi
If I close my eyes, I catch the scent of a summer day
Misuzu...
Hitomi wo tojireba futto natsu no hi no nioi
If I close my eyes, I catch the scent of a summer day
Misuzu!
Hitomi wo tojireba futto natsu no hi no nioi
If I close my eyes, I catch the scent of a summer day
Ano kawa asonderu futarikiri dorodarake
we play in the river, just we two, covered in mud
From that day on, I cried day in and day out.
Ano kawa asonderu futarikiri dorodarake
we play in the river, just we two, covered in mud
I'm completely cried out.
Ano kawa asonderu futarikiri dorodarake
we play in the river, just we two, covered in mud
Ano kumo ootteiru todoitara shiawase to
we chase after those clouds
I see...
Ano kumo ootteiru todoitara shiawase to
we chase after those clouds
Family is amazing, isn't it?
Ano kumo ootteiru todoitara shiawase to
we chase after those clouds
Happiness beyond compare and
pain beyond compare, rolled into one.
Ano kumo ootteiru todoitara shiawase to
we chase after those clouds
Happiness beyond compare and
pain beyond compare, rolled into one.
Ano kumo ootteiru todoitara shiawase to
Because they say we'll find happiness if we reach them
That, truly, is life.
Ano kumo ootteiru todoitara shiawase to
Because they say we'll find happiness if we reach them
That's why I lived.
Ano kumo ootteiru todoitara shiawase to
Because they say we'll find happiness if we reach them
That's why I lived.
Ichiban hayaku kono saka nobotta mono gachi
The one who gets to the top of this hill first wins
Why I lived with her.
Ichiban hayaku kono saka nobotta mono gachi
The one who gets to the top of this hill first wins
Reckless and tattered...
Ichiban hayaku kono saka nobotta mono gachi
The one who gets to the top of this hill first wins
Strong, yet weak...
Ichiban hayaku kono saka nobotta mono gachi
The one who gets to the top of this hill first wins
I can't understand what it is I'm saying anymore.
Ichiban hayaku kono saka nobotta mono gachi
The one who gets to the top of this hill first wins
No, I can understand. It's painfully clear.
Ichiban hayaku kono saka nobotta mono gachi
The one who gets to the top of this hill first wins
No, I can understand. It's painfully clear.
Ichiban suki na ano basho mezashite
Head for that place that you love the best
Yeah, I guess you'd be able to understand.
Ichiban suki na ano basho mezashite
Head for that place that you love the best
We're adults, after all.
Ichiban suki na ano basho mezashite
Head for that place that you love the best
You know, I feel confident now.
I can say that I am her mother.
Ichiban suki na ano basho mezashite
Head for that place that you love the best
I may not be an admirable one,
but I'm her mother.
Ichiban suki na ano basho mezashite
Head for that place that you love the best
I may not be an admirable one,
but I'm her mother.
Takusan no omoide ga aru hoka ni wa nani mo iranai gurai
where there are so many memories
I've decided to quit my job and
get a job at a nursery school.
Takusan no omoide ga aru hoka ni wa nani mo iranai gurai
where there are so many memories
That you need nothing else
I want to live surrounded by all sorts of families.
Takusan no omoide ga aru hoka ni wa nani mo iranai gurai
That you need nothing else
That's what I'm thinking.
Takusan no omoide ga aru hoka ni wa nani mo iranai gurai
That you need nothing else
Hitomi wo tojireba sugu ano umi no nioi
lf you close your eyes, you can catch the scent of that sea
I'll come and visit you sometime.
Hitomi wo tojireba sugu ano umi no nioi
lf you close your eyes, you can catch the scent of that sea
Yeah. I'll be waiting.
Hitomi wo tojireba sugu ano umi no nioi
lf you close your eyes, you can catch the scent of that sea
The end of summer...
Hitomi wo tojireba sugu ano umi no nioi
lf you close your eyes, you can catch the scent of that sea
It's the end of my vacation, too.
Hitomi wo tojireba sugu ano umi no nioi
lf you close your eyes, you can catch the scent of that sea
So many happy things
happened this summer.
I even got a baby dinosaur.
It was great.
Hitomi wo tojireba sugu ano umi no nioi
lf you close your eyes, you can catch the scent of that sea
So many happy things
happened this summer.
I even got a baby dinosaur.
It was great.
So many happy things
happened this summer.
I even got a baby dinosaur.
It was great.
Mata natsu ga kuru gin iro ni hikaru
Summer will come once more, glowing silver
Minamo ni utsusu futaribun no kage
Two shadows on the surface of the water
Is that you, Sky?
Minamo ni utsusu futaribun no kage
Two shadows on the surface of the water
You've grown quite a bit, haven't you?
Minamo ni utsusu futaribun no kage
Two shadows on the surface of the water
Or, are you a different crow? I can't tell.
Minamo ni utsusu futaribun no kage
Two shadows on the surface of the water
But, if you're Sky,
I should scold you, shouldn't I?
Minamo ni utsusu futaribun no kage
Two shadows on the surface of the water
Are you still hanging around here?
That child isn't here anymore.
Minamo ni utsusu futaribun no kage
Two shadows on the surface of the water
Are you still hanging around here?
That child isn't here anymore.
You know, you have to leave.
You've got wings, after all.
The sky is way out of reach
for us wingless people.
So, you have to fly!
For people like us who have no wings.
Take all of our dreams and hopes to the sky!
I'm counting on you!
Then we'll be able to live peaceful lives.
That's what I think.
I hope we'll be able to meet again someday.
Well, take care of yourself!
Before I realized it, I was looking at the sky.
The sky that always bore a taint of sadness.
Blue that continued into infinity.
The young girl who returned to that eternity.
That girl who still remains alone.
That is why I shall continue
on a journey to find that girl.
And one day, I shall bring her home.
In order to greet a new beginning.
My son, heed my words.
The story I'm about to tell
is a very important one.
You and I begin now the story of
a long, long journey
which will be passed on from
parent to child without end.
We will pass on the memories of this planet.
We will bear witness to every
phenomenon on this planet,
and pass them on from parent to child.
The memories of the planet
must eternally be happy ones.
When the skies are clouded
over by hatred and wars
this planet will be overwhelmed by grief
and all will be lost.
Someday, the day of destruction will come.
That end cannot be avoided.
But, in the end...
May the last child who shoulders the memories
of this planet have only happy memories.
What's the matter?
Nothing.
I was just remembering
something from the past.
The sun will be setting soon.
I guess...
Before that, do you want to go check it out?
Check what out?
The thing you've always wanted to check out.
What's beyond this shoreline.
Did I say that?
Maybe you didn't...
But I got the feeling you were thinking it.
You're right. I want to check it out.
If we go now, we can find out
what's waiting out there... you and I.
Shall we go?
Okay.
For them, cruel days await.
For us, it's the beginning.
Good-bye...
Fin
Shiroku togireta
Yume no kirehashi wo tsukamaete
Shounen wa hashiru
Te wo hanashitara
Doko mademo touku kaze no ne ni
Kiete yuku
Itsuka mieta yasashisa wa mou nai
Hitori fumidasu ashi dake miteru
Asa ni wa kieta ano utagoe wo
Itsumademo kiiteta
Bokura ga nokoshita ano ashiato wo
Itsumademo otteta