Why?
Why must we leave the mountain?
Forgive me, but I am Lady Kanna's attendant.
I cannot go against her wishes.
What are your intentions with me?
We will take you away from here.
Then you will live happily ever after
with Lady Kanna.
Our fate might have been different,
if there were more people like you.
Please stand back!
Mother!
Stay back!
My body has been defiled.
Defiled?
You must not approach me.
Mother...
We watched the vapor trails
As they disappeared
We ran from the blinding light
In vexation we let go
There are still places she cannot reach
She gazes with wistful eyes
Children walk along the tracks in summer
In both hands, their wish to take wing
We chased and chased vanishing vapor trails
Since the day we climbed over that hill
Unfailingly
And just like we have always
Stood straight and tall
We will stay as strong as the god of the sea
Surely
Episode 9
Did you say you are called Uraha?
Are you the one who found a way
through the joining boundary,
and discovered an escape route?
Yes, it was as if something led me...
You seem to have special powers.
Powers?
Quiet!
Is it a bird?
It is an arrow.
It signals the beginning of a war.
Some army is attempting to invade
this sacred mountain.
Down!
Mother!
I got her!
What?! My arrow got her first!
Don't look!
So this is the power of a winged person?
Mother!
Do not remove the arrows!
What are you saying?
She will only bleed to death.
Mother...
Do not touch me...
No!
No, no, no!
Lady Kanna!
Kanna!
Mother, mother!
Kanna... What a disobedient child you are.
I told you so many times.
Mother...
Ah, I had forgotten...
that a human's touch is so warm...
If this is my fate...
Kanna, listen carefully.
The ancient prayer was
supposed to perish with me,
but I will bestow it upon you now.
I wanted you to live as a normal girl if possible,
without the burden of a winged person.
Mother...
Strength...
Wind...
Ours... now...
We inherit a dream...
That the planet sees...
"A dream that the planet sees"?
What does that mean?
Ask... the way...
Everlasting... wings... and spirit...
That... is all.
Please forgive me. This truly is our duty.
Mother...
Now, Kanna. It is your turn.
How has your journey been?
Is it all right for you to be talking?
I lived in a shrine deep in
the forest till recently...
...I had never had such a happy trip
as this one before.
I have Ryuya and Uraha to thank for that.
Lady Kanna, your mother appears to be tired.
Do you not have something
you wish to show her?
I have trained long and hard
in order to show you when we met.
I really, really can do it.
I will throw the next one well.
This time, for sure!
The next one. The next one will be good.
Why do they not perform?
Why do they not perform for Mother?
I have been training for this day, so why?
Why do they not perform?
You are good.
You put so much effort into it... really...
Mother...
Continue on... I will keep watching you.
All right.
Lady Uraha, please do not think
this mother is coldhearted.
No, ma'am.
Sir Ryuya, you do not need to worry
about my burial.
Do not touch my body, but just leave it here.
I have nothing to regret now.
I only wanted to share...
How I wish I could have spread my wings
together with this child...
To have flown in the summer sky to our
hearts' content, with this child...
Mother?
Mother, Mother, Mother...
Mother, Mother...
Kanna, that is enough.
Leave me alone! Get away from me!
Mother never lies. She said that I was good!
If I cannot throw the beanbags well,
it will make her a liar!
I must do it.
Mother is... Mother is watching!
Mother is...
Lady Kanna!
With such shabby arrows...
Lady Kanna...
Sir Ryuya, my guardian...
It was a difficult chore.
It was such a short time, but I was, I was...
Sir Ryuya!
Sir Ryuya, have some water.
I am fine. Please give it to Kanna.
It is my order. Drink.
This is all the water we have?
All right. Let us share.
Drink up all the rest.
When we are so close together like this,
we are as if...
...as if we are a close-knit family.
You're the one who said that a true family stays
so close they almost suffocate each other.
That is so true!
Do you two have any wishes?
Where did that come from?
Let me see... Can't think of one off hand...
It is to escape this siege,
even if I have to sacrifice my life.
At least let Kanna survive.
I have one.
I wish to live with Lady Kanna
and Sir Ryuya forever.
That might be good, too.
Let us set up a small residence
somewhere quiet.
I'll manage to supply food for us,
either by farming or hunting.
If we live by the ocean,
we could dig clams, as well.
The ocean...
If we're going to live by the ocean,
the warm, west side would be good.
What is the ocean like?
You don't know?
I heard that it is an unimaginably
large water puddle,
but I have never seen it myself.
It is a water puddle, but of only salt water.
You are teasing me again, are you not?
It is true, Lady Kanna.
What is more, the ocean is as big as the sky.
What?!
You can eat all the snappers
and abalone you wish.
Is that true?
That depends on my abilities.
I hope there are summer festivals
at seaside villages.
Yes, there should be.
Let us three dance together then.
Yes, it is not as much fun to just watch.
This is a dream, isn't it?
My dream.
Dreams are not all sad.
I have enjoyed myself.
Kanna...
Both of you. Do not move from here.
I was able to forget about my wings
while I was with you, Ryuya.
Kanna...
This is my last order.
Live a long and a happy life.
Kanna!
Don't hesitate! Shoot!
What are those voices?
It is a chant.
The priests are putting a spell on Lady Kanna.
Do not stop the chant!
In order to protect this world from
the curse of the winged being,
do not think about sparing your life!
Kanna! Fly higher! Higher!
Higher!
Kanna!
Sir Ryuya...
Sir Ryuya, what are you doing?
I don't care who it is.
I'm going to die and take as many of those
who did that to Kanna with me as I can.
If you get in my way, I will kill you.
Kill me then.
This is no idle threat.
My words are no mere threat, either.
How could Lady Kanna possibly be pleased
to see you transformed into an evil being?
Kanna is gone.
No. I can still hear Lady Kanna's voice.
What?
It is faint, but I can hear it.
Lady Kanna is crying.
Kanna is?
I see that you are
Kannabi-no-Mikoto's attendants.
In accordance with my master's order,
I am here to take you to him.
The one who summoned us was
a high-ranking priest, Chitoku.
Chitoku already knew pretty much
everything about Kanna.
There once lived a winged being
in this temple, a long time ago.
Since then, this temple
has protected winged beings
and at times, offered a helping hand.
According to Priest Chitoku,
winged beings inherit the planet's dream
from previous generations,
and have imparted pearls of wisdom
to the people since days of old.
It is said that one of them is the
source of our magic.
What does it mean "to inherit a dream"?
We do not know.
Because of the power they wielded,
winged beings were incarcerated
by the authorities of the time
and were used as weapons of war.
Kanna's mother had been cursed
by all those she had killed in wars.
That is why she said she was "defiled."
The army that invaded the sacred mountain
belonged to the Imperial Court.
Its goal was to undermine the worship of the
winged beings, and to unify the gods.
According to Chitoku, Kanna was probably
the last winged being in this world.
Priest Chitoku, I have a request.
Please give me magic powers.
It was decided that we would
live in this temple.
Uraha was said to have talent that appeared
only once in a hundred years.
Many long months passed.
I shall begin.
A chant to summon the spirits of the dead.
Through it, we shall discover what kind
of dreams Lady Kanna is having.
Sir Ryuya!
Sir Ryuya, get up!
It is my order!
Why do you not move?
Why do you not open your eyes?
I will not forgive you!
You are not allowed to leave me!
Why? Why does everyone... leave me?
No, that's not right, Kanna!
I'm safe!
I'm right here!
Was that the dream Kanna's having?
Yes...
Are you saying she keeps having
this dream somewhere in the sky?
It is the curse that was put upon her
on the sacred mountain.
It continues to haunt her...
And the curses that she inherited
from her mother as well...
They will weaken those who cherish
the winged beings,
and eventually, they will lead them
to their death.
Is that the reason that my wound never heals?
Yes.
I can protect myself using magic, but you...
When am I to die?
You will not last another year.
I see.
The day will come when the curse
on Kanna will die out.
Then, her spirit will descend to
the Earth in a reincarnated form.
But putting a winged being's
spirit into a human
is like pouring the water of the ocean
into a small vial.
The vial will break before all
can be poured into it.
Her spirit will not have a chance to heal
and will continue to reincarnate.
I don't have much time.
Isn't there a way to save her?
There is only one way.
Please father a child.
Huh?
If you father a child,
you can leave your will with him,
can you not?
If not him, then your grandson, or even your
great grandson will carry out your wish.
And one day, a way to rescue Kanna
may be discovered.
I will help you.
I see.
But then, I will devote all of the
rest of my time to you.
Yes!
Time passes slowly.
In the back of the hut is the
"Writings on Winged Beings" that I compiled.
If our soon-to-be-born child seeks
Kanna's spirit, I trust that it will be helpful.
And Uraha will teach the child magic.
I'm sure any child with Uraha's blood
will be an accomplished magician.
He might be able to follow the path
that we couldn't find.
I can continue the journey through time.
The journey to meet those
precious wings again.
I have nothing more to wish for.
I have no more regrets.
The birds are flying.
Yes.
You can just forget about me and Kanna,
and be happy.
I do not want that.
I am not alone.
You and Kanna will continue
to be with me and lead me.
I am happy.
I see.
That's exactly what makes you my dear wife.
Yes.
Thank you, Uraha.
Is it raining?
The sky is so high and clear, but...
Sir Ryuya.
Shall we go, Uraha?
Kanna is waiting for us beyond that sky.
Yes. I will accompany you wherever you go.
Where is this? Why am I here?
Oh yeah, I was with someone
until just a moment ago.
With someone very important...
It's no good. My head is foggy
and I can't remember.
I'm going to go to grandma's
after school tomorrow.
Oh, no! I forgot to bring my morning glory.
My grades are falling.
Where did you come from?
Where is your mother?
My mother?
Can't you fly?
How cute!
I wonder if it's okay to leave it here...
Okay, I'll walk away a little and turn around.
If he doesn't follow me, then I'll leave him.
Oh, he's following me.
Do you want to come with me?
Okay, then let's go together.
Set, Go!
Catching hold of the remnant
Of a dream that fades to white
The young boy runs
When he lets go
It vanishes forever with
The cry of the wind
A gentleness, once so apparent, is now gone
My eyes remain on the steps my feet take
Hearing forever the sounds of singing
That had faded away by morning
Always following in the footsteps we left behind
Next Episode
Summer vacation starts tomorrow.
I'm surprised he's so friendly...
I gave him a name: Sky.
Don't you have another one?
No way!
Piko piko piko...
Pikori...
Piko?
How long do I have to live like this, I wonder...
If I'm all alone, I won't be able to keep strong.
What should I do?
Misuzu, I'll be back.
Episode 10