My child, heed my words.
The story I'm about to tell
is a very important one.
You and I begin now the story of
a long, long journey
which will be passed on from
parent to child without end.
I'm hungry...
Boy, am I hungry!
That's all you've been saying.
You walk too slow. Hurry up, will you?
Hey, you guys!
Do you know what a ramen set is?
I'm absolutely starving right now!
I desperately want to eat a ramen set!
But...
Unfortunately, I'm broke. And so...
Come. It's time for a fun puppet show.
I'll ask you to pay me before you go home.
What do you think? Isn't it great?
Isn't it interesting? Isn't it fun?
What's with this filthy doll?
How ugly-looking...
Can't he do anything else?
Take that! And that!
Honest kids are the best.
You can pay me as much as you want.
That's why I'm honestly saying it's ugly-looking.
Why should we pay money for
something like this?
Are you crazy?
Listen, you guys!
Run!
Hold it, you guys!
It's hot...
We watched the vapor trails
As they disappeared
We ran from the blinding light
In vexation we let go
There are still places she cannot reach
She gazes with wistful eyes
Children walk along the tracks in summer
In both hands, their wish to take wing
We chased and chased vanishing vapor trails
Since the day we climbed over that hill
Unfailingly
And just like we have always
Stood straight and tall
We will stay as strong as the god of the sea
Surely
A-a ramen set!
Episode 1
Hello!
What's with this girl?
Are you alone?
Hot, isn't it?
What? What is she after? Money?
I have no money.
Aren't you thirsty?
I'll go and buy something!
Here!
Had a little trouble there, huh?
Gao!
Extra Thick
PEACH NECTAR
Extra Thick Peach Nectar?
Why did you do that, I wonder...
You're trying to make a fool of me, aren't you?
Of course not.
This is delicious, you know.
Do you want to go to the beach?
Why?
'Cause I want to play.
What?!
Yesterday, the kids were playing on the beach.
I was thinking it looked fun,
and I wanted to play too...
Next to you as you slept.
You were watching me?
You've been sleeping there since yesterday,
haven't you?
I poked at you to wake you up,
but you didn't look like you were going to.
I was so hungry I couldn't move.
Where are you going?
To work.
Work? What do you do?
A puppet sho...
It's gone!
Huh?
Is it so important?
I need it to work.
It's hot, isn't it? That's enough. Go on home.
Oh!
There it is!
Crow! Crow!
You're going after that one?
Wasn't that great?
Yeah, it was. I owe you.
Now you can play with me, right?
What are you after?
Why have you been hanging around me?
Like I said, I want to play on the beach.
Go running, or splash water at each other...
And in the end, we'll say "See you tomorrow!"
And go our separate ways.
Isn't that like being friends?
Yeah. Friends...
We'll be friends.
And so...
I want to play.
We don't even know each other's names.
I'm Misuzu Kamio. Who're you?
Yukito Kunisaki...
But listen! I have work to do.
I'm hungry, so I have to earn some money.
Oh! If that's the case...
I ended up following her home,
lured by the thought of food.
It's nice to eat with someone else, isn't it?
Do you usually eat alone?
My mom gets home late. And I don't have a dad.
After you finish eating, let's go play, okay?
No. If it gets late, I'll have trouble
finding a place to stay.
You don't have a place to stay yet?
No. I'll probably be sleeping under the stars.
You can stay here!
Now, listen up. We just met today.
Yes, yes!
And you have no idea who the heck I am.
I'm a stranger.
Yes!
Who in their right mind would put
someone like that up for the night?
Your mother probably wouldn't allow it
in the first place.
My mom's really lax, so I don't
think there will be a problem.
But I guess I shouldn't be talking about
my own mother like this.
But really, it's okay for you to stay here.
I'm tired. I don't have the energy
to play with you.
Then we can play tomorrow.
It's summer vacation, so I have lots of time.
No.
Gao...
Say... What kind of use do you think math is?
Do you think quadratic functions
will be useful in my future?
How should I know?
What am I doing helping you
with your homework, anyway?
Hey, your eyes are too close.
Yukito, you sound just like my mom.
Do I?
My mom's home.
Hey!
She ran into the shed with her motorcycle.
Don't worry. It happens all the time.
Are you really sure it's okay for me to be here?
Sure! I'll smooth it over with her.
Absolutely not!
It's nothing like you said.
Enough!
There's no way we can let a young guy
like this stay here!
Gao!
How many times do I have to tell ya
to stop saying that?!
What the heck are ya to Misuzu?
CLASS-
MATE
Uh... her classmate.
What? Yer kinda old, aren't ya?
DON'T FALL
FOR ME.
Don't fall for me.
As if I would?!
Well, you do seem to have pluck.
I like that about ya.
That's right. Yukito is a really nice guy.
All right. He can stay.
You're serious?
Serious? Why, I'm dead serious.
But there are TWO conditions.
You sleep in the shed.
And...
TABI
GARASV
SAKE
And...
TABI
GARASV
SAKE
TABI
GARASV
SAKE
You will be my drinking partner.
And then in the end, this is what the guy said...
"I guess maybe I was the one who fell in love."
Whaddya think? Do I win?
And so I told him...
"The fish you let escape
was a mermaid, you know..."
How was that? Pretty good, huh?
Why does it end up like this?
Mom's in top form.
Hey, Freeloader. Why're ya looking so glum?
Why don't ya join in?
MY EYES!
Yukito!
Do something? What should I do?
Anything'll do. An erotic confession
or a hidden talent.
I see... In that case...
Oh, that puppet.
Wow! That's impressive!
This is how I earn my living.
My mother used to travel with this as her trade.
When do we get to the punchline?
No good. You've no sense at all.
But it's amazing.
There's no gimmick behind this.
Who cares?
Even if the strings show,
it's better if it's funny.
I'm going to bed.
Oh! He's going off to the shed on his own!
There's nothing wrong with having no talent!
Let's drink up and forget about it, shall we?
My name's Haruko. Haruko Kamio.
Give me another one, ma'am.
I gave you my name so ya
wouldn't call me that!
You're so thoughtless!
So... You a runaway?
I'm traveling.
Are ya following a goal or a dream?
Maybe.
You're so young...
Well, compared to you...
You're a funny guy, aren't you?
Am I?
You know, I have a pretty good eye
when it comes to men.
I wouldn't mind if you stayed on for a while.
But I have a favor to ask.
Would you look after her?
Huh?
There's something a little unsure about her,
don't you think?
She's careless, and once something catches
her eye, she goes off like a bullet.
What am I, a babysitter?
And I'd like you to correct those
funny things she says.
You've heard her say "gao," haven't you?
When she's frustrated or about to cry?
Yeah...
That's supposed to sound like a dinosaur.
She loves dinosaurs. She's been saying
that since she was little.
She's still just a child...
What's up? Isn't it summer vacation?
Well, I have to take remedial classes.
Has Haruko already left?
Yeah. She leaves early every morning.
It's been a while since I've had
company for breakfast.
What are you doing today, Yukito?
First, I'll walk you to school.
Haruko asked me to do it.
She said to watch that you don't
do anything stupid.
She doesn't trust me at all.
Gao!
I'm done! A map of this town!
You're fast.
This will tell you where you
can find people gathering.
This should help with your work, right?
Yeah, thanks.
Oh, I'm going to be late.
Oh, dear, I'm in a pinch!
I'll come for you after school. We'll meet here.
Okay!
V!
Japanese use
these, right?
Here
I'm
studying.
Munch
Its the ocean! Munch Delicious!
Japanese use
these, right?
Here
I'm
studying.
Munch
It's the ocean! Munch Delicious!
W-what in the world is this?
Is this how she sees the world?
Piko!
What do you want?
Pikopiko!
Are you this town's local legendary being?
Pikopikopiko!
If that's the case, if I do it a favor,
like in those fairytales,
maybe it'll give me something in return.
Pikopikopiko!
Okay. Come here. I'll show you something good.
Piko!
Pikopiko!
Piko! Piko!
What do you think?
Isn't it such a wonderful act it makes you
feel like giving me something in return?
Piko! Piko!
Pikopiko!
PIKO!
Hey!
Piko!
Hold it!
Wait!
Piko!
Piko! Piko! Piko!
Pikopiko! Piko!
Piko! Piko!
Give up, you evil space being.
Piko... Piko...
Piko!
You won't get away!
What are you doing?
A strange extraterrestrial
ran away with my puppet.
Piko!
You mean this?
Potato isn't an extraterrestrial.
He's a neighborhood stray dog.
You mean, that's really a dog?
Piko! Pikopiko!
I see...
Huh?
Pikopiko! Pikopikopiko! Piko!
I see...
I'm sorry he caused you so much trouble.
Why are you apologizing?
Well, Potato said that he brought
your puppet here.
It seems he wanted to play with you.
Pikopiko!
You mean you can understand what he's saying?
Yes! We're best friends.
Right, Potato?
Pikopiko!
It seems there are worlds
I know nothing about here on Earth.
Thanks.
Are you hurt or something?
Oh, this?
Well, uh...
Nope! I have to keep it a secret.
I'm Kano Kirishima. Who are you?
I'm Yukito Kunisaki.
Do you have some free time, by any chance?
I guess...
Okay! Then you will be Citizen Number 2
of Planet Dilly-Dally.
Who's Number 1?
Me! And Potato is Number 3.
Piko!
And what do the citizens of Planet Dilly-Dally do?
They just have time on their hands.
That is the fate of those from Planet Dilly-Dally.
Right? We have nothing to do, do we, Potato?
Pikopiko!
I have to go to school now.
So I'll say good-bye for now.
I thought you were from Planet Dilly-Dally?
You believed that? Such a kid!
So long!
Are all the girls in that uniform weird?
Hey!
What is it?
Have you ever wished you could do magic?
What?
You're stunned! So long!
Magic?
Oh, Yukito!
How did your work go?
I made a mint.
Really?
I'm sorry. I lied.
I have to find someplace where there are more
people or I won't be able to make a living.
Why is this place so quiet when people
should be traveling to work?
Well, this station has been closed down.
You should have told me that earlier.
Gao!
Ouch!
Why'd you hit me?
Haruko told me to scold you when you said that.
Oh! How cute!
It's Miss Tohno...
You know her?
Yeah.
What's wrong with you?
H-Hello!
Hello. This is unexpected.
Y-Yes. Quite a coincidence.
I'm astonished.
What were you doing?
Getting some sun.
Huh?
Just kidding. It's evening right now.
Hey, who the heck is this girl?
Minagi Tohno. She's my classmate.
She's smart. She's at the top of our grade,
and she's president of the Astronomy Club.
Please just call me Tohno.
Hey! Minagi!
Oh, Yukito is flying like a leaf!
Hey, hey! Let's hurry up and
go back to blowing bubbles!
You know, you know, I'm doing really good now!
Please!
Is this your little sister?
No, I'm not. I'm Michiru, Minagi's best friend.
Who are you?
I'm Miss Tohno's classmate.
That hurt, you know.
What?! Are you another one of
Minagi's classmates?
I'm an innocent passerby who got
bowled over by you.
I've got it! Minagi, this is
a perverted kidnapper who's after us!
I-I'm in this group too?
Who's are you calling a kidnapper?!
Yikes! He's agitated.
We young girls are in trouble!
Wow, did you hear that sound?
Miss Kamio, who is this?
Yukito Kunisaki. He's a traveler
who's staying with us now.
A traveler?
A homeless, perverted kidnapper?
He's a lost cause.
Miss Kamio, I think we'd better be going.
What? But I was doing really well
blowing bubbles.
Let's do it some more.
Kami-Kami can join us, too.
Kami-Kami? Me?
It's getting dark, so let's do it again tomorrow.
I'll pack a lunch for us.
So long, Kamio!
Bye-bye!
Yukito Kunisaki!
Yeah?
Get lost, will you?!
What was that?!
Hey, hey, Will you make me
a hamburger tomorrow?
All right.
Really? Hurray!
Did I do something wrong to that kid?
Hmm, I don't know.
I ended up not making a single yen today.
You were standing there like that
when we met yesterday, too.
Ever since I was little,
I've had this longing for the sky.
Why?
I don't know.
It's just...
I have this feeling like...
there's another me there...
Isn't that a romantic thought?
That the real you is in the sky.
It must feel really good.
You could see far into the distance...
Everything on the ground
would look so insignificant...
You'd probably feel very gentle.
Misuzu... You're...
That was the start of a summer that, for me,
seemed as short as the twinkling of a star,
and as long as all eternity.
Catching hold of the remnant
Of a dream that fades to white
The young boy runs
When he lets go
It vanishes forever with
The cry of the wind
A gentleness, once so apparent, is now gone
My eyes remain on the steps my feet take
Hearing forever the sounds of singing
That had faded away by morning
Always following in the footsteps we left behind
Next Episode
It might be the other you
that I've been looking for.
I'm not cut out to be a parent.
I should have stayed alone.
I had a dream. A strange dream about the sky.
I was in the sky.
It was a world I'd never seen before.
Everything went on into infinity.
Listen. Did you have wings in your dream?
Episode 2